- Good evening, everyone.
Welcome.
Calling the meeting to order at 6:00.
Please stand for a moment of silence
and the Pledge of Allegiance.
- Of the United States of America
and to the Republic for which it stands,
one Nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- Thank you, everyone.
Going to ask everyone,
please make sure to silence
any electronic devices.
Including and those of
us up here on the dais.
And also going to ask that
all of our board members,
if there are any conflicts of interest,
if you've had ex parte
communications, site visits,
research on your own, anything like that,
please make that known prior to each item.
I will remember to say that
before each item as well.
Okay.
First minutes, approval of
the September 6th minutes.
Do we have any motions regarding
the September 6th minutes?
Robert Spalding, motion to approve.
- I second.
- We have a second, Melissa Thacker.
Any discussion or changes?
No.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
I'm hearing none.
Those minutes are approved.
And next up, October
4th, PAV meeting minutes.
Do we have a motion
regarding those minutes?
- Motion to approve.
- Motion to approve, Diana.
And we have a second from Roberts.
Any other discussion or changes?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Minutes are approved.
And next up, we have the
November 15th minutes.
Do we have any motions regarding that?
- Motion to approve.
- Robert Spalding motion to approve.
And second, we have second.
Diana, any changes?
Discussion?
No.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Minutes are approved in absolutely.
Okay.
Old business, nothing under there.
New business, 5A public hearing.
Conditional use for site plan
waiver for private school.
- Yes, this is a conditional use request
for a site plan waiver
for a private school at 3030 Lions court
and at 3051 Lions Court for
the Nazaret Christian Academy.
As included on the staff report.
The existing school is
at 3051 Lions Court.
That's going to be on the right hand side,
the larger parcel.
That school has received approval
from our planning advisory board in 1995.
The church has an existing
church on the property,
which is the 8,020 square foot church.
That's going to be the
structure on the right.
There's a red structure on the right,
and the school is going to
be the structure to the left
on the larger parcel.
There is an existing church
on that property that
received approval in 1995.
In inquiring about expanding
the school to 3030,
which is a smaller parcel,
we discovered that the
existing school did not go
through this conditional use process.
So we decided to combine
and to legalize the existing
school on the larger parcel
and also the approval of the expansion
at 3030 Lions Court under one application.
Currently, right now, the
school has about 245 students.
The idea is to expand
into the smaller parcel
for the high school students,
grades nine through twelve.
That new campus will have
approximately five classrooms.
We have that in the packet.
No more than five
classrooms that are there.
The existing nine classrooms
remain on the main campus site.
As you can see,
it's not necessarily directly
across the street there.
The high school students
will have to go back
and forth from the main
campus to the new one.
So we included to make sure
that there was adequate type
of ADA striping and pedestrian improvement
so that way the students
can move back and forth
between the main campus and the new one.
In addition to that,
because the smaller parcel
does not have the room
or the circulation to
provide drop off and pickup,
we're also going to lend
it that all drop off
and pickup will have to
occur on the main campus too.
And there was a circulation
plan that was included
of how a drop off and pickup would work.
The school in the church
will not conflict.
The hours of operations
were noted on here.
The church activities will
be limited to Tuesdays,
Wednesdays, and Thursdays
in the evening time,
and Sunday services are
going to be on the weekend.
One nice thing is that
on the right hand side
you really can't see,
there is the new improvement
for Bill Beck Boulevard that's
there on the right hand side.
We are requiring, I think
it would help to as well,
for them to add an access
point to Bill Beck Boulevard
on the right hand side.
And that will utilize that
existing pavement that's
on that northeast corner,
which is the Ridge Street.
In addition to the expansion
on the smaller site,
all parking too, as well.
Parking is going to be limited
and it cannot accommodate
the high school students
which have the ability,
they have the ability to drive
in addition to the administration.
So a satellite parking agreement
will need to be entered in.
So that way the parking deficit that's
on the smaller parcel will make up
for it on the larger parcel too, as well.
And with that, staff is
recommending approval subject
to these conditions that were
listed in the staff report.
- Thank you.
Board members, any questions
for Brenda or the City?
If not, is the applicant here would like
to say anything to the board?
Address the board?
Not required, but okay.
Do we have any public comments
regarding this agenda item?
Any public comments?
Public comments?
No?
Okay, with that,
do we have any motions
regarding this agenda item?
- Motion to approve.
- Melissa Thacker, motion to approve.
We have a second, Robert Spalding.
Any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion carries.
5B, ordinance amending future
land use map designation.
Brenda.
- This is a land use amendment request
to change the future land
use designation on property,
about an acre or so,
from the commercial general
to single-family low density residential.
At one point there was a
smaller structure on this site.
It was removed in 2019.
There were attempts.
I'll get to it in a little
bit on the zoning request
that at one point that
there had been attempts
to develop this property as commercial.
However, the immediate
surrounding area is residential,
so we feel that it's
a bit more appropriate
to change the land use designation
from commercial to residential.
Access will be limited to the
street to the south there.
I believe it's Randolph or Palmetto.
It gets the two confused,
because the John Young Parkway,
looking at it from the aerial,
it seems as if the roadway is there.
But this is the beginning of
the bridge the flyover there,
so all access will be
from the existing roadway to the south.
At this time, staff is
recommending approval
to change the land use amendment
from commercial general
to single-family low density residential.
- Questions for Brenda or the City?
- I have a question.
- Go ahead, Alex.
- So I guess you said this area
is primarily low density residential.
I guess, do you have a sense
of where the nearest
commercial properties are
to the residential properties in the area?
- There is residential
across John Young Parkway
and the future land use
on the south side there,
the existing self storage
is also commercial.
So it's across the street.
I don't know if we have the land use map,
but the nearest commercial is
across the street to the south
and on the west side of John Young.
- Yeah, I guess I'm just wondering.
Putting more residential
there just means more people
that are going to have
to leave there to go elsewhere
to connect business or whatever, right?
Where just having a commercial lot
near otherwise residential
property seems like it
would open the possibility
to serve the local community
more locally, I guess.
Yeah.
Is there existing interest
in developing the property or something?
Or this is just the city
kind of thinking ahead, or what's the?
- There is interest.
There's the applicant here.
There is interest to develop
as a single family residential.
The next item on the
zoning and staff report.
There have been previous attempts.
Actually, there were
two different attempts
to develop the property
commercial, and in one case,
it was denied,
the use was not appropriate.
And the second was it was an
office space and a restaurant.
But it never went anywhere
with our committee.
So there was several attempts
to develop as commercial.
It's probably, hopefully it's
better success as residential.
- So there is an applicant
requesting this change you said?
- Yes, this is not a city initiative.
- What's that?
- This is not a city initiative.
- Got it, okay.
Any other questions for Brenda?
If not, if the applicant would like
to say anything to the board?
Address the board.
You're welcome to do so.
If not, do we have any public comments
regarding this agenda item?
Any public comments?
Public comments?
No.
Do we have any motions regarding this?
- I give a motion to approve.
- Fatima?
Motion to approve.
Do I have a second?
- I'll second.
- We have a second.
I think I heard Robert first.
And any further discussion?
If no, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion carries unanimously.
Next up, 5C.
- This is a companion,
the rezoning to establish the zoning
on the property to match
the future land use change,
changing the zoning
from the highly commercial
to the single family residential RA2
it's previously mentioned in 1998,
there was an attempt
to change to commercial
for a pawn shop.
Planning advisory board at
the time recommended approval.
However, when it went
to the city commission,
it was reversed the planning
advisory board approval
and denied that request.
Then in 2001, there was an attempt
to include commercial with office space,
with a dance studio, with
the restaurant addition.
Again, it met all the
different requirements,
was submitted formally to the city,
but it never left our committee.
At that point, there has
not been any other types
of commercial applications
to come through.
Now, we're here with the rezoning
to change it to residential.
As mentioned before,
the access will be limited to
Palmetto and South Brandoff,
and it is compatible
to the proposed future land use request.
So we're recommending approval,
subject to the approval
of the Companion Land Use Amendment.
- Okay, board, any questions?
If not, again, if the applicant would like
to address the board,
you're welcome to do so.
If not, do we have any public comments?
Public comments?
Public comments on this agenda item?
No?
Okay, any motions regarding this?
- Motion to approve.
- Motion to approve, Robert Spalding.
We have a second, Diana.
Any discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
Aye.
Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion carries, 5D.
And again, I say if anyone
has any conflict of interest,
please make that known at
this time regarding 5D.
- I have a conflict with
5D, so I'll be abstaining.
- Okay, Melissa Thacker.
Conflict with 5D.
She'll be abstaining.
Brenda.
- This is a rezoning
request to change the zoning
on about 883 acres of land
for the Harriet Isle mixed
use plan unit development.
This will contain about
3000 residential units
and up to 190,000 square
feet of commercial.
The concept plan.
So the concept plan will be
divided into different phases.
Phase one will be the village center,
where the commercial will be located.
There will be a small amount of commercial
in the amenity center that you see
on the north side towards the cove.
We'll have an opportunity for small,
nonresidential as part
of the amenity center.
And then the rest will
be part of phase one,
which is the majority of the residential.
As you can see from the concept plan,
there's approximately about
177 acres of wetlands.
They'll be preserved along the
shoreline of East Lake Toho
and also with the cove where
Boggy Creek empties out.
In addition to that,
primary and secondary access
will be off of Simpson Road.
There will be emergency
access points only,
on Aurora Court, Borinquen
Drive, Hilliard Isle Road
and Crest Drive.
The emergency access points are intended
for first responders
and emergency at those
points that you see there.
Some of the other amenities includes
as far as with the village center,
this will be primarily a series
of enhanced design guidelines
that will include street
furnishings, linear parks,
additional amenities to
provide a multimodal,
pedestrian, and pet oriented
design for the village center.
There will be a separate
developers agreement
that the city will work with the applicant
on the village center primarily to deviate
from the standards within this area.
The village center is proposed
to have private drives
and private access points,
and this is going to be a
unique project with the city.
So to continue to work on enhanced
and alternative design standards
within the village center.
Now I do want to point out
with that that there was a revision
to the condition, that was,
you have a copy of it too, as well,
an underlying strike through
of the changes that were made
from the previous original
publication to what we have
before you that we want
for you to consider.
In addition to that
with the revised agenda,
we did receive a public comment
and like we normally do here,
I will go ahead and read this out.
We'll put it up on the screen too as well.
This is from John and Michelle Lux.
My name is John Lux
and I'm a 25 plus year
resident of Osceola County,
the current resident of the
Hilliard Isle community.
Our family moved to our current home
to enjoy the rural atmosphere
that the community offers.
Our house sits on an acre
of property with just
17 homes on our street.
Behind us sits hundreds of acres
of calm, rural old Florida.
We notice it's inevitable
that the land is going
to be developed.
Our hope is that the land
will be responsibly developed,
not allowed to be more
of northern Osceola County's
rapid overdevelopment.
We've attended previous hearings
and attended the most recent open house
where they discussed the long term plan.
There remains no plan
to deal with our already
overcrowded school.
We can't field teaching and
support staff positions already.
There are no bus drivers
to transport kids.
Traffic is unbearable during the morning
and evening busy hours, while
weekends are even worse.
Developers pointed to the
Simpson Road expansion
as a solution, but the expansion is
to deal with the current traffic volume.
The Hillary Isle development
will bring an additional 6,000
plus cars to Simpson Road.
I would urge you
to consider reducing the
new residents you allow
in the community.
Our infrastructure is not equipped
to deal with additional volume.
We understand the plan
is to keep the lot 25 feet off the back
of our current property line.
25 feet is not big at all,
so we hope that can be doubled
so our rural county living is respected.
We also request that it be mandated
to be a natural barrier or berm,
with the trees and/or grass
between existing property lines
and new developments.
We strongly request
that it not be a brick,
plastic wall or fence.
Even more so, we were told there
would be no through traffic
on Hilliard Isle Road.
Please ensure that remains
and any request to
access a new development
through Hilliard Isle
Road is not approved.
Preserving the volume of
traffic on Hilliard Isle Road
and the offshoot streets
in our community is vital.
Those of us that live in
the Hilliard Isle community
are not anti-development.
But we urge you to respect
the current homeowners
and act responsibly when
considering the new development
as we are all impacted
by the decisions you make
regarding this property.
So I do want to point out,
as I previously mentioned,
that Hilliard Isle Road is supposed
to be an emergency access only.
It's not a through road
for residential traffic,
it will only be for emergency
first response only.
In addition to Hilliard Isle,
like I mentioned on the concept plan,
the other roadways will also be limited
to emergency access only.
To address that concern.
At this point, I don't think there was,
I don't have the applicant buffer
or a defined buffer of 25 feet.
We do have buffer requirements,
but this is single family to single family
so I can't speak to as far
as a specific buffer width.
And as far as with the school district,
school district comments
were included and they,
I believe were in need of entering
into a separate mitigation
and to work with the
school district separately
regarding any type
of school mitigation
to offset the students
and the capacity of the existing schools.
So it was reviewed by the school district
and they did provide the comments
that were included that typically
with the school district
you would enter separately
into a mitigation
agreement with the school.
It can be a combination of land,
it could be a combination
of different things,
but that will be handled
through the school district.
I also want to point out
that the applicant did
initiate a QA meeting
with the surrounding
residents on October 16, 2023,
and as of the rerolling of our revision,
we have not received any
additional public comments other
than the ones that I
just read aloud to you.
At this time, with the revised conditions,
staff is recommending approval
subject to the revised conditions.
I'm just here to answer any questions
or clarification because,
as you know, it's a lot.
- Okay, board members,
any questions for Brenda for the City?
- I guess, first, a quick
clarification question.
When you were talking and
discussing the map here,
I think you said,
what I heard you say was
that the mixed use area
was part of phase one,
but it's denoted in
the plans as phase two.
- It's separated out.
It is separated out.
It may not be that map,
but it's a different map
that has the different phases
of the entire project.
- Do you have a sense
of the timelines involved
with the different phases?
- No.
I mean, if it's the phase one,
we're going to assume that it's going
to be the single family residential.
But the applicant may define
a better timeline for you.
- Yeah, I guess, in terms
of a specific question
regarding the revised conditions
we just received today,
item four.
I guess I'm kind of confused
because item three says specifically
that the phase two multifamily
development standards
and the highway commercial
zoning permitting conditional
use standards for
nonresidential uses would apply.
Whereas item four suggests
that phase two village center
and any subsequent sub-phases
containing single family
development standards must comply
with phase one single family
development standards.
I guess I'm a bit confused
whether those seem
to contradict to my ear.
Am I reading it wrong?
- No, we're trying to pull up the map.
The standards were not included,
so they were not included
for phase one transitional
A for single family.
So instead of modifying it,
we're saying that any of the single family
in the phase one transitional zone will
just follow the phase one standards.
So, different standards
for the different phases.
- I can understand what you just said.
That makes sense to me.
But the item we have
in front of us specifically
says phase two village center.
Any subsequent sub-phases
containing single family
development standards must comply
with phase one single family
development standards.
- And that's also the case for
the phase two village center.
So, two things.
Condition number three is that
any single family residential
in phase one transitional
area will follow,
sorry, phase 1A,
a single family
will follow phase one
single family standards.
Condition number four, phase two,
which is a village center
for any single family,
will follow the phase one
because it was inadvertently,
it was omitted.
- Okay.
I guess I'm struggling a bit to understand
if this is just,
whether this doesn't have any real impact
or whether as read or as written
this might sort of undo
a lot of what I saw
on the master plan regarding
targeting higher density
and multiuse standards for phase two,
because, as written, if
I read it too literally,
it seems like it might undo some
of what I was seeing in the plan.
Unless I'm misreading it.
I don't know if we've
made a comment from the.
- Yeah, for sure.
Specifically, single family residential
in the phase two village center.
- Okay.
Sure, okay.
So I guess I should read this
as that the phase one single
family development standards
will apply only to the sub phases and,
I guess sub-parts of the project
containing single family developments,
but not to the whole phase,
the phase as a whole.
Is that accurate?
- The phase two, as it's developed,
can be broken down, too, as well.
So we wanted to make sure
to clarify that it will include
the sub-phases too as well,
and we allow for that flexibility.
- Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
- Other questions?
If not, would the applicant
like to address the board?
Please state your name
and your business address for the record.
- Good evening.
Celia Dorn, 17 South
Orlando, Kissimmee, Florida.
I just want to address
some of the comments,
and I would like to start trying
to help clarify that condition
a little bit for you.
At this point, there's not
necessarily any single family
that's being proposed in phase two.
What that condition does is if
those plans modify later on,
it ensures that the single
family homes will match the rest
of the community.
So that's what that
condition is trying to do.
I don't know if that
helps clarify it at all.
- Sorry.
Yeah, I do think that helps clarify,
but might raise a slight
concern on my part
of the committee in the sense that, well,
maybe we'll address this later,
but it's not clear to me,
looking at the plans,
how much of this could change
from sort of the initial plan
and whether the changes could constitute
what feel like wouldn't be
in keeping with the comprehensive plan
that we're supposed to uphold.
So to have the wiggle room
that what the park projects,
it seems like is doing
the most to address some
of residents traffic
concerns now has a cause
where it could be sort of undone.
It feels like a risk on the part of.
- I understand what you're saying.
The actual density and
intensity cannot change.
So that is maxed out.
The number of single family
homes that they're allowed
within the PUD remains
regardless of if maybe some of those go
into phase two instead of phase one.
So the ultimate number
of single family homes cannot increase
without a PUD amendment.
So I understand,
I think that's more kind
of what you're concerned
about is more homes potentially
or less commercial potentially.
But those are why those
numbers would remain in place
and they wouldn't be able to do more
than what those numbers are.
- Sure, okay, I guess, yeah.
For my own purposes, I'd be
concerned almost the other way.
If the whole development just
turned into single family,
then I feel like that could
create much worse traffic issues
than if, as currently presented,
there was a multiuse core
that could represent a place
for residents to go about their business.
In the master plan,
there's a place for a grocer
and a discussion of allocating
a place for a school
and things like that.
- And that is certainly what the plan is.
This is a what-if
scenario that staff wants
to ensure there is some
protections in place.
- Got it, thank you.
- On some of the other
issues that were raised,
I think the concern
of making sure that this
is responsibly developed,
I think that's the whole
reason for doing this PUD.
It's being developed as
one cohesive community
and a pattern that makes sense
with various different
amenities and different uses.
The commercial, the residential,
the possibility of a school
site, if that's necessary.
Those are all things that are going
to make it a community
that makes sense responsibly
developed together.
The traffic issues.
The applicant and the
city have worked very hard
to be respectful of the
neighboring communities.
That is why none of those other
roads will be through roads.
They will just have that emergency access
to make sure that traffic isn't flowing
into these more rural and
smaller neighborhoods,
but instead will be directed
up to Simpson Road, which is,
as we know, is a major
road within our community.
The 25-foot step back is a minimum.
That doesn't mean it
won't be more than that.
That's just the absolute
minimum of what it can be.
We do have a presentation that we're happy
to share with the board if
you would like to see it.
It is very similar to the
presentation that was presented
at the future land use
and annexation hearing.
That was a few months ago.
But we're also available
to answer any questions
that the board may have.
- I'll ask the board,
would you like to see the presentation?
Let's just take the
temperature of the room here.
So it's being cold.
Who would like to see it?
- I think it would add context
to the discussion I imagine
we're about to have.
- Alex, you'd like to see it?
No, no, no.
Okay.
I had a question, what schools
currently serve this now?
Is this Gateway?
What are the elementary, middle,
and high schools currently serve this?
- I believe that's in the
School Capacity Report.
- And I understand that's currently
that each year they
update and they look at,
myself being part of a number
of redistricting committees
for the school district
and chairing five different
school advisory councils.
My wife's a teacher,
I'm very keen on understanding
the ramifications
to the schools.
- Yes.
- And I think we're going
to pull up the schools.
I will say the school
district has requested
that a school mitigation
agreement be entered into,
as Ms. Ryan alluded to,
and that would put into place
ways to offset what this
development would be.
- And I do understand
that's under the purview
of the school district to
work that out with you,
but I'd like to understand
kind of a 360 of the
ramifications of this.
- So, as they stated
that they would provide
a more accurate report
as the development comes in,
the site plan development comes in.
So they did not have a traditional
or standard school capacity report showing
how it would affect the additional
residential development,
which facilities would be over
capacity or what have you.
They're deferring that
to subsequent site plans in the middle,
but they are requesting
mitigation at this time.
So they did not indicate that to us.
- Understood.
Board, any questions?
I'm sorry, did you have more
that you wanted to address?
- Not unless you want
to see the presentation.
- Okay.
- Board, any other
questions for the applicant?
Go ahead, Alex.
- Yeah.
So do you have a sense of the
timeline between the phases?
- Chris Ren, 4901 Vinelane
Road, Orlando, Florida 32811.
Are you asking specifically
between phase two and phase one?
- Yeah, I guess.
I mean, I just, I wonder.
- Yeah, I wanted to clarify some of that.
I mean, that's essentially
nomenclature that we used
in the application to identify
the two different areas
in the project.
- Sure.
- So the phase one residential
is really probably going
to be developed in eight phases.
Could be ten, it could be six.
It's kind of a market
based decision at the time,
but you're looking at six to ten phases,
probably over anywhere from 5 to 15 years,
to be quite honest.
For the phase two mixed use area, again,
that's commercial and multifamily.
So, just speaking speculatively,
it could be two different
developers that come in
at two different times
and build those out.
I mean, for the purposes
of our traffic projections
and the school board analysis,
they kind of look at that as
like a three year build out,
even though our project's really going
to be much longer than that.
And just to kind
of elaborate on what Celia said
with the school mitigation,
essentially we're agreeing
to every three years
to reevaluate the impact
that the additional
residential units are having
on the school board capacity.
So those mitigation requirements
could change over time,
but essentially every three years
we'd be reviewing existing school capacity
and how many students our
new population is putting
into the school.
Again, it's really market based
in terms of how fast
the build out will be.
But I would imagine you're going
to have both the commercial
and multifamily moving
forward at the same time
as the single families moving forward.
As we look ahead, it's really a project.
We've got to get environmental permits,
we've got to get city permits,
we got to get Osceola County permits.
So hopefully, sometime
middle of next year,
we'd actually be able
to start development,
which probably takes nine to ten months.
So you're looking into Q1, Q2 of 2025
before you've actually got
any students being generated
or additional traffic coming to the area
because of the commercial,
multifamily, or residential.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Yeah, no problem.
- Question regarding,
I understand that Hilliard
Isle would be restricted to,
other than the residents,
restricted to emergency vehicles.
Would that also apply
to construction vehicles
going through there?
Construction vehicles would not
be going down there as well?
- Correct.
- Okay.
Board, any other questions?
If not, we'll open it up to,
unless you had anything else,
we'll open it up to public comments.
Was there something else?
- The only other thing is I
would request additional time
to respond to the public comments,
if the board would allow that.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- We want to understand
clearly everything.
Public comments.
Do we have any public comments?
Yes.
Folks, please, one at a time.
Step to the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
- Good evening.
My name is Dr. Brian Agard.
My address is 2423 Aurora
Court, right off at the back,
right where the development is proposed.
We purchased this home because
of the rural atmosphere.
And also we did not
want a large development
behind our house.
That's directly, so we have a
little over an acre as well.
I'm also a real estate broker over here,
and I'm concerned about
a couple of things.
Number one, I was hoping
to find out the mix density
of single family townhouses
and what the maximum
height will be allowed.
- I can have folks respond to you,
but I just want to make sure
if there's anything else you'd like.
- Yes.
- They'll respond after your time.
- Okay.
Also, if anything changes,
will they allow our community
to also have approval process?
We don't want to have a
change, a last minute change,
and some type of modification,
and we have no input.
That was my second.
So we want to have protections.
Also, we want to know
if we will have access
to any of the amenities.
Is there any way that we could go.
They already addressed that
there'll be no traffic,
no construction vehicles in
our area, which is great.
I just want to know if
you'll have access to some
of the amenities and what's
going to be done for us.
For example, we have no sewers.
We have just regular sewers.
We have no public water.
Is there anything going to
be done for our community?
Those are my three questions.
- Okay, thank you, sir.
We'll ask the applicant if you
would like to respond to any
of that, and then also the city,
if you have any response to any of that.
Whomever would like to address this first.
You could stop the time on that.
- At this time, they don't
have a full breakdown
of what the single towns
and multifamily will be.
That's something that would happen
during the site development plan process.
They do have the maximum density,
but that can be distributed
in different ways,
and it will be market driven.
What is needed in the community.
As for changes, anytime
the PUD is changed,
that will be done
in a public hearing process
that we are in right now,
that the neighbors would
receive notice for,
just like they received
notice for this evening.
The development agreement
that is discussed
and the conditions will likewise go
through a public hearing process.
So the community will always
have the ability to have input
into the changes that
would be brought forward.
- Brenda, does the city
want to respond to any
of those questions,
or is that already
covered by the applicant?
- Yes, I think.
Was it the maximum height for phase one?
It's two stories for phase
one as proposed, two stories.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Other public comments, please
step in the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
- Good evening.
My name is Dr. Eugenia Agard.
I'm at 2423 Aurora Court in Kissimmee,
and I have a great deal of concern,
because what I'm hearing
is there's not a lot
of concrete information
before this can be approved
in terms of what we are
approving, the structure,
what we can expect in terms
of commercial property,
strip mall, what does that
look like for our neighborhood
and the changes for our composition
and the way we live currently?
Also, my concern is Simpson
Road is already out of control.
I can't even get out of the street now.
You almost have to make a right
turn just to go back left.
It is terrible.
It's a danger.
And so even though they're
saying they're going
to use Simpson Road, I don't
feel that this is a good plan.
However, the other
concern is they're going
to use the access road
through Aurora Court
and the other local ways,
which is the cul-de-sac.
It's only one way in and one way out.
If that is the case, that
this does get approved,
we need to ensure that
this can't be changed
where there's some new
dynamic that comes in.
Because we already know
that people, legislation
has changed things
after it's already been
approved and written in law.
This will change our environment.
We have children.
This is a thriving neighborhood
and most of us move there
because we love the rural feel.
We don't want to feel
like we live in a city.
And also, we have a beautiful
sunset in the backyard.
We may lose that, so I need to know,
what is the buffer,
the buffer range from this property
if it is approved, from our property line?
We don't want to see these buildings.
I lived in Long Island.
I never lived in a city for a reason.
I don't want to come to
Florida and live in city.
It's just not good.
So I need to know what the buffer line is.
Someone mentioned 25 feet.
I'm sure it can't be 25 feet,
but I would like clarity on
what the buffer line would be
from Aurora Court to this development.
So we definitely want to be
involved in these meetings.
I couldn't make the last one.
I was out of the country.
So I definitely want to
make sure we're involved
in every capacity
because this affects the
way we live in Florida,
which is why we moved here.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
If the applicant would like
to respond to any of that.
- Robert, can I just jump
in here for a quick second
to clarify for the public?
I don't think I have to
clarify this for the board
because I think you guys know this,
but what we're talking
about now is zoning.
So in terms of.
I understand the interest
in what everything is going to look like
and roads and stuff like that,
but anything that could even be offered
at this point is preliminary
and that's not under discussion right now.
So that level of detail and specifics,
that's not what this hearing is for.
This simply establishes the zoning.
And we don't have the map up right now
of what the existing zoning is,
but this essentially transforms the zoning
and makes it into this
one cohesive zoning,
which is mixed use
planned unit development
so that the developer can put
together a cohesive community.
So in many respects
it's a very progressive,
organized way of planning
development in the city.
So I appreciate the
interest in the details,
but we're just not there yet.
And those specifics are
not under consideration
before the board at this time, sorry.
- No, thank you.
Thank you for the clarification.
Yeah, I understand these
are the broad strokes,
but if I'm giving a chance
for everybody to speak
and if the applicant
would like to address any
of that to whatever extent they'd like to,
you're free to do so.
- We're happy to not address that.
- Okay.
All right.
If the city would like
to address any of that
beyond what Colin has already said.
If not, okay.
Other public comments?
Yes, ma'am.
Please step to the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
- Good evening.
My name is Elizabeth Pimentel.
I live at 2685 Hilliard Court.
So I'm right off of Hilliard Isle.
I do have lots of concerns
about this project.
We've been through many
meetings with these individuals
on their vision.
Hilliard Court and Simpson is horrific.
I've had to change my
actual schedule to work
because there is no way of
getting out of that corner.
You get behind that bus stop there.
The bus stop could not
even turn to get around.
He had to go around the
AutoZone, the Dollar General,
to come back around and block everybody
from getting to their
destination every morning.
So it is something that, in your zoning,
please take that into consideration.
There has been many talks
about expanding that street.
It needs to happen before
anyone does anything
because it is so dangerous in that corner.
All of these children,
most of them go to that
corner by themselves
because their parents
have to leave extra early
to get in front of their own bus drivers.
It is absolutely horrific
for the community.
My back is right to the farm.
I'm actually the Luxus family's neighbor.
Been there about 14 years now.
And that is the major reason
why we bought this property in Kissimmee.
We could have gone to any other county,
but we came to Kissimmee because
we wanted that lifestyle.
I wake up every morning to that sunrise.
It's absolutely beautiful.
What they're planning to do there,
please take into
consideration with your zoning
because you'll have
so many disappointed
neighbors in this community.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
- Just to address some
of the traffic concerns
that have been raised,
there is significant
improvements that are scheduled
for Simpson Road,
including additional signals
which will help with some
of this being able to turn
in and out of these neighborhoods.
The county is working on that now.
And the time frame
for those improvements should be done
before very much development
even occurs on this site,
as they're actively
building the road right now.
So I understand the
frustration with the traffic.
But there are preliminary
and actual plans already
in place to help address
and ease some of these problems
for the residents in that area.
- Thank you.
Other public comments?
Yes, sir.
Please step to the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
- Hello, good evening.
My name is Gustavo.
I am also,
I live at 2685 Hilliard Court.
I am directly the very last property,
around the corner where the
construction is supposed to be.
Question is that I understand,
I'm not quite sure about the plans,
but I heard 25 feet from our
fence to their next property.
I would like for that
to be maybe if they can.
They have a lot of room back
there to move it 25 feet more.
Maybe we can keep our privacy
which is the reason why we move there.
It's still one of those few neighborhoods
where you go in the afternoon,
but hardworking people go
and they put the jogging suits
and they walk and they run.
In the case of the bicycles,
we don't have any issues.
There's don't been anything bad happening
in the neighborhood.
We're trying to keep it safe.
A lot of good people live there.
I understand that things need to develop,
but it's unfortunate that
one day that beautiful logo,
instead of having a cow, it's
going to have a building.
Everything has been built too accelerated
to the point that I've been getting snakes
and stuff that I never seen before.
Deers, I mean, they're beautiful.
But the traffic problem is another one.
On the way here,
seven and a half minutes
just to make a left turn
on the current condition.
I understand in the future
there might be another
development of adding another line.
But 3,000 properties, that's
6,000 cars on 42 feet of road.
I'm not an engineer
but I do appreciate that
they're going to hit it out,
they're going to keep it
as an emergency access only
so we can still keep some
type of traffic control.
But I would like to recommend if possible,
instead of 20 feet from our
fence line, they add another 25.
That will give us a
little bit more privacy,
which we have right now.
And that's it.
Appreciate it.
- Thank you.
I'll give the chance for the applicant.
If you'd like to respond to any of that.
- The 25 feet that was proposed
is what the applicant
needs to remain in place.
As you can see from the plan,
there's a significant amount
of conservation that is
going to be left in place.
If you start changing
what those buffers are,
you potentially run the risk
of losing some of that
beautiful conservation land.
So that is something to consider.
Also you'll see that there are trails
in the public right of
way along the mixed use.
Those will obviously be available
for people to use to continue
to engage with this property
and engage with the natural surroundings
that the community is so fond of
in an even safer manner
than is currently available to them.
- Thank you.
Other public.
Brenda, do you have something?
- I just want to clarify.
There was something mentioned
about doing the roadway
improvements prior to development.
Well, we and county can even address this,
but even legally and statutorily,
we're not able to do that.
So the best thing I would
recommend in that case
is to engage legislative
representatives to change that.
But we were not able to
delay or to deny development
and have the infrastructure
put in beforehand.
It allows them to do it
concurrently with the development,
but not prior to that.
And as previously mentioned,
that Simpson Road is a county road.
It is phased.
So right now, the first phase.
You can also get more information
on the county website.
I believe the first phase
is on the north side,
closest to the intersection
to Osceola Parkway,
and the improvements will follow
down suddenly phase one and phase two.
I believe this development is phase two,
part of the phase two
improvements for Osceola County.
There are plans, what have you,
that are available on the county
website to show the extent
of the improvements.
I also want to point out on the land use,
we talked about density
and those types of things.
If this property
or the seven portions of property
is annexed into the city,
and with the proposed single-family,
low density residential density,
the city has a maximum of
six dwelling units per acre.
If this property stays within the county,
the single family low density residential
in the county is eight.
So there is the potential where
the number of homes is more
if it stays in the county,
because the county allows
for eight dwelling units
as opposed to the city.
For us, it's six dwelling units per acre.
And the surrounding property
and development being the
estate larger types of areas.
But that also with that density
of 812 volumes per acre,
can green develop within the county
for a much denser type of
development too, as well.
- Sorry, Brenda,
but that's for single family
low density development.
But isn't the thing
currently under discussion
is to mark this whole
lot as mixed use, MUPUD?
- That's the zoning.
So what we did on the land use,
the land use is separated
out that village center,
phase one, and that village center, sorry,
phase two is going to be the commercial.
- So today, 5D, we're
specifically talking about zoning.
- The zoning, yes.
We have already voted for
the land use, which is again,
the yellow part is up to
the six volumes per acre.
The village center is commercial.
The transitional
is the multifamily medium
density residential
who has a density between
the 10 to 20 units per acre.
It was part of the backup.
So the transitional 1A can
accommodate the multifamily.
That density is 10 to 20.
So we want for that to happen.
- Do we have other public comments
regarding this agenda item?
Any other public comments?
Another chance.
If not, board members, do we
have any motions regarding 5D?
- I'll make a motion
to approve 5D with its existing
conditions, 18 of them.
- Motion to approve, Robert Spalding.
- Can I suggest the
discussion before the motion?
- The discussion would
come if we have the motion,
and then if we have a second.
Then there'll be opportunity
for discussion prior to the vote.
Do we have a second?
- Second.
- Fatima, second?
- Okay, all right.
Discussion, Alex.
- Yeah, so I guess I'm
struggling a little bit
with this one.
So our responsibility
on the Planning Advisory
Board is to withhold,
to ensure that Kissimmee's
comprehensive plan
is looked after.
And one of the first difficulties
is our comprehensive plan
really doesn't address
this part of Kissimmee.
This is a bit of an escalade,
but at the same time,
it represents a relatively
large proportion
of what will be the
residential stock for the city.
So it's a little difficult
when the existing chapters
in the comprehensive plan
dealing with land use,
transportation, walkability,
the other aspects that we
are supposed to maintain
and ensure sort of don't
address this part of the city,
mostly because the bulk of
this lot was newly annexed.
So that provides a bit of a difficulty
for me from the get go.
But then, at the same time,
looking at the proposed master plan
for the mixed use development,
I do think that in general,
it is in keeping with
Kissimmee's master plan.
There's a strong focus on walkability,
there's a strong focus on mixed
use, and trying to really,
it seems like, create a place
where the residents won't have
to get in their car and
drive down Simpson Road.
They'll be able to do a lot of business
in the kind of core there.
And it feels like we're really going out
of their way to sort of address some
of the things that we
are supposed to look for,
given Kissimmee's current
comprehensive plan.
But then maybe at the same time,
it feels like in certain places,
like I'm worried it almost
doesn't go far enough
to withhold some of the things
that we're supposed to look for,
in particular, some of
the things we're supposed
to look for, like walkability.
Like in extreme cases,
a lot of the things on the east end
of this thing are 45 minutes
from the sort of mixed use area.
And then in particular,
the comprehensive plan
chapter which is dealing
with things like our
transportation network,
our busing network,
and things like that sort
of don't address this area.
And in particular, if
I understand correctly,
in the current plan
and the current set of things
we're going to approve,
there was a condition that
there'd be no bus depots
in this lot at all.
I don't know if we'd get a clarification
for that in a second.
I forgot to ask earlier.
On the third hand,
I understand that a lot of
residents have concerns.
On the sort of fourth hand,
a lot of the residents who
have concerns aren't residents
of Kissimmee, but of Osceola County,
which makes it a little difficult, again,
because this is like an exclave property
as far as the city is concerned.
And then on maybe the next hand,
I understand that the purview of this body
and the thing that we're
actually discussing right now
is a very inside baseball thing
of changing the zoning
designation of this property.
But if I understand it,
this is the last time this
will come before this body.
So this is sort of our
opportunity to ensure that,
as far as we can tell,
Kissimmee is in keeping with
its comprehensive plans.
So I guess.
Yeah, I'm saying all of that
because I wanted to kind
of get it out there.
Yeah, to summarize,
in my reading of the comprehensive plan,
I am sort of happy to
see that this development
in particular seems to go out
of its way to address a lot
of the concerns we have.
But then at the same time, part of it,
I feel awkward about both,
because it is like
literally out of the purview
and off the map for most
of the comprehensive plan
that we currently have adopted.
And two, because it represents
what would be a relatively large stock,
sort of exclave to the rest of the city.
And I'm not sure the impact it will have
on the rest of the
things we need to ensure,
like transportation and services and parks
and things like that,
because it's sort of on its own.
So I don't know.
I wanted to put that out there.
- So, one thing really briefly,
and Brenda can probably speak
more to this in the applicant,
but this is, because of the
magnitude of the project
and the size of the property,
it's a little bit circular.
So last time this came before the board,
we were talking about annexation
and a comprehensive plan amendment.
And in the part,
you have to amend the comprehensive plan
because you're bringing new stuff in.
So that stuff is all changing
because of this development.
So I hope that when you're considering,
how does this zoning,
does the zoning follow
the comprehensive plan?
Which is, what is your guiding
document to the zoning.
I hope that you're
considering what you approved
whenever that was.
- Yes, thank you.
- Whether it's codified or
not, because I'm sure it's not.
- Yeah, I understand that
sort of technically we have
by annexing or already
approving the annexation
of the property.
- Because that stuff has not happened yet.
- Yes, I understand that
will bring it officially
within the purview of
the comprehensive plan.
I guess my concerns are more subjective
in the sense that the bulk
of the comprehensive plan
as written, like our
sections on transportation
and bus network and stuff,
generally the maps all focus
on the core of Kissimmee,
the sort of downtown area.
And there isn't existing services
of those types addressing
this part of Kissimmee.
And that makes it harder
to know whether or not
it's sort of in keeping with the spirit
of the existing comprehensive plan.
That's what I'm trying to say.
- Right, my point only was
that the existing
comprehensive plan is going
to be different once
this is formally adopted,
codified, so.
- If it's formally adopted.
- I mean, this has been,
the annotation has been
approved by this body,
not by the city commission.
- And to Alex's point with that,
as far as this being the final
spot here before it moves on,
help us all understand the
process here after this,
if it goes one way or the
other, where does this go?
Does the city commission
then have a say so
on the next step?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- You're recommending,
you're providing a recommendation
to the city commission.
- Got it.
Just want us all to
understand the next step.
Okay.
If it's approved.
Other questions.
- And then again to clarify,
not to beat a dead horse, then that is,
in terms of your legislation,
then this continues under staff review,
multi-department staff review,
GRC for your site plans,
whether they're site plans
with the conditional use that may come up,
construction plans, with proper variances.
- As it goes along,
it has to be studied and
approved each step of the way.
- Right.
So when Mr. Ren says that this is anything
that's 5 to 15 to however many years,
there's many years in which that site
and construction development
portion is going to happen.
So that's why I'm saying
this is very conceptual.
I'm not trying to influence a decision.
I'm urging you to think of it as zoning
and not as voting on a
specific development.
- Understood.
- It's tricky.
- Yeah.
But I guess maybe to clarify for my part,
it's also true that a
particular zoning designation
under consideration, MUPUD,
is one of the most sort of permissive
under the current stuff,
in the sense that there's
more within the developer's
kind of purview than would come before.
They're going to be able to make a bunch
of decisions without
seeking direct approval.
- Not really.
And if it makes you feel any better,
the city stands to gain as well,
because there is the
potential for extra amenities,
extra concessions,
because it is a broader
swath that, you know,
right now we're talking
about what the basic entitlements are,
but that doesn't necessarily
mean that the specifics
to how the development will unfold,
if that makes sense.
It's set in caps,
but it's not mandating specific
units, locations, et cetera.
- We have spent,
I think it's going to
be almost a year now.
So this is really not something.
We have numerous meetings,
and you're right,
mixed use PED is a lot of give beneficial
and a lot of give and take.
And so in my experience here,
it's perhaps only one other development
to take that a long time.
So it's been a lot coming
through, and even up to today,
having to make changes
to present this to you.
And then also,
I just wanted to clarify
a couple of things.
I put on there the findings and
reasons on the staff report.
We have to provide that.
So if we are providing a
recommendation for approval,
this is our findings
and reasons behind it.
And we have specific policies.
These are the ones here for the comp plan.
So we go through the different aspects.
It is going to be difficult
from a transportation standpoint
because the fact Simpson
Road is a county road,
it's not a city road.
We're not going to have much data per se,
other than traffic impact
analysis that we require
or require for this magnitude that's here.
And it's also,
there's so many goals,
objectives and policies, too,
as well, that we don't have a minimum
per se where you have to
meet this amount of goals,
of policies in the transportation
element because, again,
because of location, they
may be much more heavier,
let's just say in the
economic or the conservation.
Conservation element
for this particular project is a bit more
where we can confirm that as
opposed to the transportation.
Really briefly, bus depots are prohibited,
but that doesn't prohibit bus or transit.
Again, with Simpson or with Lynx,
there could be a bus
transit type of thing.
So it's not going to
prohibit bus transit stop,
but a bus depot where you have buses
that could be housed or stored.
That's the intent of,
that not allow for something like that,
but absolutely to have
bus depot transit stops.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
That's all I have for the clarification.
- I have a question.
Do we know when the first homes
were built in Hilliard Isle?
Just curious when that
was first constructed.
- I don't know.
- It says right now
I think there's only four
buildings on the property.
- The only thing I can tell you
in my prior experience
with the county is that these were part
of these rural enclaves.
So it's not only the age,
but also the size of the lots.
These types of rural enclaves
usually are state style,
minimum one acres.
But as I previously mentioned,
that the county has changed the land uses
within these enclaves to
up to eight dwelling meters
per acre, so that they can redevelop
at a higher density than they are before,
that they are now, sorry.
- I first lived in Kissimmee in 1986,
and I've seen a lot of changes
and a lot of developments over time.
And I know that changes happen,
but I certainly am
concerned about the traffic.
I'm concerned about
the schools, as I said,
with my own involvement with schools.
So I don't take any of this lightly.
Other discussion?
No further discussion or questions.
We'll entertain any motions
regarding this agenda item.
- I'll make a motion to adjourn.
- I'm sorry, I want to clarify,
when you talk about the conditions,
to make sure it's the revised conditions.
Just to make sure.
Versus based on the revised conditions,
and to clarify your motion if it's based
on the revised conditions.
- Say it again about
the revised conditions.
- The motion to make sure
whether or not it's the revised conditions
or the conditions that the.
- Or the original conditions, stating.
Okay, Robert, would you
restate what you just said?
Okay.
Go ahead, Alex.
- I think the city is suggesting that
because there were
revisions that were made
after the agenda was sent out,
they would like us to clarify whether
or not we are making
a motion to approve it
as stated in the agenda or as
stated with these revisions.
- With the new conditions.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Would anyone like to make a motion
regarding this agenda item?
I make a motion
to approve this agenda item
with the revised conditions.
Do we have a second?
- Second.
- We have a second, Robert Spalding.
We actually,
we had the motion previously,
and we had a second,
but we're clarifying this is
with the revised conditions.
Okay, restating.
So the original.
Let me go back, make sure
we have this correct.
We had the original motion.
Sorry.
Because the original motion
was already on the floor,
and we had a second.
That's what we were dealing with.
- So for the record.
- My motion is invalid
because we already had
one and we had a second.
Is that correct?
- Yes.
We're rescinding the first motion.
And reinstating a second motion
to approve the revised conditions.
- Robert made the first.
I just want to get this correct.
Robert made the first motion, correct?
- Yes.
- On record, okay.
- And was, with the 18 revised conditions.
Okay.
- So it's the same motion.
- It's the same motion.
Okay.
And the second had come from.
- The second came from Fatima.
- From Fatima, previously, okay.
All right.
And we have the discussion.
All in favor, please?
With any abstaining, again?
- Abstaining.
- Abstaining, okay.
To clarify.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion carries, four,
one, two, three, four, five,
zero, with one abstention.
Okay.
Thank you.
Those are all the agenda items.
Public hearings, any discussion,
here are the chairman and board members.
Does anyone have anything
they'd like to discuss
or bring up next meeting?
- As of right now, we don't
have any items for the,
I think it's January 2nd or January 3rd.
So I believe it's going
to be the the second PAB,
scheduled PAB meeting in January.
- Okay.
- Whenever it is.
- Anything else?
If not, motion to adjourn?
- Motion to adjourn.
- Motion to adjourn, Diana.
We have a second, Robert Spalding.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Meeting is adjourned at 7:12.
Thank you, everyone.