- Okay, hi everyone. It is 6:01.
Are we ready to go live here?
Ready. Okay.
6:01, calling the
meeting to order at 6:01.
I'm going to ask to stand
for a moment of silence
and the Pledge of Allegiance, please.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands.
one nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for al.
- Thank you.
I'll ask everyone to
please make sure to silence
your electronic devices.
And item three, approval
of the May 17th planning,
a motion to approve.
- Approve.
- Meeting, oh, we got already.
(indistinct crosstalk)
- You got to do it.
- Thank you, a motion
approve, we have a second?
- Second.
- We got a second. All
in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no. Hearing none.
Minutes are approved for
old business, nothing there,
five, 5A.
- Christian with development services,
the applicant's requesting approval
for an annexation application.
Subject site is located on
southeast corner of Simpson Road
and Hilliard Isle, it's
this triangular shaped lot.
Before I go into details
let me just give you a brief history
about this site because
it's a bit unusual.
In the year two thousand
subject property was annexed
to the City of Kissimmee
which you can see here, outlined in red.
It was the overall site,
and to the south of this
was Hilliard Isle, which was
originally used as a road
and it was in the Osceola
County's jurisdiction.
Next one, please.
Here's the overall history of the site.
In the year 2008, a
final plat was approved
which included the realignment
of the Hilliard Isle Road
which you can see here in yellow
which intersected the subject property
and which in turn closed
off the southern portion
which is labeled in blue,
due to this realignment.
In 2015, the Osceola County
approved the vacation
of right away, which was initiated
by the property owner at the time.
This was done to offset the loss
of the property that was provided
for this realignment
of Hilliard Isle Road.
Next please.
Present data is what we have currently.
We have the subject site
and the proposed annexation.
As you can see, the yellow line
represents the city limits.
So the applicant is
requesting the annexation
of this portion, which is
in blue, of the property
in order to develop the entire site.
The proposed annexation meets
all the requirements set forth
by local and Florida State
statutes for voluntary annexation
as a property is contiguous
to the city limits
along the northern and
southern boundaries.
The Development Review
Committee has reviewed
and approved the application.
And again this is going
to be the final outcome
where we have the the city limits shifted
and the overall site will be developable
which is the final
outcome or what the intent
of the applicant wishes to do,
therefore, Staff recommends approval
of the proposed annexation and I'll be
more than happy to answer
any questions you may have.
- Board members, any questions
or comments for the city?
No? Would the applicant
like to say any words
regarding this?
Please step to the mic, say your name
and business address for the record.
- Absolutely, good evening.
My name is Jeremy Anderson.
I'm with Common Oak Engineering,
4016 Edgewater Drive, Orlando,
I'm here today on behalf
of Medina Capital Group
who is the applicant as well
as the owner of Hilliard Isle.
I'd like to thank you, thank Staff.
I read through the entire Staff package
and honestly summarized
things things quite well.
I was involved with the
development as a civil engineer
and as also in 2015 I was
involved with the vacation process
where Medina Capital Group received
the vacated right of way.
So they now own that right of way.
As Staff alluded to there,
was showing you the images
there when the county
reconfigured the roadway
of course they reconfigured it to put it
in alignment with another
road across the street.
A significant amount of
the property was, you know
given to the county for that alignment.
And so it basically left that,
if you add in with the fact
that that parcel on the corner
there is a triangular piece.
And then you add also that
loss in property associated
with the donation or I guess
it would be a dedication,
it was done by Plat, so it was almost like
not even developable.
So with this request again in 2015,
really we should as
applicant have taken it
to the next step.
I thought we thought maybe
it was just going to happen
naturally or whatever, on
its own, but it didn't,
so it's just like left as
like a zoning that is like,
kind of like dead land, right?
So that's kind of a summary of the request
a little bit more and I'm
here to answer any questions
you might have and thank
you for opportunity.
- Board members, any
questions for the applicant?
Comments?
- No.
- If not, do we have any public comments?
No, okay.
Anyone like to make a
motion regarding the motion
to approve five A?
Bob made a motion.
Do we have a second, Melissa.
Second. Any discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- All opposed, please
say no. Hearing none.
Motion carries unanimously.
Five B.
- I'm actually in charge
of this one as well.
This one is for a land use plan amendment
and this is part of the annexation request
since that portion is going to be annexed
with the previous
application, it is required
to have a land use proposal.
In this case, the applicant has initiated
the land use plan amendment
which we had before you.
And just to give you some idea
of what's going on out there,
what you see here in red
is the existing land use.
This is based on the comprehensive plan
of commercial general,
which allows primarily
commercial uses.
So in order to make this fluent,
the applicant has requested
to carry this over
to the subject site
and for the entire site
to be at this category
which is commercial general.
The land use application has
been reviewed and approved
by the development review committee
and staff is recommending
approval with conditions
for the proposed land use
plan amendment application.
And again, if you have any questions,
please feel free to ask
- Board members any questions,
comments for the city?
No. Would the applicant
like to add anything or
you don't have to if
it's summed up already.
Okay. And if they have any questions,
they'll ask certainly.
Board any motion regarding
this agenda item?
- I'll make a motion for
final motion to be approved.
- Bob, okay.
- With the conditions?
- With the conditions, any second?
We have a second. Any discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Aye
- Opposed. Please say no. Hearing none.
Motion carries five C please.
- Five C.
That's also, again it is the three part
actually with this annexation.
You have your annexation, land use,
and finally you have
your zoning map amendment
which is what gives the zoning
and development standards
for the site.
The next Thank you.
Currently the subject side is zoned at B-2
which is neighborhood commercial.
And the applicant has made
the same request similar
to the land use plan amendment
for the zoning map amendment.
They want to keep the B2
neighborhood traditional
in order to develop the site.
So in order to be consistent,
the applicant has made this request.
And again, this zoning
map amendment application
has also been reviewed by the
Development Review Committee
and approved.
So staff recommends
approval with conditions
for this same application.
Again, you have any questions?
Please dial me.
- Board members questions?
Comments for the city?
- No.
- No, applicant, anything?
Okay, any public comments
which I failed to ask
the last time for public comments
and will allow that if-
(chuckles)
Okay, board any motion regarding five C.
Motion approved, Melissa.
- I'll second.
- And we have a second, Bob.
Any discussion? If not, a call to vote.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none. Motion passes unanimously.
Thank you.
Six public hearings. Anything?
Seven, discussion. Board? City?
- It's just that I
believe we do have items
for the next meeting.
The first planning advisory board meeting.
I believe we do have items.
- The 21st?
No, it's going to be, oh goodness.
I should have this, June 21st, I'm sorry.
I'm skipping over to July already.
(indistinct crosstalk)
Yes, June 21st.
- I will not be here,
I'll be out of state.
- Okay.
- On that day, so.
- Make a note of that.
- I'll make a note of that.
But yeah, we do have several
items going to June 21st
actually be a conditional
use, I'm just wondering.
It'll be a conditional use and a rezoning.
- Okay.
I have nothing to say at the moment.
Any board members with
any comments or anything?
No?
- I do.
- Bob, go right ahead.
- I make a motion to adjourn.
- We have a motion to
adjourn. Do we have a second?
- Second.
- The second from Melissa. Any discussion?
- No. All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Aye
- Please say no. We're adjourned.
6:12, thank you.