- Going to ask everybody,
silence your devices please,
including board members.
And we're going to stand please,
ask everybody to stand
for a moment of silence
and the Pledge of Allegiance.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands
one nation, under God, indivisible
with liberty and justice for all.
- Thank you.
Item four, old business, nothing there.
Five. I'm sorry.
Let me say three, minutes.
Sorry. Three A, approval
of June 7th minutes.
- We motion to approve.
- Motion to approve from
Robert, do we have second?
- Second.
- We have second from Alex.
And all in favor?
- Aye.
- Opposed?
Hearing none, minutes are approved.
Three B approval of June 21st meeting.
Do we have a motion?
- Motion.
- Motion approved, Diana.
- Second.
- Second, Robert. Any discussion changes
on favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Oppose, please say no.
Hearing none, minutes are approved.
Old business, nothing there.
Five A proposed ordinance number 23-15.
- Yes, this is a future
land use amendment.
It's actually a city initiated
future land use amendment
to change the land use designation
from industrial business to single family,
low density, residential.
This property as well as 264 other parcels
were part of a small
enclaves interlocal agreement
or ILA with the.
- I'm sorry Brenda.
Are we supposed to have
this on our monitors here?
- Oh yes. I'm sorry.
The monitors are probably
not turned on here.
- Sorry.
- The far right.
- Okay.
- First one. Yeah. Yes.
- Okay, thank you. I got it. Sorry
- So this parcel here.
So just general here, it's just
east of the Gateway Airport
and what you see here
with the baseball fields
and the tracks, that's
Osceola High School.
So at the end of in Backer is
going to be east just outside
of view here at the dead end of Patrick.
- So this parcel, actually
it's two parcels here,
was part of that
interlocal agreement, 2019
in addition to 264 other parcels.
That initiative with
the ILA was to address
and target certain areas
where we had enclaves
and try to improve services
such as garbage collection
and also improve emergency
services responses too, as well.
But with that, because
there's 264 parcels,
the land use designations,
we tried to establish
something that was comparable
to what the future language
designation was in the county.
Unfortunately there were
some scrivener errors
and inconsistencies with the transition
of the county future land
use destination and the city.
So we are correcting this
one here with this property
had a low density
residential county land use.
So we are correcting this
with this amendment to
change that land use designation
to the single family,
low density, residential,
comparable to what it was
before it was annexed to the city.
The low density residential
is also consistent
with the, there's some small
different residential areas.
You see there Marion Avenue
is a small little subdivision.
And then of course on
the northeast corner here
at Brian Street there is residential.
So this change is consistent
with the surround area
and it's also going to be consistent
with the zoning map amendment
which will be heard next.
And it's consistent
with the land development
code requirements too.
So therefore staff is recommending
approval at this time.
- Thank you.
Board members, any questions
or comments for the city?
- Yeah, I guess I.
- Go ahead, Alex.
- I have a quick question.
I was looking through the agenda
and I noticed that there
was an email between Greg
and the landowners regarding
I think item five B,
not five A specifically. I think.
- it was actually both.
I think in the background
for the support documents,
I think it was in both.
It should be in both
because the property owners,
are item 5A and 5B is
for the same property.
- Yeah, I understand
it's the same property.
I guess I just wanted to double check.
It seemed like it was indicated
in the supporting documents
that the landowner were reached out to
and they agreed with the
switch to agricultural
and conservation zoning change,
which I think is item five B.
I was wondering whether it is important
'cause I wasn't seeing evidence
that they supported the change
in the future land use map designation.
Whether that was
important or necessary or.
- It was and I thought it
was part of the supporting.
I thought that same email was
part of the supporting doc.
It should be with this
item five A too, as well.
It should be and if it wasn't
then that was an error.
But I could have sworn
that it was in there because
it's the same property owner,
but moving forward it should be part
of this land use authorization.
I thought it was in the the overall,
it's the overall packet,
the overall packet.
- I guess maybe a naive question,
but could you help me out I guess,
what's the kind of primary difference
between the zoning map designation
and the future land use map designation?
- So within the state of Florida,
'cause we are a
comprehensive planning state,
so the state requires
that every jurisdiction
maintains a comprehensive plan
of just general types of land uses.
The requirement is those
land uses generally
dictate the number, the density,
the dwelling units per acre
or if it's commercial, floor area ratio.
Each city or jurisdiction
may have different goals
or objectives in the future.
There usually 10 to 20 year
horizons of just generally
of how a local organization
wants to grow or to improve.
So that's land use
which is this item here.
When you establish the land use,
the zoning pretty much will hone down
and make it much more
particular about this.
Land use has a certain types
of zoning that is compatible with it.
The zoning's going to get much
more detail about setbacks,
about different random height requirements
and those types of things.
Land use is overall general,
it pretty much sets the
foundation for the zoning
that can be selected or
is compatible with it,
in a nutshell.
- Thank you.
- The authorization?
That's going to be at the bottom.
Yeah. So we're going to, as
I move, I want to make sure,
but if not it should be
under both to make sure
that it is.
We got the authorization
from the property owner
for us to present this as
a city initiated change.
- Okay. Yeah, I guess in
reading the documents,
it seems like,
I think the emails are included
in the supporting documents
for both, but the actual text
to the emails was making,
it seemed like was making
reference specifically
to the agricultural and conservation.
- Oh I see what you're saying.
The actual, I see, okay, I get it.
The content in the email, I
see what you're saying. Okay.
- Is that a potential
issue or is that okay?
- It's not, but if it
means as a comfort level
moving it forward
then we can reach back
out to the property owner
to ask them the question,
Do we have your authorization to also
change the future land designation?
If you can, do you think
you can drag that email.
So that way what he's saying
is that it was attached
under both but the conversation
was just about zoning
and not land use.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah. Here. It was just
the conversation just only
addressed the zoning.
But it says and changing
the land use too, as well.
But it didn't spell out
exactly the single family,
low density, residential land use.
So I understand what you're saying.
- Thank you.
- Board, any other questions or comments?
If not, is the landowner
here to make any comment?
- The landowner is not so
that's why that authorization to
allow us to do a city
initiate and to represent,
for the city staff to
represent the property owner.
- Okay. We'll open up any public comments,
any members of the public
want to make any comments
regarding this agenda item?
Any public comments?
No. Okay.
Board, do we have motion
regarding this agenda item?
- I'll make a motion to approve it.
- Robert, we have motion
from Roberts to approve.
Second, do we have a second?
- Second
- Second from Diana.
Any conversation about
this? Any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed? Please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries 5B 23-16.
- Yes, this is the companion
zoning map amendment to
change the zoning on these properties
from airport industrial to
agricultural and conservation.
Like I mentioned before, it was part
of the small enclaves ILA
back in 2019, 264 properties,
the long list of different,
a table of different changes.
So as these scrivener's error.
Now when it comes to the agricultural
and conservation development,
that zoning is compatible
with single family,
low density, residential and
it acts as a holding zone
when perhaps the property
owner does not really
know exactly what they're going to build.
Our comp plan allows that AC zoning to act
as a holding zone until such
time they're able to redevelop.
At this point in time there are
at least three different
individual single family homes
on that property.
Being that it is existing
development and like I mentioned
that there is residential
development adjacent to it,
that feels that it's appropriate
to rezone this property
to agricultural and
conservation development.
At this time, SAC is
recommending approval subject
to the approval of the land use amendment.
- Okay. Board, any comments or questions
for the city? If not,
do we have any public
comments regarding this piece
of the agenda?
Any public comments?
If not, anyone like to make a motion?
- Motion to approve.
- Motion to approve,
Diana. Do we have a second?
- I'll second.
- We have a second.
Robert, any discussion? No. Okay.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Five C, conditional use
with site specific
redevelopment plan request.
- Good evening.
The applicant has found a
conditional use application
for multifamily use.
Subject property is located
on the southeast corner of
Dilingham Avenue and James Street
as you can see here,
delineated on your screens.
Subject property consists
of a vacant parcel,
total of land area, 0.78 acres of land.
Subject property is located
in a T4R neighborhood resident
restricted zoning district
which allows multifamily uses subject
to the approval of the
conditional use permit.
The request is for an
eight unit, multifamily,
single story residential development.
The staff has reviewed the
project and it is consistent
with the form-based code standards set
forth by the lab development code.
This project was reviewed and approved
by the development review committee
and staff is recommending approval subject
to conditions contained
in your staff report.
This concludes my report.
I'll be happy to answer
any questions you may have.
- Board, any comments or
questions for the city?
Alex, go ahead.
- So looking through the
supporting documents I noticed
that it was mentioned
that this lot is adjacent
to a flood plain, an AD
designated flood plan,
which it does seem like it is,
just on the edge of the property.
And so there was a condition stipulated
by the city that suggested that
the plan include information
about the base elevation
of the ground floor.
I wasn't able to see that
in the supporting documents.
Is that, I guess, would that be required
at a later stage given
approval or is that?
- That is actually reviewed
by our engineering department.
They have flood maps which are
consistent with their code.
It's mostly engineering that handles that.
As far as the development
or the land development code
within our planning section,
it does only mentioned
the geometrics, setbacks, coverage,
parking, buffers, making sure
that the adjacent residential
uses are not impacted.
Therefore we're reviewing
that now to make sure
that we have adequate spacing
which we have reviewed and
it meets all the standards.
But as far as flood zones and that nature,
it is public works engineering
that handle that aspect
of this project.
And they actually review that
and include documentation
within the review.
But in the later, after this is approved,
they will move into the construction phase
where it will be reviewed
under those sections required
by their codes.
- Thank you
- You welcome.
- I also want to remind
all the board members
that if there are any
conflicts of interest
or you've had any ex parte
conversations or prior research
on any of the items,
please let that be known.
Do we have the applicant here?
Would the applicant
like to step to the mic
and say a few words?
Please state your name
and your business address
for the record please.
- My name is Steve Ivans.
I am on the Board of
Directors for Park Place.
I'm kind of pinch hitting
for Jim Shanks, the CO.
He's sick today.
This project is called Res four.
It's for people that
have come out of rehab
and rather than they go
back to a bad environment,
they come here for seven to
12 months and get counseling.
We have a current operation,
I don't know if that's the right word,
but we had a facility that
it was an old motel I guess,
and that was knocked down
and the building across June
Street Apartment Project
and those people are being housed
in an old house somewhere temporarily
until this project goes.
And I'm here to answer any
questions you may have,
anyone has, and our
engineers there, Steve Boyd,
to any technical questions you might have.
- Board, any questions?
- Yeah, is this a rehabilitation?
- No, I wouldn't call it rehabilitation.
When they're in rehab,
that would be in my mind, rehabilitation.
This is when they've graduated from that
and this has a kitchen facility.
They come and they learn, you know,
they live on alone basically.
And there's a room for
a counselor to come in.
- So this is like a transition house to?
- Yes, I'd call it a
transition house, yes.
- Is there a certain amount
of time that they must be
in rehab before this becomes
a possibility for them?
Is there any minimum time
that they have to be in rehab?
- Well, like I said,
it's not really rehab.
- No. They were in rehab.
Is there a minimum time that
they have to be in rehab
before they transition into this?
- I'm not qualified to
answer that question.
I don't know.
- Anyone else?
- How much does it, I see four.
Is it four?
How many people can fit in this?
What are we looking at
here as far as residence?
- Total of eight units.
There'll be four in four apartments.
We had room for more on the
property, but we get money
from the state to pay
for the beds basically.
And that's how the
business runs more or less.
You get grants to operate that depending
on the number of beds.
And that's the number of beds we have and.
- What was the total number of beds?
I'm sorry I missed that.
- Eight.
- Eight. Okay. So one
person per unit. Okay.
- Robert, did you have something else?
- No. No.
- Okay. So the eight that are there,
what are the qualifications
for the people who are housed there?
What is the criteria I
guess for the individuals?
- They've come from another
program that Park Place runs,
I guess. I think you,
I'm pretty sure you have
and I'm just kind of guessing
here, you have to come
through the Park Place
program of rehabilitation
and then then you can come to this.
I don't know that they would take,
let's say someone off the street.
Not to say they wouldn't, but I just think
that you're part of a
program being counseled
and there's counselors
and probably, you know,
maybe some medicine, you
know, that sort of thing.
I wish I knew more and Jim
was supposed to be here,
but he's basically, he's in the hospital.
He's sick. So I can't
answer those questions.
- Okay. Diana.
- Just one last question.
When they're living there, there's no one
on staff that's actually
more monitoring these
or that's there with them? It's all.
- Correct. At this point,
they could go home if they wanted to.
- Okay.
- Okay. But a lot of these
people are in a bad situation
with people that would
probably easily get them back
in some addiction. Right?
So they want to get them away
from a bad environment,
keep them, you know,
walking a straight path, so to speak.
So it's an, I think, I'm pretty
sure it's an optional thing.
They encourage you to go
here and why wouldn't you?
It's new and clean and
you know, so they could
if they wanted to go home,
they're encourage you to get jobs too.
Most of them, it's been our experienced,
they don't have cars.
So they'll take public transportation
or their bikes and you
know, the counselors work
with them, trying to get them
back on their feet basically
and become, you know,
productive members of society.
That's what this is all about.
- Robert.
- So all of your clientele
at the transition house,
they are going to be from
a rehabilitation center?
- Yes.
- So you come out of
jail and you go into a.
- Halfway house.
- Halfway house and
then from halfway house,
you stay there so long and
you improve or you go back.
And if you improve then you
go to a transition house
and you can stay there,
promote yourself, get better,
but you go up the ladder like anyone else.
- That's my understanding. Yes.
- I'm going to state this for the record.
I don't see this as a conflict,
but I'm on the board of directors
of the Opportunity Center
which is almost adjacent, very near there.
So I have an interest in, you know,
this area, but I don't believe
that's any sort of conflict.
Okay. We'll take any public
comments at this time.
Would anyone from the public
like to make any comments?
No. More time.
Any public comments?
Okay. Any discussion from the board?
If not, we'd accept any motions
regarding this agenda item?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- We have a motion to approve from Robert.
Do we have a second?
- I'll second.
- We have a second from Diana.
Discussion, board, any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Thank you.
Public hearings.
Six. Nothing there.
Seven, discussion?
Brenda, board, anything?
- I need to confirm but I
don't think we have any items
for the first meeting in August,
but I'll definitely send you all an email.
I believe the next project
that we have is scripts
for August 16th, but I will confirm.
- All right.
And here, chairman and board members.
Alex, welcome.
What's your last name, Alex?
So I'm Alex Lanny.
Yes. Thank you.
- Welcome and thank you for being here.
- Yeah, resident of
Kissimmee, live downtown.
Excited to try to help
out the city, do my part
and yeah, cool.
- Anything from our attorney?
- I just, for you guys and for Alex also,
just to elaborate on one of
your questions having to do
with this site plan
that the conditional use
of the site plan is, Christian
was mentioning when you asked
about the flood plains,
that's something that goes
at the next level of review.
So site plan is kind of a first stage
and it's kind of an overview
of the development project.
It's a rough draft and then it
goes into construction plans.
So that's where you would
see those details just to,
construction plans never
come back to this board.
So that's as in depth of a
rendering as you would see, so.
- I'll just say thank you
to everyone who showed
up to take an interest
in what goes on here in your city.
Thank you for that.
Thank you.
Do we have a motion to adjourn?
- I'll make a motion to adjourn.
- Robert, motion to adjourn.
Second?
- Second.
- Second, Alex, any discussion?
If not all in favor, please say aye.
Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Meaning adjourned at 6:24.
Thank you.