- Good evening.
We're gonna call the meeting
to order is 6:17 PM.
If everyone could please stand
for a moment of silence and
the Pledge of Allegiance.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America.
And to the republic for which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- As a reminder, we ask you
to silence any electronics
and ladies, to just
move on to new business.
- Hi, good evening.
This first item is
for an ordinance amending
the zoning map designation
for the sub property
from open space to multiple
family medium density
which is RC2 for the Bass Road town homes.
And there's the map of the property.
This property went through
an annexation in 2019
as part of an interlocal
agreement with Osceola County
which annexed around 200 other properties.
And at the time the subject
property adopted the city's,
we used the comprehensive
plan policy, 1.1.10.5
to convert the county's land use
and zoning designation to the cities.
And the applicant
at this time would like
to amend that zoning
from open space to RC2
for town home development.
And it is in compliance with
the existing future land use
of multifamily medium density residential.
So the Development Review
Committee recommended approval
at the May 16th, 2023 meeting.
- Is the occupant here?
Yes, the property owner is here.
- Would you like to speak?
- Well.
- You'd have to come up, sorry sir.
State your name and address.
- Good evening.
It's not the first time I
develop a property in Kissimmee.
- Your name and address.
- I'm sorry, Miguel Kaled,
2305 Edgewater Drive, Orlando
Florida 32804, College Park.
It's not the first time we
developed a property in Kissimmee
and a client of mine
acquired this piece of land.
And we are developing,
we are taking very good care
of developing a good product.
So all town houses will
be facing each other
and the corridor in the middle of them
more or less 50 feet will
have only pedestrian access.
And the main thing for this
is to provide the family,
especially if they have kids,
contained environment without fences.
And all the garages
will be facing outwards
of the lot.
We have here,
so no cars in front of the
unit, cars will be around.
And I think it's a good concept.
We have that, we've done that before.
Everybody liked very much.
And I think that's it.
If you have questions,
I'm ready to answer them.
- Do you have any questions?
- No.
- No
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Does anyone from the audience?
- Quick question from the board.
There has been no ex parte
communications or site visits?
No complex?
Okay.
Just put it on the record, thanks.
- And to clarify we did not
receive any public comment
prior to this meeting.
- Is there any conditions to it?
- The only conditions
were advisory for the
whenever they submit their site plan
just advisory comments such as,
it is within the conservation overlay
and they will need to provide
a conservation impact report.
And then a few other things just related
to site plan approval
but nothing related to
the zoning approval.
- Okay.
- So do I have motion to approve?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- Yes.
- All in favor?
- Aye
- Aye.
- Anyone opposed?
Motion carries.
- Cool.
- Yes, so this next item is a request
for conditional use with site
specific redevelopment plan
for an office conversion located
at 1012 Mabbot, shown here.
And the property is currently zoned T40
which allows office convert,
or which allows office users
with a conditional use.
And this request is to establish an office
at the subject property.
And the building was
originally built in 1926
as a single family residence,
and has been used as this since then.
And the property is
approximately 0.21 acres.
The property has received some notices
of violation and has an
open code enforcement case
which went to special magistrate
on June 12th of this year.
And the property owners
were given a 90 day
extension to come into compliance
and this approval would be part of that.
And then the conversion
includes the additional
five parking spaces and
a paved access drive
to the rear of the property.
And then other improvements
include the addition
of a bike rack and pedestrian access
in accordance with the
land development code
and staff recommends approval.
And this application is
also for office use only.
Any additional commercial
uses such as personal service
or other uses that require conditional use
in T40 will need to go
through a separate approval process
but at this time staff
recommends approval.
- Is there anyone here who would like
to speak on the property?
- It's not required if you don't want to.
- No?
All right
- So just to put on the record,
there has been no ex parte
communication site
visits or any conflicts.
Great, thank you.
- And we have received no
public comment about this item.
- And the conditions that goes with that?
- No conditions apart
from this approval is
for office use only.
- Was there a site plan
for this one included?
- Yes.
- Was the bike rack required by the city?
Or is it something that,
- Can you scroll it back
for the picture of the home?
- Bicycle parking is required,
I believe up to 10% for parking spaces.
So one bike rack or five bike spaces.
So yes, that's a requirement
for all commercial
development in the city.
- Okay.
- That's the home and the access will be
on if you're facing the home
on the right side of the property.
And the left will be
landscaping and retention.
- I have a question.
So if approved, you would
be for any kind of office
or a specific one?
- So for, based on the square
footage of the property
it would likely only be
like administrative offices.
The site with the current parking
or with the proposed
parking would not be able
to support a doctor's office
because of the higher
parking requirements.
So this would just be
for normal office use,
administrative, something like that.
I believe there's a tax office
or accounting or something
there at the moment.
- Thank you.
- Okay, thank you.
No more questions?
- No.
Nobody has any questions.
- No one has any more
questions, motion to approve.
- I'll make a motion to approve then.
- Second?
- Second.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- Any opposed?
Hearing none.
Motion carries.
- Who seconded that?
- That was simultaneous.
(laughing)
All right.
Public hearings?
None?
Discussion?
- The next scheduled meeting
I believe is July 5th.
However, at this time, I don't know
if we have any items that are scheduled.
We may have to postpone
or cancel that meeting
but I will definitely provide
you, lookout for your emails
that we may have to postpone
that meeting on July 5th.
And meaning that the next
meeting would be the third.
So it's first and third
Wednesday of the month
So just keep that in mind.
I do know again, anytime in the summertime
we are aware of the different travels.
So just let us know ahead of time
that you won't be attending
so that way we just know
that we do have at least a quorum,
which is the four members.
And I will definitely
provide you an email.
But more than likely right now,
there will be no meeting on July 5th
and the item the next meeting
will be that Wednesday.
I forget.
- The 19th?
- The third, yes.
For that one here.
But I have to double check to see
because I don't think we've advertised,
but based on our schedule
I think we may have,
we have to speak to some
applicants regarding that meeting.
- Okay.
- Alright, thank you.
- It'll be a nice long Independence.
- Yes.
- Having said that, we
adhere from the chairman,
I just wanna make sure everyone a happy
and safe 4th of July.
Anything else from the board members?
- Make a motion to,
- I have a quick comment,
You did a fantastic job
chairing this meeting.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Very, very well done.
- Thank you.
All right.
You were gonna motion?
- I was just gonna wait if
your head slowed down a little.
(laughing)
- I thought you were
gonna motion to adjourn.
- Make a motion to adjourn.
- Second.
- Second
- We are adjourned.
- Aye.
- Shall I say the time?
6:28.
- Everybody say, "Aye."
- Everybody said "Aye."
We all said it together.
- We all seconded it.
(laughing)
- Cool.