- [Robert] Okay, we're good to go.
Calling the meeting to order six o'clock.
Please everyone silence your devices.
Everyone on the board here too please.
And please stand for a moment of silence
and the Pledge of Allegiance.
- [Everyone] I pledge
allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the Republic for which it stands
one nation, under God, indisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- [Robert] Thanks everybody.
Welcome, and we are looking at the minutes
from our September 6th meeting.
I actually see an error on here,
if we could change that
where it says, Chairman Robert Buotier
adjourned the meeting.
My name is misspelled.
So we've got one R in there.
Just a little detail.
Other than that,
does anyone have any motions
regarding these minutes?
Okay, actually yeah, I'm sorry
I was looking at the wrong thing here.
Yep, motion to approve by Diana.
Second Robert.
All in favor, please say aye.
- [Board] Aye.
- [Robert] Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none minutes are approved.
And we are at, I'm sorry
getting all my papers mixed up here.
Okay old business, nothing new business.
5A.
- [Brenda] Good evening.
This is a conditional use
request for the development
of town homes within our T4R Transex zone.
This property, as it's
noted here on the map
is going to be on the
south side of June Street.
It's also just south of Martin Luther King
about a block east from
John Young Parkway.
Initially when this application
came in with the applicant,
it was initially as
apartments or a fourplex,
but going through our initial
development review committee
or DRC with all the
different requirements,
it was redesigned to be
three simple town homes
just the three units for the town homes.
The new town home layout
you have in your supporting packet.
I wanna also spend some
time here to also take note
of the development that's
happening within this area here.
And I've prepared a map.
Just one second.
I zoomed out a little bit here.
So the A represents the subject
property that we're talking
about tonight.
B, I'm not sure some of you recall back
in, I think earlier this year, in July,
this was the approval of
conditional use that went
before this board in July for
the June Street apartments
which is gonna be B, that's noted here.
Also previous to that, beginning
of the year in January,
we note here on C, we actually
brought before the PAB
the redevelopment of that property.
The larger building that
you see there will remain,
but the smaller buildings
have been demolished
because they're in active
construction right now.
And what they're
developing is a three story
development that will house
as a more stable types of
multi-family affordable housing
for those that are
coming out of treatment.
This is owned by the
Park Place Mental Health.
So that building will be
more of a permanent type
of housing as the, as they
go through transitional
and go through the pro
process of rehabilitation.
Also of note that I don't
have highlighted here
further east where you
see Altman and Rose Avenue
you see a little roundabout that's also
active construction that
you see, that is also
now going to be apartments.
I think they have it
as an Allen Apartments.
That is the first
development, the first phase
of development for that
property that used to have,
some of you are are from around here,
used to be the Beaumont Middle School
and before then the county,
excuse me, had some offices there.
But that is being redeveloped
as the first phase
as multi-family apartments with
opportunities for commercial
out parcels along the frontage
of Martin Luther King.
So I just wanted to give y'all up to date
of all this different
development that is occurring
within this general area.
And I did a little summary
of that in the paragraph,
the second paragraph of the staff report.
Going back to the
conditional use application
before us, reporting documentation,
go ahead and and pull this up.
Again it's gonna be three units.
The town home units
are meeting our minimum
living area requirement
that actually exceeds
that for a town home development.
The units A and B that you see there
includes the two car garage.
The one on the the right
will be a one car garage.
It actually exemplifies
again what we're trying to
do is to introduce a variety
of different housing
types within this area.
And I think we do within the
downtown area too as well,
a different variety of
different housing opportunities.
Also include as well,
like I mentioned here
that it exceeds minimum
living area requirements.
Staff will continue to work
with the applicant as it
moves towards construction.
There'll be some revisions
on the elevations
at least we spoke with the applicant
of doing some adjustments to the different
the windows and all of that.
So we'll do some further adjustments
to the elevations, but at this time
staff is recommending approval, subject
to the five conditions that were listed
in the staff report.
I'm here to answer any questions
and also the applicant.
- [Robert] Board questions
or comments for the city?
If not, we'd like to
hear from the applicant.
If the applicant would
like to say a few words,
would you step to the microphone
please state your name and
your address for the record.
- [Vivian] Hi, good afternoon.
My name is Vivian Pasqua and
my husband is Giovania Costa
and we are doing this project, you asked
for our address?
- [Robert] Your business address.
- [Vivian] Oh, okay.
1491 Diamond Nuke Drive,
Kissimmee Florida, 34744.
- [Robert] Thank you.
Did you have anything
you'd like to mention
to the board regarding this?
- [Vivian] No, she said
everything we want to say
and for sure we want so we has
been building properties here
in Kissimmee area and we love this project
and we are going to subdivide
this property in a simple
fee simple, for to be able to do that.
- [Robert] Okay, board any
questions for the applicant?
If not do have any public comments
regarding this agenda item?
Any, yes ma'am would you like
to step to the microphone?
Please state your name and
your address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
(footsteps patter)
- [Willimae] Good evening, my
name is Williemae Prettigar.
I live at 416 North Billingham.
I'm interested in knowing what,
where's the parking lot
for this development.
Also it will there be a concrete fencing,
because I own property
adjacent to this lot
behind me and on the side of me.
[Robert] Okay, thank you.
Brenda, would you like to address that?
Thank you ma'am.
- [Brenda] So on the screen,
because there'll be townhomes,
the parking will be in the driveway.
Two of the units will
have a two car garage,
and there'll be a driveway.
So there won't be a parking lot.
It'll be like a townhome,
where each of the units
will have a driveway.
I think there's another depiction here.
(audience member coughs)
Yeah, that's a bit a better
picture there to show how
long the length of the driveways,
so the parking will all
be within the driveways.
And then the other question was
about the concrete?
- [Williemae] Yes, concrete fencing.
See I, my property, it's a
lot being, because I talked
to one of the surveyors, when
he was out there surveying,
and there posed to be three
lots that's feeding together
plus a vacant lot on the
side of when you come
off of June Street.
- [Brenda] So at this
time they're not required
to provide any type
of a perimeter wall because
if you reference the A,
which is the subject property
behind that property are town homes.
So it's the same type product.
So there's town homes
existing off of King Street.
The town homes on King,
the only difference is
that they're rear loading,
they load to towards the back.
These town homes will have the entrances
along June Street.
So because the two are
the same, they're not
gonna be required to put
any type of wall or fencing.
It would be voluntary for
each of the individuals.
Once the lots are sold,
if the individual property
owners would want to put
in any type of fencing.
- [Williemae] Also are these
townhomes gonna be rental
or property owners?
- [Brenda] It's gonna be
up to the property owner
whether or not it could be rentals or not.
For as far as with the
city, their fee simple.
The only thing is that they
cannot be short term rental,
but it can be rental.
Short term rental meaning that it's
it has to be, it cannot
be 30 days or less.
- [Robert] So it couldn't
be used for like an Airbnb.
- [Brenda] It could not.
It's not within the short
term rental overlay.
It has to be a minimum of a
month to month type of lease.
- [Robert] Alright, thank you.
Do we have any other public comments?
Any other public comments?
If not, do we have any
motions from the board?
- [Melissa] Calling for motion to approve.
- [Robert] Melissa
Thacker, motion to approve.
We have second, Robert
Capp, any discussion?
Yes.
- [Robert Capp] I guess
specifically the packet suggested
a conditional approval.
Is that a different action
that we would take besides
just making approval, or?
That's the same, okay.
- [Brenda] Accepting, your
approving with the conditions
specified.
Unless you want to do otherwise.
- [Robert] Okay, any other discussion?
If not all in favor, please say aye.
- [Board] Aye.
- [Robert] Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion carries.
Item is approved, and
public hearings discussion.
Dear Chairman Board,
actually I do have a question
going back to the minutes.
And other than my one thing
about the misspelling,
maybe this is me just
misunderstanding 'cause I
thought about this after
we already approved it.
Back in the item where
we had the future land
use designation from county low dense LDR,
and I know Melissa had abstained.
Am I looking at this incorrectly,
That at the bottom where it
says "Aye," it has Melissa
under the "Aye," or am I
looking at that incorrectly?
- [Melissa] Yeah that's incorrect.
- [Robert] That is incorrect.
So how do we go about amending this,
having already approved the minutes?
Do we make a motion to
amend the previously
approved minutes?
- [Melissa] You can
make a motion to amend.
- [Robert] Okay.
- [Melissa] And it will
come back to the board
at the next meeting.
- [Robert] At the next meeting, okay.
So we can't actually reapprove the minutes
at this meeting or-
- [Melissa] I mean, you, yeah,
I mean I think it's better
if we bring it back.
- [Robert] Okay, so
technically it's a vote
that is then announced
to the public in advance?
Okay so-
- [Melissa] And it will
be, the correct ones
will be published
with our agenda packet for
the next meeting as well.
So why don't we just do
an, an order, I mean, sorry
a motion to vacate the
approval of the minutes.
- [Robert] Okay, yeah,
I'd like to make a motion
to vacate the approval
the previous approval of the minutes.
And actually before I
follow through with that
I wanna make sure on the other
one there was the abstention
that that also doesn't
reflect her with an I.
If anybody can help me find that.
Does it show that?
Okay, all right yeah.
So I make a motion to
vacate the previously
approved minutes.
Do we have a second?
- [Robert Capp] Yes sir.
- [Robert] We have a second.
Alex, any discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
- [Board] Aye.
- [Robert] Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none.
Motion minutes are vacated.
Sorry, I didn't catch that earlier.
- [Melissa] That's a good catch.
Thank you for that.
- [Robert] That's an important item.
Okay, anything else from
any other board members?
If not, do we have motion to adjourn?
Motion to adjourn.
Melissa Packard.
We have second?
- [Diana] Second.
- [Robert] Second from Diana.
All in favor, please say aye.
- [Board] Aye.
- [Robert] Aye, opposed, please say no.
The meeting is adjourned at 6:14.
Thank you.
So should I sign this or no, not sign it.
Okay, I'll just give it back to you.