(people chattering)
- Meeting to order.
Welcome, everyone.
Yeah. Hi.
Thanks.
Always call me when I mess something up.
I have no shame in that.
Please tell me.
Please stand for the Pledge of Allegiance
And a moment of silence.
- I pledge allegiance.
- [Everybody] To the flag of
the United States of America
and to Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all
- Thank you.
You may be seated.
And we have no minutes,
correct, to approve?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Remembering that we have
to correct the minutes.
So for the next agenda,
we'll probably have three sets of minutes
because we had to
correct the previous one,
and the one that we had before
and now we're gonna have
minutes for this item.
- Right, right.
- Or for this meeting, sorry.
- Okay.
And old business, nothing there?
New business?
- Yes.
This is a conditional
use with site plan waiver
for an educational
service, vocational school
at 3357 West Vine Street.
If need be, I can go ahead
and pull up the diagrams
that are exhibits as I go through this.
They're currently requesting-
- Can I pause you for a second
so I don't forget this, which
I have a tendency to do?
I'm gonna ask all board members
if you have any conflicts of
interest with this agenda item
or have had any ex parte communications
or done any research on your
own, anything like that,
please let that be known.
Thank you.
Sorry, Brenda.
No, you're fine.
- This is for a educational
service for a vocational school,
the KCBS Advance Academy.
It is a vocational school
for comprehensive support education
for children on the autistic spectrum.
- Oh, well then, here, let me ask Colony,
because I am on the board of directors
of the Opportunity Center of
the nonprofit in Kissimmee
that works with adults with
developmental disabilities.
I have a son who's autistic.
Is that any sort of...
Okay.
Putting it out there for the record.
Sorry, go ahead.
- No, you're fine.
This is good.
- The vocational school,
there's an exhibit with the documents
will include just Suite
105 on the first floor.
There's about 3,200 square feet
within Suite 105 that they will occupy.
Total maximum of students
will be 30 students.
And then with the maximum employees
of six instructors,
teachers within this 105.
I also wanna point out
with the adjacent suite,
currently with the current
location in St. Cloud,
the students also have
additional behavioral
analysis therapy at the Kids
Corner Behavioral Services.
Part of the reason why that they want
to include the vocational school here
is to make it a lot easier
for the students to have counseling
and further therapy right next door.
The Kids Corner Behavior Services
has been there for a couple of years.
They have maintained a
business license here
with the city of Kissimmee
valid for quite some time.
So having the vocational
school right next door
will provide easier,
actually just combining
curriculum holistic
and a total comprehensive type of support
for these students.
As far as the site, again,
this is a conditional use
with site plan waiver,
meaning that there is no
additional site improvements
that need to be done.
There's adequate parking.
Landscaping has been up to date.
There's no open code
enforcement violations.
So there's no additional site improvements
that will be needed to
support the vocational school.
We did work with the school district
and with the applicant for quite some time
to make sure that we do have an ordinance
that was passed quite a bit
of 2013 to limit new public
and private schools along
the Vine Street Corridor.
At that time, there was proliferation
of new public and private
schools within shopping malls
within these different areas
that weren't originally
intended to have schools.
There were issues with
circulation or what have you.
So I attached that ordinance
that was approved back in 2013.
However, that ordinance
limited any new public
or private schools until such time
that there was enough of a population,
that population being 2,000 new units
within the Vine Street Corridor
that would create a demand
for new and public and private schools.
However, in working with
the school district,
we find that this is
such a specialized school
that the school district,
which their comments were
included in the backup,
would not have an impact
on the school district.
We felt with that
and also the specialized
vocational nature of that school,
that we could approve this
use subject to the conditions.
One being that it will
only occupy Suite 105,
the other one being that
the school cannot expand
within the building itself.
The other conditions to
transportation vans and buses.
We know that there's a problem
with circulation drop off, pickup,
the drop off and pickup where
the parents have to park
in a parking space.
And at this time, no
transportation, buses or vans
are allowed.
If for some reason in the
future there's demand for it,
we are requiring that a circulation
or plan be submitted
to the city for review
before any types of transportation,
buses or vans are implemented.
Again, because this is a plaza,
the intended use for offices,
we also felt like this was
gonna be a minimal impact
to the businesses that are
there being on the first floor.
And last but not least,
the change internally
will require what we call a change of use
with our building department.
So we wanted to make it clear
that if that change of use
building permit was not attained,
that this use would
not stay with the land,
that if that change of occupancy
and meeting the Florida
Building Code standards
cannot be met, then this
use would be null and void.
We do not want to have
it open in the future
for any other types of educational use.
If that is the case, that
individual will have to come back
with a new conditional use application
and we'll bring it back to
the planning advisory board.
So I feel with the conditions
and with the background
and with the current improvements,
we are recommending approval
subject to those conditions.
So I can address any
questions you may have.
And we also have representatives
from the (faintly speaking).
- Board members, any questions for Brenda?
The city?
If not...
Oh, sorry.
- I just have a real quick question.
Did you say dance in
the title of the school?
- KCBS Advance.
Advance. Advance.
Advance Academy.
- Still a good mission.
I just wasn't sure if I heard dance.
- Yes.
- If the applicant would
like to step to the mic
and send a few words to the board.
State your name and your business address
for the record, please.
(woman faintly speaking)
- Oh, the current one is in St. Cloud.
It is in 317 Commerce Sunset Drive.
It's in the shopping Plaza.
Saint Cloud.
- Is there anything you'd
like to say to the board?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
My name is (faintly speaking) Rodriguez.
I'm one of the directors
of the school, academy.
- This is just an opportunity
for you to address the board.
If there's anything like
that you'd like to add.
You're not obligated to,
I'm just giving the opportunity.
- As of now, no.
- Okay.
- Board, any questions?
I have a question.
What ages do you serve?
- Since fifth.
Five years old until fifth grade,
which is when they reached 10 years old.
- So five years old to fifth grade?
- Yes.
From kindergarten to fifth grade.
- Okay, so like elementary school?
- Exactly.
- Okay.
All right.
If the board doesn't have any questions,
would anyone like to
make a motion to approve?
- Motion to approve.
- Okay.
And do we have a second?
- I second.
- A second from Melissa.
Any discussion?
I will just say thank you
for this and what you do
and your mission because I
have a son who is autistic
and as I said earlier,
I serve on the board
of the Opportunity Center,
which works with adults
with developmental disabilities.
So I think the more
opportunities, no pun intended,
to help our citizens with
special needs families,
the better.
And thank you for that.
With that, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Wait a minute.
Did I ask for a motion?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
All in favor, please say, aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- And public hearings.
(woman faintly speaking)
Thank you.
New business public hearing condition.
No, that's not.
Okay. Discussion.
Discussion regarding
December 6th and the 20th?
- Yes.
We do understand it's the holiday,
so we want to be sure and try to confirm
whether or not we will have
a quorum for the December 6th
or the December 20th PAB.
I know I've received responses
but I wanted to be sure for December 6th,
'cause we need four board members
for the December 6th meeting.
- I would not-
- I think you already provided, yes.
You and Melissa already
provided your responses already.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
But I just need to make sure
that we will have a
quorum for December 6th.
I think you responded
that you'll be available.
- I'll be available.
- Okay.
- And I think I just said, yeah,
I'm available on the sixth.
- Okay.
- I am.
- So as of right now, we only
have three board members,
so we don't have a quorum.
So what we will do
is reach out to Mr. Spalding
and Sylvette too as well,
'cause right now, we don't
have a quorum for December 6th.
- And I'm sorry.
Oh, is there a business for the sixth?
(faintly speaking) minutes.
Is there anything else coming up?
- No, there's potentially an item
that we're trying to schedule.
Yeah, an item that we're
trying to schedule in December,
preferably December 6th for that item.
And then December 20th,
I know that's even closer to holidays.
I think you confirm Bob and Diana again.
So we just have every-
- I'm just double checking.
- Okay.
On the 20th.
- And I think I could
be here too on the 20th.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'm good.
So as of right now,
potentially we definitely have
a quorum on December 20th.
Okay.
All right.
And then last but not least,
I also provided to you
the schedule for 2024.
So this is available
online where it says PAB,
those are the planning
advisory board dates for 2024.
The way we have it set up for
our projects that come in,
they first start off with our committee,
that's that DRC on there.
Let me zoom in, Bob, you're squinting.
So wherever it says the PAB,
those are potential planning
advisory board dates.
So I just wanted to
provide them to you again
so we can plan ahead,
especially with the children
during spring break or so.
That way, we can plan ahead
and we can communicate with our applicants
whether or not we're gonna
be able to have a quorum.
- Am I reading this correctly?
The first scheduled
meeting is not until March.
Is that?
- No, the other meetings in
2024 are on the 2023 standby.
- Oh, gotcha, gotcha.
Okay.
- For what it's worth
that I'm not gonna be able
to make cycle three on
April. (faintly speaking)
- Cycle number three?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- This is based on application intake.
So the 2023 schedule
includes the first January
and February.
Cycle number 21 actually
includes the first January
and February PAV dates.
What I'll probably do
is also I'll send this
to you all too as well.
So the first one is (faintly speaking).
January 3rd.
Okay.
So cycle number three, we have Alex.
So again, just send us,
communicate with us,
just look it through
it with your schedule,
so that way, we can plan ahead.
- It is breathtaking
how fast the time goes.
- Yes.
Yes.
So what we'll do is...
So the 2024 that we have at the tailwind,
we'll include the early
January and February 2025
planning advisory board date.
We set this up based
on application intake.
So at the end of this, we'll...
- Did you say 2025?
(woman faintly speaking)
Did you misspeak?
Oh my gosh.
- So at the end of the 2024,
we'll include those January
and February 2025 planning
advisory board dates.
- Wow.
Wow.
- Yup.
(people chattering)
- Anything else?
- Just wondering are we...
Like right now, we're off
cycle with the city com.
- That's at least the first
and the third Wednesday.
So that follows. (faintly speaking)
The only thing is we were off this Monday,
'cause of how the calendar.
So normally, we're in sync.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
I think they switched it
for the budget hearings for something.
No?
(woman faintly speaking)
Yeah.
Normally, the same week.
That would be especially for me,
Tuesday, the city commission,
and then the next following
day is planning advisory board.
It usually happens during the same week,
but there was an offset for a while
that really confused
me and a lot of staff.
But normally, it's the same week.
All right.
So again, just notify us, let us know
so that way we can plan ahead.
That's all I have.
- All right.
Board members, anything
you wanna bring up?
If not,
I'm wishing everybody a
wonderful Thanksgiving next week.
And do we have a motion to adjourn.
- I make the motion to adjourn.
- Melissa, a motion to adjourn.
Do we have a second?
- I second.
- Second, I heard Diane.
Okay.
And any discussion about that?
If not, meeting...
All favor, please say, aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say, no.
Meeting adjourned, 6:17.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- So for the December 20th,
so we'll clear you'll bring
in the Christmas cookies, Rob?