- Testing, 1, 2, 3, testing.
- Hello.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America,
and to the republic for which it stands;
one nation, under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- Thank you, please be seated.
And I'm gonna ask
everybody to please silence
any electronic devices out of courtesy.
And we are looking at our minutes
from July 19th, 2023 PAB meeting.
Do we have any motions
regarding those minutes?
Robert, we have a motion to approve
and a second from Melissa.
Any discussion, amendments, changes?
All in favor, please say, "Aye."
Aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say, "No."
Hearing none, minutes are approved.
4A Old Business, public
care and conditional use
with site-specific redevelopment plan.
- Yes, thank you.
This is a conditional use
with site-specific redevelopment plan
to redevelop the property located
at 51 through 53 West Pine Street.
This is gonna be on the
northwest corner of Main Street.
- I'm sorry, Brenda, let
me just jump in there.
Short term memory, sorry.
I wanna ask if any board members have
any sort of conflict of interest,
had ex parte communication,
site visits, discussions,
research on their own regarding
any of these agenda items.
And this one here, as
we are addressing that,
please let that be known.
- I will for 5A and 5B,
but I do not for this.
- Okay. Brenda, go ahead.
Sorry.
- No, no worries.
So this is gonna be the
redevelopment of that site located
on the northwest, sorry,
yes, northwest corner
of Main Street and Vine.
This is gonna be a redevelopment
of a 538 hundred square
foot car wash facility.
Within your packet is a depiction
of the redevelopment of that site.
A bit of a background,
currently right now the property has
about a 3,000 square foot building,
a former 7-11, and also
a tenant space too,
located at 53 West Vine.
That was part of the approval
with the zoning being a mixed
use planned unit development.
This property, as well as
the property to the west,
are all part of the same zoning,
which is the Scottie's modification.
That was approved back in 1999.
Some of the recent changes
was with the widening
of Main Street.
It included, I believe, some improvements
to add the turn lane back in 2018.
That affected the existing improvements
on the 7-11.
So that plan, which is called a Cure Plan,
whenever we have
redevelopment that's affected
by any type of eminent domain,
or any type of roadway improvements.
So those modifications to
that site was submitted
and approved in 2018.
So fast forward today, that
PUD does allow for a car wash
via a conditional use approval
by the planning advisory board.
Within that car wash facility,
as known, includes a drive through,
which will consist of
the three lanes queuing
on the south side of the property
adjacent to Vine Street
and will move forward to the tunnel,
which will be oriented
towards Main Street itself.
It'll also include the vacuum
stations that you see there,
so that way customers,
after going into the tunnel,
will have had the
ability to use the vacuum
for interior cleaning.
With that in mind, we have
been working with the applicant
because this is part of
the city's initiative
and goal to redevelop
the Vine Street corridor.
As you all know,
in 2020 the city incorporated
the form-based standards,
form-based code, to actually
re-envision the Vine Street
to less of a auto-oriented,
but to include different design
and development standards
to make that corridor
more pedestrian friendly
and to encourage additional types of uses
to further redevelop both
the Vine Street corridor
and the downtown area.
So with that being said,
with the existing zoning
on the property being PUD,
we've worked with the applicant
to incorporate different design standards
that will, one, further the city's goals
for the form based standards,
form based standards
within the Vine Street
and the downtown area,
and to, again, further
redevelop this corridor
and this intersection in particular.
As mentioned in the staff report,
there will be some, what
we call, non-conformities
or existing improvements that will remain,
such as the south side
on the stormwater pond.
But for the most part,
as you can see here,
that the existing building
will be demolished
and redeveloped into the
layout that you see here today.
I do want you to point out
that within your packet
that you have hard copy,
I want to bring to your
attention that staff
with the publication of
this agenda included the,
was it seven?
Yes, sorry; eight conditions,
but working with the applicant,
there are changes that
you have for the car wash
that should be part of your packet
where there's a modification
to condition number one
and a modification to
condition number two.
All of the other conditions,
from condition three through eight,
will remain the same,
but we provided those
revisions to you via copy
to you to see the changes to
conditions number one and two.
So at this time,
staff is requesting that you
approve this application,
conditional use request
subject to the changes
to conditions one and two
that you have included
provided with your packet.
If there are any questions,
I am here, as well as
we have representation
regarding the project itself.
- And board, do you have any
questions for the city staff
before I call,
ask if the applicant is here
and would like to state anything?
Please state your name and
business address for the record.
- Matt Britton, 3708 West
Lawn Avenue, Tampa, Florida.
We agree with all the
conditions that were stated
and here and happy to
answer any questions.
Thank you.
- Board, any questions for the applicant?
If not, do we have any public comments?
Any members of the public
like to make comments
on this agenda item?
Any public comments?
No? Okay.
Any discussion by the board?
If not, we'll entertain any motion.
- I motion to approve.
- Heard Melissa motion to approve
and we have second from Robert.
Any discussion?
- With the conditions.
- With the condition.
Melissa, with the conditions,
I'm assuming the motion.
Okay, all right.
- I'm sorry, with the modified conditions,
number one, number two.
- Okay.
All in favor, please say, "Aye."
Aye, opposed, please say, "No."
Hearing none, motion carries.
Congratulations.
And five, New Business 5A: Public Hearing.
Again, I'll ask if any board members have
any conflicts of interest
with this agenda item,
had ex parte communications,
site visits, done any
of your own research,
please let that be known for the record.
- I have conflict of interest
and will be abstaining.
- Okay.
Yes, sir.
- Good evening.
Christian Arias, Development Services.
The applicant has filed
an annexation application
to annex approximately 556 acres of land
into the city, into the city of Kissimmee
for the project identified
as Taylor Aisle.
Before I proceed, if I
may, to add to the record,
there was a submitted
error on the public notice
regarding the legal description.
This has been corrected
and it has been presented
in front of you,
and this has been provided to you
to compliment that error that was made.
Continuing with the site, subject site,
the subject site's actually
located, as we can see,
east of Simpson Road and west
of Lake Toho.
So, we can see here, East
Toho Lake, I'm sorry.
As you can see in this map,
this is the subject site.
As part of this application,
staff and the applicant have had meetings
with the Osceola County
regarding this proposed annexation.
The proposed annexation meets
the requirements set forth
by the local and state statutes
for voluntary annexation
as the property are contiguous
for adjacent to city limits.
To the northern side, as you can see,
it's abutting the already
annexed property to the north.
The development review
committee has reviewed this
and recommended approval on
March 21st of this year, 2023.
The first staff is recommending approval
of this annexation application
and this concludes my
report and I'll have...
If you have any questions, please,
I would be more than happy
to answer any questions,
or forward any questions
to the city staff.
If not...
I'm sorry, Alex, I apologize.
There were also public
comments that were added,
as part of this application,
which will be distributed,
that has been distributed to you
and we have to identify and
also to respond to the...
Do you have those in
the package, the uptown?
- They have been included in the package,
as part of the package.
And it has been received
by the end of this day.
So that's why it wasn't added
to the original that you have,
but it's being added to
your packet as we speak.
Okay, Alex, you had a comment or question.
- Yeah, I guess I was just wondering,
looking at the planned annexation,
there's a little like abutment that,
as far as I can tell, is
part of like Borinquen Drive.
I was wondering what the
purpose of for the annexation.
Is that just the
right-of-way in the street,
or is that kind of the...
- You mean the little sliver to the-
- Yeah, the sliver.
- That's a right-of-way,
but it's actually platted.
It's part of the plat
part within the portion
of the property,
therefore it was included
in this annexation.
- It was part of the original plat.
- That is correct, yes.
- Thank you.
- Board, any other comments
or questions for the city?
I'm trying to find where the public...
I'm sorry, I thought.
I guess I misunderstood.
You're saying that-
(audience member speaking faintly)
- Okay, where can we see those comments?
- It's just one email
that we received today.
One email that it's in the back of...
- We're going to read it into the record.
- I'm sorry, say again.
- We're gonna read it into the record.
- Okay, so we're going to hear those-
- Yes, yes.
- Comments tonight, okay.
- I'm going to read this into the record.
And this is from Lisa Gonzalez in email.
"In regards to the meeting today,
the letter was placed in
our mailbox yesterday, 9/5,
and not gave us much time to plan.
I live in 237 Aurora Court.
What is an emergency egress?
Will our area be considered city
and no longer county
when this is complete?
If so, are we going to have city water?"
I conclude that.
(participant speaking faintly)
The answer to this email...
"Lisa, unfortunately we
do not have the ability
to control the delivery schedule
of the USPS regarding the notices.
Tonight's meeting is the,
it's not the final
approval of this project.
The first city commission
date has not been determined..
An emergency egress is
a roadway that is used
for emergency services only.
It is not open to the
general public to use.
The annexation to the city
will only include the areas
highlighted within the notice.
It will not include your property,
but will include the
adjacent 32 acre parcel
at the end of Aurora court.
The city does not provide water services.
Those services are provided
by to Toho Water Authority."
That's the end of the email.
- All right, thank you.
- Is that the only public comment or?
- That is correct.
- Okay, thank you.
Is the applicant here to approach
and state your name and business address
for the record, please.
- Good evening, Chair, commissioners.
Eric Raasch with Inspired Placemaking,
4767 New Broad Street,
Orlando, Florida 32814.
We are in agreement with
the staff's recommendation.
We wanna thank staff
who are working with us
on this project.
We've been working on
it for over a year now.
I do have a presentation, if
it would please the board.
Otherwise, we will be responsible
for answering any questions.
We want to reserve some time,
in case there are some
comments or questions
that we can ask at the end.
- Board, do you have any
comments or questions
for the applicant?
- If not-
- Yeah.
- Go ahead, sorry.
- I have one, I have one.
Is this a long term development or what?
- Excuse me.
- Is this a long term development?
- Absolutely.
- It is. Over a period of what?
- Oh Chris, Chris Pulti
probably has the best answer to that.
- Eight years.
- Over a period of eight years?
- Yes, sir.
Eight to 10.
- And the city plays what part in that?
- So the city is responsible for reviewing
and granting the
entitlements for this project
to move forward.
This is just the first step.
So this is the annexation and
future land use map amendment.
We also have to do what's called
a planned unit development
and that's where you're gonna have all
of the design standards.
You're gonna see, you know, the setbacks
and the general layout of the community,
all of our proposed
landscaping, rights of way,
all of those details are
typically provided a later date.
So this is the first step
where we're just bringing
the southern piece,
which is outlined in red, into the city,
and then assigning a city
land use designation,
which is required to have by state law.
- I have suggestions.
Since you have a-
- Hold on, Robert.
I'm sorry, Robert's Rules.
I'll go to the next person
and come back to you.
- Okay.
- Alex, go ahead.
- I mean, I concede my question.
I'll let Robert follow up
and then I'll wait my turn.
How about that?
- Okay.
- Since your development is
over an eight-year period,
what stages do you
intend to develop it in?
- So the plan now is to phase it
and we haven't worked
through all the details
on the phasing plan yet and
which phases will go first.
But I think it's safe to assume
that it'll come off
Simpson Road and then go
from the west to the east.
- So if you develop it by stages,
you're going to have it open and available
to the public per stages
then, is that correct?
- That's right.
And yeah, I'll just add
that each phase has to stand
on its own.
So all the infrastructure
within each phase has
to be there to support
whatever happens in that phase.
You can't just put a bunch
of units in one phase
and then not build the roads, or not build
the required wastewater infrastructure.
So each phase will stand alone.
- And what if you fall behind a stage?
- I mean, the infrastructure
has to be in place
to support the development
and I'm sure the city,
I'm not gonna speculate,
but I'm sure they would
not permit us to go beyond
what infrastructure would allow.
- And you intend to put
how many units in there?
- 3000 units.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
- Alex?
- So, I think he said
he has a presentation.
I guess I'd be somewhat
interested in seeing it.
So I guess I will move to...
Will it require me to
move to subset the rules
to see the presentation,
or can we just agree to
see the presentation, or...
- To, I'm not clear what...
- I guess I would like to
put it before the board
that we could decide collectively
to see the presentation
that the developer has.
- You can ask for that, sure.
- All right, could we
see the presentation?
- Sure.
- Alright.
- Does the board concur?
- Also just keep in mind that, before you,
what you're voting on is the annexation,
not any details of this project.
- Not the actual project in front of you.
- Just to be clear.
- It's informative
but this is not what you
should be considering per se.
Just does this meet the
standards for annexation?
- Understood.
This is a very limited
thing that we're doing.
It belongs to the county right now,
not the city, just to
clarify for everyone.
And what we're doing here is agreeing,
seeing if we want agree that
the city would annex that,
and that's it.
- And this is a voluntary annexation.
- Okay, so that's the scope of this,
is just, will it be
part of the city or not?
Not whether we like the project,
the roads, the lights, any
of that, just that piece.
So that is our responsibility
and our only authority
with regard to this.
Just wanna be clear.
Okay. That said.
All right, and thank you again
for the opportunity to
present this to you.
You know, we're all very proud of it
and a lot of work's gone into it, so.
And I know this is a pretty large project
and it's likely to garner
some public interest.
So we're really glad to
be able to explain it
a little bit more
before you vote on your annexation.
So, I'll run through the location.
I'll talk about the
vision for the property.
We'll talk about what we're
here to debate tonight,
which is the annexation
and the future land use map amendment.
We'll run through some
compatibility measures
for the project, and then
I'll wrap up with a summary.
So as staff mentioned, this
project east of Simpson Road.
It's on the northwest side of Lake Toho.
It's the east lake.
The total project is 883 acres in size.
And we're proposing to
annex 556 of those acres
in from Osceola County,
They're currently unincorporated.
The piece from the north
has already been annexed
into the city and is
within the jurisdiction
of the City of Kissimmee.
This is our conceptual vision plan,
and typically you don't see this
until much later in the process,
but you know,
we're running a lot of things
concurrent in this project.
So this is proposed to
be a mixed use community.
You would have 3000 dwelling units,
many of which would be single family,
which were located on the
east side of the site,
as you can see.
We're proposing 190,000 square
feet of non-residential,
and that would be in the
form of a mixed-use center,
which you'll see on the
frontage of Simpson Road.
So the commercial component
of it is really focused
on the frontage,
and then the residential
would be behind that.
We're proposing conservation
along the lakefront.
We know that the lake's
really a primary amenity
through this project,
and I'll talk a little bit about a rec
and open space plan in a moment,
but we're also really cognizant
of the residential
immediately to the west.
And so all those arrows that you see going
into the existing
residential neighborhood,
those are proposed to be
emergency access only,
and as staff's explained,
those would be stabilized, sodded, gated,
just to allow access for fire to get in
in case anything happens.
Our primary access is off Simpson Road.
You can see it to the north,
just south of phase two with
the mixed-use community.
So in terms of rec and trails,
we're really proposing
an interconnected system
of open space.
You can see the trail network will run
throughout the community
and provide that access
to the area that we're
preserving along the lake edge.
We've got a number of smaller
parks centrally located
within the community to allow for
what's called a mused product.
This is an example of
that on the bottom hand
of the screen there.
That's in Baldwin Park.
You can see the unit front
on the central open space,
which allows for a sense of community
and allows for folks to gather.
Those units are accessed
to an alley in the rear.
So we're proposing the preservation
of the East Lake Toho shoreline.
We've got a buffer from the
single family to the west,
and tree preservation's a big deal.
There are some really
beautiful old growth oak trees
on the site and we've
been fortunate enough
to appreciate and try to
match a plan around those.
So that's something that'll be forthcoming
on our future submittal.
In terms of access, this
is our road exhibit.
We've got, as mentioned,
the interconnected system
of streets, alleys and
private drive aisles.
We're proposing some emergency
access only to the west.
These are just a couple renderings
of what would happen
in the mixed use area.
You can see that there's a
number of different uses here.
You've got a central green
space around the tree
that's proposed to be preserved.
You've got some multi family
on one side of the road
and then you've got
walkable pedestrian urbanism
on the other.
So really trying to create a destination,
not just for the folks who
live within this community
but for the folks in Kissimmee as a whole.
This is just another perspective
of how the mixed use area would look.
This is looking towards
East Lake Toho from Simpson,
and you can see the proposed multi-family
in the back with the mixed
use area on the frontage.
So what we're here to
talk about tonight is
just the annexation and the
future land use map amendment.
This is the annexed area.
It's a pretty straightforward request,
556 acres going from Osceola County
to the City to Kissimmee.
And then we're also requesting
a future land use map amendment,
and that's a required map by the state.
You have to have a future
land use map designation.
Currently got a number
of different designations
and a lot of acronyms here.
But suffice it to say, the
portion in Osceola County,
you can see here on this chart,
has a low density residential
future land use designation.
And Osceola's density for that is
up to eight dwelling units per acre.
So if we multiply out what
we could do in Kissimmee,
what we can do under that
designation in Osceola,
we could potentially get it
almost 5,500 dwelling units
on the site under the
existing future land use.
Don't want to do that,
want to be fully within
the City of Kissimmee.
So that actually results in a decrease
of 2,493 dwelling units
for what would otherwise be allowed
if we went through the county.
We're also adding 190,000 square feet
of non-residential to support
those residential uses.
In terms of compatibility,
we're trying to be respectful
of the residential area
immediately to the west.
We oriented the non-residential
towards Simpson.
We're proposing the preservation
of those waterfronts
and wetlands,
and we're not proposing any direct access
other than emergency to the
residential that's existing.
So in summary,
we're really proposing a signature,
mixed-use destination
project for the city.
A lot has gone into the
vision and master planning.
You know, it's got three or
four different design firms
who've been working on this.
We're only considering the annexation
and future land use map at this time.
The PUD will come later,
and we feel it's compatible
with the surrounding area and
consistent with the comp plan.
So that's gonna conclude
my formal presentation
and our whole team's here for questions.
Thank you.
- Okay, board, any
questions based on this?
If not, we'll open up to any comments
from the public.
Would anyone from the public
please step to the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
We'll get to one at at time.
Please, I'm sorry, sir.
Sir, I saw the...
Oh, okay, I just saw your hand up first.
So wanna go in order.
That's totally fine.
I just saw her hand up first, so.
Go right ahead.
State your name and address
for the record, please.
You'll have three minutes.
- My name is Tony Samota and I live
at 1730 Lee Janzen Drive in Kissimmee.
It was a great presentation
but I also live just south.
I appreciated the applicant's
desire to make sure
that the residents on the
west side were taken care of.
But those of us to the south that live
in Kissimmee Bay also has some concerns
because after Hurricane Ian,
our neighborhood flooded
and we have flood water in
our neighborhood for days.
And so there is Oxbow
Pond which is just south
of this site,
and I'm concerned as
to go on the record of,
in terms of runoff and still
in terms of our neighborhood,
because we definitely
have had to deal lately
with water and flooding in our area.
So, I know this meeting isn't
about the final part of it,
but I just wanted to be
on the record to say,
those of us to the
south are very concerned
that this development
would add to the problems
with flooding in our neighborhood.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Next up, please step to the microphone.
State your name and
address for the record.
You'll have three minutes.
- Hi, so I'm Lisa Gonzalez.
I was the one that sent the email,
so thank you for responding.
So I'm actually on the west side,
so really on the bottom part.
- I'm sorry, did you state your address?
- 2372 Aurora Court.
- Thanks.
- So I'm right there, right
on the corner, left side.
So the question about
the emergency egress,
that was already answered, so that's good.
So really what I'm
concerned about right now,
not only the flooding as well,
like the gentleman over here just said,
but also if we're county in the middle
and then this site becomes city,
does that affect us in any way?
I'm not sure if this is
the right forum or not.
- Just to explain,
this is your time to make
your comments, whatever,
and then we'll discuss.
If we have questions
based on your comments,
we can address the city
but this is your time to-
- Yeah, that's really
my concern right now,
besides the emergency
exits and things like that.
- Okay, thank you.
Do we have other public comments.
Yes, sir, just step to
the microphone please.
State your name and your address.
You'll have three minutes.
I don't, I don't know.
(participant faintly speaking)
- Makes it kind of difficult.
Looks small, doesn't it?
Nice presentation, though, by the way.
It looks kind of small,
but it's a huge area,
an area that I've lived in for a long time
and I can't direct anything.
- What's your address, sir?
Your name and your address.
- My name is Thomas Vossick.
I live in 2620 Cahokia Court,
which is again, I could
point out in the region,
but you see where the
Hilliard Isle Road is,
that's what I'll be referring to
when I use up my three
minutes here in a moment.
If she can.
If she can't, I'll go ahead.
But thank you for letting
speak this evening.
You know where the Hilliard
Isle project is being located.
Some of you have lived
here for a long time,
maybe most of your lives, like myself,
and as you discuss this
develop in this rural area,
please consider these facts.
Hilliard Isle is a short,
barely two lane, country road.
It is a county road,
but it's our only access to Simpson Road
and out of our neighborhoods.
So these homes directly to the west are
what I'm referring to.
Looks like they've almost got it here.
It's already dangerously congested
and it's not signalized at Hilliard Isle
when we exit out onto Simpson Road,
which was previously Bobby Creek.
The city council previously approved
a multi-family development
in 2023 on Hilliard Isle.
I don't know if you're aware of that,
or if you're keeping that in mind
when you consider this development,
which will add an additional
300 cars on the road
and it's not yet started construction.
Where is that located?
In that area just above the word Hilliard.
That's where that development is going in.
It's not yet started construction.
Today's proposed development
would force thousands
of extra vehicles onto Hilliard Isle,
this narrow country road.
This area has gone through the county
and through the city multiple times
and we've been told different things
through those different evolutions.
But these people that
are living miles down
in the subject site are
not going to drive three
or four miles up
through the other proposed development
that's north of it to
go out to Simpson Road.
We've always been told,
and this is the first time that I've heard
and I've lived in my home
there for almost 27 years,
this is the first time we've been told,
"Hilliard Isle won't be used."
Can't get it to get up there?
Hilliard Isle is the only road
that goes all the way into that section.
There are no other roads
that go into that area.
It starts on Simpson and
goes straight through
and it dead ends right there.
Anything that's constructed,
all of the construction vehicles,
anything that's happening,
will be going up and down
our little country road,
and if you've live here, you
know what I'm referring to.
They assured,
the city council assured our
community in February of 2023,
that the Simpson Road
construction improvements
would be completed by August of 2024.
As you know in that
area, they're not begun.
Those improvements have
not only been not begun,
but they're nowhere near our area.
They're struggling with that
north end of Bobby Creek.
The infrastructure was not
in place then, nor is it now.
Road construction is already years
behind construction schedule.
Massive funding shortages
are just one of those issues
for those delays.
This isn't a race, it's not about,
it's not about the need for low, middle,
or high income housing at this moment.
This is about repeatedly rushing ahead
without considering the
long-term consequences
on the existing area.
We have to do better than that.
I'm aware of the state,
that the state law
suggests that if funding
for an infrastructure
improvement has been approved,
those improvements are to
be considered completed
before they've even been begun.
I was shocked to hear that at
the last city council meeting,
by the city council and the developer.
We all know this benefits
only the contractors
and the construction companies,
and speaks more to land
abuse than good use.
Please encourage the
council to put the brakes
on this huge development,
at least until the
infrastructure is in place
to ensure everyone's safety.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Do we have other public comments?
Anyone else from the public
like to make comment?
Any other public comments?
If not, board, do you have any questions?
- No.
- Comments to staff?
Yes ma'am.
- If we could just-
- Could you state your name
and address for the record?
Who are you?
- Yes, Cecelia Dorn, 17 South Orlando,
Kissimmee, Florida 34741.
I'm here with the developer.
If we could answer or respond
to some of the comments
that were made, we would appreciate that.
- Yeah, we'll allow that.
Go ahead.
- Great, thank you.
- Let's hear everything.
- Just to address the initial
concerns about annexation for
other properties, it should have no impact
on your home unless you want it to.
- Ma'am, please address your
comments to the board here.
- Okay.
It should have no impact on the homes
of the other individuals
that live in that area,
unless they file their
own voluntary annexation
or the city of Kissimmee decides
to file an involuntary annexation.
So, it would not have any
impact on the surrounding homes.
To address the concerns
about infrastructure
not being in place.
The soonest that construction
would potentially begin
on this site would be midyear next year.
Again, there are a lot of approvals
that would need to happen
before any construction
could begin on this site.
And even then, there would
be an another 18-month lag
before anyone lived in this development.
Simpson Road improvements would
be complete at that point.
Any improvements to the
infrastructure would be required
to be complete before the
development is finished
and anyone could move
in within that phase.
Also, the issue with the Hilliard Isle,
as was stated, there's
no plans for traffic
to be able to go on that road
There it would be emergency access only
No one from the site would
be able to use that road.
It would be gated and blocked,
and even the folks who would
be further to the south
of the project, would have no choice
but to go up and use Simpson Road
and use the exit out onto
Simpson Road to the north.
So I understand the concerns
of more traffic on Hilliard Isle,
but that's not what is being asked for.
It's not what would be presented later
in the subsequent approval.
Again, as was stated earlier,
I just want to reiterate
that this request is merely
on bringing this site into the city.
It has nothing to do
with the actual approvals
of what will ultimately be built there.
It's merely trying to
make this site subject
to city oversight, as
opposed to county oversight.
- Thank you.
Board, any motions
regarding this agenda item?
- Yeah, we're still talking
about annexing 500-some acres?
- That's the sole scope
of what we're dealing with right now.
- Okay, according to 5A...
Hmm?
I'll make a motion-
- Oh sorry, could I ask a question first?
- Sure, go ahead.
- Yeah, well what we could do though is,
if we have a motion on the floor
and then we get a second,
we would have discussion
prior to the vote anyway.
- Let's go to discussion.
- But if you wanna hold off on the motion.
- I'll hold off on the motion.
- Okay, Alex, go ahead.
- Yeah, so I appreciate the context,
both from developers and the locals.
Now if we restrict attention
to the actual annexation,
I still have a question,
I guess, for the city.
This parcel, it is a large parcel
and my understanding is part
of it is sort of floodplain
and stuff.
Are there any immediate recurring
maintenance obligations,
financial obligations
that the annexation alone
of the property in its
current state would induce?
- That, correct me if I'm wrong,
that's later in the development process.
- So the only criteria with state,
which is the same locally here,
the only criteria that we look at
for voluntary annexation is
whether or not it is
contiguous or adjacent
to another property in the city.
That is from Florida statutes.
I believe in the staff
report that's gonna be,
don't quote me on this,
but I think it's the Florida
statute 177, I think.
Well, 177,
then also with the city
that the only criteria,
again this is annexation,
this is not anything to put conditions
on how the properties get developed.
It is only whether or not
it's contiguous to the city.
It's pretty much,
the applicant is requesting permission
to enter the city of
Kissimmee from Osceola County.
Yeah, so with regards to your questions,
there's no fiscal types of analysis.
What we do, actually, for fiscal analysis
for the application is
compared to on the taxes
and the property values,
and folks during a voluntary annexation,
they weigh that, as far
as what the benefits
that they may have in entering the city
that they don't have different services,
those types of things.
So from a a financial standpoint,
that's done privately as
far as weighing the benefits
of the services that they have now versus
what they would have in city.
But for the staff and the analysis,
there's not any fiscal
or any type of financial.
It's just whether or not it's contiguous
to property in the city.
- But I guess currently,
even though it's largely undeveloped,
are there any properties, any parcels,
that are developed on the
property currently at all, or?
- I don't think so.
I don't know if there's any structures
or anything like that.
It's probably all agricultural.
I mean, the portion that's
in the city right now has
an agricultural conservation zoning
because the subject site
that's under view now
is currently within the county.
I believe you see here
even on the aerials,
that there may be some
of the property here
that may have existing
single family homes on it,
and I think on here further east
there might be another structure,
but that's pretty much it.
But for us,
there's not any type of
laying on the financial.
It is only when or not this
property is contiguous.
- But I guess because it's
a voluntary annexation,
the developer currently owns
all of these parcels under consideration.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Okay. Board, anything else?
- No? Me, my turn?
- If you like.
- I make a motion to approve 5A,
to annex 553,
556 acres 0.33 tenths.
I make a motion to approve.
- Okay, we have a motion
on the floor from Robert.
Do we have a second?
- I'll second.
Second.
- Second from Alex.
Any further discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say, "Aye."
Aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say, "No."
Okay, hearing none, motion carries.
5B.
- Thank you again, Christian
Arias, Development services.
Good evening.
This is the land use application
that's attached to the
annexation previously discussed.
Again, the applicant has filed
a land use plan amendment application
as part of the Hilliard Isles project.
Also, if I may take this time
to proceed with the record.
Same for this as the previous application,
there was a submitted error
to the public notice regarding
the legal description
which has been corrected and is included
in your staff report.
Again, we're tasked here in front of us.
We previously had the annexation.
This is just a footprint
which is required by
state statutes as well.
This is actually the footprint
which is the first layer,
which is the land use designation,
which are actually governed
and seen by our comprehensive plan.
We have in the city of comprehensive plan
with both objectives and policies.
So this is part of what's
being proposed at this point.
For the record,
the subject property is located
within east of Simpson Road
and west of the East Lake Toho.
A portion of the subject
property was annexed
into the city of Kissimmee in 2002,
and the other portion was annexed in 2006,
the northern portion
or northern parts were previously annexed.
Both of these properties
have a land use designation
currently with single family,
low density residential
and multi-family medium
density residential.
Subject property, once annexed,
will consist of a total
area of 883 acres of land.
And the proposal is to designate
the following land use designation
for the future development
of the subject site,
which will consist of single family,
low density residential,
multi-family, medium density residential,
commercial general,
and conservation areas.
We can see in this map, actually,
it's laid out how this
will work and function.
As you can see,
the applicant's designating
over 178 acres of land
for conservation to work for
the open space requirements
and to have any mitigation
within the East Lake Toho waterway.
And the commercial is mostly concentrated,
it's gonna be concentrated
towards Simpson Road.
The Development Review
Committee has reviewed
and recommended approval
on March 21st, 2023,
for this application
and the proposed land use
designation meets all the goals,
policies and objectives of
the city comprehensive plan.
Therefore staff is recommending approval
on this application,
and this concludes my report
and I'll be happy to answer any questions.
- Board, any questions for the city staff?
If not, would the applicant like
to add anything additional regarding this?
- Thank you again.
Eric Ross, Inspired
Placemaking Collective,
4767 New Broad Street,
Orlando, Florida 32814.
Just wanna say that we agree
with the staff recommendation.
We're here to answer any questions.
We'd appreciate the ability
to respond to any comments.
Thank you.
- Okay, board any questions
for the applicant?
If not, we'll take any public
comments regarding this.
Any comments from the public?
Any public comments?
No? Okay.
Do we have any motions
regarding this 5B agenda item?
- I'll make a motion to approve it.
- Motion to approve from Robert.
- Yeah.
- Do we have a second?
- I second.
- We have a second from Diana.
Any discussion?
Discussion? No?
All in favor, please say, "Aye."
- Aye.
Opposed, please say, "No."
Hearing none, motion carries.
Thank you, and lemme
go back with the record
and make sure that we
understand for the record,
Melissa, did you vote or not vote?
- I did not.
I abstained from 5B.
- Okay, again,
I will say that I should
have stated upfront that,
do we have any conflicts of interest here?
But to be clear, you did not vote.
You abstained.
Okay.
So we have the vote as the
remainder of the board.
Okay, and it was approved.
Okay, thank you.
Six, public hearings, we don't
have anything under that.
Discussion. Any discussion?
Board members.
Dear chairman and board members,
anybody have anything?
Do we have a next meeting scheduled?
- I do not, (chuckles)
but again, just look out for your emails.
Again, we try to provide you these agendas
by Friday so we know, we understand
that you're busy, just like ourselves,
so that way at least you have the weekend
to review that.
Anytime, even before these meetings,
that you have any questions or concerns,
you can provide those to us.
Please don't press "Reply to all,"
but you can also reach out
to us before the meetings
if you have any general comments,
clarification that you may have
regarding any agenda items, too, as well.
And we'll be sure to,
once we look at the different
projects that we have,
we will send out a cancellation
if there aren't any agenda
items for the next meeting.
If not, we will make sure
that we get those out to you
in a timely manner.
- Okay.
Anything else? Anyone else?
Motion to adjourn?
- I'll make a motion.
- Motion to adjourn, Melissa,
and Robert, second.
Any discussion on that?
If not, all in favor, please say, "Aye."
- Aye.
Meeting adjourned at 6:49. Thank you.
(participants chatting)
(participants chatting continues)