- Okay, it's 6:12 PM November
6th, Planning Advisory Board.
Can you hear me?
Sorry.
(speaker laughing)
So it's 6:12 PM November 6th,
Planning Advisory Board Workshop.
We're gonna go ahead and please
silence all mobile devices,
electronic devices.
I'm trying to remember, memory.
So is it the movement of silence
and pledge allegiance at this point?
Let's go ahead and rise
for the moment of silence
and pledge allegiance.
Okay.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God,
indivisible with liberty
and justice for all.
Okay, before I go into the
presentation and slide,
I wanna take the opportunity
to introduce the staff to the board.
The staff is gonna be
the development services
director and department,
and what I have here is I have
a brief experience education
from the staff members here
that I want to read out.
And then we have staff here that's present
that's gonna go through that.
But before we do that, I'm gonna go ahead
and have Kalanit start
just a brief description of experience
what have you, so that way the staff,
the planning advisor board is aware
of the different experience
and expertise that staff has.
- Hi.
So most of you know me but
I'm pleased to meet you.
My name is Kalanit Oded
and I've been with the city
for almost five years now.
I've been working in local government
for almost 15 years.
I went to Records University
and then went to Tulane Law School.
I also have been LLM in land
use and environmental law
and almost have a master's
in urban and regional planning.
And it's really great to
work in local government.
It's a privilege and an honor
and I am happy to work with these guys
'cause they're the best.
- Thank you, appreciate it.
And I also wanna take this moment in time
to introduce our new Planning
Advisory Board member
Yolanda Bernard.
Yolanda, amazingly thank you.
Was appointed last night,
at last night's city commission meeting
and we reached out to her
just from a matter of timing to invite her
to this Planning Advisory Board workshop.
So, to be appointed, you know, yesterday
and to be on this workshop.
It's fitting, so welcome to
the Planning Advisory Board.
Okay.
So really briefly,
this is Craig Holland
is the Development Services
Department Director.
So briefly here, for the city of Kissimmee
for the past 18 years, he's director.
He's worked for the city as a whole
for 25 years in the capacity
as the planning manager,
assistant director, and CRA director.
Prior to working for Kissimee,
Craig worked in Kansas City,
Philadelphia and Arizona.
He has a Degree in Psychology
from Columbia College
and a Master's Degree in Urban Planning
from the University of Kansas.
Craig joined the American Institute
of Certified Planners in 1996.
He's lived in the Kissimmee
lakefront neighborhood
for the past 18 years
with Tasheeba Inuhanzo.
He enjoys traveling,
exploring the Florida
Donut Trail on weekends.
Google it, it's over on the Gulf Coast
and quote, then you can add
to the list as you please.
And Craig is looking forward to retirement
within the next five years, end quote.
Douglas Etheredge, he's
our assistant director
with development services
for the City of Kissimmee.
He's been with the city for
over 28 years in the capacity,
I'm sorry,
assistant director overseeing
the planning code enforcement building,
fire prevention and housing divisions.
He's been with the city for over 28 years,
going through the ranks of
planner to senior planner
to planning manager.
During those years,
he was responsible for
all development review,
which included coordination
development review committee
oversaw the current
development review process
and permitting, as well as
related boards and activities.
He's a native Floridian from Ocala
where he also worked at the city of Ocala
and the Withlacoochee
Regional Planning Council
after graduating from the
University of Florida in 1995
with the bachelor's degree in Geography
with an emphasis in planning.
I'm Brenda Ryan.
I'm currently the planning manager
for the City of Kissimmee.
I have over 24 years or year 24,
both with city and county urban planning
and regulatory environmental experience.
Year five with the city of Kissimmee.
Of those 24 years, the
first seven in the capacity
of a field inspector
completing wetland assessments,
listed species, hazardous
materials, shoreline alterations,
broke dock reviews and landscaping
and recreational inspections.
From a field inspector,
the rest of my experience
is in urban planning.
It has certain capacity from
planner one, senior planner,
interim community development director,
responsible for a small planning building
and code enforcement city program.
I've also previously
served in the capacity
of a board manager similar to this year
with another municipality.
In addition to prior
experience facilitating
a development review
committee for a previous city.
I've also been appointed
by the Municipal Governing
Board to represent
the city on the Lake Sumpter
Metropolitan Planning Organization or MPO,
sitting on their technical
advisory committee.
I've also given back to my
profession by volunteering
and representing planning professionals
in the Lake and Osceola County,
while serving on the American
Planning Association,
Orlando Metro Section Executive Committee,
I joined the American Institute
of Certified Planners in 2013.
Have a bachelor's degree
in Environmental Science and Policy
from the University of South Florida
Master's Degree in Public Administration
with a concentrate in
Environmental Planning
from Florida Gulf Coast University,
and also have a graduate study certificate
in urban and regional planning
from the University of Central Florida.
John Raven who can't be with us tonight
is our new senior planner.
He's been with us for the
past about five months.
He comes to us from
Durham, North Carolina,
where he's a planner from
the Durham City County
Planning Department for
five years, reviewing plans,
plats and permits, as well as assisting
in customer service and administration.
John holds a Bachelor's of Arts degree
from the University of South Carolina
along with a Master's
of Public Administration
from North Carolina State University
and a law degree from
Campbell University's
Norman Adrian Wiggins School of Law.
John began his career in local government
with the town of Springdale,
South Carolina, where he served
as a project manager and
town clerk for five years.
He also served as a planner
with the city of Case,
South Carolina, where he oversaw
the city's rental property
registration program,
hospitality tax management,
and other planning responsibilities.
April Fisher is our planner.
She's a part-time planner,
but she has over 20 years
of urban planning experience
including the role
of the assistant county
manager, parks rec director,
planning director and planning manager.
April was also an adjunct instructor
at the University of Central Florida
School of Public Administration
teaching Urban Planning,
GIS and Government Issue courses.
She's also a small business
owner with her own land use
and planning consulting company,
and she's also a certified planner
by the American Institute
of Certified Planning.
She holds a bachelor's degree
in Environmental Studies
with the Natural Resource Concentration
from the University of
North Carolina Asheville
and a Master's degree in
Urban Regional Planning
with a concentration in GIS from Clemson.
And I'll turn over to Christian and Ryan.
- Good evening.
My name is Christian Arias.
I am a senior planner currently
holding a senior planner
title with the supervisory role
here at the city of Kissimmee.
Have been here for two years on and off
and I say on and off
because I took six months
in the private world,
the land planning manager
for a major home builder,
but came back to the city
because government is my calling.
I like the government work that we do
and I have more experience,
I feel more comfortable
and it's really, to be honest with you,
my passion to be within the,
what I do and what we do every day,
and the team that we have.
I hold 15 years of urban
planning experience
with three years in the public
sector as a project manager
and the rest of 12 years
in intergovernmental and urban planning.
I started my career in city
of Lakewood, California.
From there I moved to project management,
then moved back
to the city of St.
Petersburg as a city planner.
Got a great opportunity
for the city of Mexico
in a large telecom industry
for a project manager.
Two years there.
Came back as a senior planner after that
and then incorporated
myself with Kissimmee
as a senior planner as well.
My education consists of a master's degree
from Universidad Autónoma del
Estado de Morelos in Mexico.
This with an emphasis
in territorial studies.
I also hold a bachelor's degree
in Urban Original Planning
from Cal Poly Pomona,
California State Polytechnic,
University of Pomona.
And my experience is normally dealing
with large scale projects,
annexations, land use amendments,
everything that you guys see
and we bring the applications before you,
but mostly the large scale,
more complex projects,
project management as well,
problem solving with our citizens.
So that's my range of
experience and expertise.
Interpretation of Land Development Code,
comprehensive plans, state
statutes, land development,
the land use, that's
where my strong points
and customer service,
since I've been working
since I was I think 16 years
old in customer service.
So I feel really comfortable
being there for our public
and our community and serve
them in any way possible we can.
So that's my experience.
Thank you.
- Hello all, I'm Ryan Altizer.
I'm planner two here at
the city of Kissimmee.
I got my bachelor's in
Environmental Studies
from Florida Gulf Coast
University with a minor
in history, theater and
interdisciplinary studies.
After that I moved to Chicago to do improv
for about 10 years.
I was a regional manager
for a smoothie company.
I have a diploma from Second City
for their musical conservatory.
And then I got my master's
at the University of Illinois in Chicago
in a Master's of Urban Planning and Policy
with a concentration in
Environmental Policy.
And from there I spent a year working
with a private landscape architect firm.
Then was a planner with
the city of Fort Pierce
where I moved up to senior planner.
I was there for about two and a half years
and then I came to Kissimmee.
So that's my experience in my education.
- Now I wanted for her to
describe her own experience,
but she's not gonna get away.
Ms. Kayla Smith here is
our recording secretary.
She is a small business
owner with experience
assisting other business owners navigate
through the local government process.
She has a bachelor's degree
from Florida Gulf Coast
University in Criminal Justice
and with a minor in psychology.
So the reason why I wanna do this again,
to introduce the staff,
with the level of not only experience
but also expertise that you have here.
I don't work in the bubble
in no way, shape or form,
but this is the staff that
you have here supporting you.
- Should we introduce
ourselves and our background?
- I guess we're gonna move left to right.
I just want to say thank you
guys for all your service.
I don't think you guys
have enough experience.
Maybe we need a little bit
more, I'm just playing.
I'm just playing.
Just playing.
That's a lot of experience
behind you guys.
So that's kudos to you guys.
My name is Aaron Sabino,
I went to the Ohio State University.
I dual majored in Computer Engineering
and in Financial Economics.
I started out working
for an avionics company
helping design their avionics.
They end up putting me
in their procurement
in contracts office.
Started doing contract management
with research and development
for different things for the government.
Then the government decided
to hire me directly.
I worked for the Department
of Defense for eight years
doing research and development contracts.
Brought me from DC to Orlando.
This is how I get here.
I was working at a research park.
I have been here supporting
soldier lethality
for about four years now,
and I have just went private.
while I'm going private,
I got a little bit bored.
I don't have nearly the
workload that I used to have.
So I got accepted into George Washington
and I'm currently in law school.
So that's where I'm at, doing it online.
- You're in law school?
- I am getting ready, preparing myself
so they accepted all of them.
Pardon?
- Good luck.
- I know I'm already
regretting it a little
bit, but I'm knees deep.
They've already accepted
a lot of my credits.
I'm level three certified in contracts,
so they accepted a lot
of my credits for that.
So I've been living in Kissimmee
as a resident for now four years.
I moved here from Lake Nona, I
didn't really like Lake Nona.
I felt like it was a one dimensional city.
It didn't have all of the
desirables that I was looking for.
The desirables I was looking for was,
I didn't want to be strictly car dependent
to get around to other cities.
For instance, I like the fact
that we have the train here.
It allows me to go indulge
into different activities
into Winter Park and downtown.
Also, I liked the fact
that when I requested the
comprehensive city plans
and seeing how they were
looking to make this a real city
in cohesiveness with the county's project
for Neo City, was my biggest attraction.
Ever since then I've been
trying to get involved
with the city to see how the progress,
we are coming to making this a more
less of a car-centric
city, and more of a bicycle
and walkable city, across
all the neighborhoods
to connect them and obviously
increase making this a
more attractive place
for tech companies.
Right now, they don't have
a lot of the economics here
to support that right now,
but hopefully it could
become more attractive
in that capacity.
So that tells you a
little bit about who I am
and it tells you a
reason why I decide to be
a part of the board and
a part of the initiatives
here in the city of Kissimmee.
I yield back.
- All right, my name is Bob Spalding.
Lived in Kissimee for 14 years,
proud to be part of a number one city.
I wanna thank the board
for the work they have
done and what they do.
They don't get enough
gratification for that,
but proud to be a board member.
And I'm just a plain old 80-year-old man
giving back to the city.
Very simple.
To you.
- Okay.
Hi everyone, my name is Yolanda Bernard.
I'm from Mexico.
I am very excited to be here with us.
So it's very important for
me here today community.
I am business owner, I have my nonprofit,
I love help to the community.
I think it's really important
that help to grow this city
because it's a problem?
Oh thank you, sorry.
It's very important that I think so
help to the community to grow.
because Kissimme have
great opportunity to grow
and be different.
I have my business in downtown Kissimee,
it's really important for me.
In fact all the cities,
all the countries come
to meet Kissimme.
It's very important work together
and be possible this opportunity.
Thank you.
I want to help.
Thank you so much.
- And hi, I'm Alex Lemming.
So I actually went to high
school in central Florida
in sort of East Orlando area.
Then kind of went off and did school,
did bachelor's in Physics
at California Institute of Technology
and then a master's and a PhD
in Theoretical Condensed
Matter Physics at Cornell.
Since then, I switched fields
to do machine learning and AI stuff.
I'm a senior research scientist
currently with Google DeepMind.
But I serve on the board
because I believe in civic engagement.
I think I wish we had more of it.
I similar to Aaron,
when we were looking for
a new house in the area,
me and my family, I looked
at various municipalities,
comprehensive plans
and I really liked what
I saw in Kissimme's.
I think it gives a really great vision
for how the city can grow.
I really like the level of
engagement I find in the city.
I went through the Kissimme
School of Government
and I think programs
like that are fantastic.
And yeah, so I'm also
here, I really wanna help.
I wanna help push the city
in the direction I think it,
you know, is already
sort of promised ahead
and make it an even better place
and hope to make the board
a more effective body
at trying to make the city better.
Thank you.
- Okay, so one of the things
that I wanna start off on
is a lot of times we'll have agenda items,
but it's on the same project.
Like we'll have three
separate agenda items, right?
And it'll be on the exact same project.
You're probably wondering
why do we have three separate agenda items
on the same piece of property?
So there are different
aspects to the property.
There's different statutoric requirements
and different processes
that we have to go through.
There's different changes that
are happening on the property
that we have to separate it out.
We can't make one motion on
all the different changes.
So this is the opportunity
to break down the reason why
we have to have separate
items on an annexation,
separate item on the land use as a nation,
separate for zoning and
for conditional use.
I'd like to use this here
because on the bottom
we'll start off with,
and how I have it separated
out is to go through
each of the different
types of applications
that are presented to you as a board.
So it'll be annexations,
future land use, land use amendments.
Those are changes to the comp plan,
whether it be a map or tax.
We've got zoning and we
got conditional uses.
So the first one we're gonna start off is,
is a voluntary annexation.
So because we're a municipality,
that means it's typically
the annexation request
that we get, are gonna be a property owner
wishing they have initiated an application
to voluntarily join the
city of Kissimmee from,
and you hear unincorporated,
that means Osceola County.
So their property is
an unincorporated area
that's not within city limits
and they're requesting
now for their property
to be included into city limits.
So this goes into specifically
the Florida statutes 171.044
from the statutory requirement.
I've got a Land Development
Code cross section
that talks about the process.
Annexations as a whole,
it's probably the simplest
type of criteria that there is.
It has to be, the property
has to be contiguous,
like it says here, has to be
contiguous to city limits.
That's really the criteria that's there.
It has to be in some way on some side
or some boundary of that property
has to be contiguous to a property
that's already is in city limits.
So by way of criteria is the simplest
that the process is one of
the most complex processes
by way of public hearing.
It requires two separate
city commission meetings
after it's presented to you
at Planning Advisory Board.
But that's the essentially
what a voluntary annexation.
It's few and far between
that we have what we call an involuntary.
It's usually, typically
not something that we,
it's a forced annexation
and it requires a referendum
and what have you.
So most of the applications that you have
are gonna be voluntary.
A property owner wishing and requesting
and submitting an application.
The other one that we've had recently
is also if the city and the county
enters into an interlocal agreement,
because we had a mass annexation
via an interlocal agreement
with the county that annexed
256 properties back in 2019.
So there's other mechanisms,
it's a bit rare to have that.
But we have intergovernment coordination
where you can do annexations
via interlocal agreement.
There's involuntary, which we typically,
again, it's mostly gonna
be voluntary annexations
that you see Planning
Advisory Board agenda items.
The next one is gonna be
future land use changes.
This is going to be, so
the comprehensive plan,
I think the most of you are familiar
with the comprehensive plan.
I'll go into another slides a bit more.
But the applications that you're gonna see
are land use amendments.
There's two different types.
It's gonna be a map amendment,
meaning that that property is changing
the future land use
designation on their property,
which is the most common type
that you're gonna see before this board
is gonna be a map amendment.
So it's changing the colors
or the future land use
designation on the map.
The other types that's few and far between
is gonna be a text amendment.
That means changing the text
of a particular policy
in a different element.
We call the chapters an element.
Future land use element
is gonna be the one again
that you're primarily gonna be looking at.
But we have different elements
from different chapters.
A text is making a change to
a goal objective or policy.
Again, few and far between,
but it's gonna be, majority
of it's gonna be mapped.
Florida statutes, again,
will receive a copy of it.
If you wanna go into more detail
that 1633.3184 hasn't changed,
thank goodness for decades now.
But it just goes into the process
of what happens behind the scenes
after the application goes
before city commission
and it gets approved.
There's a lot of stuff that we have to do
as a local government, transmit
it back up to the state.
So that goes into that detail.
I put in there large because
if you talk to a planner,
it can tell you a lot
about their experience.
It used to be called a large scale.
We still look at it as
a large scale amendment.
Small scale is anything
less than 50 acres.
Those do not go through a
formal review by the state,
but we still transmit it to the state
just to make sure within
that, less than the 50 acres
with that got the LDC
code reference too as well
that you can also cross reference
in the Land Development Code.
Again, I don't wanna harp on this,
but this is, goes into
a little bit detail.
The difference between
what's an expedited and
what's a state review.
Again, this is really with staff.
We prepare a cover letter and we request,
Florida commerce is now
the, what do you call it?
State planning agency now
it's called Florida Commerce
that we send all this to.
And within our cover
letter we have to state
what type of review it is.
Expedited, it's going to be again,
small scale amendments,
which is usually gonna be
the most of the amendments that you have.
Hilliard Isle, the larger one,
again, if it's over 50 acres,
it's gonna put it into all comprehensive,
it's still gonna be the
expedited review, it's mostly.
The state ones are gonna be
when we do the evaluation
appraisal process.
But the majority of the ones
that you see are gonna
be the expedited review.
This goes into detail,
again, this is a future land use policy.
Again, the maps and the colors,
they're not just colors for us.
Again, the different colors
designate the different types
of future land use
designations on the map.
One of the things that we
look at is compatibility.
The future land use establishes
density and intensity
usually in floor area ratio.
And typically that's
how you want to keep it.
Just intensity and density
and overall broad general types of uses.
And I'll get a little bit
further into the implementation
and I wanna deep dive a bit more
into that comprehensive plan,
'cause I know there's been
some past questions about it.
- So I'm sorry Brenda,
to go back at the slide.
I guess you're highlighting
some of the differences
between expedited and state level reviews.
Do those have different criteria
for consideration by the PAB
or those are primarily
no differences as far-
- No.
- As no staff is concerned?
- It's just a staff
transmittal type of yeah,
it's not any consideration,
it's more process.
- Gotcha.
- Okay.
So this one here, it talks
about the comprehensive plan
and providing the principal guidelines
and standards from Florida statutes.
I also wanted to,
the reason why I put a
underlying through it
is because the state land plan
agency has changed around.
I know different times
it was Department of Community Affairs,
then it was Department
of Economic Opportunity.
And I think only this past year in 2024,
it changed again to
Department of Commerce.
Nonetheless, whatever the iteration is,
it's the state land planning agency.
So calls out the Department of Commerce.
Also included the local planning agency
for the city of Kissimmee is
the Planning Advisory Board.
But I really want to point out
that it does not have to be
a separate advisory board.
It just could be the governing body
of each local government, what have you,
can establish a local planning agency.
And I'll go into a bit
more detail about that.
The first one here,
although it's not something
that you wanna really practice,
is that the governing
body, in this case here,
the governing body is
gonna be city commission
may designate its own self,
as the local planning agency.
I actually worked for a
city where the city council
was also the local planning agency.
So by practice it may not be,
but it is not against the law.
So it provides on here
that the governing body
may designate itself
as the local planning agency.
And even in the central
Florida, in my experience,
you do have the case where
a council or commission wears both hats.
- But sorry, I thought
you said that as far
as Kissimmee is concerned,
the Planning Advisory Board
is already designated as
the local planning agency?
- Correct.
But I'm just pointing out that statutorily
that the governing body could also serve
and function as the local planning agency.
Like each.
Let me, if you please,
I wanna try to get
through the slides first.
But I'm just emphasizing
that the city of Kissimmee has its own,
but it's not statutorily required to,
just pointing out just by reference.
The local planning agency.
- I'm sorry, I guess I don't understand.
So you're saying right
now in the city charter,
the Planning Advisory Board is designated
as the local planning agency.
In this case, you say that
the governing already may,
according to Florida
statute designate itself
as the local planning agency?
Is that happening right
now in Kissimmee or not?
- It's not, that's why I pointed out,
so for Kissimmee, we have
a Planning Advisory Board,
but the governing body
may designate itself
as a local planning agency.
- And here governing body
means the city commission.
- City commission.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah.
So the other thing that
I want to point out
in the second slide about
the local planning agency,
that in preparing the comprehensive plan.
But the agency can be a
local planning commission,
the planning department
or the local government
or other instrumentality.
Again, the statutes provides
a lot of leeway of how to,
regarding oversight in
the comprehensive plan,
the preparation of it.
The other one is the format of
the principles and guidelines
of the comprehensive plan can be done
at the discretion of local government.
It's standard practice to have goals,
objectives, and policies.
But it could be guiding principles.
It does not have to be established
by goals, objectives or policies.
But it could be aspirational
principles, what have you.
But I think in standard
practice, in my experience,
and I think with other planners here,
that it's goals, objectives, and policies.
Again, just to point out statutorily,
city of Kissimmee compared
to statutory requirements.
And this one here also about the intent
of including different
policies, different programs.
But,
it's not the intent to include
implementation regulations
within the comprehensive plan.
It's just outlining
strategies, principles,
different types of things
that will be carried out
or emphasizing different programs.
The comprehensive plan is not intended
to be an implementing type,
it's to lay out the
different types of strategies
and plans and principles.
- So in your experience, I
guess what would be an example
of an implementing regulation there?
- Well, one,
in the case of if you have a
conditional use application,
I'll get to it.
And the conditional use
assumes the comp plan,
future land use and the
zoning is compatible.
But you are wanting to add
a condition of approval
to the conditional use based
on a policy and the comp plan.
You want to implement
it by adding the policy
as a condition, for example,
to the conditional use.
So by adding a condition
to a conditional use,
you're implementing that
by adding it as a condition
to a policy or something in the comp plan,
comprehensive plan as a
condition, if that makes sense.
Taking a policy, taking a goal,
taking an objective from the comp plan
and including it as a condition,
as part of the conditional use.
Now you're implementing it
and placing a condition
on the development.
That would be an example of that.
And that's not the intent
of, that's what it's saying,
it's not the intent to
be an implementation
using goals, objectives to implement.
It's just to establish
programs, services and goals.
I also was thinking about
an example of a 5K race.
You plan on racing a 5K race
maybe in March or April or so,
and you set up goals, objectives,
and policies in place for
you to run this 5K race.
But there's other types of
factors that may come into play
that would require you to
postpone or to change that.
That's another example.
Like, you know, you set a goal in place
but you may not actually be able
to finish or reach that goal.
It might be another
alternative in its place.
That's how I'm,
unless there's some other
example that to find.
But.
- To help me understand, I guess.
So the first example you gave,
if we try to point to some
objective policy or goal
in the existing comprehensive plan
and use it to try to create a condition
for some conditional use approval.
I guess the part I maybe
don't understand is,
anytime we approve any conditional use,
does that automatically get amended
to the comprehensive plan?
Is that part of the document?
- No, again, it's separate.
There's land use and zoning.
- So then I'm just,
I guess like could you help
me understand a little bit,
I'm trying to read the thing.
It says it's not the intent
to require the inclusion
of implementing regulations
in the comprehensive plan.
So the example you gave, like
how does that constitute
an implementing regulation
in the comprehensive plan?
If we pointed to an objective policy
or goal in the comprehensive plan?
I guess the, okay, the first question.
I'm trying to learn these words, right?
So if I have a goal objective or policy
in the existing comprehensive plan,
could it be an implementing
regulation or is it sort of?
- It's not. No.
- No.
- So now if, and similarly
if we have something
come before the board, which
is conditional use approval,
if we approve that,
that itself isn't part of
the comprehensive plan.
- No.
- So if we put a conditional
use or put a condition,
added a condition to a
conditional use application.
I guess I'm struggling to understand
how that would be an example
of an implementing regulation
in the comprehensive plan.
Because that is-
- It's not.
- In the comprehensive plan.
- If you decide to add the condition
based on a comp plan policy,
you are free to add conditions,
you're free to modify.
But this is where staff will determine,
again, if it's a condition
based on the Land Development Code
or you know what have you,
it's if you add it based
on a comp plan goal
or objective policy.
- Gotcha.
I guess just taking a step back,
like reading this thing,
the kind of reading,
just like the English
words, the takeaway I get
is that the comprehensive
plan should try to stay
sort of aspirational
and shouldn't, you know,
deep dive into the details.
Is that kind of a good read of.
- Yes.
- Yes. Okay.
- Gotcha.
- The other aspect of
the comprehensive plan
is that it can reference
additional documents.
This is where it's so important.
So you've got goals,
objectives, and policies
and they also can
reference other documents.
So case in point here,
I added the example of policy 1.2.92
that references to the downtown CRA plan.
We didn't incorporate it into
there, but it's referenced.
So this is an example of
that in Florida statutes
where we have references to other plans
and other documents too.
- And to clarify, I
guess you're saying that
163 3177 1B is saying that
if that reference to the
downtown CRA plan doesn't mean
that the downtown CRA plan is
part of the comprehensive plan
for the consideration of the
rest of Florida statutes?
- It's by reference.
A local government can
include other documents
by reference but not incorporated into it.
- Yeah, and then I guess I'm wondering,
let's say there's an objective
in the downtown CRA plan,
if we are in trying to evaluate
the things done before the
board, can we, you know,
point to something in
the downtown CRA plan
or the Vine Street CRA plan as a reason
for supporting our approval
or disapproval of the item?
- I think the answer is yes.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Gotcha. So.
- And also just as an overview,
so the idea of the comprehensive plan,
it's the constitution,
the Land Development
Code or the, you know,
statutes, right?
It's like the comp plan
is this broad, big thing
and the laws executed from that
are Land Development Code.
Sorry, Brenda.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
So yeah, I guess before,
'cause it might help me
just to make sure I have,
again, I really like to be effective,
I'd like to make sure I understand
and this is like our opportunity now
to kind of get into it, right?
So yes, my understanding in
looking at the city charter,
like maybe just take a step back,
like what's the point of the PAB?
Like what's the role?
Like what's our duty?
Right?
And I guess first I like, okay,
this is what I got from
reading the charter.
What I got is that the PAB exists
to act as a citizen advisory
board to the city commission
who is meant to
primarily refer to and
try to make our decisions
based almost entirely on
the comprehensive plan.
And so then my interpretation is,
probably like the reason we exist
is to act as a sort of check
or balance in the sense that,
you know, the comprehensive
plan is meant to be
a forward looking document
for the future of the city.
I can understand how
it'd be easy to kind of,
you know, lose sight of that
in the details or something.
And so it feels like working
in our best capacity,
our job should be to try to like,
you know, add an additional pressure
or an additional focus to
make sure that day to day
the decisions being made
are kind of in keeping
with the vision of the comprehensive plan.
Is that you think a fair?
- But it's not just
the comprehensive plan.
- And I understand that the
city has lots of other things
that they kind of are responsible to,
but I guess yeah, as far
as the board is concerned,
is it our...
It feels like the comprehensive plan
is meant to be sort of paramount
in our decision making
processes as a board.
- Just, yes.
- Okay.
- But it's not the only thing.
- Gotcha.
- It's not the only thing for the role.
Again, with an annexation,
we have policies about it,
but again, there's.
And rezoning, rezoning is
a change to the zoning map
that's not in the comprehensive plan.
- But I guess the
comprehensive plan does include
objectives, policies, and.
- Just just to be clear,
so Florida statutes requires establishment
of a land planning agency within, right,
so that's you guys.
And your mandate is comp plan.
But because the comp plan is the broader,
part of that is also
how do you execute it?
And that's in the details.
- Yeah.
- So that's the LDC.
- Gotcha.
- If that makes sense.
- Yeah, I think that helps.
Okay. And then what I'm getting
out of these couple slides
is yeah, as far as Kissimmee is concerned
and as far as the rest of
Florida statutes are concerned,
we are the local planning agency,
the comprehensive plan,
the first point here
is meant to be aspirational
and not sort of detailed
in implementing specific regulations.
And the second point here
suggests that the downtown CRA
or the Vine Street, CRA,
these other documents
that are referenced in the comp plan
as far as we're concerned,
are in the comp plan
for Yeah. Gotcha.
- Mr. Fallon, did you have a question?
I didn't know you had, you were...
If you had a question or something.
Oh, okay.
- I just had my mic on.
So you might have heard,
but I was kind of in the same situation.
I was thinking that the comp
plan as you guys refer to
is the umbrella, right?
And there's things that
fall underneath it,
like the CRA where it's referenced,
and it's kind of this one
big comprehensive plan.
And you're saying that there's others
that fall outside of that,
would be what we're also
including into that,
that we need to be kind of cognizant on
that I may not be aware of.
So is there something,
some additional literature
that we need to kind of be informed on
so that we can make educated decisions
when we're here on this?
No, there isn't. Okay.
- Land Development Code,
but Land Development
Code, that's the zoning,
the planning, the zoning element of it.
- And also just to clarify,
so the relationship between the CRA plan
and the comprehensive
plan is a little murky.
So it doesn't always,
it it is not a perfect umbrella.
Sometimes it's better to think
of the CRA plan as independent,
although it is still consumed
by the comprehensive plan.
- Right, I think of it the CRA
and a comprehensive plan
as a overlap in some areas,
and then the comprehensive plan
is kind of much broader and bigger.
But the CRA district is kind of like
a small little area here, like.
- But it gets its own-
- But the comprehensive
plan is much bigger.
- Right, but the CRA
gets its own master plan.
- And board.
- Like within,
so it's like that, CRA plan within it
and then from there Land Development Code.
- Okay.
- Does the CRA have its own
or could it have its own
Local planning agency?
- It has its own CRA board.
So our city commission
acts as the CRA board.
- And they are the local
planning agency for the CRA?
- Correct.
- Correct, okay.
- So in this case, the city,
remember that one slide I talked about,
I know this is planning but
the governing body is the CRA.
So we practice that
some other jurisdictions
as a separate CRA board.
But for the city and
I think Osceola County
for the West 192, for the longest time
the West 192 CRA was the
county commission too.
So city commission wears
the both hats in that case,
and that's an an option.
It could be together or
it could be separate.
Here for the planning,
it's separate other areas,
the city commission or city
council can also function
as local planning agency.
- And that's just to check,
that's also true for the Vine Street CRA
the commission is the Local Planning.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- They also function as the CRA board.
Okay.
So this talks about all
of the data analysis
and how we go about shaping
the goals and vision
and it talks about data.
'Cause I think there are some
questions that come up before.
I think what I wanna
point out with this one
is that to be based on the data,
means to react to it in an appropriate way
and to the extent necessary
indicated by the data available
on that particular subject
at the time of adoption
of the plan or plan amendment at issue.
So the data, and you can probably
can come across that maybe
some of the data may be a
bit dated in the comp plan.
But you have to understand
that the other objective
for the comp plan is 10
and 20 year horizons.
These are in keeping
with that broad nature,
a lot of times you'll see
the 2036 comprehensive plan
for other jurisdictions,
because there are other
sections of statutes that says
that you need to look at this
from a 10 and 20 year horizon.
Very, very broad.
So that's why it's sometimes
it also makes it very difficult
when you're talking about project specific
and trying to, another reason
why that is difficult to
implement on a project specific level
when you're talking about data
that could be 10 and 20 years out
and it's to react to it based on the data
at the time of adoption too as well.
So I just wanted to point
that out too as well.
Supporting data can be
used to aid in termination,
compliance and consistency.
Again, this is again something
for y'all to consider too from
a background from the data
and those types of things.
And it's also from
professionally accepted sources.
With the bureau, I think now
it's the Florida University of Florida
for Population Estimates.
It used to be BEBR, the
Bureau Economic Resource,
but I think it's, I'm
not sure if it still is,
but there's, it used to be BEBR
for University of Florida
for the longest time,
but there's certain standard
in the planning profession,
acceptable types of data sources.
Metro Plan is our Metropolitan
Planning Organization or MPO.
They also are acceptable NPOs
or local NPOs are
acceptable sources of data,
census track data, the,
what do you call it?
Census also too as well.
But also keep in mind too,
when you start to see some
of this stuff too as well,
it's because it has to be
from professionally accepted sources.
Like we can't go out there as planners
and do an inventory of something
and then incorporate some of
that data into the comp plan.
It has to be some professionally accepted
types of sources that we have to use.
So just to bear in mind
and to keep that in mind.
10, 20 year broad horizons too as well.
- But then I guess so but this point is,
this is relevant for at time of adoption
and amendment, right?
So I guess this is saying like,
you know, the city makes broad
changes to the comp plan,
tries to adopt new sections
or policies or stuff.
- Amendments.
- Yeah.
- And I guess those
amendments could include
even the amendments that we see regularly,
like the land use amendments
and stuff like that?
I mean most of those don't
incorporate data, right?
That's the...
- So Land Development
Code is gonna be separate.
So it's gonna be like
a comp plan amendment,
a text amendment, that would be the case.
- Yeah.
- But not land.
Land Development Code would
be completely separate.
That would be an amendment
to the Land Development Code.
- So I guess, so what are
some examples of data?
Like right now in our comp
plan we've got the maps
of like quality of service,
number of lanes, things like that.
That's the kind of data
that he's referring to?
- So, FDOT,
so we need to incorporate,
FDOT now has updated 2024
roadway classifications.
They have turn lane traffic counts,
they've updated their
roadway classifications.
They've updated their level service
for state roadways here
within the city of Kissimmee.
An amendment would be to
incorporate in our maps
the map series transportation element
to update the maps figure
2.32 what have you,
in the transportation element.
That would be a form of a plan amendment,
a text amendment to update the data.
Update the roadway classifications
level service, that FDOT,
which is a professionally
acceptable source.
That would be an example of it.
- Yeah.
- But also just,
we also have staff who
are long-term planners.
So they work on constantly,
you know, looking at our
comp plan and revising it.
So that's something that
is constantly in the woods,
but that's not like before us as a board
we're looking at specific
amendments to the comp plan.
- Yeah, I guess I'm just trying.
- Which is always in a process
of evaluating and revising.
- So are those defined under the mandatory
elements of change?
'Cause those are more changed
by FDOT as you stated, right?
And then, which would
be considered optional?
What would be considered
an optional element?
Like something like we've had
a major flooding or something like that.
- Coastal, yeah.
'Cause we're not a coastal element for us.
I mean, that's a bad example.
Some people have hazard mitigation.
I've seen some jurisdictions
have a hazard mitigation
element, that would be optional.
A mandatory land use transportation,
intergovernmental parks and rec housing
typically or mandatory.
It actually in that section
lists down the required ones
are typical but not optional.
- One would be
something much less than
they used to be by law.
- Absolutely.
What's the other one that just
got public rights element?
- Yeah. (laughs)
- That was about two years ago
now that's a mandatory public
property rights, sorry,
property rights element that
has some public participation.
So property rights, yes,
Florida state of Florida.
Very, very, very, very property rights,
very have property rights state.
But now it's mandatory
property rights element.
These are some other resources.
Florida Papers.
I know that there were other,
so there's a section that
says that we have to provide
just the current adopted
elements or chapter
of the comp plan.
But I know that there are questions
before about where to go to research.
Previous iterations.
This is at Florida Papers,
so you just will plug
in city of Kissimmee,
but this is where you can do some research
on previous plan amendments,
whether it be small or large.
This is where you can go to research,
do all that research
called Florida Papers.
- Yeah.
- That Florida commerce,
that table comp contents
goes through in detail flowcharts,
it talks about how to process,
again, this is more on the staff level,
but I think there's some
really, really good information,
particularly those statutory changes.
It lists through all the
different changes going back to,
I mean I don't think,
I think it's like 2011
or something like that.
But it is a wealth of information
about all the different changes there.
But that is a wealth of information.
But if you are interested
in about the process,
again, all of this is
behind the scenes there,
but is a wealth of information.
- So I did notice that
the city, the new website,
the comp plan is available
on the website and thank
you for doing that.
I think that's great,
If I had another request.
Yeah, so going to like
the Florida Papers are,
the bulk of our comp plan
is listed as an amendment
as well as like the future
amendments and stuff.
So it's kind of hard to navigate.
And if we could do one more thing,
it'd be nice to not only have the,
you know, like the 800 page comp plan
with the required sections
available on the website,
but maybe a PDF with like
all of the amendments
that we passed since that
2008 update available.
- But that's where it's Florida Papers.
- I know, but there's like
100 amendments in there,
and since the comp plan was
adopted as an amendment,
it took me kind of like
three hours to click through
to try to find, you know, the start date
and when it was adopted
and try to track down all
the amendments and stuff.
And it just,
the request would be like
every time we do an amendment,
since we have a PDF
anyway, if we could just.
- Right, but in preparing for this,
I think there is a section
where we are required
to have the latest and greatest.
- Sorry, are required to have?
- We are required to
have available the latest
and greatest in current comp plan.
- And what I'm saying is the comp plan
that's available on the website,
it was the, you know, 800 page amendment
that was passed in 2008.
And right now we're not making
available on our website,
the amendments that
we've made to that since.
- No, it includes when
we make an amendment
that we had like for the
future land use element,
which is one chapter of it,
that comp plan 800 pages,
is the latest and greatest for
the future land use element.
It is the latest and greatest.
- But like Hilliard Isle
wasn't in there, right?
- Hilliard Isle.
Again, you're talking
about the comp plan text,
when we did it as a map.
So the map would not be in that comp plan
when we did the Hilliard Isle
future land use amendment.
- Yeah.
And I understand that I can
find the Hilliard Isle map
that the amendment that we passed
associated with that at Florida Papers.
But seeing is that as an amendment
and is now part of the comprehensive plan,
I think it would be
convenient if the city,
when you click on the thing
that says the current comprehensive plan,
if that also included the amendments
to that plan that we passed.
- I think that's probably an IT issue.
- Okay.
- But I think he's talking about that.
- Well I think he probably
needs to understand
is when they upload it,
it's a conformed copy,
so it's like they've already updated it
and it's just references.
This is the amended version
and it's in its entirety with all changes
inside that comprehensive plan.
If you have all the additional amendments,
then it's kind of like you need to have
the base original plus all the amendments
and it's kind of like separated out,
and I think it'll cause more confusion.
But the whole conformed copy as one,
kind of the one that was sent to me,
it's not even on the
website, I had to request it.
So, but as far as when I read it,
I did see that it was an amended one,
but it was the conformed version.
- And yeah, I would love
for that to be the case
that when you go to the city website
and you click on the thing,
you get the conformed copy
that is just the current
up-to-date version.
- Correct.
- I guess I'm trying to communicate
that last time I did that,
I don't think that was the case.
- I didn't even see, maybe
it's on the website, so.
- No, yeah, it wasn't available.
It is now in the new
updated Kissimmee website.
- Okay.
- If you search for it,
there is a place to click
and maybe we should just double check
that when you click on that you get
the totally updated version, so.
- But I just wanna make sure I understand
that the Hilliard Isle
was a map amendment.
It wouldn't be in the comp plan.
- The wasn't an amendment
to the comprehensive plan?
- It was a map, it wasn't a text.
It didn't change any
text in the comp plan.
- Okay.
so now, okay, so now I
need to understand, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- In the Florida statute and on that slide
we said that there were
two forms of amendments
to the comprehensive plan.
One is a map amendment and
one is a text amendment.
- Correct.
- So when I hear that,
I think that these are both amendments
to the comprehensive plan.
And if they're both amendments
to the comprehensive plan,
if you pass a map amendment,
it seems like that should then be part
of the comprehensive plan.
- Not the map, map is separate.
Because the map is separate.
Because if we had to
incorporate map amendments
in the comp plan,
we would have to be
constantly updating the map.
And I'm gonna tell you this
also from other prior experience
also, it's gonna be standard
for other jurisdictions.
The map amendments aren't
incorporated into the comp plan.
- But then, if I hear you right,
the only way to see the most
up-to-date version of the maps,
the figures would be to go to
the Florida Papers website,
and download and read
all of the amendments
that have been passed.
- And our GIS, we incorporate
into our GIS layer.
- Good. Okay, good.
- It's also.
- Go ahead. No, go ahead.
- If you go to page 44,
you have all the updated maps.
You've got one, two, three,
four, four of those there.
It's in the comp plan,
- The one available
right now you're saying
and it has Hilliard Isle
dial and stuff on there.
- Yeah.
- Okay, good. Awesome.
Then it sounds like it's
been updated. That's great.
Yes. Now the file has 2022 on it,
so I think it's been updated.
- Yep. Yep.
So what we consider is compatibility
adequate public services and facility.
So sometimes in our staff report,
some of the things that we look at,
even for the map amendments,
we look at compatibility on the map.
If they wanna change the property
wants to change future
land use designation,
we need to see, well, is that
future land use designation
within the immediate vicinity or the area?
So is it compatible with
what's in the surrounding area?
The other thing that
we look at too as well
is adequate public services and
facilities level of service.
I don't wanna get too
much into level of service
because again, there's so
many preemptions and bills
regarding with concurrency
that has changed
what a local government can consider
as far as what level of service
and adequate public services,
public services and
facilities and capacity.
It's been chipped away of the public,
the local government's
ability really quite frankly
to require for developers to contribute
to increasing a level of service,
whether it be water, sewer, or roadway.
So for example, if the
roadway is already failing,
it's not on the developer
to try to totally eliminate
and to improve the entire
segment of the roadway.
It's the developer to pay
his or her fair share of it
based on their impact.
So there's been a lot of
changes regarding concurrency,
public services and facilities.
In a nutshell, it allows for a developer
to concurrently build
and to construct the
improvements at the same time.
And we cannot hold up or deny a project
if there's not currently
adequate roadways,
adequate utilities.
It provides for them to improve it
concurrently with construction.
I think that's the biggest takeaway
and that's the biggest change,
where they are allowed to
complete their improvements,
their fair share of the improvements
concurrently with development
is the best takeaway
that I can probably describe
when it comes to adequate
public services and facilities.
Mitigation of adverse impacts.
So again, if there are
gonna be any types of,
for example, impacts to a roadway,
it may mean that they have
to expand the roadway,
put in a turn lane.
Expand the actual length of a turn signal,
include a traffic signal.
Those are the types of things
that can be mitigate an adverse impact.
And we can perhaps take
a look at to consider
and of course again how it supports
the goals, objectives, and policies.
So on the findings and reasons,
when we do a staff report,
we usually try to put a
blurb of a specific policy
or specific section as
to how an application
supports a specific goal, objective,
or policy in our staff reports.
Again here in my past experience,
and they can probably
even attest to as well,
for us, the city is pretty brief.
Currently right now it's
not where we have to do
four and five, six page staff reports
where to go into detail.
So right now for us it's pretty
brief, concise to the point
that's the spirit of the city
of Kissimmee to be clear,
concise, direct, and to the point
and not have to do, you know,
or five or six just get to the point,
and not have six and seven pages of things
that people are probably not
gonna read or understand.
Okay, so this goes into zoning.
So in the state of Florida,
because we are a
comprehensive planning state,
this will apply to every
single property in the state.
Every property has a
future land use designation
and every property has
a zoning designation,
it's two layers.
So this is where we're moving away
from the comprehensive plan,
and now we're talking about the zoning.
And the zoning, there
are standards in our,
we talk about our Land Development Code.
So within that Land Development Code,
we have already established
zoning districts
that are compatible with
the different land use
designations that we have.
It's already spelt out already.
So the different types
of rezoning that we have
that you are going to come across
as a PUD, Plan Unit Development.
This is a customized type of zoning
where different development
standards can be customized
and a developer and an
applicant can come in
and create their own
standards that are different.
We can have an amendment
to an existing PUD
or we can have a rezoning
here in this example
to change it from a
different zoning designation
that's already established
in the Land Development Code.
Again, this is where we start
to mirror the comprehensive plan,
this is the implementing document.
The Land Development Code regulates,
the Land Development Code establishes.
Now we get into pretty
much the nitty gritty.
It establishes height,
it establishes lot dimensions.
It establishes landscaping,
but it implements those broad categories.
So it's broad goals and objectives
of the comprehensive plan.
It also establishes procedures, standards,
even includes planning, advisory board
and adopts and development
review process too as well.
So those maps too as
well, there's standards.
So this is from the American
Planning Association
that the maps really,
there's the industry standard
of different land use categories.
So the colors mean something.
So from someone for like Ryan coming down
from Fort Pierce or even with Christian,
usually residential is
some iteration of yellow.
So there's some industry
colors and standards
that we are familiar with too as well.
Even the colors mean something.
So even when we look at a
map, we can get an idea of,
okay, yellow means that this
is a residential corridor.
A residential area,
but I just wanna point
out that even the colors
are pretty standard in
the urban planning world.
Okay, this goes into the conditional uses.
So we talked about zoning,
and within the zoning
there's different uses.
This is the A table that we have here
and it points to the
different zoning categories.
And where it says P,
it means it's permitted,
it's allowable use.
So when it has a P or permitted,
it's a particular use.
That application is not gonna come
before this Planning Advisory Board
because it's a permitted use,
it's an allowable use by the zoning,
and it does not require any
type of application or request
to come before the
Planning Advisory Board.
That particular use can
essentially complete it
with our building permit
and maybe a business license
with our building and
permitting department.
But those types of uses
that speed, it's allowable.
The ones that are C are the
ones where it could be allowed.
And you're assuming, again,
the future land use designation
and that zoning are
compatible with one another,
but there's some type of use
or some type of intensity
and potential of adverse impacts
that requires a public hearing
and some considerations
and the potential for the
Planning Advisory Board
to review and include
additional conditions.
- And just to check basic question,
the Land Development Code though,
any amendments or modifications of that?
That's the purview of the
city commission, right?
Not us.
- No. It actually will come before
the Planning Advisory
Board for a recommendation.
- Sorry if there's a
conditional use application
that's gonna come before us,
but is it this body's
duty or who's responsible
for amending the Land Development Code?
Like if you're gonna add a change
one of these Ps to a C or a C to a P.
- It's primarily gonna be with staff,
but we have had
applications from developers
or property owners requesting
consideration of changes.
And those are coordinated
through staff and analyzed.
But typically it's going to be a staff
that will initiate those.
But we have inquiries
about, well, you know,
city of St Cloud has, you know,
this particular type of standard
and we'll do some research.
We'll be directed to do some
research or what have you,
to consider any type of potential changes.
But it's going to be staff
ultimately has a discretion.
- I guess, sorry, to clarify,
like you're saying staff
originates the suggestion,
but like, I guess I'm
just like the legal arm.
Can the Land Development Code be amended
without any, you know, public
consideration or anything?
- No.
- No, right.
So who is it that approves
the amendment if there is one?
- Ultimately it'd be City commission.
- City commission.
- But it will go before
this Planning Advisory
Board for a recommendation.
- Oh, even a local,
like a textual change to
the Land Development Code
would first come here?
- Yeah.
- Gotcha. Okay.
Thank you.
- Again, these are the different
types of conditional uses.
Conditional uses is just that.
We've had several of
'em that have come in.
Typically it's just requesting the use.
There's no site changes,
there's no changes to the
exterior of the building.
Typically it's gonna be
somebody that's coming in
to the existing building
and they want to change the
use inside the building.
It doesn't require anything on the site.
The second type is gonna be
a conditional use with site plan.
Either it's a vacant piece of property
or they're adding or
modifying the site itself.
And then the second category
is a conditional use
with site improvements.
That redevelopment plan is gonna indicate
it's gonna be either in the
Vine Street or downtown CRA.
Again, a lot of times
for the conditional uses
you'll see that it will include,
this one here is an example
of a condition use with the A site plan.
So it's gonna be, this is
typically included in your packet
that shows ultimately the building layout
and some of the information on there.
Again, there's certain
uses by way of the zoning
that will require,
again, public hearing,
public consideration.
We've actually streamlined
a lot of those requirements
from a couple years back.
For example, Mr. Spalding,
I know you may remember
that even outdoor storage at one point
required a public hearing.
And again, we did some further
analysis on outdoor storage
and the city just implemented
overall across the board
outdoor storage standards in
the Land Development Code.
And it no longer requires a public hearing
just to have outdoor storage.
What was the other one?
Outdoor storage was one I
think, I can't remember.
There's something else too
as well that we used to...
A landscape buffer waiver.
Somebody wants to substitute
a wall for a fence,
that used to come to
Planning Advisory Board.
Again, we just established standards
where now it goes before our committee.
Just to streamline it,
just from feedback from folks and stuff.
So we've streamlined a lot of it.
Again, conditional use is future land use
and zoning designations are
compatible with one another.
That's one of the things
that staff looks at.
And it's just with the
conditional use approval,
you'll see the additional
conditions of approval, added
where you have the right to
modify and or add conditions
to these types of applications.
By the way, planning advisory board
final approval for
conditional use applications,
those types do not go
forward to city commission.
So Planning Advisory
Board has authorization
for final approval for conditional use.
There is the appeal, I can't remember
if it's city commission or circuit,
but the Planning Advisory Board
and you have final authorization
of final approval for conditional use.
That's not so much recommendation
that it's final approval.
All right.
I'd like to just kind of,
'cause it's like a lot here.
So this is trivia here,
Including Florida,
how states have growth management programs
that require strongly encourage
the adoption of a comprehensive plan?
Anyone, anyone, anyone?
- I guess, D.
- D.
Interestingly 13.
So I included here the
different other types of states.
What we'll have in my career too as well.
You'll have planners to
come from different states.
Again, they'll look for
which other comprehensive planning states.
So I like to put it on here.
Widely recognized growth
management that either require
or strongly encourage the adoption
of local comprehensive plans.
So just a little bit of trivia.
- So I guess I'd be curious
to hear from the experts,
what are better in those 13 states
and what are worse in those 13 states?
- What was question?
- I mean like in your experience,
13 of the 50 states require
comprehensive plans.
I guess I'd just be curious to hear like,
you know, your hot take for what that is
sort of best at accomplishing
and where it sort of most
gets in the way of planning.
- I may just for my background
experience with California,
for example, they have the,
a general plan, which is different
to the comprehensive plan
and the general plan mostly over there,
they have the seven elements required by,
to adopt additional.
I think you are experienced
or familiar with California.
They have the California
Environmental Quality Act, CEQA
and they have all internal components.
So they have a general plan for,
so for them it works perfectly.
'cause there's a lot of
components attached to it.
So what I've seen here, coming
from a different perspective,
from all the way from the west to Florida,
the comprehensive plan up
here, what I'm seeing is,
it's working for what the
surrounding areas have.
Here, for example, in
Florida we don't have a CEQA,
we have it's NEQA,
which is a National
Environmental Quality Act,
which is secures the
environmental components of this.
So it's normally,
and if you can see here,
with the exception of Oregon,
it's mostly done here on the
east side of the country.
So, that's what I've seen in my experience
where I've had the opportunity
to grow as a professional in
California and then come here.
That's the different perspectives.
- Thank you.
- I think a lot of it has to do with
how it's regulated really.
For the longest time, 1985,
everyone knows here,
state of Florida, 1985,
Pivotal Growth Management Act.
A lot of people don't realize before 1985
we had comprehensive plan requirements
that they just weren't implemented
or they weren't really enforced.
It was, again, strongly encouraged.
So I think some of the pitfalls
is that it's strongly encouraged
where it's not here we have a transmittal,
like we have to transmit to the state
within 10 working days (laughs).
- And let me tell you, I can say this.
- Go ahead.
- It is one area
where Florida has actually
been very progressive
and the Growth Management Act was pretty,
I think pretty,
you know, trendsetting-
- Paradigm shift,
I mean really.
- Yeah, I mean for a
state as large as Florida
and mandating that for
the state and counties
and municipalities.
I don't know the history
of the other states,
but this is one area where I think Florida
has historically done very well,
from I think the planner perspective.
The state has kind of eed out some of
what we would like to see
in our comprehensive plans.
They have not made some of the things
as mandatory as they had been.
Concurrency is not what
it used to be, but,
and those other states are much smaller.
- It's been decimated really,
and in my opinion that
that growth management act,
and there's a lot of now go into it,
these preemptions that come
down and they're unfunded.
We don't get any additional
funding to regulate
or to enforce these bills that
are coming from the state.
In some cases, we are
not provided a direction.
It's not clear.
So we have to sort it out and
figure it out for ourselves
how to interpret or how to implement.
Do we need a comprehensive plan change?
- Should I live local?
- I'll get some of that.
- You know, do we need a
comprehensive planning state
to be in compliance with this bill
that just passed the legislation in 2024?
Do we also need a Land
Development Code change,
text amendment change to
the Land Development Code?
Or is it just a process?
Does the building department
have to change a particular process?
Do I have to implement
another development
review committee process,
or do we have to create
another application
where it's just administrative?
and it's all those things
that really, again, for us,
it's comprehensive plan is just one aspect
of the stuff that we have to do.
So the Planning Advisory Board,
and just to let you know,
I know you're taking the picture here.
We'll send this to you
'cause I'm sorry I was, you know,
had to work on a couple of things.
So we'll send this PowerPoint
to you and with the links.
So the Planning Advisory Board
is also the Brownfield Advisory
Committee for the city.
We haven't had one come in.
Now this does not mean
that the Planning Advisory
Board reviews and comments,
the actual remediation plans.
There are some provisions in the statute
that talks about compatibility.
So it's similar to your you know,
authorities and powers about
considering compatibility,
considering the impacts
on neighboring properties.
You or I don't have the
technical capability
of going through a Brownfield plan.
You probably know even bit
more on the Brownfield stuff
to technical technicality
of a remediation plan.
So your role as the committee is not that,
but it's this consideration
of a redevelopment
of a project within
the city's Brownfield's
redevelopment area.
But you are also, the
Planning Advisory Board
is the Brownsville advisory Committee.
I think we've convened only once or twice
in the past five years
as the Brownsville Advisory Committee.
This was the Mosaic Apartments down here.
There was remediation
contamination on that site,
and it was presented.
A remediation plan was put into place
and the board had to convene
as the Brownfield advisory Committee.
Any further questions on that?
We worked closely with our
CRA team here with staff,
but that was the last time
we had anything come in
when we were building that mosaic
because there was a
remediation Brownfield plan
that had to be done and
had to be brought before.
- Can you kind of tell me
what a Brownfield area is?
- It's areas that have
known type of contamination
or, I take that,
it's not because the area
that we have designated,
it's areas that have been
known to have contamination,
but the Brownfield area map that we have
also includes areas that
are adjacent to it as well.
So just because a property
is within that Brownfield area map
does not mean it has any
type of contamination.
It's adjacent to it.
It makes it difficult for redevelopment,
even for properties that
are adjacent to that.
But it's some type of,
that's why I have FDP, it's
some type of remediation
or some type of area
that has had some type of
contaminations or
properties adjacent to it.
So the city has established
a Brownfield area
that includes properties again,
that are not contaminated,
but are adjacent to it.
That's the best way
that I can describe it.
I don't know if any, you know,
as far as what brownfield areas.
- And I think also part of
designating those areas,
it is helpful to get federal funding
for any future development.
- So yeah, just to try to
get basic understanding,
make sure I get this,
apparently there's like
federal money available
for developing Brownfield area.
Brownfield areas are defined to be areas
that were contaminated
or polluted in some way,
or adjacent properties.
So if some developer comes in
and they want to unlock some federal grant
to try to help them to develop a property
that has been designated as Brownfield,
I guess we're gonna say, or some kind of,
we have to look at it and approve it
or what exactly is our role
as the Brownfield Advisory Committee?
What actions or what
responsibilities do we have?
- It's a, yeah, it's a committee.
It's the same as an advisory committee.
A recommendation.
Again, I think the last one is the plan
that was for there is to making sure
that it's compatibility.
There's also some economic types
of components to it as well.
But there is a plan.
There will be either a plan
or there will be some type of,
I think it's like a grant
or some type that will
become before the board.
- And frankly, I'm not
sure how much Brownfield
is even developable at this point, right?
- Yeah, 'cause again,
Mosaic was the only one
because that's where the
Hansel electrical plant
was for decades.
- Right, right.
- Back here, the Hansel power plants here.
So,
this is in your capacity.
- Yeah.
- I'm not sure that
this is something that,
in your terms you will ever come to.
- I think it was once the last
five years was only one time.
- Yeah.
- But it's there.
- So I also wanna point
out from the staff, again,
this our staff
recommendations too as well.
And some other considerations,
again, as we help navigate different,
again, just knowing and understand,
navigating through the comp plan,
navigating through the
Land Development Code
for statutes and processes.
So there's rhyme or reason as to why
our staff recommendations
are the way that they are.
Other considerations
would be city policies
and processes to as well.
There's a level of
consistency regarding things.
And not just even the applications,
but again, advisory boards
and our city clerk has her
Florida statute requirements
of certain things and public notices
and the due process for
applicants too as well.
Moving projects forward in
a good faith effort for,
with the property owners and development.
The other thing that I wanna
bring to your attention
is a strategic plan too, as well.
There might be in some cases,
I know you mentioned about bike trails
and different types of things,
but the strategic plan
is also something that
the city commission establishes annually
at an annual retreat,
that also provides city staff priorities.
There's high level types of priorities
that may see as focusing on instead of,
you know, bikeways and trails,
it might be affordable housing.
And so the city commission
wants to have staff
put efforts and emphasis on
probably affordable housing.
The next one might be an
effort on accessory dwelling.
We did have this come up
that there was, you know,
emphasis on accessory dwelling units,
which was an offshoot
of affordable housing.
So in some cases, that we have priorities
where different goals and
objectives or policies
that we might not give prime attention to
because we have been directed
through the strategic
plan or other priorities
or other direction from
the city commission
to shift our focus.
You have to remember that
we're trying to manage a city,
and we have to be in service all thing,
all types of citizens,
all types of businesses,
all types of property owners.
So each and every single one of us
may have our different interests,
but for us it's a juggling act
that we can't to some degree say no.
You know, if a property owner has
a dire, dire need about
noise or something,
or another where we have
to shift our focus on
that particular element.
It could be schools.
A couple years ago there
was an issue with schools
and there was a legislative
bill that came into play about
where we navigate to you,
hey, be careful if, you know,
somebody says that I
don't want a development
because the school is over capacity.
Well, technically, you know,
we have to be careful about
if you're denying an application
because the school is over capacity.
That's, you know, we would try
to just delicately remind you
that we're gonna be hard pressed
if you deny an application
because the school is overcrowded.
There's been some bills
and probably, you know,
case laws or those types
of things to be wary of.
We wanna be empathetic
to the public hearing
because it's the public forum.
But this is the rhyme or reason
why the staff recommendations
are the way they are,
because we are in the know,
means as the certified planner,
I'm required to take
certification, continuing education
to stay involved in
innovative types of law,
sustainability, same thing
with Calene2 as well.
We're required to stay up to
date with different trends
and different things to consider.
But that strategic plan,
I'm anticipating it's also.
- Can I just really quickly also,
just before, and we've
talked about this before,
but before anything comes here,
first there's meetings, right?
And then an application goes,
there's a pre-application meeting
for any development project,
pre-application meeting.
Then from there it goes,
a formal application is submitted,
then it goes to development
review committee,
which is open to the
public, and from there.
And sometimes those
applications have to come back
one or two times.
And then eventually
some of them come here.
So it is many months,
tons of work from staff.
By the time it comes to you,
it has been looked at so many times
by so many different eyes.
So staff works very, very hard
at making sure that by the
time these applications
come to you, to the board,
they've been very, very vetted.
And you know, it comes
to you for PAB board.
But keep in mind that many departments,
including the building department,
public works and engineering,
fire, legal, everybody looks at it
before it even comes to here.
Sorry Brenda.
- No, absolutely.
And I also wanna emphasize
also again with that,
the expertise is what that due process.
So we are well aware, again,
we are here to navigate
and to make sure that there's a deep,
we have multiple functions, okay?
So one of 'em is, again, like I said,
good faith effort to move
these, you know, development
folks have submitted an application.
So in a good faith effort,
they've went through
a development review
committee sometimes twice.
And now with that, they
are granted and afforded
to move forward if they
have to move forward
to the Planning Advisory Board.
We have to provide advertisement,
we have to have public notice,
a minimum in advance of the meeting.
And so in some cases during
that committee meeting,
and Kayla can attest, I'm
confirming right then and there,
this is the Planning Advisory Board date
that they're moving into.
So at that point, there's
that level of expectation
at that point that this is
gonna be this meeting here
that will decide, determine,
evaluate any types of
conditions or what have you.
But when it moves
forward with that, again,
there's a good faith effort
if they have to move forward
to city commission too, that
they've gone through the step,
they've gone through a PAB,
they've gone to city commission.
So that's what you just be
careful, and be mindful of that.
Especially when you're, you know,
projects and different things
that they've gone through this process.
And we have a set schedule too
of when they submit
applications anticipated
of when they're going to
the Planning Advisory Board
and when they're gonna city commission.
Now granted we have to confirm a quorum,
but there's a a lot
involved, and to make sure
that they've gone through
the necessary steps.
Strategic plan governing body
against city commission priorities
can take away the staff's ability to say,
you know, in consideration
with the department director
or even city manager, that
unfortunately right now,
you know, we can't focus on certain goals.
We can't focus on actively,
again, these are aspirational.
So there's a lot of aspects
that go into play with,
that you may feel that, you know,
staff is not emphasizing a certain goal
or we're not emphasizing
a certain objective.
There's a lot to, that comes into play,
and these are some of the types of things.
Last but certainly not least,
preemptions, preemptions.
Bills, bills, bills,
It is a planner's job really
every time the legislature convenes.
I mean this was unprecedented too as well.
There's things that come
down with legislative bills
that takes away.
This year is the live local amendments.
Again, it's not a new act,
but it was an amendment to live local
for affordable housing.
One of the changes is
for affordable housing,
if they meet certain criteria,
they do not need a public hearing
to change land use or zoning.
That's a preemption.
So it doesn't matter.
A particular property has
an industrial land use.
They don't have to come in.
If they're meeting the provisions
of that live local acts,
they don't need to come in
to submit a future land use application
and they do not need a public hearing.
That's a preemption, that's a bill.
So there's a lot of things
that come into play.
I'm trying to think of another example.
I think the capital improvement element.
So we talked about a tax amendment change.
I was looking at this,
I remember from my long
range planning days
where the annual updates to
the capital improvements plan,
I believe does no longer requires.
I think they just need to transmit,
I don't think it requires
a public hearing.
But typically the capital
improvement update
is the five year capital
improvements plan.
Identifying certain capital
improvements, roadways,
that type of thing, anyway,
that it doesn't require a public hearing
for the annual update.
That doesn't mean the text amendments,
it's just an annual update
identifying the certain projects now.
So that's a preemption where
that doesn't require public hearing,
it just requires the
transmittal up to the state.
So there's other different
nuances too as well with it.
I think just kind of reemphasizing
the planner and our function.
So the Planning Advisory Board
is one of many functions.
So we're kind of central to that.
So our function, our commitment
and our responsibility to
the community residents,
business owners, the public at large.
Then we have the other aspects
to development related
businesses to as well,
which is also community residents.
'Cause some of you are property owners,
but also residents within the city tax
paying both as a resident
and also as a business
and property owners.
The other one is also to government.
Our elected officials,
our interdepartmental,
we have state and federal agencies too,
that we have to be held accountable to
in certain different requirements too.
So that just shows multiple functions
and roles that we have,
considerations in formalizing
our staff recommendations
and our positions and our conditions.
This here also from the
American Planning Association.
I don't even, I have it on here.
The, I have to see if, I
think we have this copy here.
So I'm gonna also forward it to y'all.
It's a planner's dictionary
that I find very, very useful.
It also incorporates
different types of definitions
from different jurisdictions
for a planner's dictionary
to help with some of the different terms
and different things that we talk about.
This is also for planning officials.
These are some of the other resources
that we have available Plan Medicine,
about what is the planning commission
that I also like to share
with planning officials
and Planning Advisory Boards.
So many different resources.
And then there's also
additional ones here,
again, when I talk
about professional types
of different acceptable
type of organizations,
these are the ones here.
ULI, CNU, ICMA, Plan Medicine are really,
again, different types of methodology,
data industry types of
policies and resources.
This is not all exhaustive, if you will,
but these are some of
the primary larger ones.
Last final trivia question.
Which of these states
was the first to mandate
comprehensive planning?
- California?
No, you're probably gonna say D, right?
For California.
- I'm gonna go with Hawaii.
- This one was very surprising.
- Sorry, what?
- I'm gonna guess Hawaii.
- Ah, that is correct.
If you really, that is correct.
In 1961, if you really think about it
with the islands and conservation,
but it was in 1961,
Hawaii was the first state
to pass a growth management law,
and divided states where it had
the urban agricultural and conservation.
So that is correct.
With that, that concludes.
I do wanna point out, 'cause
I think that was the other,
the really quickly about the
staff recommendations again.
So, the Planning Advisory
Board recommendations,
again, they don't supersede right?
They don't supersede or modify
the staff recommendations,
they just move forward with that.
That's not to say that it can't change,
but typically the Planning
Advisory Board recommendations
are that, but it doesn't take the place
of the staff recommendations.
I will say, and it hasn't
happened in a while,
but it has happened here
where the city commission
will be different from
the staff recommendation
or Planning Advisory Board recommendation.
They have the utmost authority
to even not even take
either into consideration.
I've had staff recommendations
what, overturned by that.
We've had ones that were remanded back.
We had one remanded back to
development review committee.
We had one remanded back
to Planning Advisory Board.
You just never know.
There's all different types of iterations
and we've had all types of experiences
where the city commission
ultimately has the final
determination there.
But it's just that, it's
a recommendation on there.
So this is the contact information.
I would be remiss, I forgot
Ms. Hasley too as well.
So Ms. Hasley has nearly
20, our planning technician,
she was our former recording
secretary about this on here.
She's got nearly 20 years experience
with the city of Kissimmee.
And she is our little,
little diamond kind of,
you know, super, super diamond in a rough,
super, super smart to as well,
but she grew of our
business license queen.
Okay.
If you have any, you know,
things about business licenses,
but typically to the process
now of doing alcohol reviews.
But I want y'all to know,
like we even do things
with alcohol review.
Like we actually are
responsible to sign off
on state applications,
require local zoning approval.
Our section does alcohol reviews.
So, so many other different
aspects besides that,
that we do.
We do alcohol reviews, business licenses,
what?
- Zoning.
- Zoning verification
types, special events,
pain management licenses too as well.
- So there's all different.
- And of course
there are things that go to DRC
that never come before you
guys, which are, you know,
site plans.
Plots.
- Yeah.
- Subdivision
- Subdivisions.
- Subdivision, yeah.
- Construction plans.
- Construction plans, yep.
- Variances.
We also deal with all types of
variances that are less 30%,
10 to 30% variation variances
on different code standards also that go,
to the development review committee.
If they're up to 10%, Craig,
our department director
is administrative variance signs.
I forgot, how can I
forget about sign permits?
Signed permits.
- It's amazing.
It's amazing they can
even go home at night.
- No, I do, and-
- It's true.
- Trust me, I sleep soundly.
You do this and no serious,
you do this for so long,
you have to learn how to separate.
And I've lived and
breathed urban planning.
When you learn how to transition,
you know, negative energies
and that type of thing,
and you totally commit
yourself to something.
That was me, but I've
learned how to separate it.
So I mean, I probably
wouldn't even remember
half the stuff or how it went even.
So I've been very good at that, joy,
working for the city of Kissimmee.
Again, I hope to, you know,
it's year '24, so total,
but year five here.
So I really don't plan on going anywhere.
So I don't know if final thoughts.
Anybody else wants to say anything?
- Well, thank you so much
for the presentation.
I really appreciate it
and I think it was very
informative and clarifying.
One thing I think would be fun is
to hear your
and the rest of city staff's
perspective in the sense that
how can the PAB become
a more effective body,
or what would it mean
or what do you think it
means for a PAB to be
best aiding the city?
Like I can totally understand
if everything's functioning really well,
everything is going the
way it's supposed to be.
And in fact, the practice
seems to be both historically
and currently, almost all
the things come before us.
It's an easy approval,
everything's kind of okay
and it sort of meets some
legislative requirement.
But then as a thought experiment.
- I would say just keep
doing what you're doing.
Look at each application
before you critically
and make the best
recommendations that you can.
- Okay.
Yeah, I guess.
- I know that might not sound satisfying,
but I promise you at some point
you will recommend denial and
that will go to the commission
and they will agree with you.
- I guess I'd be interested to hear either
from your past experience,
or even hypothetically,
whether there's an example you experienced
or one you could imagine where,
you know, you think it was a
good thing or help the city
or was the right choice for a even,
you know, some other cities-
- Yes.
- Planning Advisory Board to-
- Could you share those examples?
Is that?
- No.
- Okay.
- But yes, it is definitely,
I know it seems like a slow slog,
but every now and again,
you're gonna catch something
and your recommendation
will make a difference.
- I think the best thing is to,
and I think it may be also communication,
but I think tonight with an opportunity
to lean on with the staff recommendation,
'cause that's what you
can agree to disagree
and agree to disagree,
but then just consider
the reasoning again,
why the staff recommendation
is the staff recommendation that it is.
I think that's the best thing.
And it's a hit or miss, but
it's a checks and balances.
And it's difficult because the bylaws
for this Planning Advisory
Board used to require
that the board members
be certain professions.
It used to be, where it
was an engineer, architect.
I think the county planning commission
is still that way.
So I think the challenge
is when you have citizens
and not fully understanding,
and then the same thing, vice versa
with not fully understanding the different
design aspects of it or what have you.
So that's where it becomes
a little bit difficult,
and it'd be sometimes even
frustrating because of that.
But the city changed that
because the city is smaller
and they're having difficulty
in filling those roles.
So that's why they changed it.
But most other places will
have probably two at large.
And then you have professions
and people, what have you.
It's not to say it's
a good or a bad thing,
but it just, it takes, it's
confusing and it's a lot.
But I think from here on out,
I think it is just to maybe
a different understanding
and perspective here.
We are to report to, you know,
you have questions or you
know, types of concerns.
But I think it's just
to feel those concerns.
I think it's the best way to be effective,
but understand that is not
meant to be adversarial.
I think the best thing in
my experience too as well
is that the staff recommendation
really goes a long way.
It even goes from a legal
aspect of it too as well.
And so, by the way,
I mean for injunctions
and all of that stuff, where with that,
we've already talked about that,
where you have to be involved
with a challenge too.
But it's expert staff.
There's a term for it, expert competence,
staff experience.
And it goes a long way.
- Which leads me to when would you guys
like to have legal training?
Anyone?
It's so fun.
- So just so y'all know,
the last time we did both in one night
and we said never again (laughs)
It was like, yeah, it
was just way too much,
that's why we separated out.
But with that,
that's a good segue.
- Should we be until
the new year
Meeting?
- That's a good segue.
- It was a real question.
Oh yes. No.
- It was.
- You have to go through it.
- Yes. I'm-
- I know. I wish.
- I was one sided.
- I'm personally busy in two weeks,
but like a month from
now, four weeks from now.
When is that?
That's first week of December.
- December.
- So we'll say next year.
- Next year. How about that?
- Absolutely. Next year.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Let's get through the holidays.
- Although I already know I am traveling-
- January.
- January 7th,
two weeks in January,
starting January 7th.
So I would request that we do
either do like the last week
of January or start of
February or something.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be really exciting.
- I'm looking forward to it.
(participant speaking off mic)
- No.
Even more boring than that.
Quasi-judicial, public records.
- Ethics.
- Sunshine and all.
- All the good stuff.
All the good stuff.
- Yeah, I guess that's
one thing. So, okay.
I, once again, thank you so
much for the presentation
and I sort of agree with you.
Like I also really respect the experience
and everything that city
staff has and everything.
I also, you know, I wanna kind of try
to be an effective body,
and do our civic duty
and try everything we can
to make the city better.
One of the challenges
I feel on the board is,
yeah, a combination of,
maybe we get into it
things like Robert's rules
and the fact that planning
is a very big subject
and one that does require
a lot of expertise,
I think to know well.
As a Citizen Advisory Board,
I think it's easy to feel
swamped by all of that.
And the easiest thing to
just kind of like shut down
and not try to do a good
job of evaluating things
and asking questions and stuff like that.
And I guess I just also request
some understanding or some patience
as I personally or the board
generally tries to learn
and tries to, you know,
sort of learn on the job
and try to do what's best for the city.
- But again, that's where staff comes in.
I cannot stress enough
that I was responsible
for putting together a
planning and zoning board
from scratch from another city.
And it was contentious,
but I had the support
from the city manager
and we had to vet out whether
or not we wanted to do bylaws
or what have you, and
that was a steep learn.
Oh, one of the first times,
this is a reiteration
of the same PowerPoint
presentation that I had to do.
And that was difficult enough to do.
But I think again, it's
building that rapport.
One of the things was
building that rapport
with that planning and zoning board.
I understand again that there's questions
and different things, but
it's building that rapport
with your staff.
With the staff.
I sat down with literally.
And Mike does that too,
with the agenda review.
Like there's so much vetting leading up to
that city commission.
When these recommendations go
from PAB to city commission,
that, what you see for city commission
is reviewed by my boss,
the assistant director,
then Craig, then Mike,
and Olga, and the city clerk.
There are modifications, there
are changes that are made
before you even see
that published on that.
There's so much vetting.
I do not do this stuff in a vacuum.
There's so much checks and what you see
coming out with the
agenda and modifications
and things like that.
That it's just really
building that rapport
with the staff, again.
You have questions, but I
think that really helped
the different personalities on that board.
Oh God (laughs)
I don't wanna stereotype,
but I have just really,
I had to say, okay, you can't
say that during the meeting.
(Brenda laughing)
You can't do that.
And it's just going through,
like, you definitely cannot
say that during the meeting.
You definitely cannot say
that to me during the meeting,
and just be mindful and just
building that from scratch.
So I have been there and I've done that
and I can tell you is
to build that rapport
with your staff,
'cause that can go a long
way, a long way, ultimately.
That's what we're here for.
And again, just to reiterate too, as well,
we can meet with y'all individually.
- I guess with that,
I mean, we can get into
it with the legal thing,
but again, not an expert,
but my takeaway from
things like Sunshine Law
and the things there
is that the intention,
like the full intention of
those laws are, you know,
as a Citizen Advisory Board,
as a public committee,
all of the business that we do
and all of those discussions
are meant to be in the
public eye for review.
And so I guess like that's
part of it is it feels
a little weird for there
to be too much discussion
and too much kind of decision
making outside of this room.
You know, like what's the
point of the meetings, right?
What's the point of like, isn't that like,
I guess to me it seems like that,
isn't that what's supposed to happen here?
Those sort of discussions, right?
If we have questions,
is it just the right place to ask them?
- But those meetings with
staff are not decision making,
they're questions if you may.
- And I understand that
I guess,
it also feels like this should be like
a sort of safe space to
ask questions, right?
Is that?
- And I'm not advocating
or taking that away,
but again, it's that due process nature
that we try to make this, you know,
a bit timely for the applicants
and to vet out no differently
than city commission.
They have agenda review.
The commissioners actually,
Mike sits with the city
commission individually
to go over any questions or concerns
that they may have before the meeting.
- Those are public meetings?
- They're individual meetings
as individual commissioner
with the city manager.
No differently, again, for us
sitting with any individual
board members questions or concerns.
- Yeah, I guess he meets
with each one individually one at a time.
There's not, yeah.
- And it's no different.
Here again, it is just to again,
due process and not for long.
- We'll talk about this,
We'll talk about this in February.
- Yeah.
- But yes.
And you two, I saw you two talking.
No talking, okay.
Unless you're talking about
your dogs or kids or whatever.
No talking about officials, city business
or anything that could come before you.
- And so Yeah.
- Unless you say it on the record.
- So suggestions like that make it,
yeah, just trying to be open here, right?
Like one of my initial reactions to that
is to then shut down
and sort of be unwilling
to say anything, right?
Or ask anything.
And I guess,
I would rather feel, even
if I'm learning and stuff,
I wanna feel free to ask stupid questions.
My understanding is provided
I do it in the public forum,
that's totally cool, right?
- If you do it in a public forum,
or if you do it with a staff member.
- Individually.
As long as you don't talk to any
of your other board members.
- Yes, okay. And then-
- Regarding anything that
is pending before the board
or that foreseeably could
be pending before the board
or something that may
pertain to city business.
We'll get to this in February.
It's gonna be fun, you'll love it.
- And then I guess my comment
to the rest of the board then
is since this is one of the only places
we're allowed to talk to one another,
it feels like part of being
an effective Planning Advisory Board
and having a sense of
rapport is also for us
to kind of build a sense of
rapport with one another.
So, you know, we have a discussion
on our agenda each time,
and I think we could,
that it feels like that's
one of the only legal places
that we have in order for us
to talk about planning or
the comprehensive plan or.
- So do you think we should
bring sandwiches next time?
- I mean.
- I agree. That'd be awesome.
(participant speaking off mic)
- Yeah.
- I'm glad you brought
that up too as well.
So try to make those discussions general.
I think we kind of vet,
but just, because it's a learning here,
those discussions general and
not any previous agenda items,
because again, it's due
process or what have you,
but they're intended to be
just general discussions
and not about previous agenda items.
- But then if we were ever going
to discuss a previous agenda item,
isn't this the only place that we could?
(participant speaking off mic)
- Yes.
- I know.
And then what?
- No.
- There's no exceptions.
- I mean, if something has
already been decided, finalized,
then you could discuss it.
Anything that happens in this board,
aside from conditional use,
and true work of art
- That's administrative,
that's administrative.
- Other than that, I mean,
everything that is decided
here goes to city commission.
One City commission has
a final determination.
If you guys are hanging out
and you wanna talk about
it amongst yourselves
after the fact, I would
still recommend caution
because you never know if some aspect
of that is not going to come back to you,
it probably would not.
But.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Okay, so this is probably
the kind of comment
that you would rather I not make,
but I mean in the sense that like.
Okay, part of the difficulty
I have is, on the one hand,
it feels like a lot of the discussion
that we have about the
rules and the procedures
and the laws that were sort of governed by
feels very consequential, right?
I mean, I think, you know,
sunshine law is a big deal
and these things have
potentially big consequences.
The other end of the spectrum
as an advisory board,
the like actual agency,
and power that we have is very limited.
We actually don't get
to do much of anything
except make and give advice
to the city commission.
- That's true.
- Recommendations to the city commission.
So then part of me is, I guess I don't,
it feels like if we're
gonna be most effective
and make the most
effective recommendations,
I don't know, I guess I'd
like to not feel afraid
to talk about things.
I mean in the sense that,
I mean, we're in a public forum.
As long as we're in the public forum,
we're talking with one
another in the public forum.
I mean, the reality is no one listens
to any of these things anyway.
I feel like we can talk about things
and try to come to
what we think are
intelligent recommendations.
I mean.
- Yes.
With that said, this is the forum.
- Yeah. It has to happen in here, yeah.
- To have those conversations.
And at the end of the day,
it is a recommendation.
And as frustrating as that may be,
or as extensive and as
thoughtful as the process may be
for each board member,
at the end, it is just a
recommendation, period.
So it's a yay or nay, and.
- With your example that you're using,
you made a decision last planning board,
and now you wanna come back to
it on another planning board.
That applicant that got
their decision made,
when they had it first,
they now expect legally
this is what we're doing.
So when you have a conversation
about it in another meeting,
that then leaves that applicant
outta that conversation,
and that could open us up to legal issues.
- But there, I think there's
a strong distinction, right?
Between a conversation
like, I totally understand
that if we were going to
invoke Robert's rules of order,
there's specific procedures
to try to revisit
an old motion and re rule on it.
Even if that constituted an
official re recommendation
of an old business item.
And I'm not suggesting that,
and I understand that
that would definitely
then trigger reporting requirements
and participation from the applicants.
But now as an advisory
board, as any living entity,
if you're going to get better
and learn from experience,
part of that is feedback.
And it feels like,
I guess I don't understand the danger
if we in trying to learn or trying to read
or trying to talk about
something, if afterwards we say,
"Oh, you know, a year ago we talked about
this kind of thing."
And you know, if we asked a
clarifying question of staff
or if we talked about what we thought
that meant or something,
we're not making an
official recommendation
that doesn't feel like it's legally bind,
the issue has already been settled.
- So what you're saying is,
can you bring up old stuff,
even though you're not
going to advise on that,
because the issue is
already done resolved?
Can you talk about it again?
- Just so a specific example.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- Of course.
This is the forum.
This is the only forum, period.
- Perfect.
And then okay, that's great.
That sounds very clarifying.
I guess, but I also don't
mean to beat a dead horse,
but I guess I feel like
the implication I was reading is,
maybe I did a bad job of expressing myself
or communicating that idea,
I think you did a great job.
But then the impression I get
is when that's immediately followed up
by like a careful like,
oh, but if you do this,
it might mean this,
if this, it might have legal
implications or whatever.
I interpret that as,
no, actually you really shouldn't.
And then I'm not, you
know, and that's the.
- This is a safe space, right?
This is the only safe space.
- Good.
- Do not talk about
official public business
outside of this forum.
- Understood.
- If you wanna talk about things
that have happened in the
past, that might come back,
and even if they don't,
there's always potential.
This is the forum.
- Perfect.
- And let's just be gentle.
Let's not abuse this forum, that's all.
- And just as Steph, 'cause
you asked our perspective.
Two things.
One, trust.
I understand that you are
learning, and we're learning.
We are all learning every single day.
Trust us, please.
We are here to help our community,
that's why I have my profession.
And when I have somebody
who doesn't trust me in doing my job,
that creates hostility.
Trust us.
And we trust you.
You have never asked a stupid question,
you have never asked anything.
All the questions that you
have ever asked make sense.
Please just trust us.
'Cause we wanna make sure
that we're doing best for the community.
You wanna do what's
best for the community.
You have a different perspective,
which has made us think of
our projects in other ways.
It's been great, but
there has to be a trust,
and sometimes it feels like there's not.
And then my second part,
and I think we kinda learned this today,
but I just, the comprehensive plan
is this beautiful aspiration
that we are going for.
I think what would help is the LDC
is what gives us the
teeth to then do that.
The LDC is what we actually look at,
and it solidifies code-wise,
this is what you do.
Here's your setbacks, here's this.
Comprehensive plan is this
beautiful image of what we want,
the LDC is how we get there.
So honestly, I would say look at the LDCA
a lot more than you are looking
at the comprehensive plan.
And to be honest,
with the questions that you
ask and how you ask them,
you are a brilliant person.
You're gonna read that LDC,
and it's gonna start
to make sense for you.
And the questions that I think
you have the confusion on,
it's gonna clarify it for you.
So less of comprehensive, more on the LDC.
And those are just my, thank you.
- Yeah.
So, I really appreciate that. Thank you.
And yeah, I also like, yeah,
to get it out there
like reciprocal, right?
Like I really do trust your
guys' experience and everything.
I also, you know, try to do a good job
and read things independently,
and ask questions if
they don't make sense.
And I don't want those
questions to come across,
even if I do a really
bad job of asking them
as adversarial or distrustful,
like I legitimately don't know the answers
and trying to figure it out.
And I appreciate patience as I do that.
So thank you.
- So everybody loves everybody.
- Perfect.
- God bless America.
And do we have a motion to adjourn?
- I will make a motion to adjourn.
- Second.
- I mean, so adjourned.
So I made the motion.
This is not germane,
but now that we made the motion,
we can discuss the motion
in reading Robert's rules of order.
They have a special section for how to do,
we don't have to approve
it, but go for it.
Let's vote.
All those in favor say aye.
- Aye.
- All those opposed.
- All right. Hearing
none, the ayes have it,
We are adjourned.
- It doesn't require approval for boards.
Are we gonna meet through December?
- So now we're closed for business.
- Are we gonna be doing
anything in December?
- Oh, we talking about dock?
- No, no, I meant like a
party. I meant like a party.