- Sorry.
Can you hear me now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Good evening, everyone,
we're gonna call the meeting to order.
If I could ask everyone to
silence their cell phones,
and we're gonna have a moment of silence
and say the Pledge of Allegiance.
You still can't hear me? It's on.
Closer?
Better? There you go.
All right.
You hear me?
One, two. One, two.
Better?
All right. Awesome.
Okay, now we're gonna
call meeting to order.
Good evening, everyone,
please silence any mobile devices,
and we will stand for
the Pledge of Allegiance
and a moment of silence.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America,
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- Item three minutes.
Do we have a motion to approve
the May 15th Planning Advisory
Board meeting minutes?
Motion to approve. Second?
- Second.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- Having heard none,
the motion is approved.
Approval...
I'm sorry, 3B, approval of July 17th
Planning Advisory Board meeting minutes.
Motion to approve?
- So, I guess I'd like to
make a motion to amend,
just a slight one.
- Okay.
- At the end of the minutes,
it says board member Aleni stated
to have the comprehensive
plan fully be accessible
in the city of Kissimmee's website.
I'd like to replace stated with requested,
I feel like it's just a,
you know, like,
you know, type thing.
- Okay.
- So we'll do a motion with the amendment.
Okay. All right.
Motion to approve the, the May,
I'm sorry, the July 17th.
Planning Advisory Board minutes
with the approval of the amendment.
- I mean, I guess I'll,
yeah, I'm not sure.
Should we make the motion to amend?
Approve the motion to amend,
and then make the motion to,
or do you wanna roll them into one, or?
- We can roll them into one, correct?
And we should amend them first.
- Yes.
- Okay. First motion to
amend, then motion to approve.
Okay.
Motion to amend the July 17th
2024 Planning Advisory Board minutes.
- So, I believe I'm making that motion.
- We have a motion. Second?
- There you go. Okay.
- Second?
Okay.
All in favor?
- Aye.
- All right, having heard
none, it's approved.
Now, motion to approve,
with the amendments,
the July 17th 2024
Planning Advisory minutes.
- So, I will make a motion to
approve with the amendment.
- Seconded?
- Second.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- Having heard none. Motion passes.
Item O, business note, there's none,
and under new business, 5A.
Good evening, this is,
can you all hear me?
Can you all hear me?
- I don't know about that there.
- All right. I'm gonna try my
best to project a bit better.
- That is better.
- Okay.
This is a conditional lease
with site plan waiver approval,
from the property at 1504 Patrick Street,
to establish a childcare facility.
The existing improvements include
a 3,200 square foot building
that was previously approved as a church
via previous condition use approval
by the Planning Advisory Board in 1997.
In addition to that,
there were a buffer waiver
that was granted by the city commission,
that granted a buffer waiver
on the southern eastern
portion of the property.
The southern property
has a retention pond.
- There's the aerial map.
- The southern portion of the property
has a retention pond that
provided a natural buffer,
and on the eastern side,
there was an existing fence.
The current property owner
has recently installed a fence
on the western portion,
or on the left-hand side
where the open city ditch is.
In preparation for a childcare facility,
there's a fence that has been
established on the west side
as a barrier for the open ditch.
The proposed conditional use
is intended to accommodate
for the existing parking spaces,
which is 20 parking spaces,
can accommodate a maximum of 100 students,
but the property owner
is proposing a maximum
of 75 students.
So the existing
improvements can accommodate
the childcare facility without
any additional changes,
or construction, or what have
you, to the existing parcel.
Hence this is why staff is
supporting a site plan waiver,
because the improvements
are gonna be confined
to the inside of the building,
and there's an adequate amount of parking
to support the childcare facility,
and there's no additional
buffers that's required.
There was a land use
amendment and rezoning
that was approved, actually last night,
so part of the submittal
and the supplemental
information that you have
after the publication
of this planning advisory board meeting
is the City Commission action
confirming that that land use amendment
LUPA 24-002 and ZMA 24-001
was approved at last night's
City Commission meeting,
so I'm just providing you proof
of that city commission action,
and that we can move forward
with the approval of
this childcare facility.
It's compatible within
the surrounding area,
and it is needed,
and it's encouraged and
supported by city staff.
At this point in time, staff
is recommending approval
subject to the conditions
that are listed within the staff report.
And I'm here to answer any questions,
we also have the property owner as well
that can answer any
questions that you may have.
- Okay.
Does the board have any
questions before we?
- No.
- Would anyone from the
audience like to speak on this?
- I do. Yeah.
What's the traffic level for
that street at that area?
- So when the church was
approved back in 1997,
Patrick Street was considered
an arterial collector.
Since then, that
classification has changed
to what we call a local street.
So, right now, there is adequate capacity,
because it's no longer
seen as a major roadway.
So as of right now, there
is adequate capacity
to support this childcare facility,
because it has been, again,
it was no longer deemed as a major,
what we call arterial collector roadway,
even the changes reflected in the FDOT,
there's a doing the analysis for this,
that it's been changed as of,
I think even back as 2017,
they changed the
classification on that roadway
to a local street.
- Okay. Yeah, because I
know that's a tight street,
and if you get traffic backed up on it,
that's gonna stop a lot of
traffic from going east to west.
My concern is,
is there any cars gonna
be parked on the street
waiting to pick up their kids?
- No, and that's why I'm
gonna bring your attention
to condition number four
that staff included,
that all drop off and pick up
within the drive aisles is prohibited.
So everyone has to park in a parking space
in order to do drop off and pick up.
The parking requirements,
we have different parking
requirements for childcare
that have designated
pickup areas, there is not.
So this is why we actually stated
that all drop off and pickup
has to happen in a parking space.
And the maximum capacity
is also limited to,
again, it's 100, but
they are proposing 75.
- The capacity is 100?
- Well, the parking spaces,
the existing 20 parking
spaces has the ability
to support 100, but they're
proposing less than that,
at 75 students.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Any further comments or questions?
At this time, I'll remind the board
that if you have any
particular communication
you would've signed from
the vote at this time,
and since having heard none of that,
is there a motion to approve?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- Second.
- Okay. Public comment?
- Yeah, I did. Yeah.
- Oh, did you?
All in favor?
- Aye.
- Having heard none,
the motion approves 5B.
- Good evening.
For those who didn't meet
me at the last PAB meeting,
my name is John Raven,
I'm our newest senior planner
here at the city of Kissimmee.
And what I have tonight for you
is a conditional use with site plan waiver
to establish a retail sales
use at 1220 Dyer Boulevard.
Now, this site as part of the
Kissimmee Industrial Park PUD,
and the specific allowed uses in the PUD
do include wholesale use,
which is one of the proposed
uses by the applicant,
but the applicant's also
seeking a retail sale,
direct retail sales, for
HVAC parts and equipment.
So, it's gonna be wholesale
as well as direct retail.
And while wholesale is covered,
Section 27 does allow for this
board to define other uses
to include any uses that are compatible
with the allowed uses under the PUD.
And at this time, the staff
is recommending approval
with conditions which are
outlined in the report.
- Any questions from the board?
- Yeah so, I asked Brenda ahead of time,
but this parcel is part of
one of the previous
actions this board took
to set the future land use,
change the future land use designation
from part of the Vine Street CRA area
to industrial business.
I guess I'm a little confused
how that interacts with this action,
or whether it has any interaction.
- It wouldn't have any effect on it.
The future land use and
the current allowed use
is different because the PUD determines
what the current use is.
- Right.
I guess part of why I was
just a little confused is,
yeah, in the clarification,
it was emphasized
that the existing Kissimmee
executive PUD zoning district,
which it is a part of, does
permit sort of warehousing,
but in our previous item before,
the justification we
were given by the city
for changing the future
land use designation
was because of warehousing.
I know that there were other parcels
as part of the action that
we took in the last meeting,
but I guess I just...
Okay, maybe a specific question I have is,
now that we've changed the future land use
to industrial business,
is the Kissimmee executive
PUD zoning designation
consistent within that industrial business
future land use designation,
or are we going to need a zoning amendment
in the near future?
- I don't believe that'll be necessary.
- Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
- Any public comment on this item?
Motion to approve item 5B.
- I guess, can we make a motion to approve
with the conditions outlined?
Is that?
I'll make a motion to approve
with the conditions outlined by the city.
- Thank you.
Second.
All in favor?
- Aye.
- Having heard no opposed,
we move on to item 5C.
- This is an approval,
this is a recommendation of approval
to vacate a portion of right of way
that's known as McLaren Avenue.
The portion that is being
under consideration,
that's gonna be in the red area
that's highlighted on the aerial map.
This portion of McLaren Avenue
was established by a final plat
that was courted on September 1st, 1886.
Within your supporting documentation,
I included a copy of that original plat,
and highlighted, in yellow,
that was highlighted,
what portion today that we are considering
to vacate here for that right of way.
It's about 63 feet
wide, and 122 feet long.
The right of way is
between the two parcels
that you see there to the
north at 504 Randolph,
and then there's another
separate parcel to the south
between where Clay Street bends,
there's a separate parcel there.
Both parcels have different,
there we go,
so this is based on
the recorded 1886 plat.
On the upper left-hand
side, highlighted in yellow,
is a portion that we are considering.
If you take this into consideration,
and then you look at the aerial map,
the majority of McLaren,
which runs east to west,
has been developed,
and essentially has been
already vacated already.
So this is a remaining
segment or portion of McLaren
that you see here
that the city is requesting to be vacated.
This section of McLaren
does not provide any
vehicular or pedestrian
types of opportunities.
It does not provide any additional access
to any other parcels.
To the left, immediate left, or the west,
is where the John Young Parkway bridge
starts to ascend.
There is a steep embankment,
if you scroll down a little bit,
you've got some pictures, keep scrolling.
There are some pictures indicating, here,
the right of way.
And in the background, you
see where the embankment
of where John Young
Parkway starts to go up.
So, with that steep incline,
there really isn't any
opportunity at this point,
because of their safety concerns too,
if we were ever to do something like that
with the steep incline,
to have any type of east-west connection,
whether it be vehicular,
or pedestrian, or bicycle.
So, at this point,
with the status of the majority
of the roadway to the right
be vacated, and with
the physical impediment,
with the steep incline,
staff is recommending to vacate
this portion of right of way.
And just for laymen,
when we say vacate the right of way,
that means that this is a paper road,
this has not been opened.
It's what? Doing the math, 138 years,
since the plot's been recorded.
So when we vacate that right of way,
that means that it gets split
between the property owners to the north
and the property owner to the south.
It becomes split between,
it vacates the satis of a right of way,
and then it becomes part of the property
to the north and the south,
it's split equally.
So, what we are requesting,
because of the maintenance,
as you can clearly see,
the property owners have
probably been maintaining this,
and even the previous property owners
have been maintaining
this for quite some time.
So, with that, we are
recommending approval.
I do want to point out before then,
I was able to get some clarification
regarding your questions
about resurfacing,
and we were able to
find on the resurfacing,
bear with me here,
that it was done, I believe back in 2013,
there was a contract for resurfacing,
a contract for resurfacing for it
that we were able to to figure out
on Clay Street and Randolph.
And then the width,
I think I included on
the response about the,
we were able to do a GIS approximation
of the width using a GIS approximation.
But any other questions
or concerns at this time?
We're requesting approval
subject to easements,
because, within your
supporting documentation,
there are some utilities
that were identified
by Toho Water Authority.
Those easements will
provide Toho Water Authority
and the utilities
to maintain the ability to go in there,
and to maintain the underground
utilities that are there.
But it's just for that,
it's just to maintain
those types of easements,
no differently than you have,
most properties have utility
easements or what have you,
for the abilities for
those utility companies
to come in and to maintain
those types of infrastructure.
- So, you said it gets
split between the two owners
that are currently there?
- Yes.
- And they're aware? They know that?
That's already been
discussed with them and-
- Part of the city initiation with us
is with the property owners
initially coming to the city with that.
- Okay.
- Because again, it's 138 years.
And you can see from the photography
that it's been maintained,
and it's not been by the city.
- They're both owner-occupied,
both properties,
that we know of?
- Well, one property, as
you can see here, is vacant,
so, where the tree is there to Clay,
that is another property
owner to the south,
and then to the north is
going to be the VFW on that.
- Any additional questions from the board?
- Yes so, I guess first to declare,
yes, before this meeting I emailed Brenda
for some clarifying questions,
and then also I did a
site visit yesterday,
I biked out to the plot
to get a sense of what it was like,
and how it connected to the many things.
And then in terms of independent research,
when I was there I took a speed gun,
and I measured speeds of
some cars on Clay Street.
And I also took a second,
or took a closer look at
our comprehensive plan,
and any sections that I
think might be relevant
and pertinent for this issue.
So, in all of that, I
do have some concerns.
So, in the sense that I understand
what the city is saying,
this is part of a very old right of way
for what was originally a
planned east-west street
that is no longer, you know, viable,
especially given the grade to John Young.
But then part of what causes me concern
is specifically in the comprehensive plan,
one of our objectives,
let's see if I can get it here,
namely objective 2.2.4,
which tries to ensure that this board
makes sure that we
preserve the right of way
to implement a multimodal
network throughout the city.
And specifically in policy 2.2.4.5
encourages us to prioritize,
or sorry, 2.2.4.6,
encourages us to ensure
that we can fill in gaps
to the pedestrian and
bicycle ways in the city.
Now, one thing I noticed
about the proposal
for this agenda item
is that it wasn't mentioned,
and one thing I noticed
when I visited the site
is that there's also a sidewalk
that terminates right at the
north boundary of this parcel.
So there's an incomplete sidewalk
on the south end of Randolph Avenue.
This is, I think, not great.
And then Clay Street itself
also is sort of lacking any pedestrian
or bicycle infrastructure.
Honestly, this is like one of the only,
you know, I don't want to
cross John Young on my bike,
and so I usually go down Clay Street,
but that's kind of scary,
because regularly, you
know, I was sitting there,
I had my speed gun,
and I was measuring cars
at the 15 mile an hour posted speed bump
and they go 50 miles an hour regularly.
So, it's a kind of dangerous place to go.
Now, looking at the
city's comprehensive plan,
in Figure 2.13, the city
outlines the goals that it has
in 2040 for building out
some of our pedestrian
and bike infrastructure.
And there's specifically
like a pixel on the plot
that seems to designate,
it's one of the only
ones in the plan for 2040
for additional sidewalks,
that seems to be located
exactly on this plot.
So one of the things,
I guess the first thing,
how would the city's dedication
in the comprehensive plan
to complete the missing
sidewalk on this plot
be affected by vacating
the total right of way?
Maybe that's the first thing to ask.
- Well, in response, it would not.
Because it's vacated
does not mean there's
not a future opportunity
to construct a sidewalk.
- Does it make it more difficult?
- Yes and no.
Because if it's within
a capital improvement,
or if it's within a
city priority to do so,
there are mechanisms in
place for a public benefit,
where we can go through a process
where we can acquire additional runway,
or different additional dedication
if we need to accommodate that.
And typically, there's a certain priority,
certain order of things,
where we can acquire that
additional right of way.
- So if I'm hearing you correctly,
it's not as if vacating
the total right of way
would preclude future
build out of the sidewalk,
but am I correct in interpreting
that it would create additional
hurdles down the line?
There would be things
that would have to be done
in order to enable that to happen.
- Right, it may,
but no differently right now
within our form base code,
we have a streetscape zone requirement,
and part of it,
which will require part of the sidewalks
will meander between the
existing right of way
and private property too as well.
And with the portion
that within those areas,
we go through an easement
process, what have you.
So, it could become difficult,
but then it could not too,
so this vacation does not
say that we can never, ever
have an opportunity to include
or incorporate sidewalks,
not only just along this segment,
but the remaining segment
of Clay Street that's here.
There's the process of
dedicating right of way.
We do community outreach.
In some cases, the property
may come in for redevelopment,
and in that time,
there may be an opportunity
for us to require,
and that is a land
development code requirement,
that when they propose development,
then we do require in
front of their property,
they have to provide and
construct the sidewalk.
- And so am I right in
interpreting that, currently,
because it is part of
the city's right of way,
if a sidewalk was gonna be built
to complete the network on this parcel,
that would be the city's responsibility?
And but if the runway's vacated,
and a future developer wanted
to develop on this site,
the other requirements of the MU PUD,
or sorry, the MMTD, the Mixed
Multimodal Transit District,
would require that those future developers
put in a sidewalk or something?
- The land development code
will require the developer
to put in the sidewalk.
- Yeah, I guess part of
what makes me uncomfortable
is it feels a little bit like
the city vacating its
sort of responsibility
to complete the sidewalk,
you know, in this area,
in the hopes that a
future developer would.
But that's sort of what gives me pause.
I mean, would the city be interested in
maybe not vacating the
entire right of way,
but retaining, you know,
a strip adjacent to the
road, much like other roads?
- Right now, it doesn't have...
Right now, both 504 Randolph
and that property to the south
has direct access off of Randolph,
so it wouldn't suit to where
any type access at this point
for both of those properties,
to even retain any portion of it.
Both properties have access to it,
and we've mentioned, as far as pedestrian,
with John Young Parkway and that bridge,
at this point, what we're saying is that,
there's really no reason to retain,
other than the utilities,
the existing utilities that are there,
'cause we need to continue to protect
those existing utilities within that area.
- Yeah, I guess I mean,
I can understand that, yeah,
the property of 504 and 515
do have a sidewalk connecting them north.
But if anybody's interested
in going, you know,
east to west across the city,
who doesn't wanna cross John Young,
you do have, the sidewalk
runs out at that point,
and you have to walk on
grass to Clay Street,
and then down Clay Street to
kind of cross under the bridge,
which doesn't feel safe.
Yeah so,
I guess, are the city's interests
in vacating the right of way primarily
because the city doesn't see
any utility in maintaining it?
I mean, I guess,
in the justification that
was given in the agenda item,
it seems like the city
was primarily thinking
only in terms of connecting
a road to John Young,
which I admit, given the
grade, is an impossibility.
But was the city considering
the impact that it would have
on completing the
pedestrian or multimodal,
you know, network in the area?
- Hi, Craig Holland,
Development Services Director.
I am technically the
applicant for this project.
It's a city initiated
right of way vacation.
So, how this came about is,
the VFW leadership came to the city,
the city manager's office,
requesting the right of way be vacated
so they could do an
additional parking lot.
So, and they asked that the city do it
mainly because of the expertise
of a right of way vacation
could be a little complex
for just an average property owner.
So, knowing that there was really no way
to utilize that right of way
for access onto John Young,
or to carry a road there,
and then also keeping
in mind the vacation,
if you look at the map,
this one here,
the right of way is vacated flush
with the Randolph right of way,
so any sidewalk on Randolph
would be within the Randolph right of way,
and not the right of way
that's being vacated.
So, the intent was not to,
you know, get away from our responsibility
to put in sidewalks.
And as part of the vacation,
you could make a
recommendation to public works
through staff that they
look at adding a sidewalk
on Randolph from Pennfield down to Clay,
and that can be worked into their budget,
'cause they do have a
budget for new sidewalks,
especially in the older part of town.
I hope that answered your question.
- I mean, yeah, I guess so.
I mean, when I was visiting
trying to look at the maps,
I guess it wasn't clear to me,
and the indication seems to be that, yeah,
it runs right up,
like on the satellite map
in the previous picture,
I think you can see that the sidewalk
just north of the parcel
seems to be in the same area
that was designated as
part of the new vacation.
So, I guess like, just overall,
like part of what concerns me is,
I can understand, and I
appreciate, and I agree
that this right of way no longer has
what was the original intended utility
of having a road east-west
that could connect to
or through John Young.
I guess what's still concerning me
is it feels like the city
keeps only seeing the potential
use of this right of way
for an east-west road to allow cars
to connect to John Young,
meanwhile, in the comprehensive plan,
which we have the duty
of trying to guide decisions based on,
there was specifically an
indication and a promise
to kind of complete the
sidewalk network here,
I think in concert with
what is proposed multi-use
path along Clay Street
that would better enhance
pedestrian mobility in the city.
And I guess my concern
would be that this vacation
is just creating like,
especially a vacation
of the entire parcel,
is creating like more
legal work down the ways
if we were going to,
you know if the city was gonna
keep true on those promises.
So.
- I mean, you could recommend approval
with a condition that the
easterly line move back 10 feet
to accommodate a future
multi-use path, or 15 feet,
and then, you know, if the VFW,
or the other property owner
felt that wasn't fair,
they could then speak at commission
when the commission
makes the final decision.
So, there's several different
ways to approach this
if you're looking for flexibility
on making sure a sidewalk
or multi-use path
goes down Randolph and
hooks into Clay Street, so.
And I know, right now,
the city is working on the
master bike and pedestrian plan
to incorporate that into the comp plan,
and this is one of the
things they look at,
is where there's missing segments
for the transportation network,
specifically bike and pedestrian, so.
But if that would push you at ease,
move that easterly line
back 10 or 15 feet,
probably wouldn't impact the
future use of the property
when it goes to either one.
- Okay.
- You said it wouldn't
affect them, so they'd,
Craig, did you say they'd still,
would that affect their
ability to do the parking?
- I think he said it
didn't think it would.
- He didn't.
I just wanted to know if that would,
the VFW, I wanted to make sure that-
- I believe the VFW is
looking for parking.
- Would that amendment
affect their parking?
- It has not been laid
out, so it's hard to say.
I mean, it shouldn't.
- Okay.
- And the other property, frankly,
it's like 1/10th of an acre,
to get anything on there
is gonna be really hard
even when you add another 25 feet,
'cause it's a tiny piece of property.
But it's possible it would
help them develop that
into a small single family
home, or something like that.
But it shouldn't, 10 or 15 feet,
should not impact either
property dramatically.
- Any other question?
- And I also wanna point out
the other thing to consider,
is that you can also
do it via an easement,
instead of excluding the 10 or 15 feet,
it can also be an easement.
- Okay, you had a question?
- Yeah.
We still maintain the
rights for an easement
on anything that needs to
be done to the property.
Electrical, water.
- That's right, yes, so,
right now, with the analysis,
it was identified that there
were underground utilities
that were identified,
so there have to be utility easements
to retain the existing utilities.
- So, basically, we still
have some control over
what goes under the
ground and how they do it.
- Yes.
But keep in mind,
it's for the maintenance
of those utilities.
- Yes. Okay.
- And it's not an overall general
type of, you know, public.
So, these easements are
gonna be very specific
as to what is being granted or laid over
this private property,
how, you know, what it's for,
what it's going to maintain.
So I just wanted to clarify,
just because it's an easement
doesn't necessarily mean
that it's all-out public.
So it's for specific utilities
for a specific reason,
and it will spell out maintenance
types of responsibility.
So, the other option that you also,
instead of excluding the 10 and 15,
which was part of the conditions,
you can also state that you can have
a 10 to 15 foot easement
for a sidewalk too.
That's the other option.
- Are there any amendments to this?
Are there any amendments to it?
- Are there amendments?
- Yeah, and any conditions.
- The only condition right now
is that easements must remain
over the vacated portion of right of way,
and must be provided with a final plat,
or by a separate instrument.
There's different mechanisms,
different ways to establish easements,
so we provide that option.
- So, yeah, I guess,
I think it's up to us,
we can make amendments if we want,
we could try to propose, you know,
modifications to the existing thing.
I think that's up for
this body to discuss.
I think I would feel most comfortable
if the city did maintain
the full sort of
transportation right of way,
it feels like that would enable
the most use down the line.
But that could just be sort of,
I think 15 feet to play it safe,
and I think that...
So, I'm going to make a motion.
- Do we have to hear from,
I'm sorry, we have to
hear from the public.
- Okay.
- Any comments from the public?
- My name is Pat Fisher, I am
a representative of the VFW
in a role.
We have been cutting and
maintaining that property
for many years,
and just request the right of way be split
between the two properties,
from the north and to the south.
We understand there's
underground utilities
we're willing to maintain it,
if there's any trucks or
anything that needs to go on it,
they can go on it.
Thank you.
- Okay.
- I guess, while we have you, sir, sorry.
- Sir.
- Regarding the conversation
we were having about like,
a potential, you know, sidewalk there
to complete the sidewalk,
or to tie into some
potential multi-use path
on Clay Street or something,
do you have or do you, do
you feel as though the VFW
has a strong opinion on whether there's a,
you know, 10 or a 15 foot?
- Whatever the city wants
to do, we're all for it.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- To the board now?
- I'm sorry? I think you were about to-
- Yes, I make a motion to approve it.
- Oh, well, I think...
- So, yeah, I think the procedure is,
first we should make a
motion to amend the motion
to add a condition that the city maintain,
you know, 15 feet of right
of way on the eastern part
of the parcel.
And I guess I will make that motion,
and then, you know,
we'll see if it gets
a second and approval.
- Okay.
So, the motion is to have the 15 feet,
did you say the easement,
or are you looking at the-
- I mean the...
How about, okay, I would
like to ask the city attorney
whether she sees that
there's a strong distinction
between those before we-
- I'm sorry.
And then we also have that motion made,
so I think we need to
clarify the whole thing,
because he did say that.
Okay.
- I think from a procedural perspective,
Mr. Rodney started trying
to raise his motion first.
- Okay.
I just wanna be sure.
- So, with all due respect,
let's work through this,
and then we can get to the second motion.
So, in answering to your question,
I think what you are trying to seek is,
you know, retention of 10 or 15 feet,
you gotta put that in
your motion specifically,
on the north and south side,
retaining for the city,
just not retaining that,
as opposed to vacating that whole portion,
I think is what you're asking.
- Yeah, I was imagining, let's say,
15 feet of the eastern most thing,
to not vacate the 15 feet
of what the proposed vacation is
on the eastern side of the thing.
- Right.
- I guess my question for you is,
is there a big distinction between,
or do you feel like...
What's the difference between doing that,
making that motion,
and retaining 15 feet of right of way
on the eastern part of the thing,
versus adding a condition
that we specifically
have a sidewalk easement
on the east part of the
property or something?
Is that?
- I mean, if what you're
actually trying to do
is create sidewalks, then
I don't see a distinction.
But if you're trying to
retain that right of way
for something else,
which might be a bike path,
or something less specific
than a sidewalk then-
- Okay.
Okay.
Sorry to jump around procedurally,
but I think even with
regards to a main motion,
motions to amend take precedence,
and so I'm going to make a motion
to amend the current motion.
The amendment will be, specifically,
to retain 15 feet on the
eastern edge of the parcel.
So, to amend the vacation,
to remove the easternmost 15-foot strip
adjacent to Randolph Avenue.
- So, here's what I'm hearing.
We would retain the 15,
but then that takes us back to the place
where the VFW is maintaining property,
and that belongs to the city,
or the city has to come out
at the cost of doing that.
If I heard correctly, Craig,
you said that we can
just ask for a sidewalk
if that's what the issue is,
that we need a sidewalk there.
- You can make that
part of the motion too,
you know, say that the
Planning Advisory Board
is recommending the city
installs a sidewalk,
and the planners will pass that on
to Public Works and Engineering.
- Okay.
I just, to your point, I think,
you know, what you're saying is valid,
but I think if we're going to say
that we need 15 feet for a sidewalk,
we might as well go ahead and recommend
that a sidewalk be put in.
- Yeah, I'm fine with that,
to retain the right of way,
and also make a recommendation
that the city, you know,
looks into how to specifically
make do on the promise
in the comprehensive plan
to complete the sidewalk in this parcel.
- Okay.
- How about that?
- Can we now vote on that,
or does anything need
to be clarified further?
That's good? Okay.
So, do we have a second,
to retain the 15 feet on the
eastern side, if I'm correct?
And recommend that a
sidewalk be placed in,
that's the motion.
Do we have a second?
Can I?
I'll second it. (chuckles)
- Okay.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- One opposed? Okay.
Motion carries three to one.
Item 5D.
- Well, so again,
I think, procedurally, that
was the motion to amend,
now that we've amended the motion,
I think we still have to make,
we have to pass the motion
itself, if I'm not mistaken.
- Do we have to go back and pass it,
or was it passed with the-
- There was a motion made,
seconded, three to one.
- Okay. Yes.
- But was that a motion specifically
to amend the main motion,
or was that a motion to
adopt the main motion
with the amendment.
- Okay, she seconded amending the motion
to include the language around
15 feet and the sidewalk,
that was seconded, and that was three one.
- I understand.
- You got the whole thing. We're good.
- Thank you.
- All right, item 5D.
Okay, item 5D is a
recommendation of approval
of a resolution to vacate a portion
of the Mill Slough right of way,
located on the south
side of Mill Slough Road,
in front of 1630 and
1700 Mill Slough Road.
This is also a city initiated
vacation abandonment request
of the portion, or the
vacated portion, here.
Includes right of way that's
in front of the property there
on the corner at 1630 Mill Slough Road
and Mill Creek Elementary School.
The areas have been privately maintained
by both property owners.
The width of the vacation, as
you can see on the red line,
it kind of meanders there,
it's not very square.
The reason why that it meanders
is that the vacation does not include
the existing sidewalks.
The right of way exhibit
that we're going to be looking at
shows the area in a
little bit more detail.
It's about approximately
1,300 linear feet.
This is only the portion
that's in front of the property
at 1630 Mill Slough Road.
And the other page, if we scroll down,
shows the extent that's in
front of Mill Creek Elementary.
Notice the meandering,
because what we are requesting
will keep the existing sidewalk
within the right of way that
will be maintained by the city.
The existing sidewalk is
outside the perimeter fence,
portion of the right of
way has the existing fence
of the elementary school
and the property owner.
There are no objections that were received
for the vacation abandonment
by any utility providers.
Again, what this vacation
abandonment will mean
is that the portion that's
highlighted in yellow
will be assumed or required by
the property owners in front.
So this portion that you see here,
it's in front of the elementary school,
so this portion here will
be to the elementary school.
The portion that's in front
of the property at 1630
will be assimilated or
acquired by the property owner
to the front.
I do have, as a supplemental,
that you have a printout,
was comments from the school district,
in which the staff also clarified,
there was a little bit of confusion
regarding whether or not
this right of way vacation
would include the sidewalks.
We affirmed that it does not
include the existing sidewalks.
The city will again include that sidewalk
as part of the right of way,
and the city will continue
to maintain the sidewalk.
At this point in time,
staff is recommending approval,
subject to, again, any
easements or any utilities
that they may retain
easements within that area.
I'm here to answer any
questions that you may have.
- So, I guess, once again
to start by declaring,
I reached out and asked Brenda
questions ahead of time,
I also made a site visit
to this location yesterday.
And in terms of independent research,
trying to look at the comprehensive plan
and see if things might align,
and took some speed measurements
of cars on the street.
One thing I noticed, again,
sort of absent in the presentation
from the city just now,
is that while it is clear in the proposal
that the vacation includes
just the parcel south of the
sidewalk where there is one,
what was neglected to be mentioned
is that in that right-most segment,
the kind of jog at the end of the thing,
there is no sidewalk currently,
which leaves the pedestrian
path to the school incomplete
for the adjacent development.
So I have a similar set of concerns
as in the previous agenda item,
in that it feels like the city
should have a duty from policy 2.2.4.6
in the comprehensive plan,
Pedestrian Bicycle Way Gap Infill,
to already has an obligation and a duty
to try to fill in that missing sidewalk,
and I'm concerned that the
vacation, as currently proposed,
would make that more difficult, not less.
- Okay.
So, I'm gonna point your attention
to the area that he is referring to,
it's gonna be on the right-hand side,
along the east portion here,
that there is a missing
segment between the driveway
that you see on the right-hand
side to the end here,
there's a missing segment.
Part of that, and you can barely see,
there's a small little circle.
Yep. Right there.
Which is a stormwater inlet.
So, part of the reason why that sidewalk
is not continued is because
there's that storm water inlet
that's protruding,
and that's preventing that connection now.
- I guess I'm surprised, you know,
going through it yesterday,
the ground was level,
it seemed like there was plenty of room
for a sidewalk to be completed there.
Yeah, it wasn't as if there was a gully,
you know, a culvert, or a gully,
or anything at that location, so.
I'm confused by that.
I guess, more broadly,
why is the city interested in
vacating this right of way?
What do you think the
benefit is to the city,
or how is it in keeping
with the comprehensive plan?
Normally, again, broadly,
in objective 2.2.4,
we are encouraged,
the comprehensive plan
sets a overall objective
for the preservation of right
of way throughout the city.
And then insomuch as the
land development code
has allowances otherwise,
those allowances are for places
in which vacation of the right of way
might contribute to infill development.
- Okay.
- For a strip like this,
it doesn't seem clear,
I mean, there's no hope
of any infill developments
that the city is trying to accomplish.
- So, really briefly, before
I turn it over to Craig,
those policies and our response
is for prioritized projects,
so I wanna clarify,
within the objectives,
and with the policies,
and that was the response to you
in reference to relation to
this vacation abandonment,
is that it's for prioritized projects.
And so, at this time, for this segment,
that it speaks to prioritized projects.
The purpose, what have you,
I'm gonna turn that over to
Craig to clarify to the board.
- Craig Holland, Development
Services Director,
again, I'm the applicant,
this is since this is the
city initiated abandonment.
So, how this came about is,
Judge Miller, who owns the property
at the southeast corner of
Mills Slough and Denn John,
he owns several properties there,
has been maintaining the property.
And if you look at this here,
his is in the yellow.
There we go.
So, his is in the yellow.
So he was asking,
he's been maintaining the property
from the intersection of
Mill Slough and Denn John,
all the way back to the
end of his property,
and he asked,
since he had been maintaining
it for a number of years,
many, many years,
and actually a fence had
been erected on city property
by Judge Miller,
that the city abandon that property,
and give it to him.
So, the city manager agreed.
As we got into the abandonment,
we realized that the school
district had property also
that goes from where
the yellow and blue B,
all the way over to where
that lift station is,
where the red dot is.
So, the right of way
from Mill Slough there
is exceptionally wide.
And Mill Slough is not going to be widened
for any additional lanes
or anything like that,
it's already a very wide right of way,
the lanes are very wide.
So, the city abandoning this property
would not impact Mills
Slough, the sidewalks,
or anything like that, Mill
Slough Road or the sidewalks.
So, that's the reasoning behind it,
is basically, we have two property owners
that have been maintaining the property
for a very lengthy time.
And again, with the issue with
the sidewalk not connecting,
as you go to the east side,
you could make that a recommendation,
that the city go in, and you know,
connect the sidewalk to further down road,
where there's a sidewalk on Mill Slough,
closer to Quail Hollow.
I'm surprised it hasn't come up,
because that's the main entrance for,
what's the name of the school on the plat?
Mill Creek Elementary is off Mill Slough,
I'm surprised it hasn't come up
that the kids are not able to connect
with the sidewalk there already,
which usually the school
district's pretty good
about mentioning stuff like that to us.
- But I guess I'll point out,
both in the agenda
document that I received,
Ryan had a comment in
his engineering thing
that pointed out the lack of a sidewalk
on the right side of the property,
and in the email that we just received
from the school district,
it seems like they are
showing a, you know, concern,
is the intention to
approve the abandonment
and retain an easement for a sidewalk.
If yes, then students have a
clear path to walk to school,
we should not have any
additional comments.
So, it seems like they are concerned
about ensuring that we complete the thing.
I mean, again, having walked there,
there's kind of a clear gap,
I saw several people cross
illegally across the street,
because there isn't a crosswalk.
There's only one in the
middle of that block,
there isn't one until
the next intersection,
there's sort of I think a very clear gap
in our pedestrian infrastructure there.
And I guess, again, I could
understand that the objective is
that the city has to
prioritize infill things,
but then as this board,
and our duty to enact and make sure
that decisions are in keeping
with the comprehensive plan,
I'm having difficulty seeing
how giving up this right of way
would help the city prioritize
any plan to fix the gap.
And then if we have an explicit objective
to preserve right of way,
I feel a duty to preserve right of way.
So, I'm having difficulty with this one.
- And I think, just again,
the right of way is
exceptionally wide here.
If you look at this map
here, they're showing,
for some reason that right
of way is very, very wide
in this section.
And that's probably just because
you have subdivisions to the north,
and then unplotted land to
the south is why it's so wide.
- And so one thing I want to
point out as a result of that,
in my site visit,
the western half of this block,
because the right of way is so wide,
there is a 25 or so foot gap
between the sidewalk and a
whole bunch of large oak trees
that separate the
sidewalk from the street.
And so I would let my 4-year-old
walk on that portion of the sidewalk,
I feel safe, even though
I was clocking cars
going down the marked 35
mile an hour street at 50,
the fact that there's large oak trees,
and the right of way was so wide,
enabled the city to build a sidewalk
that was well-separated from the road,
and had street trees in between,
such then I legitimately,
you know, feel safe,
and I don't feel scared for the kids
on the sort of right
half of this property.
Where the vacation here
widens, towards the right,
is where the sidewalk no
longer runs behind oak trees,
but runs in front of the oak
trees adjacent to the street,
and it feels a lot less safe
being four feet from
50 miles an hour cars.
So, that's also kind of
part of the concern I have,
is now if the city vacates
all of the right of way
beyond what is the current sidewalk,
I feel like the right half of this block
has a sidewalk that isn't
well-suited for the kids.
The right-most portion
has no sidewalk at all.
And how then are we to improve
the safety going forward?
Part of the opportunity
of the exceptionally wide right of way is,
if we aren't concerned
purely with car lanes,
but if we allow ourselves to
think about widening paths
for better bike
infrastructure or something,
it seems like it presents an opportunity
to ensure that the kids,
you know, middle schoolers,
could walk safely to school.
- Given that the sidewalk meanders
as you move east from Denn John,
I'm guessing the sidewalk
is placed to avoid the trees
and avoid the roots.
'Cause not only do you have the trunks,
but you have the root system,
and the minute you start putting sidewalks
over the large roots,
the sidewalks get popped
up as the roots grow.
I mean, if it would make
you more comfortable,
you could recommend approval
for the first portion on the west,
and not recommend approval
for the portion of the
school district side,
where there is room for improvements
for sidewalk and safety.
- Yeah, and I guess even with that,
I still have a little bit of difficulty
in the sense that we have
a very clear objective
to try to preserve the right of way
specifically to try to improve
the multimodal pedestrian
and bicycle infrastructure
in the city.
It seems like this would
be a perfect opportunity
to do that,
that that objective to
preserve the right of way,
it feels like insomuch as
there's another thing to consider
in the land development code,
there are sort of clear
justifications that are given
for when the city might consider
vacating a right of way,
and those are primarily focused on,
you know, the possibility
of infill development.
But that doesn't seem to
be a possibility here.
So, I guess, again,
like, you know, aside from the situation
where the current property owners
are kind of like mowing the grass,
I don't...
I have a hard time seeing a
justification for the vacation,
and it seems like such a vacation
would only make it harder to improve
on what's currently there.
That's sort of my piece.
- Just one comment.
If you put sidewalks in-
- Can you state your name
and address for the record?
- Pat Fisher.
My address is blocked.
If you put sidewalks in
on the north side of the Mill Slough,
where this gentleman's talking about,
then you're gonna have to
add an additional guard
going back and forth for the children
to go across the street,
where they already have one
at Denn John and Mill Slough.
- I guess, to clarify,
I do think there's a crosswalk missing?
But there's a segment of
sidewalk missing entirely
on the rightmost part of this thing,
where there isn't a cross-
- I know where you're talking about,
but I'm just saying,
in front of the school,
to that new sidewalk
that you're proposing,
you'll have to put another guard
to walk the children back and forth.
I'm just, just a comment.
- Thank you.
- Hi, my name is Elizabeth Robles,
I'm actually here
representing my grandfather,
Gabriel Santiago.
He actually owns the property
2418 Quail Hollow Court
that is attached to some of that area
that is being spoken of.
He purchased this property back in 2002.
That area where a lot of
sidewalk seems to be missing,
he's actually been
trying to take ownership
of that area of land.
So, I'm not sure how
we would go about that
in this proceeding,
just because when he had first realized
that this area was kind of
abandoned and not really,
you know, having much purpose,
he went ahead to the city,
and he tried to submit
the appropriate paperwork
to try and take ownership
of this piece of land.
And so we're here today
because he actually still wants
to be able to take ownership
of that section of land.
I have a satellite image
of it, if it's needed,
but pretty much, on my
phone, as you can see here,
this is his entire property.
And this whole area right behind
is pretty much the area that
we're speaking of today,
and he just wants to be able
to kind of essentially
add that to his property,
and be able to kind of
plant fruits, vegetables.
He's retired now, and
it's kind of his pastime,
so he'd be able to kind of take over
the maintenance of that property,
and just move that fence line backwards.
- Yeah.
- So, if you see the image
that they're displaying,
this is the exact area
that we're speaking of.
Where you see that fence line end
is actually where his property line ends.
Essentially what he would want to do
is just move that fence line backwards,
and take responsibility
for that area of land.
- Robles. R-O-B-L-E-S.
- Thank you for your comment.
- Thank you.
- Hello, my name is Alana Burkholder,
I live at 2479 Oak Mill
Drive here in Kissimmee,
and regarding the vacation,
I just want to know,
are any of the trees going to be cut,
or is the road going to be expanded?
I know that he said the road
was not going to be expanded.
I'm just concerned about the trees.
These trees are over 150
year old, I would assume.
- So, I think we could
ask the city attorney
for clarification, but yeah,
so my understanding is,
looking at the plan,
because on the right half of the property,
the vacation only goes up to the sidewalk,
and the trees are beyond that.
Those trees would remain
in the city right of way,
although I think you're
raising a legitimate question,
because the vacation includes
the land up to the sidewalk,
and on the right half of this block,
the sidewalk is beyond the trees,
presumably it would be up to
whoever the property is vacated to,
in this case, I think the middle school,
they could cut down those
trees if they wanted to, right?
It would be their jurisdiction
rather than the cities,
is that correct?
- Once vacated.
- Well, they would still
need to obtain a permit
from the city.
- But it would be, I mean
it becomes an ordinary,
you know, land tree removal
permit or something.
But they would own the tree at that point,
it wouldn't be the city, right?
- Right.
But, again, I wanna stress too,
that the option would be an easement.
You could do an easement, let me finish,
so, the other option
that I wanted to let
the board be aware of,
and to go back to the staff condition,
an easement would mean that the
vacation would move forward,
it would be private property,
but you can also request
that an easement be retained
on that property.
Now, that easement
would have to be set up,
again, there's different documents,
or there's different ways
to establish an easement,
but you could also do
an easement too as well.
And the easement can place
restrictions within that area
of what can and cannot occur.
For example, again, within
the form-based code area,
we do require easements be
placed on private property
to accommodate sidewalks along
the Vine Street corridor.
Those sidewalks too, when they expand,
portions will be in the right of way,
and portions of it is on private property.
So, I wanna also point out
that that would be the case.
And also, I wanna point
out in the background too,
of the stormwater inlet that's there,
we can include that condition,
but just know that we
would have to bring it back
if there's a condition to
construct that sidewalk,
it would still have to go back
to our Public Works Engineering department
to take a look at,
to make sure, if the
sidewalk is placed there,
that we can do that, and do
that accurately and correctly,
utilities, or what have you, to do so.
But is that your pleasure?
Is that the pleasure of the board?
But I wanted to bring
that to your attention
as some of the additional
options in this case.
- We have another comment.
- Hi, so my name's Melissa Menyel,
I live on Benjamin Drive.
So, I just have two concerns.
The first one is-
- Can you state your
name and address please?
- Melissa Menyel, I live
on 2422 Benjamin Drive.
So my first concern is,
I do agree that it would be
nice to have a sidewalk there,
I went to Mill Creek Elementary,
and so I would have to cross
where the crosswalk is currently at.
If there would be a sidewalk,
like if it would be extended,
and there would be a crosswalk there,
that would've made it more
convenient, at least for me.
So, that would be nice.
But if this just gonna stay in limbo,
'cause it hasn't been
done at all in this time,
I think it should just
go back to the people.
Because why just let it linger, right,
when they could be using it
for whatever they wanna use it for.
And then my second thing would be,
could the people who
take ownership of that,
could they just use
that land for whatever,
or is there any restrictions,
like what could be done?
Just, that's all I have.
- Thank you.
- Oh, go ahead.
- Oh, I was just thinking.
- So, yeah, do you want-
- Yes, please.
So, the property, the zoning,
so, the existing property
in whatever zone,
I believe it was RA1 for that
property, or on this portion.
So, whatever zoning
designation that that property,
adjacent property, would have,
it would determine exactly
what can be built on there.
For example, looks like a
portion of it, Oak Mill,
that's RA3,
so that portion would be
subject to RA3 zoning standards.
That would include setbacks,
that would include anything
for accessory structure.
So it'd be subject to
the zoning for setbacks,
for development, or what have you.
That's what would happen if
this vacation went through.
Same thing in the case of the CF,
which is Community Facilities,
that's gonna be the
boundary of the school.
So, the school would assume
that section if and when,
you know, they simply may maintain it,
but if they wanted to do anything else,
it would be subject
to the Community Facility zoning setbacks,
development standards,
the whole nine yards,
and also RA1 one for the property,
in front of the property
here, RA1 standards,
zoning setbacks standards, what have you.
- Okay.
So, I think, yeah, just
my sort of final thoughts.
Again, I have a really hard
time justifying this one.
We have a sort of explicit objective
in the comprehensive plan
that we have a duty to uphold
to preserve the right of way,
to ensure that the city can continue
to develop multimodal paths.
In this particular case,
it seems like there isn't any hope of,
or at least on most of the
parcel, infill development.
It feels like part of the reason
is the city has been sort of derelict
in its duty to maintain the property.
I think...
Or I think we should vote
to not approve this item,
but maybe send a recommendation
to the city commission that,
one, they ask the city
to look into completing the sidewalk,
more broadly, look into
opportunities the city has
to improve the sidewalk or
bicycle path on the street
to the middle school,
and potentially even add in a
suggestion that they consider,
you know, vacating a small parcel,
you know, like maybe
the final jog at the end
to an adjacent property owner,
if they can sort of
better take care of it.
So, I think that's kind of
where I'm at on this one, but.
- I just wanna clarify,
on the objectives, it's prioritized,
let me finish, please.
- Yep.
- It's prioritized projects,
these plans are planned
out to 2030 and 2040,
they are projected.
And so, as we move along, no
differently than the exercise
and the community exercise
that we're doing, Onward Kissimmee,
that those plans, those
exhibits are subject to change,
with additional analysis or what have you.
So, the city has to go through
a prioritization project,
but those specific
objectives are pertaining
to prioritized projects.
Some of those objectives also
pertain to new development,
as they move along for
a proposed development.
At this point in time,
there are not any proposed development.
But I just wanna be clear
that these are projections,
these are objectives,
and it's for prioritized projects.
- Is there a motion?
- There's not a motion.
- I make a motion to approve.
- As it is, approve?
- Yep.
- Oh, I'm sorry. We have another comment.
- Another comment? Okay.
Keep that in mind.
- Yes, we have a motion on the floor.
I didn't know if anybody
heard the motion that was.
Yeah. Okay.
- He made a motion to-
- My name is Jeff Miller,
I live at 1630 Mill Slough Road,
and that's all I want to talk about,
I don't want to talk
about the school business,
or that bobtail at the end.
But that's what I'm here about,
and I think you'll be interested
in what I can tell you.
I'll just come up here.
I'm 88 years old, and I'm not
in good health. (chuckles)
- Just say your name and address, please.
- I'm Judge Jeff Miller,
I was born in Kissimmee, Florida in 1936,
and I lived at 1630 Mill Slough Road.
I lived there for a half a
century, plus three years,
I moved there in 1971.
I put together seven pieces of property
that stretched all the way
from Mill Creek Elementary
to the corner of Denn John
and down Denn John 400 feet.
When I moved out there, there
was no Denn John School,
there was no Mill Creek school,
Mill Slough was a dirt road,
Denn John was almost a dirt road,
and I lived in the county.
Now, I was in the county for 50 years,
they just annexed me in
about three years ago,
and I didn't fight it.
I said, you know, I've been an
attorney 55 years in Florida,
and Alabama, and I said,
I don't wanna go to court,
I just want y'all to leave me alone,
and let's get it straightened out.
So, when they sold the property
across the street from Mill Creek,
then the developer came
to me, and he said,
I'd like to have 30 feet
of the front of yours
to make a boulevard, like Oak Run is.
And I said, "Well, what
are you giving for it?"
"Well, I won't give you nothing,
but I'll make you a nice road."
I said, "That won't get it."
I said, "I'll trade you."
"No, can't do it."
He said, "Well, I'll cut
those oak trees down."
I said, "They're real oak trees,
you can do what you want to with them."
The city found out about it,
and they said that's not gonna happen.
So they had him change his engineering,
so when you come up Mill Slough Road,
and you get to the
intersection of Denn John,
the road curves, that's
the Jeff Miller curve,
because I wasn't letting 'em
have my property for nothing,
and I made 'em change it.
So, we got it all straightened out.
Well, the only thing that's
serviced by KUA is my house,
the school is not connected with it.
The water line goes
underneath the sidewalk
in front of 1630 Mill Slough Road,
and that does not affect anybody.
There's a prescriptive
easement for the utility line,
I don't have any problem with that.
And all I've been trying to
do is get it straightened out,
the property line, away from the park.
The oak trees is a city park.
The sidewalk runs
from the corner of Denn John
and Mill Slough to the school,
and then it wraps around from there,
and I'm not familiar with
that other park down here.
The only thing I'm here
on is 1630 Mill Road.
I've spent a great deal of time and money
having it all surveyed.
(paper crinkling)
I got the same material you have.
So, the only thing I ask y'all to do
is to sever my parcel
from this continuance,
and give me some peace,
I have maintained it for 35 years.
It's all inside of my fence,
and I just want my property
line straightened out.
So if you could sever my parcel,
y'all can fight it out about the school
and the other end there,
but I just don't wanna come back,
in my lifetime, I'd
like to have it settled.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you, sir.
- So, we do have a motion
on the floor to approve it.
- Can you repeat the
motion for the record?
- I make a motion to approve.
Anything else?
- Is there a second?
- Okay, no second.
So-
- I just wanna clarify,
his motion is to approve it,
to give the judge the property, correct?
- No, he's approving the
motion in its entirety
to approve the entire resolution.
- Okay.
- I think.
- Correct, that's why you're...
Just as it is, you're approving your-
- Just say that again, I'm sorry.
- Your motion is to approve
it as is the entire thing.
- The entire 5D, yes.
- Yes.
- To vacate the land
and give him the rights.
- Okay.
Do we have a second?
- Okay, so hearing no
second, the motion fails.
Is there another motion?
- So, I guess,
assuming that now we're kind
of back to general discussion,
I think this wasn't clarified.
So, as the gentleman pointed out,
and in part of the documents,
maybe you can scroll back up,
the vast majority of this
right of way, this vacation,
is north of the fences for
the duration of the thing.
Is there any portion of this vacation
that is south of the fence?
I think you need to look
at the previous one.
This one's on the right side.
- Yes, if you-
- It's up on there.
- So, if you scroll, if you zoom in,
you can actually see the fence.
If we zoom in a little bit here.
- Yes so, it sounds like the gentleman
is primarily concerned in the
fact that the right of way
on the leftmost portion of this parcel,
you know, there's that
sort of dash dotted line
that marks the fence,
it seems like there's a small sliver
on the rightmost portion of this parcel
that is beyond his fence,
and I can understand that
that would be annoying,
and I would be willing
to amend this vacation
to only be that sliver beyond the fence.
And-
- Hold on, I wanna clarify here.
That bottom portion that you see there,
that's an overhead power line.
The fence line is on
the north side boundary.
Where it says three foot chain link fence,
so his fence is on that north side there,
where the arrow is,
that's where his fence is.
- That's where his fence is.
So, the bottom that you see there,
that's the overhead power line.
So his chain link fence meanders,
on the left hand side,
it meanders where it shows
the driveway heavy equipment,
it meanders north,
adjacent to the sidewalk,
and where it says three foot
chainlink fence, runs along.
There we go.
- Yeah.
- Runs along.
There's a gate, it meanders.
- Can we look at the right portion again?
The part by the school?
- Yeah.
And so if we zoom in a
little bit too as well...
Let's see here.
This one, there is a symbol,
if you see it, keep going,
there's like the line in the circle,
that's where the fence line is.
So, to answer your question, yes,
so there is a portion of that right of way
that's south of the existing
fence line of the school,
so that cinder there shows you
where the school's fence is,
and it's adjacent, immediately
adjacent to the sidewalk.
- Right.
- To indicate that's
where the fence line is.
- Yes. Okay.
But then there is basically
the entirety of the portion
on the right half of this diagram
is all beyond the fence line,
and includes the portion
of missing sidewalk.
Correct? Okay.
So, I'm gonna make a motion
to amend the current motion
to suggest that we
remove from the vacation
any of the property
north of the fence line.
So, on this diagram
that looks like there's,
you know, a little triangle portion
on the left part of the diagram,
that looks like there's very
little on the first diagram,
but basically the whole,
I think the clear thing to
say for the motion would be,
let's try to amend the motion
to exclude from the vacation.
- Hold on just a second.
- Go ahead.
- There is no motion yet.
- Yes, I make a motion to amend.
- You can make a motion
to approve a portion,
to not amending anything.
This is the resolution.
- True, right.
Yeah, not to get wonky, right,
but I guess this constituted
in terms of Robert's rules of order,
or the main motion under
consideration would be 5D.
Is that right?
- It would be if there was
a motion to approve it.
- Okay.
- There is no motion to
approve, that failed,
so now you can make a motion
to do what you wanna do.
- Okay, so I will make a
motion to amend item 5D.
- Yes.
- To exclude from the
vacation all of the land
north of the chain link fence.
- Okay, I wanna clarify on this diagram,
so that way we understand.
So, where we see the asphalt driveway,
so you are including
that asphalt driveway,
the one, two, and you
see where the fence line,
the third asphalt driveway,
and it meanders up.
Yeah, there we go.
I just wanna clarify,
is this where approximately
that you're amending
to exclude from your approval?
- If I'm reading this right,
there's no line with the dots,
and sort of where the mouse is,
that's where the fence line is.
So, everything north of that,
I'm hoping to exclude from the vacation.
And that fence line, at this point,
right now, the mouse is
beyond the fence line, right?
And if it goes down,
there is the fence line.
Okay.
- Yep.
- And as we move to the right,
the fence line is at the edge of the thing
for the duration of that,
and I would hope to exclude
all of that on the right,
at least in the present amendment.
It feels like this accomplishes
what the original goal was,
the gentleman who has property
that was part of the right of
way that was beyond his fence
would now have ownership of it.
Middle school would now have
ownership of a small strip
beyond the fence that they could control,
but the city would retain
all of the property
north of the fence, which would include,
or it seems like, enable the city,
to approve or make changes to the,
or give them control of the
oak trees that are there
that are nice,
give them the ability
to put in a sidewalk,
or improve on the existing infrastructure.
I guess, can I ask the
city if the city's like,
if that's okay about the city,
how do they feel about it?
- It's a motion-
- Does that mean that
the asphalt driveways
would belong to the city?
- Yeah, I mean they'd be
part of the right of way.
- They'd be part of the city's property?
- Part of the right of way.
Yeah. It's already the city.
- It is already.
- Yeah.
- So we have a motion, correct?
Okay. Second?
And there's a motion,
he gave the motion for the
way he described the property,
that's what's on the table.
So, do we have a second?
We have a second.
All in favor?
- Aye.
- No.
- I'm gonna say no also, 'cause
I'm just not clear on if...
I feel, may I speak, or do we have to...
Okay, so I wanna make sure
that I understand correctly.
I think that I wanna ensure,
and I know that he kind of
described it at the end,
you know, that we leave here,
because I hear everything
you're saying about,
you know, about what
our job is, as a board,
but I think we have a
superseding job as a board
to ensure that we're working always
in the best interest of our community
as it relates to within the confines
of the description of
what we do as a board.
So, for me, when I hear,
you know, the judge that
he's been taking care of it
for so long, and he is
willing to continue,
and I hear, you know,
that you do wanna preserve the oak trees,
and that's important, and
that we need a sidewalk,
I wanna be sure that,
before we pass anything,
that we are ensuring that
those things are in place,
or at the very least we've
done our due diligence
to ensure that we are trying to do that.
So, again, with his description
of where those lines are drawn,
are those things in place?
Does it allow the judge
to get the property,
and I'm sorry I'm referring
you to you as judge, (chuckles)
that's the part that's retained,
and the oak trees, and also the sidewalk.
I know that we can recommend
as part of it, the sidewalk,
so I know that that can be placed in.
But I just wanna ensure that, you know,
and again, in thinking about,
you know, best use of city dollars,
are we maintaining property
that we can otherwise,
you know, again, being fair,
and doing our due
diligence to look at this
from all different purviews,
to allow somebody who's been
taking care of a property
for so long
now continue, as the owner,
to maintain that property,
versus saying, you know,
okay, we're gonna retain
it, and be unjust to him,
and at the same time, incur
more costs for the city.
We're at a time right now,
it's very hard to retain,
and I'm sorry I don't
mean to get on a tangent,
but it's very hard to retain
good employees in our city,
and we have a high turnover
rate, especially in these areas,
because they're being
pulled away by hotels
that can pay more, and what have you.
So can't put more burden on our staff
because we just wanna maintain something
because of the possibility
that, in 30 years,
it may be something.
So, again, looking at this
from all those aspects,
I'd love to be able to leave here,
you know, at least trying my best
to ensure that that we've
looked at all of that.
So, again, in looking at this,
would those things be accomplished?
- Can I clarify something?
We just took three driveways
away from the owner,
half of this is not their driveway.
What do you wanna do?
- So, sorry,
so, right now,
this is already part of
the city's right of way.
All of the thing under consideration,
everything north of this yellow portion,
is already part of the right
of way for Mill Slough Road,
so this was land that the city,
I mean, correct me if I'm
wrong, but, originally reserved,
because they wanted to build a road here,
and they maintained kind of full rights
to develop all of the
land within this wide,
as Craig said, you know,
a wide right of way around the road.
And it sounds like there
was kind of a mistake,
or an oversight that
was made at some point,
where that right of way,
you know, I think they do these just,
you know, a 50 feet or whatever,
and it sounds like that includes
a sliver of the gentleman's
property beyond his fence,
which it sounds like the city,
according to his story,
erected originally.
So it was, you know,
they erected the fence within
their own right of way.
You know? Sounds like that was a mistake.
And it sounds like, originally,
the gentleman wanted
to correct the mistake
and ensure that everything
beyond the fence
was his property.
I think my impression is the city,
you know, listened to the gentleman,
took this into consideration,
and brought before us a motion
to kind of vacate the entire right of way
for everything south of the sidewalk.
And my concern was that
it feels like that's too much vacation,
and that would make it harder
for the city to address
what is a gap in the
pedestrian infrastructure,
which feels particularly troublesome
because this is a middle school.
And so that's the kind
of nature of my concerns.
I was hoping to meet in the middle,
in the sense that I hear
that there are concerns,
and I guess it was clarified for me
exactly where the fence line was,
and I am totally like, on board with,
even though, you know,
my understanding is that
we have an objective
to preserve the right of way,
this is in keeping with
the comprehensive plan.
If there is land beyond a fence line
that isn't serving the city well,
and it won't be useful for
future pedestrian pathways.
- So maintaining this will now
be the city's responsibility?
- Everything in yellow right now,
and everything north of
that on this diagram.
- He has no responsibility to
maintain and take care of it?
- It's all the city's responsibility.
The city owns all of those.
- Okay. Okay.
- If I can clarify something
with driveway aprons?
- Yeah.
- The driveway apron
is always the responsibility
of the property owner
who is entering their property
from that right of way.
So anytime you add a driveway
apron onto city right of way,
you get a what's called a right
of way utilization permit,
and that basically says you
can have your driveway apron
on city right of way,
but you are always
responsible to maintain that.
So, at your house, you
probably don't realize it,
but where your driveway
hooks into the street,
probably three feet of that
is actually on city property,
and your grass is on city
property, a portion of your grass.
You are responsible to maintain that,
so if your driveway apron were cracking,
you would have to fix that.
So, we're not taking
away anybody's driveway,
the current driveways
are owned and maintained
by the property owners
that access their property
off the right of way there,
so nothing is changing with that.
We're not taking away anybody's access,
we're not taking aways anybody's driveway.
Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you, Craig.
- This is my neighborhood,
and I know this neighborhood very well,
I lived here for 25 years.
That is why I am in favor
of meeting in the middle,
because I do see the need
from living in this
neighborhood for 25 years,
and not having the sidewalk.
I do, I would like to,
and I'm in favor of preserving, you know,
a future for a possible
driveway, I mean sidewalk,
because there's a lot of
kids walking around there.
And, as a citizen of Kissimmee,
I will feel also safer
having a sidewalk there,
but then also giving back
to the judge some of it, so.
- So, right now,
we have a motion that was made with the-
- It's two two.
Right so, we can raise another motion?
- Yeah, I forget, procedurally,
whether we can reraise
the existing motion,
or how many times we can do that.
- You can-
- If we're allowed to do that,
I would like to do that again.
- You can rephrase it in a way
that addresses some of the concerns raised
so that it's more understandable.
- So, how about,
in light of some of the
clarifications we just received
from the city,
and after further discussion
on behalf of the board,
I would like to make a motion
to amend agenda item 5D
to modify the right of way vacation
to exclude all of the property north
of the existing chain link fence.
I think that is my,
there we go.
- I think that was the same
as the previous motion.
- I was hoping that,
in saying that we, in pointing out
that we had further
discussion and clarification
that the situation was
materially different, but-
- All right, do we have a second?
- You're seconding it?
Okay.
All in favor?
- Aye.
One opposed, three to one, it passes.
- Okay.
So then, again, not to be wonky,
but to make sure we do this right,
did I just,
I made an a motion to
amend the agenda item,
do we now need a second motion
to adopt the amended item?
But I, like-
- The second motion did pass.
So, it was a motion to
amend the agenda item,
now they approve that amendment,
and now they want to
approve it, as amended.
So now you have to raise motion
to approve the amended agenda item.
- My understanding is, with Robert rules,
you have to make the amendment,
we have to pass the amendment,
once the amendment is passed,
now it's in the state
where it is now an amended agenda item,
so now I'm gonna make the motion
that we approve the amended agenda item.
- Second.
All in favor?
- Aye.
One opposed, three to one, it carries.
Item number six, public hearings.
We have none.
Item number seven, any discussion?
- Yes so, I have some general discussion.
So, I mean, just because it,
maybe because it came up several times,
I think it might be germane
to read the part of the city code,
sorry, if I can find it.
So, Objective 2.2.4,
Preservation of Right of Way
to Implement Multimodal Network.
The city of Kissimmee shall continue
to protect existing and
future right of way needs
by requiring all proposed developments
to preserve or dedicate right of way
to maintain an
interconnected roadway system
from multiple modes of transportation.
Just because we talked
about it several times,
as part of the record,
I wanted to kind of put that out there.
In terms of other discussion items,
one thing I wanted to ask,
so Onward Kissimmee just started,
which seems to be part of
the city's plan for the EAR,
the updates to the comprehensive plan.
I was wondering, as the
planning advisory board,
who have the duty, obligation,
and responsibility under the city code to,
you know, maintain and approve
the comprehensive plan,
whether there were plans for
us to meet therefore for us,
to see if we could set up a workshop
with the team responsible
running Onward Kissimmee,
to receive sort of updates
or further information
about the effort.
- Okay, so that is a
separate consulting contract
that the city has entered
within the consultant that's facilitating
those community facility workshops.
Am I understanding the
outcome of this workshop
is to have plans or documents?
So, under the current contract right now,
it only includes the community outreach
and the development of
the documents and plans,
so I can check with our
long-range planning,
but that's the scope of
the contract that they have
to facilitate the community meetings,
and then also to have
the documents or plans.
I think part of it is the bike pad plan,
and part of it is could
be suggestions, comments,
to support upcoming changes
in the transportation
and future land use element.
But that does not include
any other types of workshops
or education to the
planning advisory board.
Not part of the scope.
- Do we have to go back to amend that?
- But, in keeping, we've
had several conversations
about having an upcoming workshop,
I think part of the reasons
why that we postponed it,
because to allow for the addition
of new Planning Advisory Board members
to be appointed to the board
before we can start to
schedule a workshop.
We had already mentioned internally,
there'll be a two-part workshop,
one will be on laws,
ethics, Robert's rule,
and the other would be
the comprehensive plan
and the land development code.
I can tell you right now
that there is a potential,
not 100% confirmed,
that we have an agenda
item for September 3rd,
and we had previously mentioned that,
in order to allow for
the utmost amount of time
for the workshop,
that we would have to schedule a workshop
on a date that we don't
have any agenda items.
So, right now, that we're looking at,
at the earliest, would be late September.
And then also, it's also
subject to us having a quorum.
So, I cannot stress again,
when emails are sent
out, to please respond,
so that way we can confirm
that we will have enough folks
to have a workshop.
But that's the answer to your question,
it's not part of the contract
now for the consultants.
- Yeah, thank you.
I guess, just as like a technical thing,
is the quorum simply a
requirement for voting?
I mean, would we be potentially
allowed to have a work...
No, we need to have a quorum for anything.
Okay. Just clarification.
Thank you very much.
Okay so, thank you.
I guess I just wanted to, you know,
because of our duties in the city charter,
in Section 2.2.12,
for the authority to prepare
the comprehensive plan,
and in section 2-213
for the responsibility
of monitoring the plan
upon adoption of the comprehensive plan,
I feel a duty and an obligation to be,
you know, sort of,
I think this board should be a participant
in part of the Onward Kissimmee things,
and I guess I can understand
if the current contract
with the consultants
doesn't include additional meetings,
but I guess just,
I just wanted to emphasize
and invite the city
to invite the PAB as
to part of the process,
because I think it is part of our duties
and our responsibilities.
Sorry, so I think we're
still in the business,
one thing I wanted to...
So, part of what we discussed last time,
I think we could make a motion
to recommend that the city commission
look into completing the sidewalk,
both on the Randolph Street property
and the Mills Slough Street property.
And I think that's something
within our power to do,
is to make a motion to
make that recommendation
to the city commission.
I would like to make that motion now.
So, I make a motion that we recommend
that the city commission look
into completing the sidewalk
on the Randolph Street property,
as well as the Mill Street property
in front of the middle school.
- Do I have a second?
Okay. All in favor?
- Aye.
Motion carries, four to one,
four to none, sorry.
Okay.
And then board members here,
I think we've already covered that.
And I have a motion to adjourn.
- Motion to adjourn.
(person speaking faintly)
- He said that he'd like to know,
if that they realize they
don't need a sidewalk.
You wanna?
- I'd like to know, if we
do a survey, theoretically,
and find out that we
really require a sidewalk,
do we give the right
way back to the people,
or we just let that sit there?
- At this point, the motion's been made
to exclude any portion that's
north of the fence line.
- On my agenda it said
that we're dealing with the right of way,
we're not dealing with
sidewalks, or trees,
or anything else.
So, does the land go back to the people?
Or the city keeps it?
Or what happens?
- So, I think there's two things.
Like, so we made a motion
to amend these agenda items
to include these-
- That's not what I'm talking about.
- No, I know.
So I think the way to phrase it,
just for Brenda, is to say that we-
- No, let, let me, let me,
you don't need to speak for me, please.
- So the right of way right now
typically includes the sidewalk,
so the motion that was made right now,
with the portion that was
of concern, was not part of,
it will remain part of the city,
and will remain part of the right of way,
and remain part of the city's,
the area that has the
sidewalk that's missing.
- Okay, so it'll stay,
whether or not, or whether it is,
it'll stay part of the city either way?
- It'll stay part of the city.
And then a motion, a
recommendation was made,
to bring the concerns
for the construction,
because it's two things now, okay?
- Okay.
- So now that portion
remained part of the city,
and now a recommendation
will be brought forth
for the city commission for
the construction of that.
missing portion on Mill Slough,
and then the construction
on Randolph Avenue.
- And I'd like to ask one
other favor, if I could,
anytime we have to vacate,
or give a right of way,
just an area, or some people,
to add all the preparations.
At least behind it, like the sidewalk,
heads to stoplights, stop sign, sidewalk,
can we take all that into consideration?
- We do.
And typically, for vacations like that,
if there are utilities within it,
you know, if it's mast arms,
all that's typically in
the right of way anyway.
So, when you have a vacation,
we're coming before you for a vacation,
it typically does not
include traffic signals,
you know, those types of
things for a vacation.
And it could be a portion
of the right of way
and what have you.
Typically, if it's the
traffic signal and all that,
it needs to stay to be
maintained by the city.
- You usually, you go
through the right of way,
and then if there's anything else,
that comes up later, usually.
We don't mix it in with
the agenda that we have.
- We don't, but then
it's up to the discretion
of the Planning Advisory
Board to make conditions,
or you can modify as you so choose to.
- Okay, gotcha.
- One thing, maybe one way to just,
what I see,
what I hear you saying, Bob,
is that like you wanted
to kind of tell the city
that if,
after we make the recommendation
to the city commission,
if it is determined that
that's sort of too hard,
or too expensive, or impossible,
that you're telling the city that we'd be,
that, you know, you're inviting
them to kind of come back
to us with another motion
to do another vacation.
Is that what you're thinking, or?
- It doesn't matter.
- You're here to look
at what's on the paper,
make a decision whether
they're right or wrong,
and if they're wrong, they'll
go back and correct it.
If we're right,
then it'll go on to the commissioners,
and the commissioners will pass it.
- But I guess it is,
it is fully within our
duties to make amendments
to the things coming before the board.
That's part of our job.
If we think that those amendments are,
I'm sorry?
- Say that again.
- So, my understanding
is this board, right,
we are set up by the city charter,
we have a responsibility
not only to adopt,
but to consider amendments
to the comprehensive plan,
and to consider actions that
come before this committee,
and to judge them whether or not
they're keeping with
the comprehensive plan.
Since this board is governed
by Robert's rules of order,
Robert's rules of order allows
for not only the adoption
and rejection of motions,
but also the amendments of motions,
and so it's fully within
our power, as a board,
to make amendments or suggestions
to the agenda items that come before us.
And I think that's uncontroversial.
- All right. If there's
no more discussion.
- No discussion.
- Okay. Do I have a motion to adjourn?
- Motion to adjourn.
- All right. Seconded.
(person speaking faintly)
Adjourned. Thank you.