- We're good to go.
Okay, we're good.
- We're good, okay.
Calling the meeting to order at 6:02.
We'll ask everyone to stand for a moment
of silence and pledge allegiance.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of
America and to the republic
for which it stands, one
nation under God indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
I'm gonna ask everybody
to silence your devices
in the audience and on
the board here, please.
And also if anybody has
any conflicts of interest
with the agenda item we have tonight
or has had ex parte communication
or done your own research
or anything, please let that
be known, or site visits.
Nothing under, okay, minutes
approval of February 7th,
I just have a question, I
just wanna make sure that,
I saw where something happened before
where someone abstained and
that wasn't caught in here.
I wanna make sure there
were no abstentions
that were not caught in the minutes.
No, okay, I was saying
here, I was gonna say.
- That's not how we do it.
- Okay, all right, motion
to approve the minutes?
- I'll make the motion to approve.
- Alex, motion to approve, second,
any discussion changes, all in favor?
Robert I saw as the second.
All in favor, please say aye, aye.
Opposed, please say no, hearing
none, minutes are approved.
Old business, nothing there,
five, new business, 5A.
- Good evening, this is a
right of way vacation to vacate
a right of way that's located
on a portion of this property.
It's about 0.269, and it's a
portion of the larger parcel.
This right of way dedication
or what have you was actually
established in agreement
with the city of Kissimmee back in 1972.
At that time, I guess there was a plan
to have a roadway from Vine
Street to cut across down.
There we go, there's some
kind of north south road
at some point in time to cut
across Vine to head south
into the property to the south.
And eventually, what you don't
see offline is Oak Street,
see it as well, heading east to west,
but I don't think that portion
of Oak Street was actually
in existence at that time.
Nonetheless, the current property owner is
in development review now
to redevelop this property
for a hardware store
that's currently in review.
The standard process in
any type of vacation,
whether it be a roadway
vacation or an easement
to see if Kissimmee has
to send out the request
to all the utility providers
and we get those responses.
Those responses were
included in the packet.
We have a couple of folks, as
indicated in the staff report
that they had no objections
to vacating this,
I think it's 47 foot wide
existing right of way agreement,
but they did want to have
and dedicate an easement
in the place where as this
develops, there are utilities,
drainage, or what have you,
so that is the one condition of approval
that can be done either via a final plot
or those easement agreements.
Dedications can be done
by another instrument.
So at this point in time,
staff did not receive
any objections to any utility providers,
nor do we have any objections
from any city department
or with our Toho Water or
Kissimmee Utility Authority.
So staff is recommending
approval subject to the condition
of any utility easements or stuff be done
to go to final plat or
through another instrument.
- Board members, any
questions for the city?
- Yeah.
- Alex, go ahead.
- So yeah, I guess in the packet it noted
that the property below
doesn't seem to be maintaining
the right of way, is that accurate,
or do you know, was that
even given or was it?
- We're not clear whether
or not, so that property
to the south right now is
actually under development.
- Yeah.
- It's been under development
for quite some time
for a multi-family apartment.
I think it was public works
engineering that made mention
about, I think it was a drainage easement
and not so much a roadway dedication.
- Okay.
- For that,
so it wasn't any use for a roadway,
but there was a question
about drainage easement.
- So I guess like you
said, Oak Street is there,
and in terms of the auto network,
it seems like the area is well
served, but once, you know,
right of ways they're given
up, they're hard to get back.
Would there, do you know if
there'd be any interest either
on the city side or whether
the developer would be
interested in maintaining, you
know, not the full 47 feet,
but maybe like a pedestrian
path or something?
Because I think this,
in keeping with the comprehensive plan,
it would be nice to improve
pedestrian, you know,
a dedicated walkway, especially
for multifamily homes
behind it or something, you
know, that might only be 10 feet
or you know, some small portion
of the existing right of way.
Do you know if that's a
possibility of something the city
or the developer might be interested in?
- So in review for this application,
there wasn't a department that
indicated the need to have
or to retain any of this portion
as is part of the right of way.
And there wasn't any
indication during the review
to have any plans to dedicate
any new easement for that.
Now, the redevelopment of the site,
you can see the remnant here.
So I believe based on, and
you can can speak to this,
but the existing access
is going to remain,
the building is going to
be pushed towards the front
because this is in our
form based code area,
and the circulation, if you
will, both the vehicular
and with the pedestrian
is going to be similar
to what you have here, you
can go in on the one way area
and you come back out, so that's a-
- Yeah, I guess, I
mean, Vine Street's kind
of horrendous to either bike or walk on,
and this area of the city in particular,
not particularly well
served pedestrian wise.
So it seems like it would
be an opportunity to try
to improve pedestrian
connectivity, you know,
and there's already the
existing right of way.
Yeah, is that, again,
this gets to the point
where I'm not sure this is
in the purview of this body
or not to suggest or to amend, you know,
to add additional condition
or anything like that.
Is that within the purview
of this body or not?
- It is, but the thing
is I'm not sure whether
or not to the south there,
to me it may appear,
it looks like it might be a canal.
I'm not quite sure what that
is to the immediate south
where it says 12-10 and 12-14.
I don't know whether or not
there's some kind of drainage
or what's within that area,
so that's why I'm, you know,
you can include the condition,
but not knowing for sure
that it can be something
that could be explored.
But I'm not 100% sure whether
or not A, if that's drainage,
or those plans there, there's like a wall
or some type of buffer.
- Yeah.
- Because it's residential
against the commercial
that there might be a wall, a
fence or a wall requirement.
- Yeah, I imagine that's the current plan.
I mean, in the plans that were
submitted in this proposal,
it looks like the plan
was to put a fence up
all around the property line anyway.
But I also feel like that
doesn't do a good job
to serve pedestrian
connectivity, and that's part
of why this corridor isn't
well served currently.
So again, yeah, I'm not sure what to-
- To your point, because
it's redevelopment
for form-based code,
part of the proposed
development will require
a direct pedestrian, I believe
it's on the sidewalk
connection from inside
of the property to the
existing sidewalk along Vine.
- Okay.
- Because of the existing drainage,
and you can see the size
of that right of way
from where the property
line is to the edge
of that travel lane,
there's a huge amount
of swales and drainage.
We typically do require that
the sidewalk be widened,
but because of the drainage
issues on the frontage of this,
they're not gonna be able
to widen that sidewalk.
Our long range planning team
has been working with FDOT,
and I believe it passed maybe a year ago
with the Vine Street CRA,
there was a master landscaping plan.
We went through this exercise
of having improvements
along the Vine Street corridor
that includes landscaping.
But part of that exercise
also included constraints,
where we wouldn't even be able
to put in the adequate amount
of landscaping to further
buffer pedestrians
with that traveling,
because that's the intent
of providing landscaping
or have what we call a
furnishing zone, introduce
more green space between
the property and all that.
- I guess, yeah, I understand
that's the long-term plan for Vine Street.
Vine Street's also a state road,
so a lot of this is outside
of the city's hands.
So then I guess it feels like
as far as the city's concerned
as far as this comprehensive
plan is concerned,
it does feel like, again, I
guess it feels like instead
of giving up the entire right of way,
I could understand giving
up the right of way
or the plans to build a road
at this location in the future.
But I feel like it would
be in the city's interest
and would help to comprehensive
plan to retain some right
or easement for a pedestrian
path in the future.
Just it feels like otherwise once lost,
then the existing connectivity issues
in this corridor would be cemented,
and that feels like, you know,
I don't know, it feels
like retaining five feet
or something to allow
for a potential path,
allowing all those residential
units better connectivity
instead of having to walk, you know,
a half mile around the Oak Street
and back to the front feels
like something worth exploring,
and it feels like this is the
last opportunity for that,
because once the right of way is given up,
then it feels like there would be no,
there'd be no opportunity in the future.
- So when you say it's
five feet, are you talking
about retaining, it's
47 feet wide right now,
so you're talking about
retaining five feet of that?
- Yeah.
- North-south?
- Yeah, well a strip, you know,
instead of the 47 feet wide,
or I don't know what the requirements are
for the city for pedestrian paths.
I should have looked that up,
but certainly don't need 47 feet, right?
And that feels like still the
developer would get access to,
you know, 42 feet for their parking lot,
which seems like it's the plan,
but the city would also
have the opportunity to try
to improve some of the
connectivity for bikes
and pedestrians in this area,
which is poorly absorbed currently.
And I'm not sure what the
long-term plan there is,
especially given that
Vine Street's a state road
and we don't have control.
- But at this time, is the applicant here?
Sir, would you like to say any words?
You don't have to, but
you have the opportunity
to speak if you like.
Please step to the microphone,
state your address,
your name and your address
for the record please.
- Good evening, the Michael Hadad.
I am representing Kelly Horn
today who's representing
then the applicant address
is 200 South Orange Avenue,
Orlando, Florida.
So well, I'm here
representing the applicant.
I cannot speak in regard to the easement.
I know they needed it
for planning of the site
and shifting the building
and accommodating parking and
all, but and I can't speak
for the five foot easement
north-south connection.
I know the development to the south,
I don't know if there's direct connection
that can even accommodate
that five feet north-south
if it's trying to be accomplished.
- Yeah, I'm not sure either,
but I guess, you know,
if the easement is given up
then there'd be no opportunity
to connect any of the
adjacent properties, right?
Whereas if it was retained
or that could be a reason
to add a door or a gate through
the wall if there is one.
You know, again, I don't know the status
for the south (indistinct) property,
but yeah, go ahead.
- Yeah, understood.
It'd be worth looking at the site plan
for the development to the south,
but I mean, there could be a wall
that prevents that entirely.
So I mean, I can take this
question back to the applicant
and look at that further,
but I mean, we're still
planning to move forward
with approval and agree with
staff's request to do so.
- Do we have any other board members
with questions or comments?
If not, we'll ask any motions
regarding this agenda item.
(indistinct)
Asking for any motions
regarding this agenda item.
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- With the easement condition?
- Yes.
- Okay.
We have a motion to approve
with the easement condition
already regarding utilities.
- Can I clarify like just
how general of the condition
so I can capture that the
additional added condition?
- Sorry.
(overlapping speech)
- Hold on, hold on, we
have motion on the floor.
- Yeah.
- Specifically state it again.
- Make motion to approve (indistinct).
- As proposed by the city or?
- Is that with the drainage easement?
- Okay, so easements for
utilities were already
in place, yes, agreed upon?
- That was the condition
recommendation for the utility.
- Okay, is your motion inclusive of that?
- Yes.
- Okay,
do we have a second for that?
- Do we need to-
- We can have discussion,
we'll have opportunity
for discussion, but if we
don't have a second, it dies.
So do have a second of the motion?
- I think I'd like to discuss more,
at least get Alex's concerns tabled.
I mean, I think Brenda, were
you talking about adding his?
- Okay, I'm sorry, Melissa,
I'm just asking strictly for
a second, do we have a second?
- I think he's concerned procedurally
in order to proceed and even
have a discussion on the item.
- Yes, we will have the discussion,
absolutely welcome to that,
but I need to know if we have a second.
We have a second for
Melissa, okay, discussion.
- Okay, yeah, so regarding discussion,
I understand the city came
to us and they didn't really,
they didn't have a problem
with giving up the entire
right of way, I guess.
Yeah, looking at it, looking
at this area of the city,
it does seem like this is a
particularly poor served area
for pedestrian and bike traffic, right?
This is Vine Street and
Oak Street right there.
And so I just know that, you know,
once the right of way is given
up by the city, these things,
you know, they never get 'em back right?
'cause the developments
are on 'em and stuff,
and so it seems like that would preclude
any future opportunity to
try to build things out.
And so yeah, it just, I guess it just,
it feels like something
that we should weigh.
And I guess I wonder whether, you know,
looking at the site plan, if
the city retained, you know,
a few feet, then it seems
like it would still provide
an opportunity and wouldn't
really impact, you know,
there'd be a few feet of extra
concrete for the parking lot.
Felt like something worth
considering and suggesting, so.
- Can I just clarify for a second?
Just because this right
of way is being vacated,
it doesn't mean that the city,
if this is gonna be platted,
so the reason to request for the vacation
of all of it is that it would
change your boundary lines
for purposes of setbacks
and stuff like that,
and other buffering requirements,
so that would be why,
part of why the request is being made.
If it's granted and the applicant
goes to develop the site,
that doesn't necessarily
mean that some of the things
that you wanna see on the site
won't actually come later on.
So if you platted it, that
doesn't mean that you,
I'm not saying that the applicant
is planning on doing this.
It's not necessarily a lost
opportunity for this city,
'cause you don't know if some, you know,
right away would be dedicated to the city
when that property is being improved.
So I see what you're saying.
It just kind of makes it clear
to develop the whole site
if that unused right of way
is vacated in its entirety.
- I understand.
- I'm sorry,
Robert's rules of order.
I wanna give Melissa a chance to speak
'cause she hasn't spoken on it yet,
and I know you had some
comments, go ahead.
- I was just trying to make sure
that we had gotten Alex's
concerns brought up.
(indistinct) items, and
then also to mention
the applicant's comment
that it doesn't appear
this plot is (indistinct) also,
so there's not another easement
adjacent to the sidewalk
(indistinct) if that works
being on the frontage.
I mean, if it was all
developed (indistinct),
essentially, a five foot gap
that may never be developed,
and just becomes (indistinct)
water (indistinct).
- Other board members,
comments or questions?
Alex, if you have something
else we'll come back to you,
but I wanna make sure we get
everybody else's before you.
Anybody, Alex did you have more?
- No, I mean I think I voiced my-
- Okay, my thoughts about
this are a couple things.
If we're talking about a walkway,
we're talking about the
city developing that
and paying for that, are we
talking about leaving that
for the city to do in the future?
And the other thing is
we don't know the intent
of the developer to the
south if they would even want
such a thing to access their
property, I don't know.
- The development to the
south is quite a large.
(indistinct)
- Yeah.
- It's a quite (indistinct)
type plot of ground
that they're developing a portion.
(indistinct)
- Okay.
- It's a huge complex
that they're putting in,
so he's actually locked in.
(indistinct)
And the parcel we're talking about,
they're gonna have a right of way anyway.
If the city needs to get in,
they're gonna get in there.
So for us to let him have
it, that's no problem,
because we have access to it anyway.
- For utility purposes?
- For utility purposes.
- Yeah, I guess my
concern is just, I mean,
do we know, I dunno the
details of the development
to the south, but looking at it, it looked
like it was a multi-family
type development.
So it's gonna be a lot of
people, and if we don't want
all those people to always
have to get in their car
in order to drive everywhere,
there are businesses
on Vine Street within a block of there,
there's, you know, a deli that
I like that's really good.
There's things like that, and you know,
if this is all closed off,
then that means having to walk
out to Oak Street, up Oak Street,
and along Vine Street,
and nobody enjoys that.
And it just feels like
this is the kind of thing
that we're put here to try to think about
and consider these alternatives,
and so I wanted to put it out there.
I understand it would
be slightly inconvenient
for the applicant and for
the city to reconsider this
and do all that planning, but I would feel
amiss not to have brought up the issue.
- Just to clarify further,
there could be opportunities
for, you know, traversing the property
and connectivity up to Vine Street
without it being city right of way.
- But if I understand,
I can understand that that
would totally be a possibility.
But if I understand correctly,
it would also totally be
up to the applicant at that point, right?
- To a certain extent, but the
applicant would not be able
to develop the property
all the way over to the property line.
- No.
- So they're gonna have,
I don't know what their site
plan is, but I'm assuming
because it's a place of business,
they're gonna have drive aisles.
- Yeah, at least looking at
the site plan that we got
in our materials, it looked
like that plan was to build
a fence around the entire
property, close everything off,
and yes, have access from Vine Street,
primarily for automobiles, but.
- Brenda, just outta curiosity,
how long has that land been vacant?
- I found that there
was a demolition permit
that was pulled in 2011.
So there was a building that was there.
I couldn't find the exact building permit
when that building was
established, but it was demolished.
A commercial building
was demolished in 2011.
- Okay, so about 14, 15 years, okay.
- Do we have another
picture of the wider area?
(indistinct)
- It's pretty white out.
- It's white rabbit in a snow storm.
(indistinct)
- Correct me if I'm wrong.
A development that's this
small would not require
to put in any kind of
street, so that's where,
and I don't think that, you
know, the city wouldn't,
at this point in time, put in.
I see what you're saying,
to preserve it for future
development, right?
- Yeah, I guess, sorry, I don't know,
can I make another comment?
Are we still in the
comment period or whatever?
I just wanted to make sure
I'm not violating the
Roberts rules, we're good?
Yeah, oh, so anyway, looking
at the comprehensive plan,
one of the things the city plan, you know,
promises to do was to
increase the level of service
for pedestrians and bikes.
It's not clear to me where
we are on that thing,
on the way to doing that,
or what the sort of detailed
plans are for building this.
Looking at this site, knowing
now that the city has a right
of way on this property and
this property is heading
directly towards a multifamily unit,
and in an area that does have multi use,
it feels like one of the
places the city should consider
or should have considered
for potentially improving
pedestrian and bike level
service, and I understand
that there would still be opportunities
if the developer was willing
to do things in the future,
but my understanding is
also that once this right
of way is given up, that it is like,
then it's at the goodwill of the developer
and no longer in the city
kind of loses a degree
of control as to whether
or not they can execute
on the plan, if I'm
correct on that, right?
Yes.
- I'm trying to see,
what is the width of this easement?
- 47 foot wide.
- 47 foot wide, okay.
- 250 feet long.
- Okay.
- I think the city's priority,
because we have to set
priorities, is the Vine Street corridor
for pedestrian
connectivity, so this is why
for redevelopment along
Vine Street, we're requiring
that the sidewalk be widened
to 12 foot wide where possible,
because we understand
that there are utilities,
there are drainage issues, what have you,
and all of that now is the
requirement for by the developer,
but it's where it is feasible to do,
'cause we understand again,
like for this particular
property there's a huge swale,
there's utilities that
makes it impossible,
so the priority is
along the Vine Street corridor east-west.
- Yeah, and I guess, I
mean, maybe to clarify
what I'm thinking, given what you said,
level of service for pedestrian and bike
along Vine Street is already poor.
It sounds like with
this site in particular,
there's already issues with
trying to extend the sidewalk
facing Vine Street east-west.
But another part of the
story of connectivity
to Vine Street for
pedestrian and bike is giving
other alternatives for
pedestrians and bikes to get to,
you know, on and off Vine Street,
and so what I was imagining
was instead of giving up
the full 47 foot easement,
if the city retained,
it sounds like if the
plan was to try to go
to 12 foot sidewalks,
then it would make sense
to try to maintain as
much as 12 feet of the 47,
and still provide an
developer with the space
that I imagine they would
need to try to build
a nice property that would
give the city an opportunity
to try to improve what
is otherwise a difficult
to improve pedestrian and bike story
for this segment of Vine Street east-west.
- But keep in mind I think part
of what you are also requesting
hinges upon cooperation
from that development to the south
as far as even accessing the property.
So if we move forward with the retaining
of the five feet, again, if
there's not that coordination
or feasibility to provide
continuing connection
to the south, so this is
why we put that if it's,
I wanted clarification on that condition
to where if it's feasible to
do, because we have to go back
and see whether or not that
connection can continue
to the south or be if that
property owner is interested
in continuing that connection
through the property.
- Right, but things like that don't happen
without dedication and
wherewithal of the city then
to try to make things like that happen.
But I think the alternative
to give up the full right
of way means that it's
much less likely to happen
than retaining it, so I again
felt as though it was my duty
to look out for, especially
like the pedestrian
and bike parts of the comprehensive plan,
felt like this was a place to voice that.
- I have a question, is it okay
if I look at my phone
to look at Google Maps,
to look at a satellite image of this area?
I just wanna make sure I'm not.
(indistinct)
I just wanted to see-
- I think Brenda can pull it
up on the screen for everybody.
- I just wanna get a wider satellite view.
Yeah, so that's okay.
I guess I speak from a
little bit of experience,
'cause I regularly bike
along Oak Street here,
and go, you know, I
also try to regularly go
to a couple of places on Vine Street,
but I'm terrified to go
east-west on Vine Street,
so I instead try to look for
any other opportunity to get on
and off Vine Street as
kind of near as possible,
and part of the way I accomplish
that is to go through,
you know, parking lots
and things like that
and try to find other ways
to connect, and I mean,
especially if there's
a lot of families there
that want to try to frequent any
of the little restaurants
and stuff along the way
instead of having to
walk all the way around,
which one would have to
do, it's more a chance-
- This is a, the business
again is a hardware store?
- Yes.
- Okay.
I'm gonna ask the applicant's
representative a question.
Could you see, well, and maybe
you can't even answer this,
but maybe would it be actually
potentially beneficial
for a business like your
client's to have access
for these are these multi-units,
these many multifamily units
to be able to get there,
would that be beneficial
for them possibly?
- I actually came up to say
I could not answer that question, but-
- I guessed that, but you
know, I thought I'd ask,
because you know, a lot of
times with retail business,
having traffic coming by
in a good way is a plus,
and to Alex's point, I
understand some of the concerns.
Does this development to the south,
well, I guess to the south,
would they even want this,
do they have plans of some sort of wall
or some sort of, you know,
we don't know any of that,
but I can certainly see
where it could be beneficial
for the people living here,
and potentially beneficial for the client
if they then have potentially
all these customers
that could then just access that.
But it's their property,
do they want that or not?
But I also see that that
would cut off a huge amount
of walking or whatever to
get over to Vine Street
and so forth, so I get that,
and possibly alleviate,
you know, the foot traffic
or the car traffic,
although is there any other,
what I'm looking at here,
do any of us know if there's
any other pedestrian access
to go up to where the Wells
Fargo and the restaurants are?
I don't see it.
- Go up Magnolia.
- Don't see it.
- That's better for me.
So I regularly avoid
going along Vine Street
by coming up Magnolia,
'cause that's quiet.
- I go by this area quite a
bit actually, and then there's
the Orlando Health Physician Associates,
the preschool there, but
again we don't even know
if something could be physically put there
because of the swale
and because of the drainage and all that,
so it would take a lot more to figure out
if that could be possible.
But I understand what you're saying,
just having it an easement
for a future foot traffic path
or sidewalk going from
this area up to there.
A lot of questions, and
if it didn't turn out
where that development
to the south wanted that,
or if they're putting in a wall
or something that wasn't
gonna work for that,
then it would be a moot point anyway,
and it wouldn't cost anyone anything,
and it could be a potential plus.
Potentially, I mean, I could see
some potential downsides too,
but for a retail business, your thoughts?
- So just to give a little bit flavor
of your question of whether or
not it would directly impact
or be beneficial to the
applicant, when you think
of a pedestrian generator,
you're thinking of a restaurant
or something similar to that nature.
So as a, you know, for
the applicant itself,
you know, for a hardware
store, I wouldn't expect it
to be a high pedestrian generator
as a restaurant would be,
to back up and give some flavor
to your question previously.
- Okay, okay, so at this point,
unless we have any other
comments or questions,
we do have a motion on the floor,
we have a second, and
we've had discussion,
so I'm gonna ask for a vote for approval.
If it passes, it passes.
If it does not, then another
motion could be made.
Go ahead, Alex.
- And I guess just to clarify,
right now we are voting on the, you know,
item 5A as presented to us by the city,
which would mean giving
up the full easement
but retaining, or sorry,
giving up the full right of way
but retaining a utility easement
and that is all, correct,
that's what we're voting for?
- Utility would not somehow
include pedestrian walkway,
just strictly for KUA, Toho, whatever.
- And it's not just, it's any,
because also it was Spectrum.
There was a cable, they
have infrastructure,
so that's why we worded the condition
to say any new utility easements,
not just the, you know,
electricity, the Spectrum.
- Any utilities, okay, but
that would not envelope
a pedestrian walkway, that
wouldn't be inclusive of that.
Okay, so we have a motion on
the floor, we have a second.
If we don't have any further discussion,
then I'll put it to a vote.
All in favor, please say aye, aye.
Opposed, please say no.
- No.
- Okay, so we had Alex with a no.
Do we have the rest aye?
Four to one, aye,
okay, so the motion carries.
Next, public hearings, nothing there.
Discussion, nothing there.
Here, chairman and board members,
I just wanna point out that
when I actually ended the,
you know, what you were saying, Alex,
and what you're saying, Melissa,
you know, it's just trying
to make sure we get through
the procedure and get it done,
because yeah, I've been in meetings
before where it gets bogged down.
Not that those comments shouldn't be said,
they absolutely should
be heard on the record,
but we have to do it in a certain order
so we don't go round and round around,
so please accept that in the
spirit in which it was done.
Board members, any other comments?
- We have a motion to adjourn.
- We have motion, well, next meeting?
- I believe we are working on another item
for the next April 3rd meeting.
I will keep you posted and updated.
It's still like a project
in progress for people.
- So that would be for what date?
- April 3rd, I think.
(overlapping speech)
Please look out for the
emails, and when you do,
just you could say yes or no
when we get to that point,
but I think I'll know
hopefully the next couple
of days whether or not
we will have an item
for that April 3rd Planning
Advisory Board meeting.
- Okay.
- One item.
- Okay, and Melissa, I heard
you made a motion to adjourn?
- Yes sir.
- Do we have a second?
- I second.
- Second, Robert, any discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Well, yeah, I guess.
- Anybody opposed, please say no.
- I'm not opposed to adjourning.
I was hoping to just thank you, everyone,
for tolerating my comments
and discussion, so thank you.
- Absolutely.
- It's not toleration, it's part
of what you're supposed to
do is voice your thoughts.
(indistinct)
- I'll check it out.
- 'Cause we're not far from it at all.
Bowling alley is here, then
you've got your businesses,
and then they can put
a restaurant in there.
It's a real good one.
- I will check that out.
- I've seen that vacant.
I've come by that I don't
know how many times.
(indistinct)
They're building a big,
I think it's a medical center in here.
They gotta leave this open
and that one for the drainage.
Anyway, have fun, nice seeing you.
- Nice seeing you.
I'll see you in a couple weeks.
- Possibly, as long as it's
not April 1st. (laughs)
(indistinct)
- Ready to go?
- See you, Jerry, see you, Robert.
(indistinct)
- Yes.
- Maybe stop by (indistinct).
(indistinct)
- Thank you, guys, have a good night.
- You could suggest to them.
(indistinct)