- And it's six o'clock.
Welcome, everybody.
Calling the meeting to order.
I'd like everyone to stand please
for the Pledge of Allegiance
and a moment of silence.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America,
and to Republic of which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- Thank you.
I'll also ask everyone to,
and I'll do this myself,
make sure to silence your devices please.
Board members too.
Sometimes we've forgotten.
Thank you.
And upfront, if any of the board members
have had any ex-parte communication,
done any research on
your own, site visits,
anything like that for
any of the agenda items,
please make that known
if there's potentially any
sort of conflict of interest
or thing that you need to disclose.
Let's start with the approval
of the December 20th meeting minutes.
Do we have any motions
regarding those minutes?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- We have a motion to approve from Robert.
- Second.
- We have a second from Alex.
And all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, minutes are approved.
Brenda, could you just explain to me,
'cause I think it came up also,
the detail of these minutes here
if that's what we're
gonna see in the future,
just to manage our expectations
of how detailed this was.
- Sure.
If I recall,
I think those minutes included
the Hilliard Isle PUD.
And also, we do have
Alicia here as an addition.
We're gonna continue to work
with the City Clerk's Office
because I know that
there's some guidelines
of what to include with city minutes.
So it's twofold.
That was a longer meeting.
We had quite a few public
comments that were there,
but we'll continue to work
with the Clerk's Office
regarding the meeting minutes,
what we need to include in there,
or paraphrasing, or what have you.
- Alicia, this is not a knock.
- Yeah.
- If you did these minutes.
I mean, they're incredibly
detailed, and kudos to you.
I just-
- It's a lot to get down.
- Yeah.
Glad I don't have that job, but nice.
All right.
Old business, nothing there.
5A, conditional use with site plan
to establish a chiropractic
office with a live-work unit.
Brenda?
- Yes.
This is a conditional use with site plan.
It's about a .2 acres of land.
It's actually here on the
south side of Vine Street,
so it's a pretty small lot.
This will be, as I remember,
this will be the first live-work unit-
- I'm sorry, I said live
work, live work, sorry-
- It's okay.
- Sorry.
- It's a live-work unit.
And so, what's included in the packet
was a 3,000 square foot building.
The first floor will
have the actual office,
about 1500 square feet
for the chiropractic,
and on the second floor will
be the residential portion.
The difference between a home occupation
and a live-work unit.
Home occupation, the city limits,
the presence, customer presence,
where it's pretty much the computer
and there's not customers
that are coming to the home.
A live-work unit, we are
encouraging that interaction
where the property owner
can reside on the property
and they can have, in
this case, a chiropractic,
have patients and they're
on the first floor,
but the property owner can
reside on the property.
I know there's certain other
communities in the county,
like your Celebration
or even City of Orlando,
where they have live-work units.
It's internally connected,
so where you can have office
space for your practice,
but you can actually
reside there too as well.
So this will be the first
of its kind in the city.
The form base code, or
the Vine Street corridor,
there are some incentives that we have.
One being the property street frontage.
In this case, the, how
much of the property width
will consist of the building.
And we have those standards.
In this case, it'll be 52%,
but if you have a live-work unit,
we don't require that
minimum frontage to be met.
In that case,
because it is being proposed
as a live-work unit,
it can't readily be converted to separate
where you have a separate
business on the first floor
and then renting out the second floor.
And part of the conditions
of approval that we have
is that cannot occur, and that if there-
- I'm sorry, it cannot what?
- It can't occur to where
the residential unit
is rented out separately to
someone that does, number one,
doesn't have their business
on that first floor.
It cannot happen
because we're already
waiving the requirement
for the frontage requirement.
And in addition to that, any other use
would require either additional parking
or other site improvements
if it was converted to something else.
So that's part of the
conditions of approval,
that it has to remain a live-work unit,
in addition to providing a fence to buffer
the existing Orange Gardens
community and residential
to the south.
Bicycle lockers were also introduced.
That's also a city-wide
incentive to reduce parking.
We encourage bicycle lockers
or other types of modes of transportation.
So the city provides an incentive
for every bicycle locker.
The parking requirement
can be reduced by two parking spaces.
With that in mind, staff
is recommending approval,
subject to the conditions listed,
and I'm here and the applicant's
representative is also here
to answer any questions that you may have.
- Okay.
Upfront, does the board have any questions
for Brenda and the city?
Before I ask the applicant if, sir,
if you'd like to step to the
microphone and state your name
and your business address for the record?
- Yes, my name's Lee
Hale, and business address
is 111 South Maitland
Avenue, Maitland, Florida.
- Just if you have anything
you wanna add or say, okay.
You don't have to.
- I'm just here to answer questions,
make sure everyone's on the same page.
- Okay.
Board members, any
questions for the applicant?
- No.
- If not, you can be seated.
Thank you.
Do we have any public comments?
Any comments from the public
regarding this agenda item?
Any public comments?
No?
Okay.
Board, do we have any motions
regarding this agenda item?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- Robert, motion to approve.
- Second.
- And we have a second from Melissa.
Any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
Aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
And 5B.
And again, I'll ask if anybody
has any conflicts of interest
they need to disclose, please let us know
if you've had any ex-parte communication,
research, site visits, et cetera.
Brenda?
Thank you.
- This next item is a land lease amendment
for the property located at
the end of Patrick Street.
If this site does look
familiar, it was presented
to the Planning Advisory
Board back in July,
at the July 19th meeting last
year, for the Carter case.
At the time, the property owner
was in the process of
selling the property.
We changed the land use,
I believe, from airport,
I think it was the airport,
to low-density residential.
The property has since changed hands,
and hence the land use change.
Initially, this property was part
of an inter-local agreement to
annex a number of properties
into the city, about 264
parcels, back in 2019.
That effort was part of, again,
to decrease these enclaves,
better provides services,
emergency services, garbage
collection, or what have you,
in coordination with
working with Osceola County.
With the change back
to industrial business,
staff is recommending
approval at this time,
and it's gonna be, I'm
finding more information
with the next item with the rezoning
as far as what the new owner
is intending to build on the property.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Board, any questions for the city?
If not, is the applicant here?
And would you like to say
anything to the board?
- I'm just here to answer questions.
- Okay, you don't have to,
but you're welcome to if you'd like.
Do we have any public comments
regarding this agenda item?
Public comments?
If not, board, do we have any
motions regarding this item?
- Motion to approve.
- Melissa, motion to approve.
- I'll second.
- We have second from Robert.
Any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
5C.
Again, if anybody is any
conflicts of interest,
please let that be known.
- So this is a companion
rezoning to rezone the property
from its current agricultural
conservation development
to business park.
Again, property was part of
that ILA before previously.
The reason why staff does not
want to rezone the property
to industrial to exactly match
the proposal to industrial
is because of the existing residential
that's nearby with it.
The surrounding property
to the east and south,
as noted on here, is the
business park, or BP,
and we felt that it was more appropriate
to rezone it to business park
so that would limit the type of uses
that could be reintroduced
on this property.
As of right now, there are
three different structures.
There is a duplex at 2810 and 2812,
about 4,000 square feet,
that was built in 1988.
There we go, put on there
so you can actually see it.
There's also, at 2804, is
a 1200 square foot building
that was built in 1939.
And at 2814 Patrick Street,
there's also another building,
about 3,000 square feet,
that was built in 1978.
Both buildings can remain on the site
and it can be used as residential
until such time that the applicant decides
to fully redevelop.
But it would be a legal non-conforming
that those structures can remain
until it's time to redevelop.
The applicant is intending
to have the storage
of exotic types of cars.
It's not a self-storage facility,
but it's just a structure to
house imported or exotic cars.
So we felt, again, this would
limit the type of industrial
or intense uses to the
residential area that's there.
And two, it would match
the existing business
park zoning designation
surrounding the undeveloped parcels
that's to the east and south.
So staff was recommending approval
subject to the approval
of the land use amendment.
I'm here to answer any questions,
and also the applicant owner as well.
- Board, are there any
questions for the city?
Alex.
- So maybe I should have
asked with the last one,
but, yeah, I noticed that
the adjacent property
is right now is designated
as business park in zoning.
Is it also...
industrial business in the future land use
or is that a different designation,
for the surrounding property?
Yeah, okay.
I thought, I just, yeah,
wanted to double check.
- Yeah.
It does, and the zoning and
that land use is compatible.
Again, the difference is
business park is less intense.
It does allow for that
intense type of manufacturing,
allow for some light commercial,
but not intense type of manufacturing.
- Gotcha, thank you.
- Okay, any other questions for the city?
If not, would the applicant
like to say anything?
No?
Okay.
Any public comments?
Public comments?
If not, any motions
regarding this agenda item
from the board.
- Make a motion to approve.
- Robert, we have a motion
to approve from Robert.
Do we have a second?
- Second.
- We have a second from Melissa.
Any discussion?
- No.
- If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
And public hearings, do we have anything?
Nothing?
- We don't.
As of right now, I'm 99%
sure that we will not have
a February 21st Planning
Advisory Board meeting.
We don't have any
applications that are ready.
But I will confirm that
with a meeting cancellation.
- How are we gonna earn our pay here?
You need to maybe send Alicia
out with a sandwich board,
accepting applications for reasons.
No.
- Yeah.
- Brenda's good.
(chuckling)
- Yeah.
Again, I do wanna apologize for
the lateness for the agenda.
Again, I was feeling under the weather,
but to provide that out to you.
The only thing that I
just wanted to reiterate
is to make sure
when we do send out
those email notifications
about a week before the
meetings, just to go ahead
and to respond whether or not
you would be attending or not,
so that way, we're aware
of it moving forward.
I do understand that
things happen the day of,
but just respond so
that way we can confirm
with security and confirm
with the applicants
that we're gonna have the
meetings the week before.
- Okay.
Is it the pollen, you said?
- Pollen, what?
- The pollen.
- Oh yes, yes, I'm so out of it, yes.
- I have a white car and a black car.
Right now, they're both yellow, orange.
- Yes.
- Kind of.
- Mine is about the
yellow bumblebee, yeah,
color right now with the pollen.
- Suffering together.
Discussion.
Board members?
I have nothing.
Anyone?
Deputy City Attorney?
Alicia, Brenda, anyone?
Robert?
No?
Okay.
Anyone wanna make a motion to adjourn?
- I'll make a motion to adjourn.
- Robert, motion to adjourn.
Do we have a second?
- I second that.
- And we have a second from Melissa.
Any discussion on that?
Public comment?
No, okay.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
Opposed, please say no.
Meeting is adjourned at 6:14, 6:14.
Thank you.
I know, I know.