- Okay, calling the meeting
to order at 6:02 PM.
Thank you all for being here.
Can I ask everyone to stand
for a moment of silence
and the pledge of allegiance please?
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation under God,
indivisible with liberty
and justice for all.
- Thank you, please be seated.
I'm gonna ask everybody to,
and I'll make sure I do also,
silence your electronic devices
please, board members too.
Okay, first up, we have
approval of the July 17th, 2020
PAB meeting minutes.
Do we have any motions regarding that?
- Can I interject really
quickly too as well before,
just to remind the board,
the Planning Advisory Board,
to maintain consistency with
our other advisory boards
and City Commission, if
there are any motions
to make modifications to the PAB
that it should not be for verbatim.
The city clerk and city policies
is that any motions that you may entertain
should not include verbatim
because the general practice
is the minutes are not verbatim.
So I just wanted to keep that in mind
as you go through the
minutes and the motion.
We got that clarification
from our city clerk's office
that we have to maintain consistency
with our other advisory
boards and City Commission
being it's minutes should not be verbatim.
- Okay.
- And you'll see the slight changes
because this is why we have
three minutes brought back,
that we brought it back to you
consistent with city
policies regarding minutes.
- So we're approving, like,
are there inaccuracies
or things like that?
Like, wrong dates and stuff.
- There were motions
that were made before-
- Specifically what was said-
- And that's why we're bringing back
three sets minutes to you.
- Oh, okay, okay, so Robert, you?
- To make a motion.
- Motion to approve?
- Yes.
- Robert Kaplan, do we have a second?
- Second.
- Second from Alex, any discussion?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- And I'm gonna, after
discussion with Kalanit,
I'm just gonna abstain
because I wasn't here,
because I'm saying,
yeah, I agree with this,
so I wasn't here so I'm
abstaining from that.
And then August 7th PAB minutes.
Do we have a motion regarding
that meeting minutes?
- Motion to approve.
- Robert, motion to approve,
do we have a second?
- Second.
- Second from Alex.
And do we have any
discussion changes, anything?
If not, all in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- And abstain 'cause I wasn't
here, and for September 4th.
Do we have a motion to
approve or any motion?
- Make a motion to approve.
- Robert, motion to approve,
do we have a second?
- I'll second.
- We have a second from Alex.
Any discussion or changes?
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- I was here for that
one, okay, all business.
Nothing there, new
business, 5A public hearing.
- Might hope if I turn
this on, there we go.
Board members, before you today
is a request for an approval
of a conditional use
with site plan waiver
to establish a driving
school at 400 Church Street
on approximately 0.34 acres of land
with a mixed use T5-M zoning designation.
The structure was built in 1955
and was used at the church
for multiple tenants,
including Calvary Assembly of God
and St. Luke's Missionary Church.
In 1980, a permit was submitted
for the concrete pavement that now exists
and the parcel zoning was
B4 Main Street commercial
before it was rezoned
for the T5-M mixed use
center transect zoning,
which is its current zoning now.
It also has a future land use of MUD,
which is mixed use downtown.
Currently there are multiple
businesses tied to this parcel.
Currently Your Holistic Center, LLC,
which is a retail professional
service establishment
and essential services for u-inc,
which is another professional
service establishment,
have current 2025 business license.
In 2024, there were also business license
for a dental office and
a chiropractic office.
This proposed conditional use
is intended to use the property
as an educational service establishment,
specifically an online driving school
that will include spaces for people
who do not have access to computers.
There will be two computers on site.
Since the building is considered
a legal non-conforming
and this conditional use
is not expanding that non-conformity,
the development review
committee did not see the need
for major improvements
to the parking area.
For the findings and reasons,
this is compliant with the intent
of the mixed use center T5-M
as a conditional use per section 14 5 4f
of the land development code.
It's in compliance with
section 14 5 6, table 5 1,
which is our use table,
as educational service
establishments are conditional use
in this zoning district.
It's compliant with section 14 3 29c2
for the site plan waiver
as there's no all interior,
all modifications will be
interior there's no exterior,
you know, for existing parking or loading
or the existing building
happening or occurring.
It's in compliance with
section 14 3 29g 1 through 13
for the conditional use review
from our land development code.
And it is compliant
with comprehensive plan future
land use element policy 1292
for the mixed use
downtown future land use.
The development review
in September 9th, 2024
approved this with conditions,
and those conditions are as followed.
One, approval of an educational
service establishment
for a driving school
is for 400 Church Street Unit 109 only.
This educational service establishment use
cannot be transferred or
expanded to another suite.
A separate conditional use application
and approval by the
Planning Advisory Board
will be required to transfer or expand
this educational service
establishment on this parcel.
A business license for the driving school
must be issued within one year
of the conditional use approval.
If a business license is
not issued within a year,
the conditional use
approval will be revoked.
Once the business license is issued,
the conditional use is
valid on this parcel.
If there's ever a lapse of one year
with no business license
with this conditional use,
the approval will be considered void.
For the driving school
is limited to a maximum of
two students at any given time
for those computers and for the parking,
and there shall be no modifications
to the Toho infrastructure, and that's it.
- Okay, board members, any
questions for the city?
If not, are the applicants
here, the applicants?
You're welcome to step to the podium,
and if you'd like to say
anything or add anything,
you're not required
but you're welcome to if you'd like.
- No, just to say hello to everybody,
but know we're fine.
- Okay, thank you.
Board, do we have any motions
regarding this agenda item?
- I missed what kind
of educational program?
- Sorry, a question, go ahead.
- It's an online driving school,
but they are offering two computers
for those who don't have
access to the internet
to go get the certification
for the driving portion.
- Okay.
- So, sorry, Aaron, do you
have something, go ahead.
- When I was reviewing this
particular conditional use
for this particular property,
knowing the vibrancy in the direction
the downtown city is going,
my concerns with bringing in
an educational institution
at this particular location
could cause some issues with the growth
going into that main street
where it's crossing from
Broadway to Main Street,
you have that tattoo shop
that's right behind it.
I feel like there are restrictions
in the state of Florida.
I'm not quite sure what
they are in Osceola County.
What can open and not be
open near a educational?
I do know, I believe, in
Orlando it's 500 feet,
but I'm not sure if it's the
same here in Osceola County.
But I just wanted to make sure
will that cause any issues
if other shops wanted to open up nearby
that may be the extension
of maybe restaurants
that have bars, right?
Would that be a issue
with them being there
as an educational institution
at this particular location?
- I mean, the s, oh goodness,
'cause I wanna get the
verbiage just perfect.
The educational service establishments
are more like vocational,
they're not like institutions or schools,
but they do give training for other,
for certification or something like that.
So usually with the limit
of being near an alcohol store or bar
or something like that,
that's primarily for colleges,
elementary school, middle.
But this kind of educational establishment
wouldn't be considered.
So anybody could be able
to have their bar on the next parcel.
- Okay, I had to, I think,
I can't recall what Florida statute or-
- I think you're referring to.
- I have to look at
it, exactly what it is.
But I think the terms was private.
I think the way it reads
in the actual language,
it doesn't permit just for middle schools,
high schools, and secondary schools.
I think it also included
any type of private type of institutions.
This would be considered a
private business, correct?
- It would not.
The key difference is
that for your business,
you don't have to coordinate
and get certification
department education.
- Yeah, and they're only gonna be in with,
it's not a consistent daily people
coming as an institution for education.
It's just for to take testing.
- I'm sorry, actually,
if he's gonna speak,
he should please step to the microphone,
state your name and your
address for the record, please.
- Sorry, good afternoon,
I'm Ruben from MBG Traffic.
- State your name and address
for the record, please.
- Ruben, that's my name, yes.
Oh, my address, 9029,
Reflection Point Drive,
Windermere, Florida, 34786.
It's not a typical institution
where educational institution
where you actually go daily
to get some kind of
information or testing,
it's just is an online service
that when people do not
have access to online,
they could have the
opportunity to make a date
and go in, sorry, in
office and tailor testing
for those who don't have
the ability to do it online.
But it's usually very seldom
and typically everything is done online.
So there is no really,
like, constant education taking place.
Like, you're going to
sign up for something,
you have to go Monday through
Friday or anything like that.
It's just a occasional kind
of assistant to the office.
So we're not really gonna have
a lot of people coming in
or out nor on any basis.
And certainly is only till
four o'clock in the afternoon or so.
So that's pretty much the extent
of what we're gonna be doing in that.
- But I think the statute that
you're referring to, Aaron,
has to do with proximity
of certain businesses
to educational facilities.
Kalanit, can you weigh in on that?
Is that just public schools
that that's a concern with?
- I don't think that that
is applicable to this,
but yes, typically it is a school.
This is not actually a school.
This is, I mean, it's
educational services,
but I think it's more internet access.
- Okay, thank you,
any other questions or
comments from board members?
- I have no further questions.
Thank you for the explanations.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- I have nothing further, I yield back.
- Okay, anyone wanna make a motion
regarding this agenda item?
- Make a motion to approve
with this conditions.
- Okay, Robert makes a motion
to approve with the conditions,
do we have a second?
- I'll second.
- We have a second from Alex.
Any further discussion?
If not, oh, wait a minute.
Let me ask before I move to the vote,
do we have any public comments?
Do we have any public comments?
Public comments, no?
Also, let me say before we move to a vote,
I apologize, Kalanit, I forgot
this piece outta practice.
If anybody has any conflicts of interest
or have done any site visits
or had ex parte communications
regarding this agenda item,
please let that be known before we vote.
If not, we'll move to a vote.
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries,
thank you, thank you.
And next on the agenda, there we go.
Okay, public hearings, we have anything?
We don't have anything.
Discussion, any discussion
from board members?
I always wondering,
what is the difference between discussion
and here chairman and board members.
Isn't that kind of redundant
or is there a specific thing
that's supposed to be slotted into that?
- Again, it's the advisory boards
and City Commission has the same template.
So they have the same sections,
it's the same template throughout
for all advisory boards
and City Commission.
So it'll have that section,
but it won't be applicable.
- Okay.
- We all use the same template
for City Commission and Advisory Board.
- Got it, got it, so we will
move to number eight here,
chairman and board members,
I don't have anything in
particular board members.
- Well, I guess I so sorry,
Brenda, could you clarify again?
You said the minutes came back
and we had to re-approve them, why?
What was the kind of the,
that's different, yeah.
- So when the motion was made,
we couldn't approve the minutes.
We had to bring them back.
Staff went to city clerk's office
for clarification about
the proposed changes.
And it was reiterated to us
that there is for minutes
do not have to be and really
should not be verbatim.
So if there are any motions
making where a statement
to change the wording to
where it was verbatim,
that is not something
that should be under consideration
to make for future
modifications to the minutes.
So if their motions made to change wording
to where it's verbatim
based on the city policy
and to maintain consistency
with advisory boards,
those motions should not be made
because minutes should not be verbatim.
That was the clarification that-
- And did that happen recently?
- Yes, I think one of 'em
was to change one word
from what the staff had.
It wasn't a verbatim,
but it was a motion made to
change that word to verbatim,
a verbatim statement.
- I mean, yes, several
times ago I made a motion
to modify one of the minutes
because I felt as though
not to change the word to be verbatim
but to the word that was used,
but to change the word because
the word in the minutes
didn't have the same
connotation or meaning
or definition as the
word that what happened.
I didn't think that they were accurate.
So I guess whether or not, you know,
the minute should or
shouldn't be verbatim,
they ought to be accurate
and they ought to reflect
what was actually done or said
or happened presumably.
- But it was a word again, if
it's overall context to it,
and we need to maintain that consistency
with all the advisory boards
and City Commission minutes.
If there was a wrong motion,
and I don't know if you
even noticed too as well
that we've changed it
to where it's not specific board members,
it's just discussion.
And that was the advice and direction
that our city clerk provided to us
where it's not, "Chairman
so-and-so said this,"
it was discussion ensued.
That is the proper way moving forward
to maintain consistency
with other minutes.
- Fair enough, I guess the other thing
I guess I just wanted to discuss or say,
so in our last meeting we had
that mill slew street vacation
that we discussed and we
proposed an amendment too.
When that went before the City Commission,
city staff recommended
kind of going with the original proposal,
in the agenda packet for the board,
I think there was a few sentences
describing the discussion that we had,
the extensive discussion I
think we had in the meeting.
But overall I was a little
sort of disappointed
with the presentation of our discussion
before the City Commission.
And I guess I just wanted to make aware
to the other board members
that sort of that happened, so.
- Okay, let me address that.
The motion and discussions for
the Planning Advisory Board
is reflected in the
minutes or the actions,
and we as staff as well as
the Planning Advisory Board
should not change, modify
any actions that took place.
The action and discussion
is reflected in the minutes.
So we are not to inflect
expand on any motion
that was made on the
Planning Advisory Board.
Staff's responsibility
is to present the staff
recommendation and to state,
"This was the Planning
Advisory Board motion
"and recommendation and that was it."
No board member ever outside
of the form of this meeting
should embellish or modify any action.
It's reflected in the minutes,
it's reflected in the staff report.
It should not occur anything
outside of the actions
with the Planning Advisory Board,
really, it should not, ever.
- I guess I'm not sure-
- This was the motion,
this was the conditions, and that was it.
We, even as staff,
don't have the authority
to embellish or say anything
beyond what was done in those minutes.
- I'm gonna take the floor
and just see if I understand
you clearly, Brenda.
Basically, when you're presenting
an action that we take here to the city,
you are saying factually
that this is what was done.
And my understanding is
always that in minutes,
it should state what is
done not what is said.
And so the actions that were taken.
So you're presenting here's what happened
without any emotions or regard to that.
And that if we as board
members and citizens
want to discuss any item on the agenda
for the City Commission meeting,
we have the right to go and
make public comment as a citizen
about how we feel about that.
We have that right to do that, correct?
- Yes.
- If we do that, should that not be,
that should be us as a citizen,
private citizen, not as,
"Hey, I'm Planning Advisory Board member
"and here's my thoughts."
I mean, although it's a matter of record
that we're a member
Planning Advisory Board.
So it's not inaccurate to say it,
but we are speaking for ourselves
as a citizen about our opinion.
Am I correct on that?
So we could do that and state that,
or state whatever we wanted to state
under those circumstances.
- Yeah, so-
- But all that you're to present is,
"This is what was done, this
is the action was taken."
- And I think I understand
what everyone is saying.
I guess from my part I'd
like to point out that yes,
I spoke before the City Commission
and I tried to make clear that
I was speaking in my capacity
as a citizen at the time.
I also understand that the
city staff cannot embellish
or sort of say things
sort of beyond the actions
that this board takes.
I guess I'm making a comment
now because I feel like,
you know, we discussed
and passed a amendment
to the proposal that came
before this board and,
I mean, I guess the question is
what constitutes presentation
of that to the board, right?
You know, we approved amendment
to kind of change the boundary,
and I guess being in that room,
it didn't seem like that was
communicated to the board.
You know, that wasn't kind of drawn up.
There wasn't a map, there wasn't, yeah,
anything of that sort.
The city agenda had the sort
of original proposal in it.
- So for clarification, are you asking
what is the extent of PAB recommendations
that go before City Commission?
Like how detailed does the
recommendation have to be?
Is that your concern?
- Yeah, I guess going
forward, I'm wondering about,
in so much as we have a
role as an advisory board,
if matters come before this
board that we think either,
you know, basically how are we best
to operate in our capacity
and what steps can we take
as a board to try to ensure
that the City Commission
is making the best
and most informed choices
and the ones that we think aligns
with the city comprehensive plan.
And I guess just going forward,
if we wanted to communicate
our concerns to the board,
what's the sort of
appropriate way to do that?
Is it most appropriate to make comments
as independent citizens before the board?
Or are there actions that
this board could take
to sort of better prepare things
to present to the commission?
- I just wanna clarify
because we're bringing this
up in a public meeting,
the Planning Advisory Board recommendation
and the condition about changing it
was reflected in the staff report
and was presented to the City Commission
and there was a map that
was displayed during that.
It was done.
- Was the map the original proposal
or was it the boundaries that
we amended in the PAB meeting?
- It was the original proposal.
- Yes.
- We were not to draw a separate map
reflecting the Planning
Advisory Board recommendation.
It was included in the action.
It was included in the staff report,
the recommendation and the
motion about the missing segment.
It was verbally stated
and it was also included
in that staff report.
So I'm a bit confused at this point.
- I guess, I mean, I am too.
So I'm wondering, in the
future, hypothetically,
if another action comes before this board
and we feel like there's a
mistake in the original proposal,
I mean, even something minor,
like a mistake in the original map,
and let's say even, I mean,
and we want to amend it
to address that mistake,
how then do we effectively
communicate that
to the commission?
Is there any steps we could
take to, I don't know,
communicate that to the commission?
- Let me ask you a question
to see if I understand
what you're saying, Alex.
Are you saying that because,
I mean, during the meeting,
whatever the discussion is-
- Yes,
- That's the time where we
present our opinions, our ideas,
and correct me if I'm
wrong on this procedurally,
legally, or anything,
and we are asking questions,
we're presenting our opinions,
all of that sort of thing,
and then we come to an agreement,
majority rules following
the voting process.
Are you saying that once that's done
and, you know, whether the
vote goes our way or whatever,
once that's done
and they go to present it
at the City Commission,
are you saying if we are at the meeting
and we think that they
are presenting something
that is inaccurate or not factual?
Is that what you're saying?
- No, I guess I'm just worried.
I'm wondering, going forward,
for the most part, historically this board
tends to approve the
motions that come before us.
I think in part because we
don't find issues with them,
we think that the proposals
are in keeping with
the comprehensive plan.
But if something does
come before the board
that we think doesn't,
if we wanna modify
conditions or something,
I mean, that happens
somewhat frequently, right?
We either approve things
with or without conditions
at the recommendations
of the City Commission
or the city staff.
I guess I'm wondering, if we, as a board,
make any sort of recommendations
or changes or amendments,
what, I don't know, how does that,
or do we have any influence on,
how can we best act to then ensure
that the City Commission has access to,
I mean, hopefully the benefits
of our own process, right,
as this board,
and I guess just in this particular case,
it felt like we looked at the
proposal, we had discussion,
there were people from the public,
we kind of talked everything out.
I understand that's all
matter of public record.
But then kind of when it went
before the City Commission,
the city staff recommendation
was to go with the original proposal
and the presentation amounted to,
you know, a statement that
the PAB passed an amendment.
- Okay, I think I understand
now where you're coming from.
The PAB made a different separate
recommendation from staff,
but that doesn't mean moving forward
that staff only presents
the PAB modification.
- Okay, hold on,
I'm following Robert's rules of order.
Robert, Robert has a comment
and he hasn't spoken on
this topic yet, and we have.
So, Robert, go ahead.
- I just wanna bring in mind
that basically we don't change anything,
we're just fact checkers.
If we find something,
it goes back to them,
and they look at it and see
if we're right or wrong.
They may have overlooked
something, sometimes they don't.
Most of the time they don't.
But we're here just to see if they did.
And if we accept it,
then they go and say,
"Okay, it's done right."
It goes through the
commission, they vote on it.
But we just check what they're doing,
we don't change anything.
- Well, I guess disagree a
little bit with you, Robert,
right, in the sense that
the city charter outlines
our responsibilities and
obligations and powers and duties
and those include considering or proposing
any sort of amendments to
the city comprehensive plan.
And you know, whether or not
that's a power that we
historically executed as a board,
like it is in the city charter
and it is part of our own responsibility.
And I guess regardless of that, you know,
the outline in the Florida State Code
is that we're an advisory board
and we have an obligation and a duty
to advise the City
Commission on these actions.
I mean, the reason we exist is
to kind of give citizen input
to these choices before they
go before the commission.
I'm trying to better understand
how that process works
and what we can do to
most be effective in this.
- The process works like
this, we're here to help them.
We don't really make decisions,
we don't make decisions, they do.
We're here to look at what
they brought to us and say,
"Hey, did I dot my T, cross my I,"
and we say yes or no.
- Well, I, yeah-
- In some respect.
- I'm gonna say
I am not completely in
agreement with that, Robert,
in that if we think
that something goes
against the best interest,
because again, as Alex said,
we are representing our community-
- That's part of our job.
- And the citizens.
- We don't make the decisions
to say, "Change it."
- Okay, so just to-
- Go, ahead, Kalanit,
just to briefly clarify,
your role is to send an advisory opinion
to City Commission, that's it.
- Yep.
- So what you recommend to City Commission
may at times be different
than what staff recommends
to City Commission.
And it is up to City Commission
to decide between those options,
if that's even what's before them.
- And the city has overruled
our opinions in the past
on things gone the other way.
- They've overruled staff
recommendations too.
- Sorry?
- They've also overruled staff
recommendations too as well.
Yes, it's not just you guys.
- Yeah, and I guess,
so my question is how-
- How do you ensure that whatever is-
- That our proposals
are presented in the way
that we think is most
effective to the commission?
It sounds like the basic
operating procedure
is anything we do in the PAB,
it's already kind of
part of public record,
it's part of our own minutes
and the minutes from our meeting
are kind of part of the packet
that goes into the agenda
for any of the corresponding
items that go before the board.
- Correct.
- Are there any-
- Can you have a greater influence
than what is decided by the board, no.
- No, not then what is
decided by the board.
But is there, I guess like, do other-
- I mean, by PAB, your board,
your casting a recommendation.
- Yes.
- And is your concern that it
is not presented accurately,
and you wanna make sure
that it is presented accurately?
What is the disconnect?
- Yeah, I guess the question is-
- How do you ensure that
it is portrayed accurately?
- That it's portrayed, yes, accurately,
or yeah, portrayed in a way
that yeah, portrayed accurately.
- I think staff does a good job
of giving the PAB recommendations
in your capacity as a citizen.
You can absolutely rate your
commissioners in advance
and dispute the findings.
- I guess, yeah, I don't know.
I guess, like, do other municipalities,
is there ever, you know,
representatives from the PAB
to present the PABs actions
before the commission?
- I can speak on that in another city
that I was a board liaison,
my same role here to as well,
no, because it can invalidate
that planning that local,
it can invalidate potentially
the action that the board takes
when you have individual
Planning Advisory Board members
conflict acting on changing
or modifying motions
and things that were made previously,
when you have actual representatives
coming as PAB members
to those city council meetings,
to those City Commission meetings
where you're essentially
potentially a conflict
where you are modifying
changing the action
that was taken by the
Planning Advisory Board.
It's also potentially for
the applicant too as well.
'cause they're moving
forward in good faith
that their item was presented
to the Planning Advisory Board.
There were motions that were made,
there were conditions that were made,
there may have been
modifications that were made,
and then now it moves forward
to a city counselor, City Commission.
And you have of Planning
Advisory Board member now,
and you're talking to the City Commission,
presenting a potential conflict
that there are modifications or things
that are happening outside of
that Planning Advisory Board
as a body, it's a
potential risk liability,
and it's also to the applicant
too that they can come back
and say potentially
that if that project doesn't
get approved, what have you,
because of statements
and things that were made
by a Planning Advisory Board member
outside of a Planning
Advisory Board meeting,
that could clearly invalidate that project
and grounds for that city
organization to be liable,
'cause you're making potentially changes
or modifications outside of this board.
- I'm sorry, what were the
changes and modifications
that you believe I made?
- No, to answer your question
about the reason why we just have to,
during the City Commission meeting,
we have to factually state,
"This went to the Planning
Advisory Board on this day.
"This was a recommendation,
this was the conditions."
Matter of fact, that was it.
- And then if we, but
if we pass an amendment.
- Which was included in the staff report,
which was also presented
to the City Commission
regarding this particular item.
- And that's the extent
of the presentation
that will ever be made.
- Correct.
- Let me ask again, just for
clarification purposes, Alex,
if I understand what you're saying,
let's say we take an action,
we vote on it, we approve something,
and we feel very strongly about it
and we've had a lot of discussion
and maybe it's unanimous
and we all feel very strongly about this.
And so Brenda and her
team go to the commission
and they present it in a factual manner
because they don't have, you know,
maybe the passion or whatever behind,
whatever it is, whatever it is, okay?
And they present it.
Are you concerned that the
com City Commission hears it
and they only see the
black and white details
of what was happening?
They don't hear the discussion
or all of the whys and wherefores
of why we voted necessarily.
So therefore the message
isn't, or not the message,
but the intent isn't conveyed adequately
to the City Commission
so that they're thinking,
"Okay, based on the numbers,
I'm gonna vote against it."
Again, this is all hypothetical.
- Yeah.
- Versus somebody, you know,
we all felt very strongly we
really want this to happen,
and then the city, the staff says,
"This happened, this
happened, this happened,"
and they hear it very cut and dried.
And so is that your concern
that then they don't hear
all the why's and wherefores,
they just see the actions
that we're taking?
- Yes, I'm trying to, I'm trying to,
I like what you're saying.
Yeah, like, hypothetical future scenario,
something comes before the board,
we feel very passionate about it,
we have extensive conversations about it,
we suggested amendment that we think
brings it in alignment with
the comprehensive plan.
I guess again, 'cause I'm
relatively new to this,
what I've observed now and my
understanding going forward
is all that will kind of get communicated
to the commission at that point
is sort of like our minutes.
It might be a couple sentences,
you know, after discussion,
the PAB proposed an amendment
to the thing that does
x, you know, one sentence
and then in the chambers
at the City Commission,
the following City Commission meeting,
my expectation going forward the,
my understanding is that the city staff
will present the sort of original report
that we heard before our board
and then say the PAB
proposed an amendment to do x
and voted, you know, 301.
My understanding at this point
is that's the sort of extent
of what happens here
that will go before the City Commission.
- I think it's supposed
to be kind of a dragnet
just the facts kind of thing.
That they're supposed to present.
But Kalanit, did you have
something you wanted to add?
- Just briefly.
- Okay.
- And I don't mean this
to be kumbaya or anything,
but I think it's part
of the democratic
political process, right?
You're tasked with
bringing a recommendation
to City Commission
and then it's left to the
public to then come forward
and say whatever it is they have to say
in support or in opposition
to the agenda item proposed.
- Sorry, go ahead.
Okay, so again, just to clarify, again,
is there any problem if any board members
wants to come to a City
Commission meeting,
speak on the record?
- Absolutely not.
- As a private citizen and state,
I'm not representing the board.
This is my opinion about this
and this is what we should do.
- No, I mean, it is absolutely
within everybody's right
to go as a private citizen
and say whatever they have to say.
But I understand what you're saying, Alex,
and it can be frustrating at times,
but I think the idea is, you as a board,
you are charted with
bringing a recommendation
to City Commission.
I understand the frustration
if it's not articulated
as well as you would like it to be
either written or verbally,
but at the end it is just like
you said, the facts, right?
We recommend with
conditions, blah, blah blah,
and then it goes to City Commission.
And at that point it is open to the,
we don't get much public here,
but you know, at City Commission,
that is definitely the opportunity.
- So it's not the staff's
job responsibility
or even prerogative to sell the idea to
the city commission, correct?
- It's a conflict
because it can begin seen as favoritism
over one projects over another.
This is why it has to be
matter of fact and factual.
It can't be where there's a perception
where there's some level of favoritism,
you know, overly, you know,
with one project over another.
You have to understand
that perception too,
that there cannot be
any type of favoritism
or any type of perception of that.
So as Kalanit is saying, as a
private citizen, absolutely,
but it presents liability
and issues and problems
if you go before the City Commission
as a Planning Advisory Board member,
it causes problems
potentially for that project
and for that applicant.
It's a conflict really, because
it's that potential, again,
decisions were made
and it's also respecting
the Planning Advisory Board
as a whole too as well
and not an individual
where you have your own
individual interest as a citizen.
So that way there's not
any potential conflict
where you are presenting
to the City Commission
outside a Planning Advisory Board.
It could potentially, again,
be a liability for the city as well.
- So I have a solution potentially,
if there are motions of this board
that are different than
what is proposed by staff,
I think that those motions
should be very specific and detailed
and therefore the record
will speak for itself
and there won't be ambiguities.
And we did that for, we made
it separate as Capital Fox.
- Yeah, and maybe we disagree on that.
I was both at the PAB boarding
and then I was at the
City Commission meeting
and I don't think anyone,
any of the members of
the public in that room
who are the people who
supposedly can speak then
to the action that we're taking.
I don't think any of them understood
that we amended the proposal.
I don't think any of the commissioners,
at least from the discussion
that happened in the commission meeting,
understood any of the action that we took
or the discussion that we had.
And so that makes it hard
to feel though democracy
could play its role.
- Regrettably that is
the peril of democracy.
- Yeah.
- Unfortunately if there's
not an educated populace,
then there cannot be
any informed decisions.
- Yeah.
- By policy makers, but
that is a broader problem.
- And it sounds like, yes, okay.
So it sounds like, it sounds
like going forward in so much
as we, as a board feel
as though an amendment might be necessary
to bring things in alignment
with the comprehensive plan,
it sounds like we should
try to make such amendments
as sort of as detailed
and impactful as possible
that will be brought before the board.
And then it does sound
like we have every right,
as an individual citizen to
speak at City Commission.
But we need to be very careful
to not speak as members of
the Planning Advisory Board
before the City Commission
as that would create
some kind of conflict.
- Correct.
- Thank you, anyone else?
If not, do we have a motion to adjourn?
- Motion to adjourn.
- I heard Alex actually,
do we have a second?
- I second.
- We have a second from Aaron.
- All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
Meeting adjourned, 6:48, thank you.