- Let me know if you guys are ready?
Okay, calling the meeting
to order at six o'clock.
Please stand for a moment of silence
and Pledge of Allegiance.
- I pledge allegiance to the Flag
of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation, under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
- Thank you.
Please silence all electronic devices.
Let me make sure mine is.
And if any board members
have had any sort of outside,
done any outside research
about any of our agenda items,
or have any conflicts of interest,
or had ex-parte communications
with any of the parties,
please make that known.
And let's take a look at
the March 20th minutes.
Do we have any motions
regarding those minutes?
- I make a motion to approve.
- We have a motion to
approve from Robert Spalding.
- Second.
- Second from Melissa Thacker.
Any changes or discussion, any discussion?
If not, oh yeah, Alex, go ahead.
- Sorry, I was just checking
Greg's email last week,
and I was double-checking Robert's Rules
and I think you were right.
You said that according to Robert's Rules
the minutes generally do consist of just
the business that was done
in the meetings, and less-
- My understanding is what
is done, not what is said,
is my understanding.
- Yes.
I mean, but these minutes also include
some of our commentary, I mean,
I think it does seem
like there's a precedent
to have sort of an
overview of the discussion,
but I think if you wanted
to, you could (indistinct).
How do we feel about that?
- As far as these having
what was said by individuals on here?
Is that-
- Yeah.
- Okay, is that, are you asking that...
Kalanit, what is your take on it?
- So, minutes, just the
requirements by statute,
is that minutes must be taken,
there's no specificity of
what those minutes need to be.
Typically, we like to have
them just action-based,
so not too much back and forth dialogue.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't think it hurts,
but, you know, what
part, I don't know, Alex,
where you're coming from
with this, but, you know-
- Alex, are you talking
about like where it says,
'Planning Member, Ryan, stated that,'
those things there?
- Yeah.
You know, and again, I guess I just
tried to do some homework.
- Yeah.
- Our Board is governed by Robert's Rules,
the Rules, Section 48-2 says,
'In minutes you retain
what is done in meetings,
'not what is said.'
- That's always been my understanding.
Are you asking that these
be amended to delete the-
- I think staff would
very much be in favor
of just having just very condensed-
- Makes her job easier.
- Action-based minutes, moving forward.
- Yeah, but I also wanna
point out that the city,
it's Robert's Rules,
but the city also has policies
by the Clerk's Office.
We've streamlined a lot of it
because before it was verbatim,
and so the changes that we have,
that we had training from
the City Clerk's Office
to stream line a lot of that.
So that maybe could be something
that we could take up
with the Clerk's Office,
but I know they have their own guidelines.
- I agree, less is best,
and just put on the record,
regardless of what's in our minutes,
it is not verbatim.
It's nothing that's
particularly actionable,
if somebody was to contest
any decision of the Board
they would have to have had
a court reporter present
and use that as their basis for appeal.
So it doesn't incriminate us,
if that's a concern, Alex.
But yes, I think we can probably,
moving forward we can just
have an action-based and not...
- Yeah, so I guess I will (indistinct),
I'll make a motion to amend-
- Well there's a motion on the
floor already to approve it.
- Amendments get precedent
over (indistinct), right?
- Can anybody-
- Motion to amend the-
- Second, okay.
Okay, so you are motioning what?
- So I will make a motion
to amend the minutes
and to strike the subsequent paragraphs
starting with 'Board member Lenny asked'
then, as well as 'planning
member Ryan stated'
followed by 'Board member Lenny asked'
followed by 'planning member Ryan stated'.
And it's-
- Ending where?
- Those paragraphs.
- Okay, just those, okay.
Okay, then do we have a second
for that motion to amend?
- Yeah, I'll second that.
- Okay, we have a second.
Any further discussion?
If not, all in favor as
amended, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, minutes are approved.
I don't disagree with-
- I'm sorry you said
the minutes are approved
subject to the amendments,
so that means that you're
wanting to bring it back?
Or approving it as is?
- Approved with the strikeouts.
- The strikeouts, strike through?
- Yeah, so it doesn't need
to come back, correct?
It was approved with the removal,
with the redaction of that.
So I, yeah, I don't object to it
'cause it's simpler for everybody
and that was always my understanding
is what's done and not what is said.
- And so I think that what I'm gathering
is the consensus of the
Board is, moving forward,
we should just have an action-based-
- That is my opinion, I'm just one voice.
- Well why don't we, why
doesn't somebody make a motion?
- Well, so I'm not sure we need to.
My impression is we wouldn't
need to move on that
if that's already sort of the
governing rules for the body.
- Apparently it is not, so.
- But I think, is it just
a function at this point
of perhaps not understanding
what should be included in the minutes
of whomever wrote this?
- No.
- No?
- Respectfully, no, no.
It was, again, it was
part of cross training
from the City Clerk's
Office across the Board
for Advisory Boards.
So there's some consistency
in certain types of detail
and information.
I understand with Robert's Rules,
but because especially in the case of
if this particular amendment moves forward
to City Commission, they
would like to know perhaps
sometimes part of the discussion
if there was some type
of issue that came up,
the reasoning and justification behind it.
So this is why this has
been a long standing,
where a bit more information is included
on some of these types of amendments,
zoning map amendments, what have you.
It provides a little bit more
clarity and justification
as to there was some
concerns about traffic,
there was some concerns about
certain types of things,
and they understand and,
looking at the minutes,
they understand that these
were particular issues
during the Planning Advisory Board.
- Okay.
I guess, is there a workaround
where the Commission
can get what they need,
but still be adherent to-
- Again, we've streamlined,
it used to be verbatim,
that this was training that
our staff has gone through
with our City Clerk's Office,
as to how minutes are
presented, are streamlined.
- What's the city's legal
opinion on this discussion?
- I mean, policy is one thing
and practice is another thing.
The law does not specify what
needs to be in the minutes.
Nothing, I mean, again, as I said,
if anybody was to challenge a decision
that's something where the
minutes would scarcely help them.
They would have to have
a court reporter here,
having a verbatim transcript,
not our audio recording.
But I do believe we have
audio recording back up.
- Okay, let me ask this,
read verbatim for us Alex,
what it says regarding-
- Yeah, so Robert, so
my first understanding
is reading the City code
it very clearly says
that the Planning Advisory Board
is governed by Robert's Rules.
- Okay, but what does that
specifically state, verbatim?
- 48.2 says 'Content of minutes,
'in an ordinary society,
the minutes should contain
'a record of what was done at the meeting,
'not specific-
- Okay, so in a legal sense
it says should, not shall,
there's a difference there.
- Right.
- So should does not dictate
that there shall not be, correct?
- Right, I mean, basically the requirement
is that you have to have the
action taken by the Board.
- So it doesn't, it's not stating
in Robert's Rules of Order
that it must not include that.
- Correct.
- It is just saying should,
which is the legal difference
between should and shall.
- Right.
- That and the fact that
these meetings are recorded,
audio recorded-
- Yes.
- So everything, verbatim, is available.
I think the only thing that
shortening the minutes would do
is take ease on the person taking minutes.
- Yes.
- But if there's no
harm to having it, then-
- There is-
- If it's helpful for City Commission.
- Provided that they're, you
know, accurate depictions,
which is what staff aims to do.
- And that's why we check
the minutes before moving on.
- Right.
I mean mostly to make
sure that there aren't
misrepresentations, that
the vote is correct,
the outcome is correct, and
that any, you know, opposition.
I think a big portion is not really to
capture everybody's back and forth,
but really to get the
public's input on the record.
- Mm-hmm.
So, if we were to do any sort of vote
that's not already on the agenda,
would that need to be pushed forward
to another meeting where
that item would be published?
Three days in advance?
- I mean, not if it's
something that's house keeping,
which this would be.
Again, as I said, if I'm an applicant
and my application gets denied,
I'm not looking to the
minutes for my appeal.
- I'm ambivalent about
whether it's on there or not,
but I believe that it
should always be accurate,
and when it states that,
because these are not specific quotes,
we don't have a court reporter,
it really is more of a guideline I guess,
like you're saying, to
the City Commission.
I'm pretty ambivalent about this.
But, again, my understanding
always was that it's,
the minutes should be what
is done, not what is said,
but again, reading that,
verbatim, the should versus shall,
to me there's a leeway as to
whether we should or shall.
- Correct.
- Sorry, Robert, go ahead.
- I'm thinking out loud, okay.
- Speak out loud, and be heard.
- We went through this
with Tom, do you remember?
Between Robert's Rules and
how the City does things
compared to how we see it on the agenda?
It was more better for
you guys to do the work-
- Would you activate your mic?
- It was better for the City
to go ahead and do the work
and give us a short term agenda
so we didn't have to
follow everything by line
or by the rules, you
guys already did that.
The City did that.
We didn't have to do that
because it was already done.
And we took it at the generality of it
rather than the specifics.
We did that with Tom.
- Okay, so I think for now we can just
leave things as they are?
- Well, unless Alex is making a motion,
unless someone is making a motion.
- Well, I guess I just, again I'm also,
like I personally don't really,
I definitely, this feels
like a happy medium
compared to a couple weeks
ago or whatever it was-
(indistinct)
- Yeah.
- That's what sparked me
to try to dig into it,
I was wondering what, you
know, it's supposed to be,
and that's when I found the suggestion
that the minutes be what
is done not what is said.
I can understand that the,
I agree with what she said
that it said should rather than
shall so this isn't binding,
I can understand that the City would want
like an overview of what was discussed.
So I'm sort of like okay
with them as designed,
as they came forward here.
You know, my understanding
though, right now,
is I think we just approved the amendment
so that we could now
make a motion to dismiss,
or overturn that amendment if you want.
If we're already gonna let this one go-
- Well, I-
- But we just struck out those-
- Yeah, so-
- I feel like that-
- Sprawling dialogue.
- Spaces where we feel it's necessary
in those meeting specifically
and the minutes from those meetings
we could go and strike whatever.
- I don't know that, unless the City has
some reasoning, Brenda,
that we really should have
those comments back in there.
If it's not gonna matter,
I think we should just move
forward with the agenda.
Your thoughts?
- I can tell you that there
are certain City policies
that have been placed,
there's certain department policies too.
So this is why I'm gonna check and verify
about content in certain things
of what needs to be
included in those minutes.
- We need to undo the amendment.
- So is-
- Well but that strikes me as odd
because that isn't reflected in City code,
since the City code has the-
- Well there's-
- The Advisory Board doesn't
have any special designation
for how minutes should be taken.
- There's City code,
and then there's policy.
- Right, I-
- And policy is not
always enshrined in code.
And so for this stuff, I think,
for example the Clerk's Office is trying
to streamline all of the
Advisory Board proceedings.
So, for example this nice young man,
who's new to our city, three
days in, don't scare him.
(board members chuckling)
If he's not already scared.
- Welcome.
- So, you know, everybody takes minutes,
they get uploaded into our Civic Clerk,
theoretically, platform,
and so then the minutes can get published.
- So all right, let's
cut to the chase here.
Brenda is there a reason you believe
that we should have
those comments in there?
That it would be important for us to
put those comments back
in, or is it gonna matter?
- I think we can go
ahead and leave it as is
with the strike through, but
I would just request that
we can perhaps report back
on, again, the City Clerk,
the city wide policies regarding minutes
and minute preparation.
'Cause I know that we
did go through retraining
about minutes, preparation.
The difference between minutes,
and the difference
between an action summary.
When you have to have a
summary, when it's not approved,
an action summary is
different than minutes.
But the City Commission
has the same thing,
they have an action summary, pretty much,
versus the minutes, there's a
distinction between the two.
- Okay, so to Melissa's point,
maybe we look at it case by case, I guess.
If somebody has an objection to something
specific in there in the future,
but at this point we'll just work with
what we have approved at this point.
Everybody okay with that?
- Yup.
- All right, moving forward to,
already did the minutes, okay.
Old business, nothing there,
new business, 5A, Brenda?
- Okay, this is a City
initiated land use amendment
that's gonna change approximately 27 acres
of the properties that
are highlighted in red.
This general area is an
industrial hub, if you will,
of the city, Armstrong Boulevard,
just north of the airport.
The City and Development
Services, our staff,
has received increase in request
to develop addition warehousing
on the vacant properties
that you see there.
There's a total of 14 parcels,
and of the 14, six of them remain vacant.
The current mixed use Vine
future land use designation
does not facilitate
any additional warehouse within this area.
So we're requesting the land use amendment
to chance it to industrial
to further facilitate that.
As you can see that there's a
number of existing warehouses
within this area.
Had made mention that the
warehousing has been built
and developed between 1971 and 2008.
That mixed use Vine land use amendment
was established in 2010, so
a lot of that development
predates the mixed use designation itself.
In addition, I do want to point out
that we want to be
mindful and consideration
of the redevelopment efforts that we have
on the west Vine Street,
on the Vine Street corridor
that this land use amendment
will continue to allow for
industrial development, but
the intensity, if you will,
will be restricted.
Currently, right now, the mixed use Vine
allows for an FAR of six.
It will be substantially
reduced, down to 0.5.
So it will allow for
industrial development,
but not as intense or large
as the existing development that's there.
As you can tell, some
of the properties there
are a bit smaller, too, as well,
so we're doing this to
allow for the opportunity
for warehousing, but not as large
as some of the existing
development that's there.
The nearest residential
areas are going to be
on the east side of Oak Street there,
on the Dyre Boulevard and Oak Street
on the southeast corner,
is the nearest residential development.
So we definitely want
to be mindful of that.
And we've got the airport there,
a little bit on the southwest
side to show the airport
and the close proximity
to the airport itself.
And it will further attract
different types of warehousing,
that includes logistics
and also air cargo and transportation.
So we feel that this amendment
is necessary and needed,
and staff is recommending
approval at this time.
Welcome to answer any questions
or concerns that you all may have.
- Board, do you have any
comments or questions?
- Yeah.
- Alex, go ahead.
- So, yeah, when I was
looking at the motion,
why does it, is there a reason why
one of the parcels isn't included?
So like looking at the
current future land use map
most of the parcels south of here
are already designated
industrial business,
but that one at 931 Armstrong
Boulevard, Kissimmee
would be left is MUV.
- Yeah.
- What's the deal there?
- Yeah, we had talked about that,
just even before the meeting.
Either a couple of things
that we weren't able to
reach out to those property owners.
Even though these things
are City-initiated,
we like to coordinate and to
let the property owners know
that we're going through this process,
we're gonna do this for them.
So at this time with the
background information,
we did not receive that.
At some point that is
gonna create a problem
because now it's gonna be an enclave,
but one of the good things about it is
it's already developed already, as is,
unlike the vacant pieces of
property that's remaining,
but we're gonna have to address
that at some point in time.
We were just talking about
that before the meeting.
- Yeah, it strikes a bit...
So you also say that it wouldn't be,
I guess I didn't understand
trying to look at
the designation in the comprehensive plan
for the MUV future land use designation.
Why are warehouses not permitted?
It seems like it's a very
permissive designation.
- Right, the warehouses
were there prior to
that mixed use Vine designation.
- Yeah I guess, in
reading it, it's not clear
that warehouses would be
prohibited going forward,
or new warehouses would be prohibited-
- Well the overall objective
of that mixed use Vine
is primarily commercial.
It's primarily commercial,
and it's not really
conducive to industrial.
The flip side, the zoning categories,
this is land use, this is not zoning,
the zoning category that's
ideal for mixed use Vine
does not allow for that warehousing.
So the land use sets the
stage for that zoning.
- Yeah.
- And so that current mixed
use Vine is not conducive
or compatible, really, for any type of
additional light warehousing.
- But I guess, yeah, but specifically here
we're talking about the
future land use amendment
and I, you know, correct me if I'm wrong,
but looking at the MUV
future land use designation
that does seem to be very permissive
and would that explicitly forbid
new warehouse development?
- The land use itself, goals,
objectives, and policies-
- Yeah.
- But the zoning-
- Sure, but that's not what's
under consideration here.
- It would prohibit.
The land use, again, goals,
objectives, and policies,
the overall goals,
objectives, and policies
it does not support industrial.
And the zoning clearly
does not allow for it.
- But I guess the motion before us today
is regarding future land use,
it's not regarding zoning.
Correct?
Gotcha.
Yeah.
I guess, so I also have a
question in the sense that
looking at, you know, one
of the main objectives
in the comprehensive plan is, you know,
objective 1.1.5 to promote
land use strategies
and research conservation,
including in the community
redevelopment areas,
including the Vine Street community CRA.
Looking at the future land use map
it seems like basically the
entirety of the Vine Street CRA
is designated as future
land use designation MUV.
These parcels are part of
the current Vine Street CRA,
and these would now be
the only IN designated
future land use in the Vine Street CR.
Do we need to worry that
that sets up a conflict
of the type that we are
supposed to protect against
as the Planning Advisory Board and policy?
- No, no.
Because there actually is another area,
another industrial hub, that's
on the east side of the city
that has same situation, mixed use Vine,
and it has an existing industrial,
it's called the Kelly
Industrial Park area.
So this would not create a precedence,
we have other pockets
in the same situation.
- But this would, these
parcels still would be
part of the Vine Street CRA.
Changing the future land use to IN
wouldn't remove them from that-
- Correct.
It would still be part
of the Vine Street CRA.
- Right.
- CRA's a completely
different from the land use,
yes, it will remain in the CRA.
We're not removing the
properties from the CRA.
- Do we need to be, then, concerned
because one of the things
we're supposed to do,
especially in the, you know,
the transit development areas,
the mixed use development areas,
one of the things we're supposed to do
is encourage permissive
future land use and zoning
and, you know, mixed use.
Changing from a mixed use
future land use designation
to a single use designation seems like
it could be in conflict with that policy.
- Right.
I do not think that
this is part of the TOD,
transit oriented development.
There are specific areas
that are called out in the
comp plan that are TOD,
one of them being the
downtown inter-modal areas.
This is part of the MMTD,
with the multi-modal
transportation district, MMTD.
- Right, and policy 1.1.6.1 says
to enable mixed use transit
or development pattern
within the MMTD.
And it, I mean, it feels
like one could feel as though
changing future land use from MUV to IN
could be in, you know, could
be against that policy.
It would not be encouraging
mixed use within the MMTD.
- Within this industrial
area, being it's most intense,
you need to be really careful
about mixture of uses anyway.
With industrial.
Industrial is the most
intense type of land use,
and the most intense type of zoning
where you don't necessarily
want to have residential.
This is why I pointed
out that the residential
is not immediately adjacent to this,
but within industrial areas,
you really need to be very careful
about the mixture of uses,
which is one of the reasons why
that we're moving forward with this.
'Cause industrial is one of those uses
that you need to be very careful about
to where there's mixture of uses.
Mixed use can be very
difficult in industrial areas
because we need to have
industrial areas within a city,
because of the noxious,
intense types of uses,
but they don't necessarily
mix, if you will.
- And these aren't currently designated
as industrial business, right?
They're designated as MUV.
- But the zoning side of it is a PUD
that has industrial
types of uses within it.
So this is cleaning up an
inconsistency, if you will,
even with the zoning categories
that are on these properties.
- Do we have any other board
member comments or questions?
I will say that I drive past this area,
not as a point of any
research on this agenda item,
but I drive past this area
literally every 5 days a week
and I know the area very
well as I go down to
Osceola High School, and I don't see
a problem with this land use
being industrial business,
based on what's there now.
That's my opinion.
I will ask if we have any public comments,
and we have one person
from the public here,
Mr. Jerry Gemskie.
Sir, do you have any public
comments you'd like to make?
- None.
- Okay.
So, I've asked for public comments.
Regarding this agenda item,
do we have any motions?
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- We have a motion to
approve from Melissa Thacker.
Do we have a second?
- I'll second it.
- We have a second from Robert.
Do we have any further discussion?
Any further discussion?
- I mean, I guess, I feel
like I'm inclined to reject
because I feel I don't understand,
I don't think the city made clear why
the future land use designation,
which is the thing that's
under question today,
prevents the use of these
properties for warehousing
as they wanted.
There's a zoning issue that
might come before the Board
in the future, but that's not
the issue before us today,
and I feel like it is in
violation of the policies
of the comprehensive plan
where we were, you know,
put in as stewards that are trying to
encourage mixed use
development in the MMTD,
and this is in the MMTD,
and this is a move away
from mixed use future
land use to single use.
- Okay.
Any other discussion?
If not, all in favor please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
- No.
- Okay, the eyes carry,
and motion carries.
Public hearings, we have none,
discussion 7-8, Planning
Advisory Board workshop.
- Yeah, and I think I may have
probably flipped this around
but we like to have,
schedule tentative dates.
I know the summer's coming up,
but I think it's fitting to consider
planning an Advisory Board workshop,
but skipping over the
7B, I wanted to point out
that we do have reappointments.
We have two of our Planning
Advisory Board members
with terms expiring at the end of May.
- Who's that?
- Diana, and Ms. Fatima.
They had opportunities to reach out to us
to see whether or not they are
interested in reappointment.
Diana, I think it's going
to the City Commission
sometime in May, but we
would like to have, Fatima,
that she's going to be moving on
to other future endeavors,
so we'd like to appreciate
your volunteerism
and your involvement with
the Planning Advisory Board,
and she has opted to not
seek a reappointment term
to the Planning Advisory Board.
So we will have a vacancy
for a Planning Advisory Board member.
- So we should probably delay our workshop
until we're fully staffed, so to speak?
- Yes.
So what will happen, just so you all know,
that she will continue
to serve on the Board
until City Commission reappoints.
- Okay.
- So that way it won't affect
quorums and what have you,
so it may be after May
31st, but if we have not,
City Commission has not
appointed a replacement,
she will continue to
serve until such a time.
I think one time that happened where
it was a couple of months where
a board member continued
until we had a vacancy,
or a reappointment.
- Okay.
And 7B, does that, is that
inclusive of what you just said?
- Yes, I think just in general,
for every board member to
know where they're at with it
because it was deliberate,
where it's tiered.
So this year we have two board members,
I think next year, in 2025,
we have two board members,
and then the following year is two
so that way it's staggered,
so that way, to make
sure that we don't have
like four or five vacancies
on the Board at the same time.
- Mass resignation, vacancy.
- No.
It happens, we understand.
So I think it was just
more for informational
for all the board members to know
exactly where they are with their terms
and the appointments.
So I think, from what I'm hearing,
until we get the reappointments done,
then we'll have and schedule a workshop.
- I think that makes sense.
- For the workshop.
- What's everybody else's opinion on that?
- When's the workshop?
- Well we don't, that's the idea
is that we wouldn't set it until we have
our group here fully staffed.
- Yeah, that's what I wanted to know.
- Also, you guys, think about
what you want, you know,
remedial courses on, in a workshop.
So brainstorm a little bit.
- Be careful. (chuckles)
- About what you think
you need refreshers on.
We'll be the same from
a staff perspective,
but, you know, if you guys
have burning questions
of how does this all work,
what are we supposed to do,
conflicts, all that good stuff.
- So one thing I noticed,
it was news to me
reading the City code,
but apparently this body
is also the Brown Field development
overseeing body of the city?
- Yes, that is 100% correct.
- I don't know anything about Brown Field.
- Okay, that's a good one.
- That would be good to know.
- Okay, we can definitely work on that.
- Good update.
- That is something that
does not come up very often,
but we have in the past few years-
- It's hard to see our end-
- Yeah.
(board member speaking indistinctly)
Yeah, we can definitely bring
in a bigger discussion of that
'cause that is good stuff that we do.
Yeah.
- Okay, this was just tentative dates
and kind of talk it through
and that way we know
just from a planning standpoint.
And then after that too we'll talk about
appointments of Chair and
Vice Chair too, potentially.
- When does the city,
when would they be looking
to replace Fatima?
- I think it's the second
meeting in May, I think-
- Okay, so it's coming up.
- City Clerk, yes.
- Oh, okay.
- Are there people being proposed for-
- I don't know.
A lot of times, that's the thing,
that they actually, the
commissioners will appoint,
or the applications coming
in, or they'll appoint,
but they can also request
additional time, too, as well,
to consider the vacancy.
And I think there's like a cycle,
for each of the commissioners
to be responsible for
a replacement on an Advisory Board.
So I think that is coming up.
- Does anyone want to through a date,
a couple of dates out there
that would work for them?
Summer is kind of in flux for me
with travel and stuff at the moment,
so I don't really know.
- Well you know we're here
on the first and the third
Wednesday of every month, so.
- Hmm?
- Whenever you guys-
- Yeah, I guess, you know.
But I'm probably going to
be doing some traveling
at some point, I don't
miss too many meetings,
but there may be one.
But don't need to hold up that for me, so-
- We can revisit again once we know
what the reappointments and
vacancies and things like that.
And we can even halve it,
or we can maybe do one
after something and we can
break it apart if we need to.
- How long would we be talking about?
'Cause we've had some that were lengthier.
- Yeah, I mean we can break it apart.
You know, we can do one
Robert's Rule, comp plan,
one time, and then-
- We don't want to bore you guys,
we just want to educate you.
Robert is, he's so over this, okay.
But, I mean, maybe like
an hour with Brown Fields?
But we can push this into like the fall,
'cause the summer is kind
of difficult for everybody.
And by the time we get, you
know, the band back together-
- Somewhere around September?
- Yeah.
- I mean I intend to
come to every meeting,
but we probably will
be doing some traveling
as a family at some point in the summer,
so there could be a chance
that I miss one of those meetings,
and I would like to be
around for a workshop.
- Okay.
- So if we can do it in September,
my preference would be
September or October
or something after summer.
What does everybody else think?
- That works for me, September's good.
- We can take a look at that,
because we also tend not to have,
where we don't have any items,
so it's just dedicated
just for the workshop,
not any items, so it also depends on
where we're at with items and things.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
- Okay, that's all I have.
- I want to say something.
- Yes.
- I want to say thank you for allowing me
to be part of this board,
and it has been very educational for me
and informational too.
So it's been a pleasure,
and thank you so much,
and I hope that you guys continue
doing an amazing job,
like you have been doing.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
Anyone else, comments?
Alex?
- So, okay, one thing I'm
sort of interested in,
I'm not sure whether we need to,
whether I need to make
a motion or something,
but one thing I'd be sort of interested in
is again looking at
the comprehensive plan,
one of the policies sets level of service
and quality of service
standards for the city.
Both the roadways
and the pedestrian and
bike infrastructure.
The comprehensive plan was adopted in 2020
and the first goals that
it sets are for 2030,
so we're about half way there.
So I'd be kind of curious to hear,
you know, an update from the city
on what quality of service is,
how its changed since 2020,
and whether we're on track to meet
the goals set out in
the comprehensive plan.
I don't know if that's just
something I can request
or whether you would prefer if the body
like made a motion to hear
a report from the city
or something, yeah.
- There's different avenues to that.
Our long range planning team, probably,
but I know that we're gearing up
for some ear based evaluation
and appraisal report
which is a state requirement anyway.
- Brenda, are they gonna,
is Ashley gonna present
your stuff to PAB?
- You would have to-
- It will have to come through
Planning Advisory Board.
- Do you know, is it like-
- I'm thinking that we're opting not to.
I think we're just gonna
do the letter, I think.
- Oh, okay.
- 'Cause I think we're,
I know we're gonna have
a consultant for transportation,
but I think like required amendments?
I think no.
- Okay.
- But I think, I know we're gonna be
hiring a consultant
for the transportation.
- Okay.
Or maybe Ashley could come give us a-
- Ashley and (indistinct)
were the consultants-
- Yeah.
- It's, we're going through
our piece now for a consultant.
- Another random question,
what's the city ditch?
- What?
- What's the city ditch?
The comprehensive plan
makes three references
to the city ditch.
- Did you say dish?
- Ditch, ditch.
- Ditch.
- Like a water ditch.
- I was like, yes,
their main, Mill Slough,
it's a series of probably that main Emory,
it's a huge, huge, ditch
system that travels through
and traverses through the city.
- I'm sorry miss, I didn't understand.
- Yeah, D-I-T-C-H.
- Oh, ditch!
- Ditch, ditch, D-I-T-C-H.
- Okay, okay.
- I thought you said
dish too, so I was like
I don't know of the official
city dish, food-wise.
That's why, but ditch, ditch system.
- There was some indication
it might be in the downtown area.
Is it the like retention
pond behind the library, or?
- Part of it is Emory, the
main, or Martin Luther King,
part of it we ditched
a couple of years ago,
we actually piped in a lot of it,
but it's a main, main ditch system
that traverses from the
south side of the city
up to the north side.
Yes, it is a main ditch system.
- Ditch, okay.
- And these microphones,
from where I sit anyway,
I hear so much, it's not feedback,
but reverb or whatever,
it's really hard for me to-
- You hear what you're
saying and then what the-
- Yeah, so I'm hearing it's-
- It's the volume on this thing,
and quite frankly this is, I'm sorry,
I don't the iPad thing and
it's kind of hard to do that.
- No, it's not just you
it's like everybody.
I really struggle sometimes
to make out, clearly,
what's being said because of the,
I don't know if it's proximity, how close,
are we too close, am I echoing, you know?
So I just-
- Concentrate.
- Yeah, so that's why
I didn't hear clearly.
Anyone else?
- Yeah, I'm gonna keep going. (chuckles)
I had one other sort of
comment I wanted to make.
So, you know, the ship has
sailed, process played its part,
but the motion that we
considered last time
to give up the right of way,
just for our own edification,
reviewing the comprehensive plan,
the comprehensive plan is sort of explicit
in policy 2.2.1.2 that
we are supposed to ensure
that the city preserves
its existing right of way
and does not, you know, too
easily make street vacations.
So I just wanted to, I didn't,
I wasn't aware of that at the time,
but probably good to keep
in mind going forward.
The only other thing I wanted
to comment on was, yeah-
- Hold on, sorry, let me just make sure
nobody else has comments
on that or anything else.
Okay, go ahead Alex.
- And then I guess the last one was, yeah,
reviewing our comprehensive plan
as well as Osceola county's
comprehensive plan.
There was at least one, maybe
a couple, policies that I saw
in the Osceola county comprehensive plan
that we seem to be missing in character
from the Kissimmee one.
And looking at the City
code, one of the duties
of this body is to propose amendments
to the comprehensive plan
and I guess I wanted
to take the temperature
of whether or not we'd
be at all interested
in proposing amendments for consideration
by the DRC or something.
- So what I would suggest is that
you reach out to staff
with some of those policies
that you feel are within
the county comp plan
and not in the City's and then sort of
work with staff to see if, you know,
A, there's a reason why it's not
part of our comprehensive plan,
but sort of start it at a staff level
before bringing it up to the Board.
'Cause it might just be, you know,
a very good reason, or an oversight,
in which it does need
to come to the Board,
but I don't know that it's expedient
or even wise for that matter
for members of the Board
to be proposing, you know,
of their own volition, comp plan changes
that are not vetted by staff.
- Gotcha, thank you.
- I think that, yeah, that's a smart move
to talk to the staff, find
out all the particulars
and the 360 on it and then,
if it's beyond our purview,
that's certainly always something
that you could take up with the Commission
in public comments
or communicating with the
commissioners or something,
that you feel, or anyone feels,
should be a change overall.
Anything else?
Anyone?
If not, do we have a motion
to, wait, our next meeting,
do we know when our next
meeting is for sure?
- No.
There's a potential, there's...
Actually, we might have to
bring something back June 1st.
Yes, yes.
June 1st is the tentative item
to bring back to the Board.
- Okay, so June 1st.
- June 1st.
- Okay, all right, do we
have a motion to adjourn?
- I'd like to motion to adjourn.
- Awesome.
- I'll second.
- Robert, motion to adjourn,
I heard second from Alex,
any discussion on that?
All in favor please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed please say no.
Carries unanimously, meeting
adjourned at 6:43, thank you.