- Let turn my mic on.
Good evening everyone.
We're gonna call the meeting to order.
If you could please stand
for a moment of silence
and for our national anthem.
I'm sorry, pledge of allegiance.
I pledge allegiance
to the flag of the
United States of America
and to the republic for which he stands,
one nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
All right, I just wanna remind everyone
to please silence all mobile devices.
We have no minutes.
We have nothing under old business.
So we will begin with our new business 5A,
public hearing ordinance
amending the future land use map
designation from single family,
low density residential to institutional.
Yes, good evening, this is
"Future Land Use Amendment".
It's been an, the institutional
future land use designation,
(indistinct),
has been established
within the general area
to the property to the west.
This institutional future land substation
can accommodate semi-public uses,
including schools,
educational institutions,
civic facilities, and cultural facilities.
The property owner intends
to utilize the property
as a childcare facility.
There has been a
conditional use application
that has been submitted, however,
that separate application
has be placed on hold
until this land use amendment
and the following item to change
the zoning on the property
is approved by the city commission.
At this time, the proposed
future land use change
to institutional is compatible
with the zoning map amendment
that you're gonna be hearing
during the next item,
and it's compatible with
the surrounding area.
Staff is recommending
approval at this time,
and is available for any
questions that you may have.
Thank you.
Is there any discussion from the board?
Any questions?
Anyone from the audience
that has a question?
Okay.
At this time I'd ask for
the board to disclose
if they have any ex parte communication,
have visited the site, or is
there any conflict of interest?
If not, I'd ask for motion to approve.
- I make motion to approve.
- Thank you, seconded.
- Second.
- All right.
All in favor?
- Aye.
Having heard, oh, sorry, opposed?
Having heard none, the
motion carries approved.
5B, ordinance amending the zoning map.
This is the companion zoning map amendment
to change the zoning
designation on this property,
which is about a little over a half acre.
It's on the south side of Patrick Street
as shown on the map exhibit.
The property in that structure
was constructed as a church
originally back in 1994.
There was another
conditional use application
that came in in 1997,
and that 1997 application,
they expanded the church to
a seating capacity of 54.
That building is about 3,200 square feet.
It has 22 parking spaces.
There was a buffer that
was requested back in 1997
that waived the buffer
requirement on the southern
and on the eastern side of the property.
(indistinct).
That buffer on the south side was waived
due to the proximity
of the retention pond,
the retention pond, it felt at the time
provided a buffer from any
of the adjacent residential.
So the city commission at the time
granted that waiver on the south side,
and on the east side of the property,
instead of placing a wall,
there was a fence that was approved.
The current property
owner currently right now
has submitted a building permit for the
installment of aluminum fence
on the west side of the
property adjacent to the ditch
as the intended uses
support childcare facility
that fences for tag security protection
for the children on the west side,
because it's an open ditch.
As stated before, the property intends
to utilize the existing
structure as a daycare facility.
Now you, as the planning advisory board,
that condition use application
will come before you at a later date,
again, this land use amendment
and rezoning has to take place first
to establish the land use and the zoning.
At this time, this zoning map amendment
is compatible with the
future land use designation,
and therefore staff is
recommending approval
subject to the approval
of the land use first.
- Thank you Brenda.
Any discussion or
questions from the board?
None.
All right, motion to approve.
I'm sorry, from the audience.
I forget that all the time.
Sorry.
(speaker chuckles)
Motion.
Motion to approve.
- I'll make a motion to approve.
- Thank you.
Second.
- Second.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- Any unopposed?
Having heard none,
motion care is approved.
All right, under public hearings, we have.
- So I guess before we
move on from new business,
I was hoping to make a motion,
so I guess with new people on the board
and just sort of in general to
make us a more effective body.
I was hoping to make a motion
to add an agenda item for our next meeting
where we could maybe start reading through
and discussing different chapters
of the comprehensive plan.
So I was thinking we could
start that next meeting
by discussing chapter
one, future land use.
And so that's my motion to add the agenda,
to add an item to the
agenda at our next meeting
to discuss the first chapter
of Kissimmee's comprehensive plan.
- So to add it as a motion, 'cause if we,
and you can clarify,
to add it as a motion to
indicate that there's some action
or just general discussion,
'cause we can bring it as
a general discussion item,
but if you add it as a.
- Yeah.
- An agenda item.
- My intention is to add it
as a general discussion item.
I was under the impression
I need to make a motion to
suggest a new agenda item.
So, the motion is to add the agenda item,
but I'm perfectly fine
with the agenda item being
under general discussion.
My hope was, you know,
because we've got sort of
new members and things,
and also to try to make
our body more effective,
my understanding is the mandate
for the planning advisory board is to be
a citizen advisory board whose
duty it is to ensure that
the decisions coming before our board
and keeping with the
city's comprehensive plan.
So the city's comprehensive
plan is a document that,
you know, is produced
every decade or something
and we can all get a copy from Brenda.
I mean, it's a big thing,
it's a big document,
but it is the document
that governs our actions on the board.
And so it's also in coming
in the coming year or two,
Kissimmee is going to
have to review the comprehensive plan.
And so I thought it might
be an appropriate time
to start reading
through the existing
objectives in the plan,
to familiarize ourselves
with them as well as to
discuss whether, have
an open discussion about
whether there were things
we might wanna suggest the
city considered going forward.
- Actually, one would enjoy
being able to understand, but,
and to learn more and
to be more effective.
So for me, I just, how would that,
again, explaining where it would go
and how it would play out.
So I wanna recall also to the board
that we had discussed
about having a workshop,
but we postponed it
because we knew that we had
two appointments coming up,
I recall.
- Yes.
- So I think bringing it back
to the meeting yes, will help,
but then also this may be fitting
to maybe discuss a workshop.
And we had some internal discussion
to have the workshop
be two parts, twofold.
The first part to go over
ethics, Robert's rules
just in general as a
planning advisory board.
And more so with (indistinct)
about Florida statutes.
And then the second part to go
into the comprehensive plan,
correlation with the zoning map amendment,
the different types of applications.
So it may be where we discuss
a time that we have a workshop.
Typically what we do for the workshop
is that we schedule it to
wherever we have no items.
So that way the entire hour,
because we think an hour
is usually is tapped
because we know a lot of
information coming at you
that we dedicate
and look at our schedule to see
when we don't have an
item that's scheduled
or moving forward to the city commission,
and to reserve that night
for a workshop number one,
part one, and do another
workshop part two.
That's just a suggestion I think
that we can separate it out to where
(indistinct) will go through
Florida statutes, ethics
and those types of things,
just as a board member
for you to be aware of.
And then with the comprehensive plan,
because this is a planning advisory board.
Exactly, the comprehensive
plan and zoning.
- So I would, to piggyback
on what Brenda just said,
I would suggest we do that first.
- Sure.
- To get everybody,
you know, on the same page
so we understand what we're all doing.
And then, now when you're proposing,
like you said, chapter one,
is your idea to systematically
chapter by chapter.
- That would be the idea, yeah.
- Okay.
- But you know, the company's of plan
as a whole is quite large,
so it feels like breaking it up would be.
- It's quite large.
- Yeah.
So I'm willing to retract
that motion at this time.
But maybe it'd be a good time,
you wanna discuss now the future?
Yeah.
So I'll retract my motion at this moment.
(people laughing)
- Hello everyone, my name is Aaron Sabino.
I'm now a resident here
in the city of Kissimmee
for four years.
The reason why I even moved to Kissimmee,
because I truly read the
comprehensive plans for the city,
it's a 50 year build out.
One thing I wanted to bring
to the attention of you all is
do we need to have training
and understanding during a public meeting
where we should be addressing
the topics of people
who are submitting various amendments
to move their initiative forward,
or how, wherever we wanna
misutilize the land or whatever
to that regard.
But I don't mind if you guys
would like to give me some slides or give,
or anyone that's new.
I would love to get
myself full up to speed.
I don't really watch TV, I read.
But more importantly, I
want to advise the board,
I'm here to be fully engaged.
I am fully cognizant of
what's going on with the city,
which gave me the initiative
to be a part of this board.
That's where I stand.
I think that having some understanding
of what the comprehensive plans are
is very important for anybody
who sits on this board.
In addition training I think
is very important to know
how your duties and responsibilities
being apart of this program are important.
But I'm not sure if it is necessary
for us to use this during public time
when we have the public here as well.
Maybe that could be something
that could be done on like a Saturday.
Is that allowed to be
done or, I'm not sure?
- Yeah.
Part of my, I yield back,
with Florida Sunshine
and things like that,
if we were to discuss items
or topics that might
come before the board,
we're required to have those
meetings in a public forum.
But we can check with the city attorney.
- Yes, absolutely.
Like, it's best for us
to do it in this forum.
And you know, we do have the luxury of
not having too many items
on each of our agendas,
so we can schedule a time for education.
And I love the fact that you've
read the comprehensive plan.
I applaud that.
I think one thing that
Brenda will talk about
when we go through the
education process is,
you know, there's the comprehensive plan
and then there's the land
development regulations,
and there's how those two
things mesh with each other,
and also our city process.
Before anything comes before this board,
it goes through a pretty
rigorous vetting process by staff
and it's not just internal staff,
it's also Toho School Board, KUA.
There are many different
agencies, sometimes the county,
well, this sounds very weird, sorry.
Who are looking at these,
what comes to you as agenda items.
So we'll talk about all
of that in further detail,
but I think it's best for
us to do it in this forum.
But I think what you're saying is that,
that's why with the workshop,
if we know that there aren't any items,
I see what you're saying,
for instance, if we have multiple items
and we have folks that have the items
and to take up that time
with the education component,
that's why we're suggesting
to have a workshop.
Those workshops, they have to be public
and we have to advertise
that they're open to the general public.
But it's a general education
session for the general public,
there won't be any items,
we won't be asking you to
make any recommendations
on a particular item.
We will know, usually,
depending on the submittal
applications, where the entire,
again, the entire meeting
will be just for education,
it's not just for you as a board,
but it's also the general
public is welcome to as well.
When it's a workshop, it's a workshop.
No different than city
commission workshops too as well.
Those are all public, general
public are welcome to attend.
But it doesn't take away, for instance,
you know Mrs. Garcia, where they have,
there's a certain
timeliness and expectation
for these applications to
come in that we have to vet,
we have to discuss it
and not unduly delay their applications
that they have submitted.
So I understand what you're saying,
but I think that workshop can be that,
where we can have this
for multiple members
of you at one time, it
has to be in the Sunshine,
but we can do that as a workshop
and not take away from
anyone else's opportunity
for their application to be delayed
or to have to be by the wayside for that.
That's what those workshops for.
We can have multiple,
there's nothing to say that
we can have a maximum amount
of workshops, if we decide
that we can have a third one,
we can schedule a third workshop
or even a fourth or even
quarterly, however we see fit.
We can look at our schedules
and dedicate the time to
have multiple workshops.
- Understood, and noted
for the record, thank you.
And understood and noted.
- And also for the new
members also any questions
that you have that are in
general, you are more than welcome
to bring them up before
us in this public forum,
or you can email me or Brenda
with any specific questions
about process, procedure,
even details.
So we are always
available to you as staff.
Yes, you can do that,
as long as it's individually, you can,
and if it's your project
planner, what have you
'cause we have a number of planners
will get to that during discussion,
you know, we have two board members,
we also have new planning staff
that I want to introduce to you as well.
But you'll be assigned a
certain planner to as well
for that particular application.
So you can email them with
any questions or concerns
that you may have ahead of the meeting.
No differently within the
commission meetings too as well.
I get questions sometimes
from the city manager
of a particular item before the meeting,
and that's vetted prior to the meeting.
- Considering sometimes when
we don't have an agenda,
can we still have, quote, a workshop?
- That's the idea.
That's the idea.
- To get 'em working
little by little to get 'em up to speed.
So, 'cause if you could hit
'em with the whole book,
(indistinct)
and they won't know what
they're talking about.
- But that leads to my other
component, communication.
So when we send out that email,
that email is our primary contact.
We have to make sure ahead of time
because we have to advertise,
and notification has to
be sent of a workshop.
We have to confirm that
that quorum ahead of time.
So we need at least four
voting members to confirm.
So there is a timeliness, we
have to know ahead of time
that when you are attending to as well
'cause we need a minimum of four.
We cannot convene as a board,
whether it be a workshop
or a regular meeting with
less than four members.
- I know this is voluntary,
but if it's a workshop, it
should be mandatory that we show
because it's where everybody's benefits.
But.
- Yeah, I agree with you.
(people laughing)
I agree with you.
- Every meeting.
- But it's.
- We can't people to come.
- Yeah.
- Unfortunately.
So.
- I had to say it though.
- I wish.
All right, moving on.
- Okay.
- So other discussion,
I wanna personally say
that I appreciate the board
and the staff during the time
that I was unable to be here.
The last couple months, my
father has been in hospice
and then I was also doing
school of government,
so it butted up against this.
So, for the times that I wasn't here,
I know that I did clearly tell you,
but just so that you guys are aware,
I do appreciate that this
board was understanding
of what was happening with me.
And just for clarity, I
wanna point out, once again,
we are going to have during
our regular meeting times
workshops to discuss
Robert's rules of orders,
the land development
code, all of these things
that some of us need some
refreshing on or some clarity on.
And then your second
part of your question is,
could we have a copy of it?
So is that something that
you can provide to us?
Absolutely.
We have, yes, we have a link
to the comprehensive plan.
Again, it's 600,
I mean, if you look at
all the different elements
are the chapters, I think
it's seven, 800 pages.
- If you include all the
amendments, it's 1200.
- There you go.
- Which, I mean, maybe
this is now a good time,
once again, I'd like to request the city,
make the comprehensive
plan publicly available
on the city website if possible.
- So the website right now,
the last update is going through that.
So if we receive a request,
we do make it publicly accessible
and provide the link
to the general public.
- Yeah,
I understand that the
city is in compliance
with the requirement to make
it accessible upon request.
In the spirit of making
the comprehensive plan
broadly accessible,
I think it would be
even better if the city,
much like it has a link to,
you know, the city code, community code,
and it does make available a link
directly to the PDF for
the downtown CRA comp plan
and the Vine Street CRA comp plan.
I think it would be a good idea
to have the city comprehensive plan
and the past amendments available
as a link on the city website.
- I concur with that.
This was the first time
I wasn't readily available to
get the comprehensive plan.
I actually had to email
the city manager to get it,
to actually read it.
Normally,
because I worked for the
Department of Defense
and I travel across the country
and I'm staying in various cities,
every city, I read their
comprehensive plan.
It's normally readily available online.
This is the first time it wasn't,
so I definitely like to
piggyback off his and.
- We'll try to make that happen.
(indistinct)
Our control,
but we'll see what we can do.
- I think.
- To provide to you.
- I'm sorry, the website is
under new development now,
like they're making changes,
maybe that's something you
can suggest since you said
you wrote city manager just mentioned how
difficult it was for you and
in comparison to other cities,
it was readily available.
Now that we're already
working on the website,
this might be a good time to add that.
- I'm pretty sure he's fully cognizant.
- Yes.
And that's what I wanna say,
It's been noted and there's
whole bunch of different,
there's a test I think
that was actually even
sent out for that matter.
So I'm thinking again,
I can't speak for IT.
- Yeah.
- But I do know
that there has been reviews
with the website update too as well.
But I know that it's been noted,
I just don't know when that rollout.
And I do apologize for that.
I just don't know when that rollout is,
but we can provide an
update to give you an ETA
as to when they're gonna have that rollout
or if they're gonna make
an interim, you know,
temporary link that we can
provide on the website.
All right.
Next item is here from
chairman and board members.
I think we've already done that.
So.
Then at 6:25, we are.
- (indistinct) something.
- Yes.
- Just really quickly, I wanna from staff,
from city staff,
I do want to introduce
and welcome Rebecca Marin
as a newest planning
advisory board member,
and also Aaron Sabino to as well
(speaker laughing)
to our planning advisory board.
Again, like we mentioned
to you as well, city staff,
what have you is available.
I want to probably,
for emails, we'll probably
bring you some tentative dates
that we're looking at.
I'm not sure the second week of August,
but again, we need to make sure
that we have enough members
before we can confirm the workshop.
So it might be, I don't
know, late August, September
and try to figure it out,
and make sure that we
do have enough members.
With that also, I wanna
introduce additional staff
behind us here too as well.
So to my right, we have John Raven,
who's our new senior planner.
It's been about a month now, I believe?
It's about a month now since
you've been with the city
joining us from Raleigh, North Carolina.
So welcome John.
Chris, well, you all know Christian Arise
is our senior planner, has been with this.
Ryan Althizer, actually during
the last meeting too as well,
he's also a planner from
Fort Pierce, Florida.
Again, planners with prior experience,
again, run the gamut from
annexations, complexity,
so it is welcoming, it is long overdue.
I know as much as y'all
are familiar with me
and with my face,
we have a good group of planners.
We do have plans in place to start
maybe incrementally taking a look at
our land development code.
We do have a separate
long range planning team
that looks at the comprehensive plan,
Ashley Cornelson and John Handley.
So we do have another
separate set of planners
that actually part of their responsibility
is to coordinate directly with the state
to make sure we meet state requirements.
We do have another requirement
coming up in August.
But these are the current
planning team here
for representing the items
that are going to be presented to you.
Oh, and Kayla, I'm sorry, Kayla
Smith is also too as well,
about three weeks or so, or I don't,
it's about three weeks or
so coming from Pompano Beach
there?
- Yes.
- From South Florida to you as well.
So this is the new current
planning team here.
And again, thank you so
much for what you all do,
and thank you.
- All right, well, welcome
to the new board members
and welcome to Kissimmee
those of you who are new here.
And now we can adjourn.
Okay, 6:28 we adjourn.
(speaker chuckles)
Motion to adjourn.
- Motion.
- Second.
- All right, we're all set.
All in favor?
You want me to do all the.
- Yeah, you go too.
- All in favor?
- Aye.
- None opposed.