- Calling the meeting to order.
Thank you all for being here.
Please stand for a moment of silence
and the pledge of allegiance.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag
and to the republic for which it stands.
One nation.
- Thank you.
And please silence all electronic devices.
I'm making sure mine is on silent.
And if any of our board
members have any conflicts
of interest or had any
ex parte communication,
done any site research, site
visits or anything like that
regarding anything on our agenda tonight,
please let that be known,
prior to our discussions.
- So I will declare I visited the site
for item 5A this afternoon.
- Okay.
- To check it out.
- Duly noted.
Thank you. Anyone else?
- No.
- Okay.
Minutes, we don't have
minutes from the last meeting,
I understand, correct?
Okay. Old business, nothing there.
And new business, 5A, public hearing.
- Sorry, that was on automatically.
I'll be presenting this for Brenda
since she's out this week at a conference.
If you haven't met me yet, I'm John Raven.
I'm one of our new senior planners
and this is a condition use
for the site plan waiver
to establish an educational
service establishment,
Angels Touch Dental Institute,
a Dr., is it Menard?
(person speaking indistinctly)
Montero, sorry. Yes.
At her office on 715 East Vine Street.
All right, so to explain,
this is just a dental school
in an existing dental office
on the site that is going
to be offering classes
for a dental assistant program.
The plaza, currently where it's located,
has 101 parking spaces.
That is one parking space
for every 200 square feet
of commercial area for the existing uses.
Due to the limited number of
the parking spaces on site
for the existing uses,
the hours of operation
of the dental school cannot take place
during the same operating
hours as the dental practice.
In addition, the maximum
number of students
is going to be limited to four.
Staff is supporting a site plan waiver
since there is no work
being done to the exterior
of the building and
see, our recommendation
is to approve with conditions.
The conditions would be that the approval
of this educational service establishment
for the dental school in Suite C, sorry,
715 East Vine Street only.
The educational service establishment
use cannot be transferred or expanded
to other sites at 715 East Vine Street.
A separate conditional
use application approval
would be required for any such expansion.
The dental school has to be accessory
or secondary to the
existing dental office.
The approval of the educational
service establishment
does not include any public
or private school uses.
So it is solely limited to the classes
for a dental assistant program.
It's going to be, again,
limited to four students
at any given time.
And the hours of operation
for the dental school
cannot overlap with the
existing dental practice.
And any exterior, or sorry,
any interior alterations
required to add classroom or other spaces
will require a state certified contractor
to apply for permit and submit plans.
And lastly, a business
license for the dental school
must be issued within one
year of this approval.
- Thank you. Board members, any questions?
- Yes.
- Go ahead, Alex.
- I guess I was hoping for
some clarification for 0.3.
I don't understand what that means.
The approval of educational
service establishment
does not include any public
or private school uses?
- So essentially, it means that there's
not any other educational programs
or other courses that can take place
aside from that for dental assistance.
- Okay.
- Other questions from the board?
If not, would the applicant
like to address the board?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Please step to the microphone
and state your name
and your business address for the record.
- Actually, it's not a dental school.
It's a expanded duties
dental assisting school.
Meaning that it's-
- I'm sorry,
could you say your name again
and your business address for the record?
- Okay.
My name is Francisca Montero
and the business address
address is 715 Vine Street,
Suite 3.
But in the beginning I was
applying for unit seven,
no three, and because I
have like already a license,
they are already..
Tax received, I thought that
will expedite the process.
And I've been waiting
for this for three years,
so it's ridiculous.
I don't know what happened,
but I was very busy
and I receive email and
I didn't see the email,
but I'm beginning to use
my dental assisting school
upon the duty within my dentist's office.
But in the future, I want
to expand to another unit.
- Okay, so at this time though,
we're adjusting this
specific unit being used.
- Okay.
- For the instruction of dental assist.
- Yes, but the clarification
is not a dental school,
it's a dental assist on the duties.
- Understood.
Questions, board members
for the applicant?
Alex?
- So then I guess in light
of the applicant's comments-
- I'm sorry, who's ever
got their phone on,
please silence that.
- Oh, sorry.
- Thank you.
(phone ringing)
Alex, you had a question?
- Yeah, so I guess I just
wanna kind of check with you.
Have you looked at the
conditions that the city
has put forward on approval
and are you kind of happy
with those conditions?
Are those adequate or you..
- Well, not really because you know,
I think that I can fit in my
office at least 12 students.
'Cause they work as a partner.
- Right.
- But, you know, I will be happy to start
because I have people waiting for me.
- Okay, thank you.
I guess so I have a question
for the city attorney.
Given that the conditions
specifically refer
to a dental school,
will that cause any difficulty
if it's meant to be used
as a dental assistant training program?
Or should we amend the conditions
or do you think that's fine?
- I think it's fine.
I don't think you can get accreditation
to have a dental school,
like for four people.
So I think it's understood.
But I mean, we could always change it
to say dental assistant training program.
- Okay.
- And also,
I'm a licensed dentist
in New York and I used to
do classes for foreign
dentist to become hygienist
to pass the boards.
And because they are limiting
to dental assisting only,
I think it's not fair because I can train
like in FaceTime or Zoom somebody
to become a hygienist here.
- Okay. So then I guess I..
I guess one last question.
How much leeway do we have as a board
in the sense that the city
made these recommendations
because they think they're necessary
to comply with the land development code?
Are we free to waive these conditions?
Or if those waivers are not in keeping
with the land development code, does that,
you know, how much authority do we have
to change the conditions?
- You have some discretion,
but the reason why, my understanding,
the reason why it is
limited to both the time
that the students can be on the premises
and the number of students is tied to the
layout and the parking.
So I think that it's just
an issue of capacity.
So we don't wanna cause, you know,
potential emergency or
hazardous conditions
within the unit or in
the surrounding units.
- Does anyone else have questions?
Comments?
Aaron, did you have something?
Go ahead, go ahead.
- Hello, everyone.
My name's Aaron Sabino,
and based on the statements
the young lady has made,
we're discussing the particular unit,
but she already has plans for expansion
and based on what this gentleman
said that she can't expand,
so I wanted to kind of
get an understanding of
if we were to pass this,
we're taking the notion that
she's going to fulfill it
and she's going to grow
and this is going to
cause a hazardous concern
and a potential matter in the future
for that particular plaza
right off 715 Vine Street.
So wanna take that into consideration
that we're talking about 715 C today,
and only 715 C in the conditions in which
she's trying to go into.
I'm not sure if we're approving
for her to license that
particular for a dental school.
Is that what I'm understanding
what we're doing?
- No, I'm licensed by
the Board of Education
and I have the permit from Tallahassee,
the Health Department to
teach, expanded duties,
dental assistant.
It's just that I've been
waiting for three years
and I've been paying rent for unit seven
that is like in the city
will be like G, I think.
But I am paying like almost $5,000.
I already spent $200,000
trying to get this permit.
- I think some of these questions might be
directed to the city, could we..
- Yeah.
It's mostly directed to the city,
at this point, just so
I can have more clarity-
- Yeah, let's have a city representative
step to the microphone so we
can ask you some questions.
- I just need more
clarity, a little bit more.
- You can have a seat, ma'am,
and then we can have you come back up.
- Okay. Originally I wanted-
- I'm sorry, everything's
gotta be on the microphone
and on the record.
What I'd like to do is
address questions to the city
at this time and then
we'll give you a chance
to respond to that, so if
you have a seat, please.
- Oh, okay.
- Yes, please.
Thank you.
No, that's okay. That's okay.
- I thought that you say
that I ask the question.
- No, no, no, no, no.
We're gonna ask the city questions.
Could you help us understand better why,
if this is my understanding,
if I'm wrong, I'm wrong,
let me know, that the unit seven was
the city declined for
her to use that for this?
Am I understanding that or no?
- I'm not specific with the, or sorry,
I'm not familiar with the
specifics in that situation,
but this doesn't preclude her from ever
being able to expand,
just that she would need
another conditional use
application to do so.
- Yeah, okay, so just
so we're clear on this,
tonight is for the approval or not
of this specific unit under the terms
that have been laid out.
- Yes, sir.
- And anything beyond that
would require a further application
to use another unit for
more than the four students?
Is that what the city is saying?
- Correct.
- Okay.
Board members, do you have
any questions for the city?
Go ahead, Alex.
- Yeah, so could you explain a little bit?
So I was trying to look at
the land development code
and, you know, I understand that
because it's in the T5 U transit zone,
there's certain minimum
parking requirements,
but this is a like shared unit.
And so I guess one,
could you clarify for me
how you allocate or decide
what the minimum parking requirements
would be for individual units?
And then secondly, I didn't
fully understand why the number
of students would be restricted to four.
You know, given that the
entire parcel has 101
parking spots currently, right?
As denoted in the plan or the document.
- Well, as the Deputy
City Attorney here said,
it is a matter of the capacity,
there are other uses that
are existing within that
shopping center.
So people, you know,
will also be coming in
to use those other establishments.
And so this is more of a
shared parking agreement
in the sense that you
can't have the two uses
overlapping at the same time
or else it would potentially
like shut some people out
of being able to find
parking either for this use
or for some of the other.
- Yeah, I guess just..
So I visited the site this afternoon,
more than half of the
parking spots were free.
It doesn't seem like the
parking lot is fully utilized.
I've never seen it full.
I understand that for this particular use,
I feel as though we have to go with
what the land development
code currently says.
But it feels like in reviewing
the land development code
and taking another look
at the comprehensive plan,
the existing minimum parking requirements,
especially in the
multimodal transit district
feel as though they're a bit oppressive
and might be getting in the
way of some of the other policy
statements in the comprehensive plan.
Especially ones targeting
pedestrian mixed use
infill development.
So this isn't germane to
this particular issue,
but maybe after this,
I'd be interested in
having conversation about
whether or not the Board
would be interested in
discussing or making a recommendation
that the commission consider revisiting
some of our minimum parking requirements,
especially in the Vine
Street CRA or the MMTD.
- Just to provide the Board
with a little more information.
The parking is based upon the
square footage of each unit.
- What are the other businesses
that are in that plaza?
- Good evening.
There's actually mainly retail uses,
which is one per 255
(indistinctly) correctly
and the one per 300 square feet.
So everything has been
established, the whole entire,
it's the Rainbow Plaza has been,
it's actually in the
max capacity right now
with the parking
requirements which are there.
So the dental office requires
a bit more parking spaces
due to the magnitude of
clients coming in and out.
For the actual vocational school,
which is part of the land development code
for the parking requirements, 14-722,
it's one parking space
for every 3.5 students
and plus two spaces per three employees.
Hence the maximum capacity
during the daytime.
When the hours of operation
for the dental office
are non-operative, then
the school can utilize
and it cannot impact the parking demands,
because it is during separate hours.
But in retrospective,
staff takes a look into
the maximum capacity
when it's operational,
during the daytime and hours of operation
for all retail users are within the plaza.
So that's how the analysis is done
in order not to impact
additional parking spaces
to be utilized by the
patrons coming in and out
and/or employees.
So that's the logic behind the analysis,
behind the parking demands
and the parking requirements
that are existing in the plaza.
So we cannot over park it,
meaning bringing more clientele in
when there's not sufficient spaces,
according to the land development code.
So that's the criteria that we utilize.
- Okay.
First of all, I wanna say I love the idea
that there is gonna be training going on
for professional positions here
and to help people to
get professional jobs.
I think that's great.
I'm thinking about this, I'm
just wondering about this too.
And I certainly understand
the other tenants there
that are leasing their
spaces have a right,
I'm sure per their leases,
for X number of parking spaces
within that based on their square footage
is what I'm guessing that they've got.
"Okay, if you've got this business,
then you have the right to
this number of spaces there."
So what is allotted to this unit is that
number of spaces that we're saying
and, sorry, I'm just trying to get,
and I'm trying to also listen
through the echo that goes on here.
I think it's a little bit
hard to hear sometimes.
So how many spaces are allotted
for the dental practice?
- The dental practice, I have
to double check on the number,
but if it is for dental
office, professional office
is one per 200 square feet.
So it is 20, dental office is
50, so we divide that by 200,
which is 10 parking spaces for that unit.
- Okay.
- 10.1.
The fraction goes over, so it's 11.
Plus the school, whatever
the school requires.
Which is-
- How many are we saying
for just the dental assistant training?
- For the vocational school,
it's one space for every 3.5 students,
plus two spaces for every three employees.
So that brings it up to
three parking spaces.
But if there's more students,
then you're gonna require a higher demand.
Hence why does the students are limited
or capped at a certain amount.
- Okay. Okay, get that, get that.
I'm just trying to work through
this to see, to understand.
Go ahead.
- One more thing to add.
- Sure.
- Each entire individual
tenant space, for example,
when we get a business tax receipt,
we look into the parking requirements.
If it is a professional office,
it's one per 200 square feet.
If it is a retail use, it's one per 300.
So the retail utilizes less parking.
The leases does not
allocate the parking spaces,
but staff looks to make sure
that there's adequate parking for the use.
So when, for example, there's
a vacant tenant space,
if it is within, if it was a retail before
and it becomes, for
example, the dental office
and it increments the parking demands,
we gotta ensure that the entire site
has adequate parking for those uses.
So for example, if that tenant space,
one per 200 is gonna require 30 parking,
I'm just putting numbers,
30 parking spaces
and they're only allowed to have 20,
then we're over 10 and we
have a parking analysis
that we conduct in order to
approve the business licenses
for this particular
shopping plaza, for example.
And we do it throughout
the commercial sites
that we have throughout the city
to ensure there's adequate
parking for the site.
- Okay, so, and correct me if
I'm missing something here,
just so I understand.
Okay, so we've got four spaces
for the vocational school?
- Correct.
- Correct, okay.
And 10 for the, how many for the dental?
- 11 because you have
a fraction because 50.
- But they're not operating
at the same time, correct?
- That is correct.
- So what would preclude
if this same tenant
is leasing both for the dentist office
and for the vocational school,
then she has a right to those
spaces for the dental school.
But what would preclude the
use of those spaces then?
Because if the dental school is not open,
and nobody else can use
those spaces either, correct?
- Well the spaces cannot be
given to any specific person,
the space is for everyone
in the shopping plaza.
But there's hours of
operation for other tenants
there within the plaza, for example.
- Okay.
- If there's someone that opens at 10
and closes at eight or nine,
we cannot say these spaces
are removed from these folks
and they're given to the school.
We have to play it fair
and the entire parking
works for the entire plaza.
We can take a look into a parking analysis
or a parking demand, as far
as share parking agreements
and things of that nature,
but in this particular case,
and I don't have the full
details, to be honest with you,
I'm just giving you overall how we work,
as far as internally.
But that was how it was allocated
for this particular use.
- Hold on, I'm hearing,
does somebody else over
have comment or a question?
If not, Alex, do you have a question?
- I guess, yeah, I was just gonna..
To my own understanding, right,
this is one unit in this
kind of shared unit,
it's allocated about 10 spaces
amongst the allotment for the lot.
The city, part of the conditions
that they're putting on this thing
that we're trying to
approve is they're saying
they need to have 10 spaces,
a dental school needs to have one
for every three and a half students.
They're saying two things.
The maximum number of students
they could have is four.
And then they're also adding a requirement
that the dental school
has to operate on hours
that are different than
the dentist practice
because they're saying that these things
require parking spots
and there's only sort of
10 for this business.
Personally, I feel as though both,
well, first I have to clarify that
in checking the land development code,
I think the city's right
that right now the way the land
development code is written,
that would be the way
they would have to do it.
But I also wanna say that personally,
I feel like this is overly restrictive
and getting in the way
of some of the objectives
we have in our comprehensive plan
of trying to encourage infill development
or like vocational programs
in our Vine Street CRA.
My understanding is that I don't think
that we can really lift
those requirements ourselves,
'cause that's part of the
land development code.
But I think after we address this motion,
I think one thing we could do as a board,
if this has come to our attention,
is we could make a suggestion
that the City Commission
revisit some of these parking reports.
- Okay, so let's do this.
Let's take, 'cause there
isn't, you mentioned motion.
There is no motion at this point.
Let's address this as stated herein
and then we can discuss,
or the city can look at the idea of-
- So I will make a motion to
approve the conditional use
with the restrictions the city suggested.
- Okay, we have a motion on the floor.
Do we have a second?
- Second.
- Second from Diana.
Any discussion? Any further discussion?
All in favor, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed, please say no.
Hearing none, motion carries.
Approved.
Let's go ahead and go through the,
can I have the agenda up again, please?
Okay.
Public hearings, okay.
That was our public hearing, discussion.
Okay, let's open the
floor up to discussion.
- So if I may?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
So yes, so in..
Okay, in the land development code,
we've got an entire chapter
dealing with parking requirements
that sets down requirements
for all different kinds of business types.
Like the representative
from the city was saying,
for retail spaces, it's, you know,
one for every 300 square feet,
one for every 200 square feet
for dental practice, things like this.
And these parking spaces are required
for any sort of new development.
Now across the country, lots of cities
have discovered that these
kinds of parking requirements,
one in general, they're
like way more conservative
than you need to.
And I think if we drive around,
you can see that there's
lots of parking lots
that are empty.
When I visited this site today,
less than half the spots were taken up.
And I think that's the
kind of norm everywhere.
I also think that as the
experience of our applicant today
highlights, things like
parking requirements
become a real burden for
people to actually try
to make things better in our
city or improve things, right?
It's one of these things
that people have to kind of dance around.
Now I think in light of this,
lots of municipalities across the country
have started to loosen
or a lot of times, completely
lift parking requirements
as part of their own
land development codes.
And for the most part, the
experience has all been positive.
This sort of allows for more development
and things like that.
In our own comprehensive plan,
I mean, it's sort of clear
that we have an overall objective, 1.1.5,
to promote innovative land use strategies
and urban design principles
and resource conservation.
And as part of that
there's specific policies,
including 1.1.5.8 to target density
and intensity proximal
to transit in our MMTD,
the Multimodal Transit District,
of which Vine Street is a part.
As well as policies like 1161,
to enable mixed use transit
oriented development pattern
within the multimodal
transportation district specifically
and policy 1162 to require
pedestrian oriented
site design, as well as 1163
to require pedestrian
oriented building design
within the MMTD.
So our comprehensive plan is telling us
that one of our responsibilities
is try to ensure that as
people try to make things
that we try to turn Vine Street over
from the kind of development
and car-oriented development
that it currently is
and try to encourage
the city and applicants
to kind of make things more innovative,
more pedestrian-friendly
and stuff like that.
I think the city in recognizing
that things like parking
requirements get in the way,
we specifically in
Kissimmee exempt the core,
like Broadway, the core downtown
as part of our downtown CRA
is exempt from parking requirements.
But we do not extend that exemption either
to the whole of the downtown CRA,
nor to any of the parts
of the Vine Street CRA.
So yeah, basically I feel
like this is one of the things
that kind of makes it hard for people.
This is one of these sort of policy things
that I'm not sure the
benefits outweigh the cost.
And I think maybe one thing
that we should consider is,
you know, I could imagine
sort of three levels.
One, we could sort of recommend
that maybe the City
Commission study or consider
lifting parking requirements
entirely in Kissimmee.
That's something lots of other
municipalities have done.
If we're uncomfortable with
that as the sort of next step,
I could imagine trying
to extend the exemption
that we already have on
the books for sort of
the broad street area of downtown
to the rest of the
Multimodal Transit District,
which we sort of have specific policies
in the comprehensive
plan trying to target.
Or maybe just as an
intermediate, we could try to
target some specific region
of the Vine Street CRA
that might be exempt from
parking requirements.
Or maybe one last thing
to throw out there,
if we still feel as though
the work the city has done
in these traffic studies
and stuff is useful,
one strategy I've seen some cities adopt
is they really just like
change one word, right?
They change it from parking requirements
to parking recommendations
and they become sort of non-binding.
Already in our parking chapter,
we have a mechanism by
which someone could appeal
to the City Commission and get up to 50%
of the parking requirements waived.
But another strategy I
could like, you know,
one thing I could imagine
doing is just saying
that everything is
instead of a requirement,
a recommendation and
you know, let that go.
And that would be very kind of loose
or I could imagine expanding
our existing, you know,
procedure for exemption
to allow up to 100%,
you know, basically like upon appeal to
either the City Commission
or with approval of the PAB,
we could let people be no longer subject
to the parking requirements,
and add that as a tool to our disposal
to try to consider things conditionally.
- Okay.
- Can I just say one
thing really, really fast?
And of course, you can recommend anything,
but just a couple of things to consider.
One is if you extinguish
all parking requirements,
no developer will ever put in parking,
'cause it costs them money and space.
That's one thing.
The other thing is, you
know, this matrix, right?
The 200 square foot,
300 square foot, that is
in accordance with the use
and not the specific business.
So you can never estimate the success
of the business itself.
You're only looking at that generic use
to give you that equation.
So, you know, I applaud what you're,
and I appreciate what you're saying,
but I think that definitely
in like the planner's minds,
those are pretty big considerations
that have them still
interested in a scheme
that is consistent.
- Other board members?
- If I may.
So as being a main street director
and working with the
main street businesses,
yes, there are some areas of the downtown
that don't have the parking restrictions,
but there are some that are still in
that CRA that we represent.
And I've come across this
situation where we've had
to look at shared parking
from a church allowing parking
for a business.
When that didn't work,
we had to ask for a special
variance to see if and prove
that that business doesn't
need those parkings.
So I've gone through this personally,
in my position at Main Street.
But one thing I want us
to be considerate of is
that we just spent 20 minutes
talking about something
that ultimately we
couldn't do anything about
today right here.
So I think that we had
a discussion earlier,
a couple meetings ago where
we talked about training
and we talked about the
fact that we would sit
and these are some of the
things that we can discuss,
'cause again, I agree with you,
in the perspective that
it needs to be reviewed.
I don't have the vast
knowledge of the code,
which I would hope to get
through that training,
but I can't even address some
of the things that you said,
because I don't have enough of
that base knowledge for that.
And I don't think the time and the staff,
you know, that's allowed here allows them
to be able to train us
and to properly let us know as you did,
breaking down each of those suggestions
as to say this won't work or this one.
And this is not the arena for that.
So I beg the question if this is something
that when these types of things come up,
if we can't table and say,
we already said we would
have our trainings publicly,
that if those aren't things
that we can do at that time
and be considerate of the audience
that we have in the time
and what people are actually here for
and what is in our capacity to do.
If we want to do more,
then we should table those discussions
for when we are in training
and have the opportunity
to have those discussions.
- We can, this board can never
change the land development code.
And this board also cannot
change the comprehensive plan.
Except when an amendment,
I mean an amendment,
you can propose an amendment.
A lot of times, you are
voting on amendments
to the comprehensive plan.
But those decisions,
this board is not the final voice.
Those are all recommendations
that go to City Commission.
So-
- Understood, yeah.
- The fast and quick is that, you know,
that is the limitation to your authority,
in terms of what we would
consider a legislative review.
- Right.
- So you are really
confined to a certain extent
when an application comes before you
to what our current code and
comprehensive plan allows for.
- And I think-
- I'm sorry Alex, Robert's rules.
Anybody else have anything
to say regarding this?
- Yeah, I do.
So when you present something to us,
we're supposed to evaluate it, look at it,
and if we see something
that might be of question,
bring it to your attention
and let it go at that
and vote on it, yes or no?
- You know, you're supposed
to come in, you know,
staff gives you their recommendation.
They're giving you all
the information, you know,
what the basis, what
their analysis is based on
what their conclusions are based on,
and the different code
or comp plan provisions
that they're relying on.
You're supposed to look at that
and see if that is consistent
with those original documents,
the comp plan and the
land development code.
- So we're not the
developer or the planner
or the instigator or anything.
We just see what's there and evaluate it.
- That is your primary, but
you also are charged with
making recommendations, you
know, in a broader scale
having to do with the comprehensive plan,
but not the land development code.
- So to Diana's point, I understand that,
you know, I probably should
have narrowed that down
or filtered that to the
specific agenda item
and then let's vote on that
and then have this discussion
as we're doing right now.
I always like to try to let
everybody speak their piece
so that, you know, I'm
not cutting anybody off,
everybody gets to to speak,
but with regard to this
in a general sense,
I'm just, I have questions.
Go ahead.
Sorry, did you wanna throw something in?
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Please.
(person speaking indistinctly)
- No, it's Doug.
- For those that don't know
me, I'm Douglas Ethridge,
I'm the Assistant Director
of the department.
It's a valid, valid issue,
and frankly, it's already on
the docket to be reviewed.
We already have consultants
lined up to do these things
and to go with Commissioner, or excuse me,
Member Diana's suggestion,
it would be advantageous
for us to get together
and train and talk.
Then we can talk to you on what things
were already on the docket,
already being reviewed
and brought back before City Commission,
because the parking study
is just not a simple factor
that we can do overnight.
That will probably take
years to actually do,
because there's just so
many facets that go into it.
It's just not one use and
applies across the board or such.
We have to look at every aspect
of things that consistency,
the fairness, all those
things that goes into it.
So I just wanted to mention
that we already have that,
it's already been directed
by commission to do that.
It's just identifying the
priority orders of the things
that they've already given us to do.
And that will be coming
to you in the future.
- And having the staff numbers
to be able to accomplish
everything that you're tasked at doing.
- Correct, because it's just not planning
that goes into this.
It's fire, access liens.
- Sure.
- It's handicap
accessibility with the state.
There is a variety of different things
that we have to look at to go through.
- Yeah, I'm sure there's a
lot more than meets the eye
and we are not going to
have the working day-to-day
expertise that you and
your staff have on this.
But we're asking the questions,
and I'm gonna say this, I'm just thinking,
in general here, if you've
got, like Diana was saying,
I think if I heard her
right about the shared usage
of the spaces, if you've
got X number of spaces
and you've got a tenant
who is going to have
two different units in a development
and that person has a
right to 10 spaces here
and four spaces here,
isn't that to some extent
fungible for that tenant
in that they would,
"Okay, during the evening,
the 10 spaces that I have
because of my dental
operation are not being used.
But there are still those 10 spaces
that are allocated for my practice
that can't be used for
something else after,"
unless I'm wrong about that.
Like at eight o'clock at
night, they can't use that.
Somebody else next door can't use it,
'cause that's 10 spaces
for the dental practice.
So does that mean in the
evening they sit empty?
And could that not again, be fungible
towards another unit that
that same tenant may have?
That's just what's going through my mind.
There's probably a lot more
to it than meets the eye.
- There is.
There's a lot of factors
and this one being
a little bit more detailed than most,
because most instances
it's a single business
and a one unit structure.
That's simple, quick and easy.
If it's a shopping center type of field
and a larger than 25,000
square foot building,
it combines all the uses into
a larger parking requirement.
But when you don't exceed that 25,000,
it requires every single tenant
to have its own parking requirement.
So in this particular
instance, it's not happening,
but you have to plan, you
have to potentially plan for
every single one of those
units in that building
to be at the highest intensity use.
Which could be a restaurant.
That's one for 80 parking spaces,
or excuse me, one parking
space for every 80 square feet.
So if you have five tenants
that have one parking,
excuse me, one for every 80 square feet,
it's gonna fill up that
parking lot, plus more.
Plus, we don't control the
hours of business activity.
So they can be open 24 hours or however,
we don't control that.
Nor do we control the aspect of what
a landlord allows for its tenants.
We just say this is the maximum of parking
that you have to have for
that business activity.
However you distributed that
amongst your tenants is up to you.
So there's a lot of factors
that play into those things.
- All right, Alex, go ahead.
- And so I can understand
what the city is saying
and I fully respect the
fact that the city has
a level of expertise and
experience with these things
that we lack.
At the same time, the duty of this board,
the reason we exist at all,
the reason we're a City
Advisory Board I think is,
you know, as the city said,
they've got a lot to worry about.
They've got a lot of things
that they need to consider.
All different kinds of
aspects of planning and zoning
and legal and things.
What we're tasked with,
and the reason we exist
is because we're tasked with sort of
looking at the comprehensive plan,
maintaining a comprehensive plan,
suggesting amendments to
it, and try to ensure that
the evolution of the city
and the things going on
and the things reflecting
the land development code
are sort of in keeping with the vision
laid out in that document.
You know, the city has
a lot to worry about.
We're supposed to worry about one thing.
We're supposed to worry
about the comp plan.
And I guess what I'm trying to say is,
I also understand that these
things are under review.
I think the city
acknowledges that some of its
parking restrictions
might be too oppressive.
And part of what the new
consultants are looking at,
I think, are changes like this.
But I think our role, one
of our roles, could be
that looking at the existing comp plan
and some of the objectives
the city has to try to,
you know, improve development
and try innovative uses
in the Vine Street
code, we could, I think,
add to the discussion,
show a bit of support
and highlight and make a recommendation.
That's all we're doing.
All we can do is say that we,
you know, believe something.
We don't actually have
any power or authority
over the land development
code, as the attorney said.
But one thing we could as
a body is we could voice
that like, "Yeah, we believe that maybe
the current parking requirements
are getting in the way
of Kissimmee vision to
try to really transform
the multimodal transit, the
MMTD, the Vine street CRA,
the downtown CRA.
And that's a thing we could
say and we could say as a body
and it's just a statement we could make.
And I feel like it's one we should.
- And no disrespect, but I
think you've already said that
and that could be on record to prove that
that's part of your saying.
I don't think there has
to be a separate motion,
because it's already been
directed to staff to do so.
- Yeah, I don't think we're
making any motions here.
We're just having part of the discussion.
So anything else? Anyone else?
- As he alluded to, I just wanted to make
everyone understand that
this is enhancing downtown,
'cause there's stuff
that's not being utilized
and she's bringing in a good business
that's going to bring
in professional jobs,
that's going to also be a part of the city
that could use their
tax dollars to our city
to enhance it in other ways,
as far as maybe shopping downtown,
eating downtown for lunch.
I think that we really need to take more,
approach of kind of seeing
what they're offering
instead of trying to get into the weeds
and trying to be the engineers. (laughs)
More so just be the advisory
of making sure that,
like, as he stated, does it affect
the comprehensive city plans of
what we have over the 50 years.
State me if I'm wrong,
but that's what I see that
what she's offering right now
for that space on that city
where that strip is, that
could be a really good space
of use for the short term that she has
until she grows into something bigger.
I would just more, my
questioning was more aligned with
him stating that this unit
can only has a limited amount
of space inside of this she can use for,
but it's kind of, she's
already, in my mind,
is already thinking
that it's already bigger
than what she has planned.
And she's probably already thinking about
the expansion part of it.
Is that taken into question with the city?
'Cause I can't make that
decision and determination.
I just wanna go for what
she's advocating for,
for conditional use with
the site plan waiver.
So that waiver itself
is what we're discussing
and advising say, "Hey, please.
Thank you guys for giving
me the information.
You know, I think a motion to approve this
for this particular
waiver for this school."
- Well, and that was done.
That was done.
- Right, right.
I'm just making sure that that's clear.
- No, with this, we're just,
this is just general discussion
about parking overall,
how it fits in with comprehensive plan.
- But I think to agree
with what you're saying
and kind of lean in, right?
I like the story that came before us.
I felt as though they
were being overly hampered
in the parking requirements,
but I felt like my hands were tied.
I felt like this was a
thing that wasn't keeping
with the comp plan, but we are bound by
the land development code
and it felt like our land
development code was overly rigid.
It didn't allow us any leeway.
It doesn't allow the the
applicant any leeway.
There were no sort of release valves.
And that just feels like,
yeah, the part of the issue
is overly restrictive requirements.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'll allow you say a few words
and then we're gonna move forward.
- Okay. Sorry about..
I'd like to say that I have,
I allow by the landlord
to use like 14 spaces.
But at night when I go to operate
the dental assisting
school is like 60 or more
parking spaces available every day.
Is a pharmacy there that they don't have
any client coming in.
They deliver the
medication to the patients.
Is a carpet store that they
don't have any clients coming in
but my point is that
with those limitation,
I don't have any room to roll.
- Okay.
And I'm gonna just have to say
that's something you'll have to take up in
whatever application process with the city
and move forward with that.
But I am going to move
to the next portion here,
Chairman and board members,
of this, but thank you.
We've approved what we had before us
and I encourage you to
discuss with the city
any further application at that point.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- And also I'd like to ask
what the gentleman said
about the getting the city more quality
in the environment in
particular in that building
is a lot of homeless people
that goes there at night.
- Yes, I understand.
Ma'am, I'm sorry, we're gonna
move forward with the agenda.
- Okay, no problem.
- Thank you.
And I think we are pleased to hear
that the city is going to move forward
with studying the parking
issue and I think we all have
questions about that and
think it can be used more,
but we did approve your-
- Okay, thank you.
- Application. Thank you.
Hearing Chairman and board members,
I'm just gonna say again, encourage.
Yeah, let's look at that
and see what makes sense.
Because if somebody's got 14 spaces
and she's allowed, just
like Doug had said,
not that we can't, we
don't dictate the hours
that they can be used,
whether it's midnight,
11, 2:00 AM whatever,
that if she can use those at any time,
then if it's the same,
it's not like she's gonna
be in conflict with herself
between the 10 or 11
for the dental school,
the dentist practice,
and then the four for the,
she's not gonna sue herself
over that as opposed to a
different entity altogether.
So to me it would make
sense to be able to, again,
I use the word fungible for
if that person is allotted
that number of spaces.
And I'll listen to anybody
else before we adjourn.
Anybody else? Anything else?
- I make a motion to adjourn.
- We have a motion on
the floor to adjourn.
- Second.
- We have a second, okay.
Any discussion around that?
No? Okay.
All in favor of
adjournment, please say aye.
- Aye.
- Opposed? Please say no.
Hearing none.
Meeting is adjourned at 6:48. Thank you.