<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:29:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11447911</link>
      <description>LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS
PROJECTS:
1) AR-26-15636-HL  Mobile Hydraulics Repairs


--- Full Notice Text ---
LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS
PROJECTS:
1) AR-26-15636-HL  Mobile Hydraulics Repairs. There will be No Pre-Bid Conference for this project. Deadline for Questions: Tuesday January 13, 2026, at 12:00PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday February 10, 2026, at 2:00PM Local Time. Contact: Heidi Lockwood (407) 742-0927.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org [http://vendorlink.osceola.org]
January 8, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11447911</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11443750</link>
      <description>OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:   1


--- Full Notice Text ---
OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:   1. AR-26-15636-HL  Mobile Hydraulics Repairs. There will be No Pre-Bid Conference for this project. Deadline for Questions: Tuesday January 13, 2026, at 12:00PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday February 10, 2026, at 2:00PM Local Time. Contact: Heidi Lockwood (407) 742-0927.  FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.   1/04/2026 7914875</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11443750</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441769</link>
      <description>LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1) PS-26-15567-LA - Architectural and Engineering Services For The Osce...


--- Full Notice Text ---
LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1) PS-26-15567-LA - Architectural and Engineering Services For The Osceola County Solid Waste Transfer Station. The solicitation document and any addenda can be accessed and downloaded from VendorLink at the following web address: Vendorlink.osceola.org. There will be a VIRTUAL NON-MANDATORY PRE-PROPOSAL CONFERENCE held on Monday, January 12, 2026, at 1:00 PM Local Time. Dial in at 407-906-2344, and when prompted, enter the following conference code: 852 500 276#. Please note the meeting will be audio recorded. The deadline for questions is Friday, January 16, 2026, at 4:00 PM Local Time. DUE DATE: Tuesday, February 3, 2026, at 2:00 PM Local Time. Contact: Luis Aviles (407) 742-0937.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441769</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434822</link>
      <description>LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1) AR-26-15628-EN-Reflective and Electrocut Film Vinyl Contract


--- Full Notice Text ---
LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1) AR-26-15628-EN-Reflective and Electrocut Film Vinyl Contract. There will be no Pre-Bid Conference for this project: Deadline for Questions: Tuesday January 6, 2026, at 12:00 PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 2:00 PM Local Time. Contact Evelyn Nunez (407) 742-0935.
2) RFP-26-15629-MB  Mowing and Landscaping Services for Cypress Parkway. There will be no pre-bid conference for this project. Deadline for Questions: Tuesday, January 13, 2026, at 12:00 P.M. Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 27, 2026, at 2:00 P.M. Local Time. Contact: Melissa Baumwell (407) 742-0938.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.
December 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434822</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428233</link>
      <description>Notice at Sections 13 and 24

Location: Sections 13 and 24

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE
Notice is hereby provided that the South Florida Water Management District, on December 4, 2025, issued an Environmental Resource Permit #49-102288-P, Application #251010-57911 to Harmony West Community Development District, 2300 Glades Rd #410W, Boca Raton, FL 33431, and Osceola County Board of County Commissioners, 1 Courthouse Square, Kissimmee, FL 34741. This permit is a minor modification to Special Condition #2 to update the operation entities and a permit transfer to the operating entities, the Harmony West Community Development District (CDD) and the Osceola County Board of County Commissioners (BOCC), serving 53.66 acres of a 268-lot single family residential development known as The Villages at Harmony Phases 1C and 1D in Osceola County, located at Sections 13 and 24, Township 26, Range 31. A copy of the permit can be obtained by contacting the Regulatory Records Management Section, during normal business hours, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday, except legal holidays, at 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, FL 33406, Regulation Division, by telephone at 561-682-6911, by e-mail at permits@sfwmd.gov, or by accessing the permit directly from the Districts website (www.sfwmd.gov) using the Application/Permit Search on the ePermitting page.
The District's agency action is final unless a timely petition for an administrative hearing is filed under Sections 120.569 and 120.57 of the Florida Statutes before the deadline for filing a petition.
As required by Sections 120.569 and 120.60(3), Fla. Stat., the following is notice of the opportunities which may be available for administrative hearing or judicial review when the substantial interests of a party are determined by an agency. Please note that this Notice of Rights is not intended to provide legal advice. Not all of the legal proceedings detailed below may be an applicable or appropriate remedy. You may wish to consult an attorney regarding your legal rights.
RIGHT TO REQUEST ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
A person whose substantial interests are or may be affected by the South Florida Water Management Districts (SFWMD or District) action has the right to request an administrative hearing on that action pursuant to Sections 120.569 and 120.57, Fla. Stat. Persons seeking a hearing on a SFWMD decision which affects or may affect their substantial interests shall file a petition for hearing with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD, in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein, within 21 days of receipt of written notice of the decision, unless one of the following shorter time periods apply: (1) within 14 days of the notice of consolidated intent to grant or deny concurrently reviewed applications for environmental resource permits and use of sovereign submerged lands pursuant to Section 373.427, Fla. Stat.; or (2) within 14 days of service of an Administrative Order pursuant to Section 373.119(1), Fla. Stat. "Receipt of written notice of agency decision" means receipt of written notice through mail, electronic mail, or posting that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action, or publication of notice that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action. Any person who receives written notice of a SFWMD decision and fails to file a written request for hearing within the timeframe described above waives the right to request a hearing on that decision.
If the District takes final agency action which materially differs from the noticed intended agency decision, persons who may be substantially affected shall, unless otherwise provided by law, have an additional Rule 28-106.111, Fla. Admin. Code, point of entry.
Any person to whom an emergency order is directed pursuant to Section 373.119(2), Fla. Stat., shall comply therewith immediately, but on petition to the board shall be afforded a hearing as soon as possible.
A person may file a request for an extension of time for filing a petition. The SFWMD may, for good cause, grant the request. Requests for extension of time must be filed with the SFWMD prior to the deadline for filing a petition for hearing. Such requests for extension shall contain a certificate that the moving party has consulted with all other parties concerning the extension and that the SFWMD and any other parties agree to or oppose the extension. A timely request for an extension of time shall toll the running of the time period for filing a petition until the request is acted upon.
FILING INSTRUCTIONS
A petition for administrative hearing must be filed with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD. Filings with the Office of the District Clerk may be made by mail, hand-delivery, or e-mail. Filings by facsimile will not be accepted. A petition for administrative hearing or other document is deemed filed upon receipt during normal business hours by the Office of the District Clerk at SFWMD headquarters in West Palm Beach, Florida. The Districts normal business hours are 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m., excluding weekends and District holidays. Any document received by the Office of the District Clerk after 5:00 p.m. shall be deemed filed as of 8:00 a.m. on the next regular business day. Additional filing instructions are as follows:
 * Filings by mail must be addressed to the Office of the District Clerk, 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, Florida 33406.
 * Filings by hand-delivery must be delivered to the Office of the District Clerk. Delivery of a petition to the SFWMD's security desk does not constitute filing. It will be necessary to request that the SFWMD's security officer contact the Office of the District Clerk. An employee of the SFWMD's Clerk's office will receive and file the petition.
 * Filings by e-mail must be transmitted to the Office of the District Clerk at clerk@sfwmd.gov. The filing date for a document transmitted by electronic mail shall be the date the Office of the District Clerk receives the complete document. A party who files a document by e-mail shall (1) represent that the original physically signed document will be retained by that party for the duration of the proceeding and of any subsequent appeal or subsequent proceeding in that cause and that the party shall produce it upon the request of other parties; and (2) be responsible for any delay, disruption, or interruption of the electronic signals and accepts the full risk that the document may not be properly filed.
INITIATION OF AN ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
Pursuant to Sections 120.54(5)(b)4. and 120.569(2)(c), Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.201 and 28-106.301, Fla. Admin. Code, initiation of an administrative hearing shall be made by written petition to the SFWMD in legible form and on 8  by 11 inch white paper. All petitions shall contain:
 1. Identification of the action being contested, including the permit number, application number, SFWMD file number or any other SFWMD identification number, if known.
 2. The name, address, any email address, any facsimile number, and telephone number of the petitioner and petitioners representative, if any.
 3. An explanation of how the petitioners substantial interests will be affected by the agency determination.
 4. A statement of when and how the petitioner received notice of the SFWMDs decision.
 5. A statement of all disputed issues of material fact. If there are none, the petition must so indicate.
 6. A concise statement of the ultimate facts alleged, including the specific facts the petitioner contends warrant reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 7. A statement of the specific rules or statutes the petitioner contends require reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 8. If disputed issues of material fact exist, the statement must also include an explanation of how the alleged facts relate to the specific rules or statutes.
 9. A statement of the relief sought by the petitioner, stating precisely the action the petitioner wishes the SFWMD to take with respect to the SFWMDs proposed action.
MEDIATION
The procedures for pursuing mediation are set forth in Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.111 and 28-106.401.405, Fla. Admin. Code. The SFWMD is not proposing mediation for this agency action under Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., at this time.
RIGHT TO SEEK JUDICIAL REVIEW
Pursuant to Section 120.68, Fla. Stat., and in accordance with Florida Rule of Appellate Procedure 9.110, a party who is adversely affected by final SFWMD action may seek judicial review of the SFWMD's final decision by filing a notice of appeal with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein within 30 days of rendition of the order to be reviewed, and by filing a copy of the notice with the clerk of the appropriate district court of appeal.
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428233</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428211</link>
      <description>LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1)RFP-26-15570-JG  Prequalification for Printing, Signage, Banners, Pro...


--- Full Notice Text ---
LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY 
BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1)RFP-26-15570-JG  Prequalification for Printing, Signage, Banners, Promotional Awards, Embroidery and Screen Printing on a Task Authorization Basis. There will be no Pre-Proposal Conference for this project. Deadline for Questions: Monday, December 29, 2025, at 12:00 PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 2:00 PM Local Time. Contact: Jovany Galarza - (407) 742-0943.
2) AR-26-15392-PC  Monitoring and Maintenance of Fire, Security, and Critical Alarm Systems. There will be a VIRTUAL Non-Mandatory Pre-Bid Conference held on Monday, December 22, 2025, at 10:00 AM local Time, via the Microsoft TEAMS Application.Dial-in Number: 407-906-2344, and when prompted enter the Conference Code: 357 304 89#. Note: The Meeting will be audio recorded. Deadline for questions is Wednesday, January 7, 2026, at 12:00 PM local time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 2:00 PM local time. Contact: Paul Callaway (407) 742-0931.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428211</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11423413</link>
      <description>OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS   1


--- Full Notice Text ---
OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS   1. RFP-26-15570-JG  Prequalification for Printing, Signage, Banners, Promotional Awards, Embroidery and Screen Printing on a Task Authorization Basis. There will be no Pre-Proposal Conference for this project. Deadline for Questions: Monday, December 29, 2025, at 12:00PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 2:00PM Local Time. Contact: Jovany Galarza - (407) 742-0943.  2. AR-26-15392-PC  Monitoring and Maintenance of Fire, Security, and Critical Alarm Systems. There will be a VIRTUAL Non-Mandatory Pre-Bid Conference held on Monday, December 22, 2025, at 10:00AM local Time, via the Microsoft TEAMS Application. Dial-in Number: 407-906-2344, and when prompted enter the Conference Code: 357 304 89#. Note: The Meeting will be audio recorded. Deadline for questions is Wednesday, January 7, 2026, at 12:00 PM local time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 2:00PM local time. Contact: Paul Callaway (407) 742-0931.  FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.   12/14/2025 7907409</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11423413</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420499</link>
      <description>LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY
BOARD OF COUNTY
 COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1)AR-26-15523-HL-Sports Field Clay and Sand for Parks and Austin Tindall


--- Full Notice Text ---
LEGAL ADVERTISEMENT
OSCEOLA COUNTY
BOARD OF COUNTY
 COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:
1)AR-26-15523-HL-Sports Field Clay and Sand for Parks and Austin Tindall. There will be no Pre-Bid Conference for this project: Deadline for Questions: Tuesday December 16, 2025, at 2:00 PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, JANUARY 13, 2026, at 2:00 PM Local Time. Contact Heidi Lockwood (407) 742-0927.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org [http://vendorlink.osceola.org]
December 11, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420499</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416898</link>
      <description>OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:   1


--- Full Notice Text ---
OSCEOLA COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS PROJECTS:   1. AR-26-15523-HL-Sports Field Clay and Sand for Parks and Austin Tindall. There will be no Pre-Bid Conference for this project: Deadline for Questions: Tuesday December 16, 2025, at 2:00PM Local Time. Due Date: Tuesday, January 13, 2026, at 2:00PM Local Time. Contact Heidi Lockwood (407) 742-0927.  FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.   12/07/2025 7904620</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416898</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
