<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:28:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LUPA-25-0007 - 610 Buckley Dr</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/29/11426529.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 610 Buckley Dr: SF-LDR (Single-Family  Low Density Residential) → IN (Industrial Business) -

Type: Future Land Use Amendment (LUPA)
Meeting: Wednesday, January 7, 2026 at 6:00 p.m.
Location: 610 Buckley Dr
Zoning: SF-LDR (Single-Family  Low Density Residential) → IN (Industrial Business) -
Parcel ID: 19-25-29-0000-0290-0000 and 19-25-29-0000-0280-0000 and 19-25-29-0000-0281-0000
Reference: LUPA-25-0007

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/17/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD  The City of Kissimmee proposes to change the use of land for the area described in this advertisement by adopting an ordinance with the following title: An ordinance amending Ordinance No. 3050 known as the Ordinance Adopting the Comprehensive Development Plan for the City of Kissimmee, Florida, under the authority of Florida Statute 163.3184; Directing the City Manager to amend the Comprehensive Land Use Plan as herein provided after the passage of this ordinance; Providing for a public hearing as required by law; Repealing all ordinances in conflict herewith; and providing an effective date. The Planning Advisory Board will hold a Public Hearing on this request, Wednesday, January 7, 2026 at 6:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, located on the first floor of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida 34741. The purpose of this Public Hearing is to make a recommendation to the City Commission concerning the request to amend Ordinance No. 3050. The proposed Ordinance would amend the 2026 Future Land Use Map of the Kissimmee Comprehensive Plan by changing the land use classification for the area described below as follows: FROM: SF-LDR (Single-Family  Low Density Residential)  City TO: IN (Industrial Business) - City The subject properties are located at 610 Buckley Dr. Legal Description: Parcel 1: 19-25-29-0000-0290-0000 BEG 9 FT N OF SE COR OF NW 1/4, N 200 FT, W 450 FT, S 200 FT, E 450 FT TO POB Together with Parcel 2: 19-25-29-0000-0280-0000 COM AT NE COR OF SE 1/4 OF NW 1/4, S 1000 FT TO POB; CONT S 100 FT, W TO E BANK OF SHINGLE CREEK, NELY ALONG CREEK TO PT W OF POB, E TO POB LESS E 30 FT FOR R/W Together with Parcel 3: 19-25-29-0000-0281-0000 BEG SE COR OF NW 1/4, N 209 FT TO POB; W 450 FT, S 200 FT, W TO E BANK OF SHINGLE CREEK, NELY ALONG CREEK TO PT 1100 FT S OF N/L OF SE 1/4 OF NW 1/4, E TO E/L OF NW 1/4, S 27.45 FT MOL TO POB LESS E 30 FT FOR R/W PROPOSED ORDINANCE# 26-01: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING ORDINANCE NO. 3050 KNOWN AS THE ORDINANCE ADOPTING THE COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT PLAN FOR THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA, UNDER THE AUTHORITY OF FLORIDA STATUTE 163.3184; DIRECTING THE CITY MANAGER TO AMEND THE COMPREHENSIVE LAND USE PLAN AS HEREIN PROVIDED AFTER THE PASSAGE OF THIS ORDINANCE; PROVIDING FOR A PUBLIC HEARING AS REQUIRED BY LAW; REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The proposed amendment and the supporting documents, including a parcel  description, may be inspected in the Development Services Department, City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida, between 8:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday. Please direct any questions to the Development Services Department, (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov . Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person. Reference # LUPA-25-0007 PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD 610 Buckley Dr. KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA  In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made. In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26)  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD  7908569</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426529</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11426529.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZMA-25-0011 - 610 Buckley Dr</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/28/11426528.pdf</link>
      <description>Rezoning at 610 Buckley Dr: RA-1 (Single-Family Residential) → AI (Airport Industrial)

Type: Zoning Map Amendment (ZMA)
Meeting: Wednesday, January 7, 2026 at 6:00 p.m.
Location: 610 Buckley Dr
Zoning: RA-1 (Single-Family Residential) → AI (Airport Industrial)
Parcel ID: 19-25-29-0000-0290- 0000, 19-25-29-0000-0280-0000 and 19-25-29-0000-0281-0000
Reference: ZMA-25-0011

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/17/2025 This is to inform you that the City of Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board will make a recommendation to the City Commission concerning a request to amend the official Zoning Map, the City of Kissimmee Land Development Code Ordinance No. 3110 for the property described herein: FROM: RA-1 (Single-Family Residential)  City TO: AI (Airport Industrial)  City The subject property is located at 610 Buckley Dr. Parcel IDs: 19-25-29-0000-0290- 0000, 19-25-29-0000-0280-0000 and 19-25-29-0000-0281-0000 Legal Descriptions: Parcel 1: 19-25-29-0000-0290-0000 BEG 9 FT N OF SE COR OF NW 1/4, N 200 FT, W 450 FT, S 200 FT, E 450 FT TO POB Together with Parcel 2: 19-25-29-0000-0280-0000 COM AT NE COR OF SE 1/4 OF NW 1/4, S 1000 FT TO POB; CONT S 100 FT, W TO E BANK OF SHINGLE CREEK, NELY ALONG CREEK TO PT W OF POB, E TO POB LESS E 30 FT FOR R/W Together with Parcel 3: 19-25-29-0000-0281-0000 BEG SE COR OF NW 1/4, N 209 FT TO POB; W 450 FT, S 200 FT, W TO E BANK OF SHINGLE CREEK, NELY ALONG CREEK TO PT 1100 FT S OF N/L OF SE 1/4 OF NW 1/4, E TO E/L OF NW 1/4, S 27.45 FT MOL TO POB LESS E 30 FT FOR R/W PROPOSED ORDINANCE #26-02: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING ORDINANCE NO. 3110 KNOWN AS THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE, REZONING THE PROPERTY HEREINAFTER DESCRIBED, REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The Planning Advisory Board will hold a meeting to consider their recommendation on said request on Wednesday, January 7, 2026 at 6:00 p.m. in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, FL, 34741. Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person. Any questions may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov . Reference # ZMA-25-0011 PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD 610 Buckley Dr. KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA  In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26) In accordance with Florida Statues 286.0105: Any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the Planning Advisory Board with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made.  CITY OF KISSIMMEE PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD  7898547</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426528</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11426528.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CU-25-0017 - 1720 W Oak St Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/35/11411335.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 1720 W Oak St Kissimmee

Location: 1720 W Oak St Kissimmee
Parcel ID: 21- 25-29-1670-0046-0180 Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person. Any questions regarding this public hearing may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov. Reference # CU-25-0017 PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD 1720 W Oak St. Office KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26) In accordance with Florida Statute 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made. 7901507 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD
Reference: CU-25-0017

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/1/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD  This is to inform you that the Planning Advisory Board of the City of Kissimmee will consider a request for a Conditional Use to establish an office at 1720 W Oak St. The Planning Advisory Board will hold a meeting on Wednesday, December 17, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. at the City Commission Chambers, 101 Church St., Kissimmee, FL 34741. The subject property is located at 1720 W Oak St Kissimmee, FL 34741 Parcel ID: 21- 25-29-1670-0046-0180 Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person. Any questions regarding this public hearing may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov. Reference # CU-25-0017 PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD 1720 W Oak St. Office KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26) In accordance with Florida Statute 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made. 7901507 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING PLANNING ADVISORY BOARD</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11411335</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11411335.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
