<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:21:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437887</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING ORDINANCE NO. 2024-50   Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2024-50 entitled:  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, READOPTING THE ORDINANCE ADOPTING A LARGE SCALE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN AMENDMENT INCORPORATING COMMENTS SUBMITTED BY THE STATE OF FLORIDA AFTER THE INITIAL ADOPTION OF THE ORDINANCE AND PURSUANT TO SECTION 163.3184 FLORIDA STATUTES AMENDING THE FUTURE LAND USE ELEMENT OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, PROJECT # CPA24-00007; PROVIDING FOR AMENDING THE OFFICIAL FUTURE LAND USE TEXT AND MAP OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, APPLICABILITY AND EFFECT, SEVERABILITY, CONFLICT, CODIFICATION, COPIES ON FILE, SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND EFFECTIVE DATE.  Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered  and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon.  This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.   If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud.  (FS 286.0105)  In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting.  (FS 286.26) 				 Ivy Llauro, City Clerk 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769 407-957-7300   12/29/2025 7913794</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437887</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/82/11437882.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL

Meeting: MONDAY, JANUARY 12, 2026 at 6:30 PM
Location: WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/29/2025  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS  NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN THAT THE CITY COMMISSION PROPOSE  TO CONSIDER THE FOLLOWING: ORDINANCE NO. 2025-17  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COMMISSION OF THE CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA; AMENDING CHAPTER 20, ZONING, ARTICLE V, SUPPLEMENTAL DISTRICT REGULATIONS, OF THE CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS CODE OF ORDINANCES TO ADD PROCEDURES FOR PROCESSING REQUESTS FOR REASONABLE ACCOMMODATION FROM THE CITYS LAND DEVELOPMENT REGULATIONS, WHICH SHALL ALSO BE APPLICABLE TO CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES IN ORDER TO COMPLY WITH FLORIDA STATUTES SECTION 397.487; AMENDING ARTICLE III, ESTABLISHMENT OF DISTRICTS, TO ESTABLISH CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES AS PERMITTED OR CONDITIONAL USES IN CERTAIN ZONING DISTRICTS; PROVIDING FOR THE REPEAL OF PRIOR INCONSISTENT ORDINANCES AND RESOLUTIONS, INCORPORATION INTO THE CODE, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. CITY COMMISSION PUBLIC HEARINGS FOR SECOND READING/ADOPTION WILL BE HELD ON MONDAY, JANUARY 12, 2026 AT 6:30 PM OR SOON THEREAFTER IN THE COMMISSION CHAMBERS LOCATED AT WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL, 1126 EAST STATE ROAD 434, WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA THE CITY COMMISSION RESERVES THE RIGHT TO POSTPONE OR CONTINUE THE PUBLIC HEARING ON THIS ORDINANCE AT THIS MEETING WITHOUT FURTHER NOTICE. The proposed ordinance may be obtained by interested parties between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m., Monday through Friday, from the office of the City Clerk, located at 1126 E. SR 434, Winter Springs, Florida. For more information, call (407) 327-1800 #237. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Employee Relations Department Coordinator, 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 327-1800, #236. This is a public hearing. Interested parties are advised that they may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed resolutions. If you decide to appeal any recommendation or decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at this meeting, you will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes, you may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made upon which the appeal is based. 7907930</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437882</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11437882.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437055</link>
      <description>ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on January 13, 2026, at 2 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on January 13, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the following proposed ordinance:  AN ORDINANCE PERTAINING TO ORANGE COUNTY SEALS AND LOGOS; AMENDING SECTION 2-3 OF THE ORANGE COUNTY CODE; UPDATING THE LOGOS AND SEALS; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  You may examine the notice and the proposed ordinance at the office of the Comptroller Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Fourth Floor; Orlando, Florida; between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m., Monday through Friday.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS NOTICE, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY OFFICE OF COMMUNICATIONS, 407-836-5429, Email: Jeff.Williamson@ocfl.net  PARA MAS INFORMACION EN ESPANIOL ACERCA DE ESTAS REUNIONES PUBLICAS O DE CAMBIOS POR SER EFECTUADOS, FAVOR DE LLAMAR A LA OFICINA DE LOS ABOGADOS DEL CONDADO, AL 407-836-7320.  POU W KA JWENN PLIS ENFMASYON AN KREYL AYISYEN SOU REYINYON PIBLIK SA YO OSWA SOU CHANJMAN KAP FT YO, TANPRI RELE 407-836-3111.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7912650 12/28/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437055</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437052</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF A WORKSHOP MEETING FOR NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Work...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF A WORKSHOP MEETING FOR NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Workshop Meeting of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities will be held by the Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida, on Thursday, January 8, 2026, at 3:00 p.m. at 200 Canal Street.  Copies of the agenda will be posted on the doors of the first floor of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities office at 200 Canal Street and also on NSBUs website - www.nsbufl.com.  Pursuant to section 286.0105 of the Florida Statutes, if an individual decides to appeal any decision made by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities, with respect to any matter considered at a meeting, that individual will need a record of the proceedings and will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made.  The transcription of such a verbatim will be provided to an individual at a cost to be determined by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities in accordance with the full cost to reproduce such transcriptions and copies.  In accordance with the American with Disabilities Act, persons with disabilities needing a special accommodation to participate in these proceedings should contact the individual or agency sending the notice; if possible no later than five days prior to the proceeding at the address given on notice. 7912098 12-28-25</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437052</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434830</link>
      <description>Notice at 8 Broadway

Location: 8 Broadway

--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater East Community Development District (District) will hold a Regular Meeting on January 8, 2026, at 9:00 a.m., at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., located at 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, http://edgewatereastcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
December 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434830</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434825</link>
      <description>EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater Wes...


--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater West Community Development District (District), will hold a Regular Meeting on January 8, 2026, at 9:15 a.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, https://edgewaterwestcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
December 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434825</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434816</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO. 2026-002R


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Resolution No. 2026-002R entitled:


A RESOLUTION OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, GRANTING A SUBDIVISION VARIANCE TO REDUCE FRONT YARD SETBACKS ON A PREVIOUSLY APPROVED SUBDIVISION CONSTRUCTION PLAN IN THE R-1B ZONING DISTRICT ON THE +/- 42.57 ACRES OF LAND KNOWN AS TYSON RESERVE (VAR24-00001), GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF K C DURHAM ROAD, EAST OF NORA TYSON ROAD, AND WEST OF CHATSWORTH CIRCLE, AS DESCRIBED IN THE BODY OF THIS RESOLUTION.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this RESOLUTION is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed RESOLUTION at the Public Hearing thereon. This RESOLUTION in its entirety can be reviewed at the City Clerk's office between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 2:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
December 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434816</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434256</link>
      <description>ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF ZONING ADJUSTMENTMEETING NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGNotice is hereby given that the Orange County Board of Zoning Adjustment (B...

Parcel ID: 11-24-29-1141-00-0102. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-082  APPLICANT: DEREK WALTERS  OWNER: US PIPE FABRICATION LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variance in the I-2/I-3 zoning district to allow a dumpster to be  located in the front yard in lieu of the side or rear yards  ADDRESS: 202 4th St., Orlando, FL 32824  LOCATION: Located south of 4th St., east of Ave. E, west of Ave. D, and north of  5th St., north of Taft Vineland Rd., east of the FL Turnpike, south of  E. Landstreet Rd., west of S. Orange Ave.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 2.06 acres  DISTRICT#: 3  PARCEL ID: 01-24-29-8516-40-201   9:30 AM   3. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-084  APPLICANT: OMAR SANCHEZ  OWNER: ZOMAR CAPITAL LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variances in the R-1A zoning district to allow a new residence as  follows:   1) A 55.2 ft. lot width in lieu of 75 ft.   2) A rear setback of 25.88 ft. in lieu of 30 ft.  ADDRESS: 731 Timor Ave., Orlando, FL 32804  LOCATION: North side of Timor Ave., east of Adanson St,. south of Lee Rd., north of W. Fairbanks Ave., west of I-4  TRACT SIZE: +/- 7,707 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 5  PARCEL ID: 02-22-29-8472-05-2204. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-02-086  APPLICANT: DENNIS DELABY  OWNER: DENNIS DELABY  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variances in the R-1 zoning district as follows:   1) To allow a pool and deck with a Normal High-Water Elevation  (NHWE) setback of 9.3 ft. in lieu of 25 ft.   2) To allow an existing accessory structure (shed) with a Normal  High-Water Elevation (NHWE) setback of 6.2 ft. in lieu of 25 ft.  ADDRESS: 2914 S M U Blvd., Orlando, FL 32817  LOCATION: West side of S M U Blvd., north of E. Colonial Dr., east of N. Goldenrod Rd., south of University Blvd., west of S.R. 417.   TRACT SIZE: +/- 13,105 sq. ft.  DISTRICT#: 5  PARCEL ID: 12-22-30-8831-01-090   5. CASE NUMBER: VA-25-09-042  APPLICANT: MANTIN QAMAR  OWNER: CT16 LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Laekin OHara; 407-836-5943; Laekin.OHara@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variances in the I-4 zoning district as follows:   1) To allow an exterior stairway with a south side setback of 18.48 ft.  in lieu of 25 ft.   2) To allow 31 parking spaces in lieu of 86 parking spaces  ADDRESS: 11136 Satellite Blvd., Orlando, FL 32837  LOCATION: West side of Satellite Blvd., east of S. Orange Blossom Trl., south of  Central Florida Pkwy., west of FL Turnpike, north of W. Wetherbee  Rd.   TRACT SIZE: +/- 0.68 acres  DISTRICT#: 4  PARCEL ID: 10-24-29-1234-00-13010:00 AM   6. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-083  APPLICANT: LUCILLE GHIOTO  OWNER: HABITAT FOR HUMANITY GREATER ORLANDO AND  OSCEOLA COUNTY INC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; 407-836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variance in the R-2 zoning district to allow a structure to be located  nearer the side street lot line than the required front yard of such  abutting lot (18 ft. in lieu of 20 ft.)  ADDRESS: 1002 26th St., Orlando, FL 32805  LOCATION: Southwest corner of 26th St. and S Westmoreland Dr., north of W.  Michigan St., east of S Orange Blossom Trl., west of I-4, south of W.  Kaley Ave.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 6,747 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 6  PARCEL ID: 03-23-29-0180-52-010   7. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-085  APPLICANT: AMIT UBALE  OWNER: NIRMAN DEVELOPMENT LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; 407-836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variances in the R-CE-C zoning district as follows:  1) To allow a minimum lot width of 75 ft. in lieu of 100 ft.   2) To allow a 3-story residence in lieu of 2-stories  3) To allow a maximum height of 39.83 ft. in lieu of 35 ft.  ADDRESS: 1372 Lake Olivia Ln., Windermere, FL 34786  LOCATION: South terminus of Lake Olivia Ln., east side of Lake Olivia, west of  S. Apopka Vineland Rd., north of Windy Ridge Rd., south of FL  Turnpike  TRACT SIZE: +/- 3.81 acres (0.69 acres upland)  DISTRICT#: 1  PARCEL ID: 33-22-28-4668-00-12010:30 AM   8. CASE NUMBER: SE-25-11-061  APPLICANT: ADRIENNE DOWNEY-JACKS FOR EVOLVE CHURCH  OWNER: FIRST BAPTIST CHURCH ORLANDO CAMPUS INC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; (407) 836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Special Exception and Variance in the A-1 zoning district as follows:  1) Special Exception to allow a day care facility within the existing  church structure.   2) Variance to allow grass parking in lieu of parking on an improved  surface   ADDRESS: 10550 Clarcona Ocoee Rd. and 10564 2nd Ave., Apopka, FL 32703 LOCATION: South of Clarcona Ocoee Rd., west of N. Clarke Rd., east of  Highway 429, north of Wurst Rd.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 3.78 acres   DISTRICT#: 2  PARCEL ID: 05-22-28-6052-01-090, 05-22-28-6052-04-040   9. CASE NUMBER: VA-25-11-055  APPLICANT: EDYNARDO WEYNE  OWNER: MAGIC HOUSES LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Daniella McCloud; 407-836-2939; Daniella.McCloud@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variance in the R-2 zoning district to allow a new residence with a  side street setback of 6.1 ft. in lieu of 15 ft.  ADDRESS: 1111 Derby Ave., Apopka, FL 32703  LOCATION: Southeast corner of Derby Ave. and E. 11th St., north of E. 13th St.,  east of Clarcona Rd., south of S.R. 441, west of S.R. 424  TRACT SIZE: +/- 8,645 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 2  PARCEL ID: 15-21-28-7532-00-150 7910391 12/24/2025

--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF ZONING ADJUSTMENTMEETING NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGNotice is hereby given that the Orange County Board of Zoning Adjustment (BZA) shall  consider the requests listed below at their January 8, 2026, public hearing. Public  hearings will be held in the County Commissioners Chambers located on the first floor  of the Orange County Administration Building, 201 S. Rosalind Avenue beginning at  9:00 a.m. or as soon thereafter as possible.   Please be advised that Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person  decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to  any matter considered at a meeting or hearing he will need a record of the proceedings,  and that for such purpose, he may need to ensure a verbatim record of the proceedings  is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to  be based.   The notated public hearing is quasi-judicial in nature. As such, any verbal or written  communication with a member of the Board of Zoning Adjustment prior to todays quasi judicial hearing should be disclosed on the record or made a part of the record during  the public hearing by or on behalf of the party who communicated with the Board  member to allow any interested party an opportunity to inquire about or respond to such  communication. Failure to disclose any such communication may place the party who  ultimately prevails at the quasi-judicial hearing at risk of having the Boards decision  overturned in a court of law due to prejudice against the party who was not privy to the  ex parte communication.   Para ms informacin referente a esta audiencia pblica, favor de comunicarse  con la Divisin de Zonificacion al nmero (407) 836-3111.  Pou plis enfmasyon odyans piblik sa a tanpri kontakt Divizyon Zn nan nan  nimewo (407) 836-3111.   AGENDA: 9:00 A.M.  PLEDGE OF ALLEGIANCE, REVIEW OF THE MINUTES FROM THE  DECEMBER 4, 2025, BZA MEETING, and PUBLIC COMMENT   ELECTION OF OFFICERS FOR THE 2026 BZA MEETINGS.   THE FOLLOWING PUBLIC HEARINGS WILL OCCUR AFTER PUBLIC COMMENT:  1. CASE NUMBER: VA-25-11-064  APPLICANT: ROY E. TYSON  OWNER: CROWN ENTERPRISES INC  PROJECT PLANNER: Bryan Salamanca; 407-836-9616; Bryan.Salamanca@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variance in the I-4 zoning district to allow the parking of commercial  vehicles within the front fifty (50) percent of the required front yard.  ADDRESS: 10066 General Dr., Orlando, FL 32824  LOCATION: Southwest corner of Taft Vineland Rd. and General Dr., east of FL  Turnpike, west of S. Orange Ave., north of W. Wetherbee Rd.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 16.87 acres   DISTRICT#: 3  PARCEL ID: 11-24-29-1141-00-0102. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-082  APPLICANT: DEREK WALTERS  OWNER: US PIPE FABRICATION LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variance in the I-2/I-3 zoning district to allow a dumpster to be  located in the front yard in lieu of the side or rear yards  ADDRESS: 202 4th St., Orlando, FL 32824  LOCATION: Located south of 4th St., east of Ave. E, west of Ave. D, and north of  5th St., north of Taft Vineland Rd., east of the FL Turnpike, south of  E. Landstreet Rd., west of S. Orange Ave.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 2.06 acres  DISTRICT#: 3  PARCEL ID: 01-24-29-8516-40-201   9:30 AM   3. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-084  APPLICANT: OMAR SANCHEZ  OWNER: ZOMAR CAPITAL LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variances in the R-1A zoning district to allow a new residence as  follows:   1) A 55.2 ft. lot width in lieu of 75 ft.   2) A rear setback of 25.88 ft. in lieu of 30 ft.  ADDRESS: 731 Timor Ave., Orlando, FL 32804  LOCATION: North side of Timor Ave., east of Adanson St,. south of Lee Rd., north of W. Fairbanks Ave., west of I-4  TRACT SIZE: +/- 7,707 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 5  PARCEL ID: 02-22-29-8472-05-2204. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-02-086  APPLICANT: DENNIS DELABY  OWNER: DENNIS DELABY  PROJECT PLANNER: Jacqueline Boling; 407-836-5955; Jacqueline.Boling@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variances in the R-1 zoning district as follows:   1) To allow a pool and deck with a Normal High-Water Elevation  (NHWE) setback of 9.3 ft. in lieu of 25 ft.   2) To allow an existing accessory structure (shed) with a Normal  High-Water Elevation (NHWE) setback of 6.2 ft. in lieu of 25 ft.  ADDRESS: 2914 S M U Blvd., Orlando, FL 32817  LOCATION: West side of S M U Blvd., north of E. Colonial Dr., east of N. Goldenrod Rd., south of University Blvd., west of S.R. 417.   TRACT SIZE: +/- 13,105 sq. ft.  DISTRICT#: 5  PARCEL ID: 12-22-30-8831-01-090   5. CASE NUMBER: VA-25-09-042  APPLICANT: MANTIN QAMAR  OWNER: CT16 LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Laekin OHara; 407-836-5943; Laekin.OHara@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variances in the I-4 zoning district as follows:   1) To allow an exterior stairway with a south side setback of 18.48 ft.  in lieu of 25 ft.   2) To allow 31 parking spaces in lieu of 86 parking spaces  ADDRESS: 11136 Satellite Blvd., Orlando, FL 32837  LOCATION: West side of Satellite Blvd., east of S. Orange Blossom Trl., south of  Central Florida Pkwy., west of FL Turnpike, north of W. Wetherbee  Rd.   TRACT SIZE: +/- 0.68 acres  DISTRICT#: 4  PARCEL ID: 10-24-29-1234-00-13010:00 AM   6. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-083  APPLICANT: LUCILLE GHIOTO  OWNER: HABITAT FOR HUMANITY GREATER ORLANDO AND  OSCEOLA COUNTY INC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; 407-836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variance in the R-2 zoning district to allow a structure to be located  nearer the side street lot line than the required front yard of such  abutting lot (18 ft. in lieu of 20 ft.)  ADDRESS: 1002 26th St., Orlando, FL 32805  LOCATION: Southwest corner of 26th St. and S Westmoreland Dr., north of W.  Michigan St., east of S Orange Blossom Trl., west of I-4, south of W.  Kaley Ave.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 6,747 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 6  PARCEL ID: 03-23-29-0180-52-010   7. CASE NUMBER: VA-26-01-085  APPLICANT: AMIT UBALE  OWNER: NIRMAN DEVELOPMENT LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; 407-836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net REQUEST: Variances in the R-CE-C zoning district as follows:  1) To allow a minimum lot width of 75 ft. in lieu of 100 ft.   2) To allow a 3-story residence in lieu of 2-stories  3) To allow a maximum height of 39.83 ft. in lieu of 35 ft.  ADDRESS: 1372 Lake Olivia Ln., Windermere, FL 34786  LOCATION: South terminus of Lake Olivia Ln., east side of Lake Olivia, west of  S. Apopka Vineland Rd., north of Windy Ridge Rd., south of FL  Turnpike  TRACT SIZE: +/- 3.81 acres (0.69 acres upland)  DISTRICT#: 1  PARCEL ID: 33-22-28-4668-00-12010:30 AM   8. CASE NUMBER: SE-25-11-061  APPLICANT: ADRIENNE DOWNEY-JACKS FOR EVOLVE CHURCH  OWNER: FIRST BAPTIST CHURCH ORLANDO CAMPUS INC  PROJECT PLANNER: Catherine Glase; (407) 836-9615; Catherine.Glase@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Special Exception and Variance in the A-1 zoning district as follows:  1) Special Exception to allow a day care facility within the existing  church structure.   2) Variance to allow grass parking in lieu of parking on an improved  surface   ADDRESS: 10550 Clarcona Ocoee Rd. and 10564 2nd Ave., Apopka, FL 32703 LOCATION: South of Clarcona Ocoee Rd., west of N. Clarke Rd., east of  Highway 429, north of Wurst Rd.  TRACT SIZE: +/- 3.78 acres   DISTRICT#: 2  PARCEL ID: 05-22-28-6052-01-090, 05-22-28-6052-04-040   9. CASE NUMBER: VA-25-11-055  APPLICANT: EDYNARDO WEYNE  OWNER: MAGIC HOUSES LLC  PROJECT PLANNER: Daniella McCloud; 407-836-2939; Daniella.McCloud@ocfl.net  REQUEST: Variance in the R-2 zoning district to allow a new residence with a  side street setback of 6.1 ft. in lieu of 15 ft.  ADDRESS: 1111 Derby Ave., Apopka, FL 32703  LOCATION: Southeast corner of Derby Ave. and E. 11th St., north of E. 13th St.,  east of Clarcona Rd., south of S.R. 441, west of S.R. 424  TRACT SIZE: +/- 8,645 sq. ft.   DISTRICT#: 2  PARCEL ID: 15-21-28-7532-00-150 7910391 12/24/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434256</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432186</link>
      <description>CELEBRATION COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR POND BANK RESTORATION AND NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING TO OPEN PROPOSALS   The Cel...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CELEBRATION COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR POND BANK RESTORATION AND NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING TO OPEN PROPOSALS   The Celebration Community Development District (District) hereby informally requests proposals from firms to provide services necessary for the Districts Pond Bank Restoration Project (Project), as more particularly described in the project manual (Project Manual) and in accordance with the plans and specifications prepared by the District Engineer, Mark Vincutonis, Hanson Walter &amp; Associates Inc. The District is a special purpose unit of local government established under Chapter 190, Florida Statutes, for the purpose of financing, acquiring, constructing, operating and maintaining community infrastructure improvements for the District.  To be eligible to submit a proposal, and in addition to any other requirements set forth in the Project Manual, an interested firm must hold all required local, state and federal licenses in good standing and be authorized to do business in Osceola County and the State of Florida.  The Project Manual, including instructions to proposers, proposal and contract specifications, and other materials, will be available beginning on Monday, December 29, 2025, by emailing Mr. Kerry Satterwhite, Kerry.satterwhite@inframark.com. The District reserves the right in its sole discretion to make changes to the Project Manual up until the time of the proposal opening, and to provide notice of such changes only to those proposers who have requested a Project Manual.  Firms desiring to provide services for this Project must submit one (1) original and one (1) electronic copy (PDF format on a USB flash drive) of the required proposal no later than Friday, January 16, 2026, at 12:00 noon to the District Managers Office at 313 Campus Street, Celebration, FL 34747. Proposals shall be in the form provided in the Project Manual and submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with a notation RESPONSE TO PROPOSAL FOR CELEBRATION CDD POND BANK RESTORATION PROJECT. The District reserves the right to return, unopened to the proposer, any proposals received after the time and date stipulated above. Each proposal shall remain binding for a minimum of one hundred twenty (120) days after the proposals opening. The District intends to award the Project or portions of the Project a proposal at their regular board meeting on Tuesday, January 27, 2026.  Proposals will be evaluated in accordance with the criteria included in the Project Manual. The District reserves the right to reject any and all proposals, make modifications to the work, award the contract in whole or in part with or without cause, and waive minor or technical irregularities in any proposal, as it deems appropriate, and if the District determines in its discretion that it is in the Districts best interests to do so. Price is only a portion of consideration.  NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING TO OPEN PROPOSALS  Pursuant to Section 255.0518, Florida Statutes, the proposals will be publicly opened on Friday, January 16, 2026, at 12:00 noon at the District Managers Office, 313 Campus Street, Celebration FL 34747. The purpose of the RFP opening will be to announce the names of the proposers and pricing. Any proposal not completed as specified or missing the required proposal documents as provided in the Project Manual may be disqualified.  The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. In accordance with the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the RFP opening is asked to advise the District Managers Office at 407-566-1935, at least 48 hours before the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800- 955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  Any and all questions relative to this Request for Proposals, the Project or the RFP opening shall be directed in writing by e-mail only to Mr. Kerry Satterwhite, Director of Field Operations, at Kerry.satterwhite@inframark.com no later than Monday, January 12, 2026, at 12:00 noon. Answers and Questions will be emailed to all proposers who have requested a project manual. No phone inquiries please.  Celebration Community Development District Kerry Satterwhite, District Manager12/23/2025 7911562</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432186</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432181</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE NARCOOSSEE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A public hearing will...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE NARCOOSSEE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors of the Narcoossee Community Development District (District) on January 27, 2026, at 3:00 p.m., at 6200 Lee Vista Boulevard, Suite 300, Orlando, Florida 32822.  In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, Chapter 1. The purpose and effect of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. Prior notice of rule development was published in the Orlando Sentinel on December 16, 2025.  The Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure may address topics such as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings and competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings, as well as any other area of the general operation of the District.  Specific legal authority for the adoption of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes (2025). The specific laws implemented in the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 189.053, 189.069(2)(a)(15), 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011(3), 190.011(5), 190.011(15), 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0992, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes (2025).  A copy of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure and any material proposed to be incorporated by reference may be obtained by contacting Jason Showe at the District Managers Office by mail at Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, by telephone at (407) 841-5524, or by email at jshowe@gmscfl.com.  Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes, must do so in writing within twentyone (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.  This public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at a public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least three (3) business days prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1800-955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  District Manager Narcoossee Community Development District   12/23/2025 7906626</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432181</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431371</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING DATES  REUNION EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT  FISCAL YEAR 2026   The Board of Supervisors of the Reunion East Community Dev...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING DATES  REUNION EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT  FISCAL YEAR 2026   The Board of Supervisors of the Reunion East Community Development District will hold their regularly scheduled public meetings for Fiscal Year 2026 at 12:30 pm at the Heritage Crossing Community Center, 7715 Heritage Crossing Way, Reunion, Florida  34747, on the second Thursday of each month as follows:  January 8, 2026 February 12, 2026 March 12, 2026 April 9, 2026 May 14, 2026 June 11, 2026 July 9, 2026 August 13, 2026 September 10, 2026  The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. A copy of the agenda for a particular meeting may be obtained from the District Manager at 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801; (407)841-5524, during normal business hours, or by visiting the Districts website at https://reunioneastcdd.com.   A meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place as evidenced by motion of the majority of Board Members participating at that meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors will participate by telephone.  Any person requiring special accommodations at a meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (407) 841-5524 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Tricia L. Adams Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC District Manager   12/22/2025 7911348</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431371</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431369</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
Everest GMR Community Development District Notice of Board of Supervisors Meeting   A Board of Supervisors Special Meeting of the Everest GMR Community Development District will be held on Monday, December 29, 2025, at 11:00 a.m. at 8298 W Irlo Bronson Memorial Hwy, Kissimmee, FL 34747. A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, located at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, (407) 723-5900, during normal business hours. Additionally, a copy of the agenda may be obtained at http://everestgmrcdd.com/.  The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the pertinent provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.  Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5940 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.  Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jane Gaarlandt District Manager   12/22/2025 7910822</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431369</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431367</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING   You are hereby notified that the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida, which also sits as the...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING   You are hereby notified that the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida, which also sits as the Local Planning Agency and the Land Development Regulation Commission will hold a public hearing. The hearing will be held at 6:00 P.M., Thursday, January 15, 2026, or as soon thereafter as is reasonably possible in the Maitland City Hall Council Chambers, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida 32751.  The purpose of the hearing is to take public comment, both written and oral, concerning a petition filed by the City of Maitland, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida, to amend the Land Development Code, Section 2.5 Subdivision, Section 2.5.2(b)  Site Development and Platting, and Section 6.4 Subdivision 6.4.2  Bond Inspection, Report and Acceptance, establishing a process for a subdivision plat or replat to be administratively approved if the plat or replat complies with the requirements of s. 177.091, Florida Statutes.  A complete copy of the proposed amendment to the Land Development Code may be inspected by any interested person Monday-Thursday, 7:00 A.M. - 6:00 P.M., in the Community Development Department, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida, 32751. The public is invited to attend the public hearing and may submit written comments at or before the public hearing or attend the public hearing to be heard by the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida. Questions concerning the notice of public hearing may be directed to the Community Development Department at (407) 539-6212.  Any person who desires to appeal any decision made at this meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings and, for this purpose, may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office (407) 539-6219 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  Sara Blanchard Chief Planner City of Maitland   12/22/2025 7908271</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431367</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431363</link>
      <description>Notice at the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue

Location: the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGFor the purposes of Section 147(f) of the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, as mended (the Code), notice is hereby given that the Florida Local Government Finance Commission (the Issuer) will hold a public hearing on December 29, 2025, at 10:00 A.M., or as soon thereafter as practicable. In accordance with Internal Revenue Service Revenue Procedure 2022-20, this public hearing will be held by telephone conference. Interested persons are encouraged to attend the telephone conference using the following instructions:  TELEPHONE CONFERENCE INSTRUCTIONS:  TOLL-FREE DIAL IN NUMBER: 1 (877) 304-9269  PASSCODE: 359237#  The public hearing is being conducted for the purpose of receiving comments and hearing discussion concerning the proposed adoption by the Issuer of a resolution approving the issuance and sale by the Issuer of not exceeding $17,000,000 of its Florida Local Government Finance Commission Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds (Cornerstone Charter Academy Project) to be issued in one or more tax-exempt and/or taxable series of qualified 501(c)(3) bonds, as defined in Section 145 of the Code (collectively, the Bonds), pursuant to a plan of finance.  The proceeds of the Bonds, when and if issued, will be loaned to Cornerstone Charter Academy, Inc., a Florida not-for-profit corporation and an organization described under Section 501(c)(3) of the Code, or one of its affiliates (the Borrower). The proceeds will be used by the Borrower for the purposes of: (a) financing and  refinancing all or a portion of the costs of acquiring, constructing, equipping, and/or improving of certain educational facilities located at the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue, (ii) 5903 Randolph Avenue, (iii) 6300 Hansel Avenue, (iv) 6049 Randolph Avenue, (v) 5929 Hansel Avenue, (vi) 942 Fairlane Avenue and (vii) a contiguous approximately 2.4-acre parcel known as Wallace Field bordered to the south by E. Wallace Street and located to the north of the intersection of E. Wallace Street and Matchett Road, each in the City of Belle Isle, Orange County, Florida, 32809 (the Project); (b) funding necessary reserves and capitalized interest related to the Bonds, if deemed necessary or desirable; and (c) paying certain costs of issuance associated with the Bonds.  The Project will continue to be owned by the Borrower and will continue to be operated as a public charter school by the Borrower (or an entity or entities affiliated with or designated thereby pursuant to one or more qualified use or management agreements).  The Bonds shall be payable solely from the revenues derived by the Issuer from a loan agreement, mortgage and security agreement and other financing documents entered into by and between the Issuer and the Borrower prior to or contemporaneously with the issuance of the Bonds. Such Bonds and the interest thereon shall not constitute an indebtedness or pledge of the general credit or taxing power, if any, of the Issuer, Brevard County, Charlotte County, Lee County, Osceola County, Sarasota County, St. Johns County, the State of Florida, or any political subdivision or agency thereof (including Orange County and the School District of Orange County). The Issuer has no taxing power.  Issuance of the Bonds shall be subject to several conditions including satisfactory documentation, the approval by bond counsel as to the tax-exempt status of the interest on all or a portion of the Bonds and receipt of necessary approvals for the financing. The aforementioned hearing shall be a public hearing and all persons in attendance will be given an opportunity to be heard and to express their views on the proposed issuance of the Bonds and the location and nature of the Project by accessing the telephone conference as indicated above. Written comments may also be submitted prior to the hearing to the Florida Local Government Finance Commission c/o Nabors Giblin &amp; Nickerson, P.A. at 2502 N. Rocky Point Drive, Suite 1060, Tampa, Florida 33607, directed to Issuers Counsel or via email sent to the following email address: rharb@ngn-tampa.com. Comments made at the hearing are for the consideration of the party(ies) providing an approval of the Bonds but will not bind the Issuer or such party(ies) as to any action it may take.  ALL PERSONS FOR OR AGAINST SAID APPROVAL CAN BE HEARD AT SAID TIME AND PLACE. IF A PERSON DECIDES TO APPEAL ANY DECISION MADE BY THE ISSUER WITH RESPECT TO SUCH HEARING OR MEETING, (S)HE WILL NEED TO ENSURE THAT A VERBATIM RECORD OF SUCH HEARING OR MEETING IS MADE (AT THEIR SOLE COST AND EXPENSE), WHICH RECORD INCLUDES THE TESTIMONY AND EVIDENCE UPON WHICH THE APPEAL IS BASED.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is requested to advise the Issuer at least twenty-four (24) hours prior to the meeting by contacting counsel to the Issuer at (813) 281-2222 or via email sent to the following email address: rharb@ngn-tampa.com.   By order of the Florida Local Government Finance Commission.  FLORIDA LOCAL GOVERNMENT FINANCE COMMISSION  /s/ Nicole Jovanovski Chair   12/22/2025 7908878</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431363</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431361</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF INTENT TO USE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTING NON-AD  VALOREM ASSESSMENTS   The City Commission (the City Commission) of the City of Longwoo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF INTENT TO USE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTING NON-AD  VALOREM ASSESSMENTS   The City Commission (the City Commission) of the City of Longwood (the City) hereby provides notice, pursuant to Section 197.3632(3)(a), Florida Statutes, of its intent to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments to be levied over a number of years within certain areas of the incorporated area of the City. The potential special assessment areas could include areas created to fund the cost of providing: (i) road paving improvements and ancillary drainage facilities; (ii) certain neighborhood improvements (e.g. walls, signage, irrigation, landscaping, etc.); (iii) residential and non-residential improvements near a potential light rail station for the purpose of promoting economic redevelopment; (iv) certain qualifying renewable energy, energy efficiency and conservation and wind resistance improvements; (v) water and/or wastewater services and facilities improvements; (vi) fire station improvements and/or operational and maintenance cost of providing fire services; and (vii) residential solid waste collection services. Each assessment area is to be located in a separate, to be established, assessment area which may be located within the incorporated area of the City for the Fiscal Year beginning on October 1, 2026 and thereafter.  The City will consider the adoption of a resolution electing to use the uniform method of collecting such assessments authorized by Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes, at a public hearing to be held on Monday, January 19th, 2026 at 6:00 P.M., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at City Hall, 175 West Warren Avenue, Longwood, Florida. Such resolution will state the need for the levy and will contain a legal description of the boundaries of the real property subject to the levy. Copies of the proposed form of resolution, which contains the legal description of the real property subject to the levy, may be obtained from Citys assessment coordinator at (407) 260-3475.  All affected real property owners have a right to appear at the hearing and to file written objections with the City Clerk any time prior to the public hearing. If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at the hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be made. In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing a special accommodation or an interpreter to participate in this proceeding should contact the ADA Coordinator at (407) 260-3466 at least seven days prior to the date of the hearing.  If you have any questions, please contact the Citys assessment coordinator at (407) 260-3475. Dated this 10 th day of December 2025. Liane Cartagena, City Clerk CITY OF LONGWOOD, FLORIDA12/22/25 12/29/25 1/05/25 1/12/2025 7907463</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431361</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430568</link>
      <description>Notice at 1871 Staunton Avenue; generally located on the north side of Staunton Avenue

Location: 1871 Staunton Avenue; generally located on the north side of Staunton Avenue

--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct public hearings on January 13, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as these matters may be heard, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the appeal.  Applicant: Zoltan Kecskes, Jr. Appellant: Frank Diefenderfer Case: Planning and Zoning Commission RZ-25-09-002; October 16, 2025 Consideration: Appeal of the recommendation of the Planning and Zoning Commission on a request by applicant to rezone from R-1A (Single-Family Dwelling District) to R-1 Restricted (Single-Family Dwelling District) to split the lot and develop two detached single-family homes on minimum 50 foot wide lots Location:	District 5; property located at 1871 Staunton Avenue; generally located on the north side of Staunton Avenue, east of Ohio Street, west of Clay Street, north of W. Fairbanks Avenue; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  AND  Applicant: Charles Zoebelein Appellant: Frank Diefenderfer Case: Planning and Zoning Commission RZ-25-10-011; October 16, 2025 Consideration: Appeal of the recommendation of the Planning and Zoning Commission on a request by applicant to rezone from R-1A (Single-Family Dwelling District) to R-1 Restricted (Single-Family Dwelling District) to split the lot and develop two detached single-family homes on minimum 50 foot wide lots Location: District 5; property located at 1860 Staunton Avenue; generally located on the south side of Staunton Avenue, east of Ohio Street, west of Clay Street, north of W. Fairbanks Avenue; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  You may obtain a copy of the legal property descriptions by calling the Orange County Planning Division, 407-836-5600; or pick one up at 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Second Floor; Orlando Florida.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THESE NOTICES, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY PLANNING DIVISION, 407-836-5600, Email: planning@ocfl.net   PARA MS INFORMACIN, REFERENTE A ESTE AVISO PARA UNA AUDENCIA PUBLICA SOBRE UNA PROPIEDAD EN SU AREA/VECINDAD, FAVOR COMUNICARSE CON LA DIVISIN DE PLANIFICACION, AL NUMERO, 407-836-8181  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7909402 12/21/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430568</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430567</link>
      <description>ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct public hearings on January 13, 2026, at 2 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct public hearings on January 13, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the following requests by:  Applicant: Constance Silver, PE, Tri3 Civil Engineering Design Studio, Inc., Kensington Church  Village H Planned Development (PD), Case # CDR-25-06-144 Consideration: A request to remove the previously approved waiver and conditions of approval allowing for a temporary athletic field with grass parking; to decrease the square footage (sf) of pre-school from 9,970 sf to 8,132 sf. (a decrease of 1,838 sf.); to increase the square footage of church uses from 17,296 sf to 29,042 sf. (an increase of 11,746 sf.); and to reduce the number of full-access connections to Old YMCA Road from two (2) to one (1); pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 30 Location: District 1; property generally located South of Old YMCA Road / West of Lake Hickory Nut Drive; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  AND  Applicant: Brandon Sansaricq, P.E., Kimley-Horn &amp; Associates, Redditt Property Planned Development (PD), Case # CDR-24-02-034 Consideration: A request to increase the development program from 110,647 square feet of industrial uses to 346,300 square feet and to allow for the development of 316,000 square feet of light industrial uses on Tract 2; pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 30 Location: District 4; property generally located East of Innovation Way / South of Alafaya Trail; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  You may obtain a copy of the legal property descriptions by calling Orange County Planning Division 407-836-5600; or pick one up at 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Second Floor; Orlando, Florida.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THESE NOTICES, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY PLANNING DIVISION, 407-836-5600, Email: planning@ocfl.net  PARA MS INFORMACIN REFERENTE A ESTA VISTA PBLICA, FAVOR DE COMUNICARSE CON LA DIVISIN DE PLANIFICACIN, (PLANNING DIVISION) AL NMERO, 407-836-8181.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7909397 12/21/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430567</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430566</link>
      <description>Notice at 11486 Corporate Boulevard; South of Corporate Boulevard/ West of Quadrangle Boulevard / North of University Boulevard / East of Rouse Road; Orange County

Location: 11486 Corporate Boulevard; South of Corporate Boulevard/ West of Quadrangle Boulevard / North of University Boulevard / East of Rouse Road; Orange County

--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTY  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct public hearings on January 13, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the following requests by:  Applicant: Carlos Perero, Kimley-Horn and Associates, Southchase Planned Development (PD) Case # CDR-25-06-146 Consideration: A PD substantial change to add a helipad / vertiport use to Parcel 44. The proposed helipad would be an ancillary use to an AdventHealth stand-alone Emergency Room, for which a development plan (DP) (DP-24-03-083) has already been approved; pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 38, Article VIII, Division 1, Section 38-1207 Location:	District 4; property generally located South of W. Wetherbee Road / East of Floridas Turnpike / West of S. Orange Avenue / North of State Road 417; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  AND  Applicant: Christopher Leppert, Kimley-Horn and Associates, Inc., The Quadrangle Planned Development (PD), Case # CDR-25-05-095 Consideration: A PD substantial change to split PD Tract 12 into Tracts 12A and 12 B. The request is to assign the existing 103,000 sf of office uses to Tract 12A, and to use the approved trip equivalency matrix to convert 147,808 sf of office uses to 900 student housing bedrooms to be assigned to Tract 12B. The following waivers from Orange County Code are being requested: 1. A waiver from Orange County Code 38-1259(3) is requested to allow nine hundred (900) student housing beds, in lieu of seven hundred and fifty (750) student housing beds for tract 12B only. 2. A waiver from Orange County Code 38-1476(a) is requested to allow 0.90 parking spaces per bedroom, in lieu of one (1) space per bedroom for tract 12B only. 3. A waiver from Orange County Code 38-1254(d)(2) is requested to allow a building height up to eighty-five (85) feet, in lieu of forty (40) feet for tract 12B only; pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 38, Article VIII, Division 1, Section 38-1207. Location: District 5; property located at 11486 Corporate Boulevard; South of Corporate Boulevard/ West of Quadrangle Boulevard / North of University Boulevard / East of Rouse Road; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  AND  Applicant: Jennifer Stickler, Kimley-Horn &amp; Associates, Inc., West Orange Plaza Planned Development (PD), Case # CDR-25-07-186 Consideration: A PD substantial change to add the existing Master Sign Plan (MSP) from the PSP to the LUP and update the MSP for additional signage proposed for Parcel A. The applicant is also requesting the following two (2) waivers from Orange County Code: 1. A waiver from Orange County Code Section 31.5-15(a)(2) within Parcel A to allow a maximum copy area of 350 sf in lieu of a maximum allowable copy area of 138 sf. 2. A waiver from Orange County Code Section 31.5-67(e) is requested within Parcel A to allow separation of 58 between signs in lieu of 100 between signs; pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 38, Article VIII, Division 1, Section 38-1207. Location: District 6; property generally located South of W. Colonial Drive / East of Dorscher Road; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Planning Division)  You may obtain a copy of the legal property descriptions by calling Orange County Planning Division 407-836-5600; or pick one up at 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Second Floor; Orlando, Florida.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THESE NOTICES, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY PLANNING DIVISION, 407-836-5600, Email: planning@ocfl.net  PARA MS INFORMACIN REFERENTE A ESTA VISTA PBLICA, FAVOR DE COMUNICARSE CON LA DIVISIN DE PLANIFICACIN (PLANNING DIVISION) AL NMERO 407-836-8181.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7909386 12/21/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430566</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430559</link>
      <description>CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN by the City of Alt...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN by the City of Altamonte Springs, Florida, that the City Commission will hold a public hearing in the City Hall of Altamonte Springs, 225 Newburyport Avenue, Altamonte Springs, Florida, on January 6, 2026 at 7:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, to consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 1840-26 entitled:  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE ALTAMONTE SPRINGS CODE OF ORDINANCES BY AMENDING SECTION 2-5, CRIMINAL HISTORY SCREENING REQUIREMENTS FOR EMPLOYMENT, OF ARTICLE 1 , EMPLOYMENT PREREQUISITES, OF CHAPTER 2, ADMINISTRATION, TO REVISE REQUIREMENTS FOR STATE AND FEDERAL CRIMINAL HISTORY SCREENING FOR SPECIFIED POSITIONS OF EMPLOYMENT AND FOR OUTSIDE CONTRACTORS OR VENDORS; PROVIDING A BUSINESS IMPACT ESTIMATE; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION; PROVIDING FOR SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. The hearing on such ordinance may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the City Commission. If anyone decides to appeal any decision on this ordinance, the person will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings, which includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, is made. The City of Altamonte Springs does not provide this verbatim record.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings must contact the City Clerk Department ADA Coordinator 72 hours in advance of the meeting at 407-571-8122 (VOICE), 711 (TTY) or email CityClerk@Altamonte.org.  The proposed ordinance can be obtained from the office of the City Clerk, 202 Newburyport Avenue, Altamonte Springs, Florida, and may be inspected by the public during office hours (7:30 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. M-F, excluding holidays).  Dated December 21, 2025 Angela Apperson, City Clerk City of Altamonte Springs, Florida 7908478 12/21/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430559</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430558</link>
      <description>CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE   TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN:  NOTICE IS HEREBY...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE   TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN:  NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN by the City of Altamonte Springs, Florida, that the City Commission will hold a public hearing in the City Hall of Altamonte Springs, 225 Newburyport Avenue, Altamonte Springs, Florida, on January 6, 2026 at 7:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, to consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 1838-26 entitled:  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF ALTAMONTE SPRINGS, FLORIDA, MODIFYING CITY PLAN 2030, THE ALTAMONTE SPRINGS COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, BY UPDATING THE CAPITAL IMPROVEMENT PROGRAM (CIP) TO UPDATE TABLE 8.1, 2024-2025 FIVE (5) YEAR CAPITAL IMPROVEMENT PROGRAM, TO 2025-2026 FIVE (5) YEAR CAPITAL IMPROVEMENT PROGRAM TO ADJUST THE PLANNING HORIZON TO COVER FISCAL YEARS 2026 THROUGH 2030 RATHER THAN 2025 THROUGH 2029; BY UPDATING THE TIMING AND FUNDING OF THE CAPITAL PROJECTS SET FORTH IN THE TABLE; AND BY AUTHORIZING THE UPDATED TABLE 8.1 TO BE PUBLISHED IN CHAPTER 8, CAPITAL IMPROVEMENT ELEMENT OF CITY PLAN 2030; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, PROVIDING FOR BUSINESS IMPACT ESTIMATE EXEMPTION, AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. The hearing on such ordinance may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the City Commission. If anyone decides to appeal any decision on this ordinance, the person will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings, which includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, is made. The City of Altamonte Springs does not provide this verbatim record.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings must contact the City Clerk Department ADA Coordinator 72 hours in advance of the meeting at 407-571-8122 (VOICE), 711 (TTY) or email CityClerk@Altamonte.org.  The proposed ordinance can be obtained from the office of the City Clerk, 202 Newburyport Avenue, Altamonte Springs, Florida, and may be inspected by the public during office hours (7:30 a.m. to 4:30 p.m. M-F, excluding holidays).  Dated December 21, 2025 Angela Apperson, City Clerk City of Altamonte Springs, Florida 7908433 12/21/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430558</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11429977</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING   You are hereby notified that the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida, which also sits as the...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING   You are hereby notified that the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida, which also sits as the Local Planning Agency and the Land Development Regulation Commission will hold a public hearing. The hearing will be held at 6:00 P.M., Thursday, January 15, 2026, or as soon thereafter as is reasonably possible in the Maitland City Hall Council Chambers, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida 32751.  The purpose of the hearing is to take public comment, both written and oral, concerning a petition filed by the City of Maitland, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida, to amend the Land Development Code, Article 5  Development Standards to add code of ordinances Section 5.16, establishing a process for the review of Reasonable Accommodation Requests for Certified Recovery Residences pursuant to Florida Statutes Section 397.487.  A complete copy of the proposed amendment to the Land Development Code may be inspected by any interested person Monday-Thursday, 7:00 A.M. - 6:00 P.M., in the Community Development Department, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida, 32751. The public is invited to attend the public hearing and may submit written comments at or before the public hearing or attend the public hearing to be heard by the Planning and Zoning Commission of the City of Maitland, Florida. Questions concerning the notice of public hearing may be directed to the Community Development Department at (407) 539-6212.  Any person who desires to appeal any decision made at this meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings and, for this purpose, may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office (407) 539-6219 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  Sara Blanchard Chief Planner City of Maitland   12/15/2025 7908267</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11429977</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428472</link>
      <description>REVISED   NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold public hearings on the following:ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
REVISED   NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold public hearings on the following:ORDINANCE NO. 36-2025  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF DELTONA, FLORIDA, AMENDING SECTION 110-814, ADDITIONAL REGULATIONS FOR CERTAIN PERMITTED PRINCIPAL USES AND STRUCTURES, OF CHAPTER 110, ZONING, AND CHAPTER 74, ADMINISTRATION, OF THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE UPDATING PROCEDURES AND REGULATIONS RELATED TO CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES IN COMPLIANCE WITH FLORIDA STATUTES; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Public hearings will be held as follows:  Planning and Zoning Board  December 17, 2025, at 6:00 p.m.  City Commission (First Reading)  January 20, 2026, at 6:30 p.m.  City Commission (Adoption Hearing  February 2, 2026, at 6:30 p.m.  at City Hall, 2345 Providence Boulevard, Deltona, Florida.  All interested parties are invited to provide their comments, views and objections to the Deltona Planning and Zoning Board and/or City Commission as part of the Public Hearing. The failure of a person to appear during said public hearing and to object either in person or in writing to said case may severely restrict the ability of such a person to contest it at a later date.  The associated paperwork may be inspected by the public at the Deltona City Hall, 2345 Providence Blvd., Deltona, Florida, Monday  Friday, 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m.  For further information, contact the City Clerks Office at (386) 878-8500.  The date, time and place of any continuance of the above scheduled public hearing will be announced at said public hearing and no further notice regarding said continuance is required to be published.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Deltona City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. The City does not provide this verbatim record.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact City Clerk Joyce Raftery 48 hours in advance of the meeting date and time at (386) 878-8500.  All parties in interest and persons for or against aforementioned items will be given an opportunity to be heard at said Public Hearing.  Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona  If you should have any questions regarding the above ad, please contact my office at (386) 878-8500. Thank you.  Sincerely,  /s/ Joyce Raftery Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona   12/18/2025 7906971</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428472</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428249</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF
 BOARD WORKSHOP
Pursuant to Florida Statutes, the School Board of Osceola County, Florida, hereby proposes to hold a Board Workshop on th...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF
 BOARD WORKSHOP
Pursuant to Florida Statutes, the School Board of Osceola County, Florida, hereby proposes to hold a Board Workshop on the proposed revisions to the School Board Rules, including the Student Progression Plan and the Code of Student Conduct . The workshop will be held on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 5:30 PM in the School District of Osceola County Administrative Center Board Room, 817 Bill Beck Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida.


NOTICE OF
 PUBLIC HEARING
Pursuant to Florida Statutes, the School Board of Osceola County, Florida, hereby proposes to hold a Public Hearing on the proposed revisions to the School Board Rules, including the Student Progression Plan and the Code of Student Conduct . The public hearing will be held on Tuesday, March 10, 2026, at 5:30 PM in the School District of Osceola County Administrative Center Board Room, 817 Bill Beck Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida.


Interested persons may review related School Board meeting agendas and any proposals at:
https://go.boarddocs.com/fl/osceola/Board.nsf/Public [https://go.boarddocs.com/fl/osceola/Board.nsf/Public]
An Equal Opportunity Agency
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428249</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428234</link>
      <description>Notice at 1 Courthouse Square

Location: 1 Courthouse Square

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING


NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Board of County Commissioners of Osceola County, Florida will at 1:30 P.M. on Monday, January 5, 2026, or as soon thereafter as practical, and in the Commission Chambers at 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 4100, Kissimmee, Florida, consider and act on the following proposed County Agreement. Access to the meeting is also being provided telephonically. Please call (407) 205-0551 Code 301797 to listen to the meeting.


The Development Agreement, with KB Home Orlando LLC (Developer) for the design, permitting, right-of-way dedication, and construction of approximately 0.25-miles of Framework Road Improvements (Westside Boulevard) generally located south of W Irlo Bronson Memorial Highway, north of Bella Citta Boulevard, west of S Goodman Road, and east of US Highway 27. The total cost of the Framework Road Improvements including right of way is $761,474.43, with the Jurisdiction responsible for $755,568.66 ($478,193.78 for construction, $229,591.80 for roadway right of way, and $47,783.08 for pond right of way). The purpose of the public meeting is to consider whether it is in the publics best interest to accept the proposal and enter into an agreement pursuant thereto.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at such meeting, a record of the proceeding will be needed, and for such purposes, it may be needed to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.


Copies of the proposed Ordinance may be obtained from the Recording Secretary to the Board of County Commissioners, located at 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 4400, Kissimmee, Florida.
Individuals with disabilities requiring accommodations (i.e., sign language interpreter or materials in accessible format) in order to participate in meetings, please contact the Countys ADA Coordinator, (407) 742-1200 (TTY Users Dial: 711 for the Florida Relay System) or ADA.Coordinator@osceola.org, at least four (4) business days prior to the meeting.


Ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades (ADA) y Asistencia del Ttulo VILa Junta de Comisionados del Condado Osceola garantiza un acceso significativo a los programas, servicios y actividades del Condado para cumplir con los Derechos Civiles Ttulo VI y Ttulo II de la Ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades. Las personas con discapacidades que requieran adaptaciones (es decir, intrprete de lenguaje de seas o materiales en formato accesible) o las personas con dominio limitado del ingls que requieran intrpretes de idiomas para participar en reuniones patrocinadas por el condado, comunquese con el coordinador de ADA/Ttulo VI del condado al (407) 742-1200 (Usuarios de TTY marcar: 711 para el Sistema de retransmisin de Florida) o ADA.Coordinator@osceola.org, al menos cuatro (4) das antes de la reunin o evento.
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428234</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428230</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2024-50


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2024-50 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, READOPTING THE ORDINANCE ADOPTING A LARGE SCALE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN AMENDMENT INCORPORATING COMMENTS SUBMITTED BY THE STATE OF FLORIDA AFTER THE INITIAL ADOPTION OF THE ORDINANCE AND PURSUANT TO SECTION 163.3184 FLORIDA STATUTES AMENDING THE FUTURE LAND USE ELEMENT OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, PROJECT # CPA24-00007; PROVIDING FOR AMENDING THE OFFICIAL FUTURE LAND USE TEXT AND MAP OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, APPLICABILITY AND EFFECT, SEVERABILITY, CONFLICT, CODIFICATION, COPIES ON FILE, SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428230</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428228</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO. 2026-003R


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Resolution No. 2026-003R entitled:


A RESOLUTION OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, GRANTING A SITE VARIANCE (#VAR25-00001) TO REDUCE REQUIRED OPEN SPACE FROM APPROXIMATELY +/- .048 ACRES TO +/- .017 ACRES ON THE PREVIOUSLY APPROVED SITE DEVELOPMENT PLAN IN THE HIGHWAY BUSINESS HB ZONING DISTRICT ON THE +/- 5.94 ACRES OF LAND KNOWN AS NARCOOSSEE COMMONS SOUTH (# 18-75.04); ALLOWING THE OPEN COURTYARD BETWEEN UNITS 1386 AND 1388 TO ACT AS AN OUTDOOR PLAY SPACE FOR ADVENTURE WORLD KIDS A CHILD CARE CENTER, AS DESCRIBED IN THE BODY OF THIS RESOLUTION.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this RESOLUTION is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed RESOLUTION at the Public Hearing thereon. This RESOLUTION in its entirety can be reviewed at the City Clerk's office between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 2:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428228</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428190</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2025-78


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the enactment of Ordinance No. 2025-78 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, AMENDING DIVISION 27 -ENTERTAINMENT DISTRICT, SECTION 3.13.3, C. 2 - OUTSIDE DRINKING LIMIT, G  HOURS FOR MUSIC AND ENTERTAINMENT, AND H  GAMES SPORTING EVENTS, AND ENTERTAINMENT AND REPEALING SECTIONS 3.13.3 C5- PERMIT REQUIRED THROUGH F  FIRE PROTECTION, PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the City Clerk's office between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 2:00 p.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Ivy Llauro, MMC
City Clerk
City of St. Cloud
1300 9th Street
St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428190</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/25/11426525.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of public hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of public hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170.07, Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of public hearing to consider adoption of assessment roll pursuant to Section 197.3632(4)(b), Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of regular meeting of the South Lake Toho Community Development District
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426525</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11426525.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/24/11426524.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of public hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of public hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170.07, Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of public hearing to consider adoption of assessment roll pursuant to Section 197.3632(4)(b), Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of regular meeting of the South Lake Toho Community Development District
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426524</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11426524.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11426526</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF BOARD MEETING AND NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE CASCADES AT  GROVELAND COMMUNITY DEVE...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF BOARD MEETING AND NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE CASCADES AT  GROVELAND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Cascades at Groveland Community Development District (District) will conduct a regular Board meeting and a public hearing to consider adoption of the proposed Amended and Restate Rules of Procedure on January 14, 2026, at 2:00 p.m. at the Magnolia House Sports Pavilion, 100 Falling Acorn Ave., Groveland, Florida 34736.  In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, Rule No. 2026-01. The purpose and effect of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. Prior notice of rule development was published in the Orlando Sentinel on Wednesday, December 10, 2025.  The Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure will address topics such as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings and competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings. A detailed summary of the proposed rules, including the text of the proposed rules, the economic impact statement, and the statement of estimated regulatory costs required by Section 120.541, Florida Statutes, is available for public inspection at the District Managers Office and on the Districts website.  Specific legal authority for the adoption of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes (2025). The specific laws implemented in the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 189.053, 189.069(2)(a)(15), 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011(3), 190.011(5), 190.011(15), 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0992, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes (2025).  A copy of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, the full text of the proposed rules, any material proposed to be incorporated by reference, the statement of estimated regulatory costs if one has been prepared pursuant to Section 120.541, Florida Statutes, and any other materials required by Section 120.54, Florida Statutes, may be obtained by contacting David McInnes at the District Managers Office by mail at Vesta District Services, 250 International Parkway, Suite 208, Lake Mary, Florida 32746, by telephone at (321) 263-0132, or by email at dmcinnes@vestapropertyservices.com. These materials are also available for public inspection at the District Managers Office during regular business hours and on the Districts website at https://www.cascadesatgrovelandcdd.org.  Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes, must do so in writing within twentyone (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.  This public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at a public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least three (3) business days prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1800-955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  District Manager Cascades at Groveland Community Development District   12/17/2025 7906259</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426526</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424659</link>
      <description>Greater Orlando Aviation Authority Notice of Workshop and Board Meetings for 2026Notice is hereby given by the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority t...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Greater Orlando Aviation Authority Notice of Workshop and Board Meetings for 2026Notice is hereby given by the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority that board meetings of the Aviation Authority Board have been set for the following dates, commencing at 2:00 p.m. in the Carl T. Langford Board Room of the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority offices located in the Orlando International Airport, main terminal, One Jeff Fuqua Boulevard, Orlando, Florida.  The purpose of these meetings will be to take any action that could be taken at a workshop or regular meeting of the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority. The public is invited to attend these meetings.  JAN 21   FEB 18   MAR 18   APR 15 MAY 20  JUN 17   JUL 15AUG 19 SEP 16   OCT 21   NOV 18   DEC 16  The agenda for each meeting is available on www.flymco.com the Monday before each meeting after 10 a.m.  PLEASE NOTE: Any person who desires to appeal any decision made at this meeting will need a record of the proceedings and, for that purpose, may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Please contact the Senior Manager of Board Services at (407) 825-2032 or angelica.matos@goaa.org for additional information.   12/16, 12/23/2025 7899631</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424659</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424094</link>
      <description>CITY OF KISSIMMEE NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TEXT AMENDMENT   The City of Kissimmee proposes to adopt the following ordinance that would update Chapt...

Meeting: Tuesday, January 6, 2026 at 6:00 p.m.

--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF KISSIMMEE NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TEXT AMENDMENT   The City of Kissimmee proposes to adopt the following ordinance that would update Chapter 14-11, Signs and Chapter 14-2, Definitions in the Land Development Code as described below. A public hearing to consider the proposed ordinance will be held by the City of Kissimmee City Commission for Second and Final Reading on Tuesday, January 6, 2026 at 6:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida.  Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person.  Any questions regarding this public hearing may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or at planning@kissimmee.gov.  PROPOSED ORDINANCE #25-21: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING THE CODE OF THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA CODE OF ORDINANCES TITLES; REORGANIZING AND UPDATING CHAPTER 14-11 SIGNS; UPDATING SIGNAGE DEFINITIONS IN CHAPTER 14-2; REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE  In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made.  In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26)   12/15/2025 7908001</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424094</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424090</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF CANCELLATION OF MEETING OF THE BOARD OF COMMISSIONERS OF LAKE APOPKA NATURAL GAS DISTRICT TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN:   The December 22, 2025...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF CANCELLATION OF MEETING OF THE BOARD OF COMMISSIONERS OF LAKE APOPKA NATURAL GAS DISTRICT TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN:   The December 22, 2025, meeting of the Lake Apopka Natural Gas District Board of Commissioners has been cancelled in order to allow for full observance of the Christmas Holidays. The next regular meeting of the Board of Commissioners is scheduled for Monday, January 26, 2026.  Thank you, Lake Apopka Natural Gas District   12/10/2025 7906636</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424090</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424142</link>
      <description>Notice of Adoption
NOTICE OF ADOPTION
PETITION TO VACATE # 25-08-022
WHEREAS, pursuant to procedures adopted by the Board of County Commissioners, ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Adoption
NOTICE OF ADOPTION
PETITION TO VACATE # 25-08-022
WHEREAS, pursuant to procedures adopted by the Board of County Commissioners, a petition was filed with the Board to vacate that certain 60-foot-wide unopened and unimproved right-of-way known as Palm Avenue that lies between three residential lots located within the Winter Garden Manor Subdivision containing approximately 0.258 acres in Orange County, Florida (the legal property description is on file in the office of the Comptroller Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners).
WHEREAS, notice of a public hearing before the Board of County Commissioners on December 2, 2025, was published in the Orlando Sentinel, a newspaper of general circulation in Orange County, Florida, one time at least two weeks prior to the date for the hearing; and
WHEREAS, the Board finds that the vacating of that certain 60-foot-wide unopened and unimproved right-of-way known as Palm Avenue that lies between three residential lots located within the Winter Garden Manor Subdivision containing approximately 0.258 acres will not operate to the detriment of Orange County or the public.
THEREFORE, BE IT RESOLVED BY THE BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF ORANGE COUNTY: The county road, right-of-way, easement, or park described above is vacated as of this date and Orange County renounces any rights in it.
RESOLVED THIS SECOND DAY OF DECEMBER 2025.
Phil Diamond, County Comptroller
As Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners
Orange County, Florida
December 12, 2025
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424142</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/91/11422391.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 174 W

Meeting: Monday, December 15, 2025 at 6:00 P.M.
Location: 174 W

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/12/2025 NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN BY THE CITY OF LONGWOOD, FLORIDA, that the City Commission will conduct a second reading and public hearing on Ordinance No. 25-2275 on Monday, December 15, 2025 at 6:00 P.M., or as soon thereafter as possible in the Longwood City Commission Chambers, 175 West Warren Avenue, Longwood, Florida. The purpose of the public hearing is to receive public comment and to consider the proposed amendments. The proposed amendments affect the use of land within the municipal limits of the City of Longwood.  ORDINANCE NO. 25-2275  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF LONGWOOD, FLORIDA, AMENDING PART III, LONGWOOD DEVELOPMENT CODE, ARTICLE IX, TO CREATE SECTION 9.4.0, TO ESTABLISH REGULATIONS AND PROCEDURES FOR CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES, INCLUDING A PROCESS FOR REQUESTING REASONABLE ACCOMMODATION AS REQUIRED BY CHAPTER 2025-182, LAWS OF FLORIDA; PROVIDING FOR DEFINITIONS; PROVIDING FOR A REASONABLE ACCOMMODATION PROCESS IN ACCORDANCE WITH FEDERAL AND STATE LAW; PROVIDING FOR APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS, REVIEW PROCEDURES, AND DEADLINES; PROVIDING FOR REVOCATION AND REINSTATEMENT; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION; AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  At this meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the request. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is complete. A copy of the proposed Longwood Development Code Amendment is available for review in the Community Development Department between 8:30 A.M. to 4:00 P.M. during regular work days. The office is located at 174 W. Church Avenue, Longwood, Florida, or you may call the office at 407-260-3462. NOTICE: All persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at the meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record to include the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based (per Sec. 286.0105, Florida Statutes). Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these meetings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator at 407-260-3466 at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting. Publish: Friday, December 12, 2025  CITY OF LONGWOOD, FL CITY COMMISSION NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGS  LONGWOOD DEVELOPMENT CODE AMENDMENTS  7907237</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422391</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11422391.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420498</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Corporate Boulevard

Location: 3501 Corporate Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
HARMONY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF AUDITOR SELECTION COMMITTEE MEETING AND REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETING


The Board of Supervisors of the Harmony Community Development District will hold an Audit Selection Committee meeting and regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors on December 18, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. at the Su Mesa Caf at 7250 Harmony Sq Dr S, Harmony, FL 34773. The regular meeting will take place immediately following the adjournment of the Auditor Selection Committee meeting where the Board may consider any other business that may properly come before it. The Audit Selection Committee will review, discuss and recommend an auditor to provide audit services to the District for Fiscal Year 2025 . A copy of the agendas may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC., located at 3501 Corporate Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, (407) 723-5900, during normal business hours.


The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meetings. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in these meetings is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board or the Committee with respect to any matter considered at the meetings is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Lynne Mullins
District
December 11, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420498</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420463</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING 
AND AUDIT COMMITTEE MEETING


The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Sou...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING 
AND AUDIT COMMITTEE MEETING


The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) and the Auditor Selection Committee (Audit Committee) of the District will hold a regular meeting and audit committee meeting on January 8, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room - HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741. The Audit Committee will review, discuss and evaluate any proposals the District receives pursuant to the solicitation for auditing services. A regular Board meeting of the District will also be held at that time where the Board may consider any other business that may properly come before it.


A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, c/o Wrathell, Hunt and Associates, LLC at 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, Ph: (877) 276-0889 (District Managers Office) during normal business hours. The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law for community development districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. There may be an occasion where one or more supervisors will participate by telephone.


Any person requiring special accommodations in order to access and participate in the meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meetings is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
December 11, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420463</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/90/11419690.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170.07, Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of Public Hearing to consider adoption of assessment roll pursuant to Section 197.3632(4)(b), Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of regular meeting of the South Lake Toho Community Development District
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11419690</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11419690.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/89/11419689.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing to consider imposition of special assessments pursuant to Section 170.07, Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of Public Hearing to consider adoption of assessment roll pursuant to Section 197.3632(4)(b), Florida Statutes, by the South Lake Toho Community Development District
Notice of regular meeting of the South Lake Toho Community Development District
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11419689</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11419689.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/88/11419688.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2025-81
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, FL
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11419688</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11419688.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11419592</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED RULES ADOPTION/REPEAL/AMENDMENT   The Valencia College District Board of Trustees will consider adoption and repeal of the propo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED RULES ADOPTION/REPEAL/AMENDMENT   The Valencia College District Board of Trustees will consider adoption and repeal of the proposed rule listed below, for which the notices of rule development were published in the September 19, 2025, December 8, 2025, October 22, 2025, and October 21, 2025, editions of the Orlando Sentinel, respectively, at a public meeting to be held as follows:  DATE AND TIME: Thursday, February 5, 2026 9:30am PLACE: Valencia College West Campus  Building 8, Room 111 1800 S. Kirkman Rd. Orlando, FL 32811 ADOPTION RULE TITLE: College Policy 6Hx28: 3C-01.2 Faculty Workload College Policy 6Hx28: 4-04 Student Learning Outcomes and Course Outlines College Policy 6Hx28: 4-05 Course Syllabus College Policy 6Hx28: 4-09 Instructional Materials PURPOSE AND EFFECT: Amend the above referenced policies to comply with current laws and regulations, and improve institutional effectiveness. SPECIFIC AUTHORITY: 1001.64 FS LAW IMPLEMENTED: 1001.64 FS  THE PERSON TO BE CONTACTED REGARDING THE PROPOSED RULE IS: Dr. Kathleen Plinske, Secretary to the District Board of Trustees of Valencia College, Post Office Box 3028, Orlando, Florida, 32802.   12/10/2025 7906414</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11419592</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11418203</link>
      <description>CITY OF KISSIMMEE NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TEXT AMENDMENT   The City of Kissimmee proposes to adopt the following ordinance that would update Chapt...

Meeting: Tuesday, January 6, 2025 at 6:00 p.m.

--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF KISSIMMEE NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TEXT AMENDMENT   The City of Kissimmee proposes to adopt the following ordinance that would update Chapter 14-11, Signs and Chapter 14-2, Definitions in the Land Development Code as described below. A public hearing to consider the proposed ordinance will be held by the City of Kissimmee City Commission for the First Reading on Tuesday, December 16, 2025 and the Second and Final Reading on Tuesday, January 6, 2025 at 6:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida.  Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person.  Any questions regarding this public hearing may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or at planning@kissimmee.gov.  PROPOSED ORDINANCE #25-21: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING THE CODE OF THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA CODE OF ORDINANCES TITLES; REORGANIZING AND UPDATING CHAPTER 14-11 SIGNS; UPDATING SIGNAGE DEFINITIONS IN CHAPTER 14-2; REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE  In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made.  In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26)   12/09/2026 7905339</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11418203</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11418202</link>
      <description>GREENEWAY IMPROVEMENT DISTRICTNOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETINGNotice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Greeneway Improvement Dis...


--- Full Notice Text ---
GREENEWAY IMPROVEMENT DISTRICTNOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETINGNotice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Greeneway Improvement District (District) will hold a regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors on Tuesday, December 16, 2025, at 2:30 p.m. at 6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd, Ste 200, Orlando, FL  32827. A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, c/o PFM Group Consulting LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Phone: (407) 723-5900 (District Managers Office) during normal business hours or from the Districts website at https://www.greenewayid.org/.  The public meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida law. The public meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when staff or Board members may participate by speaker telephone.  Any person requiring special accommodations at the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jennifer Walden District Manager 7894202 12/9/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11418202</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11417556</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING  REUNION EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Reunion East Community Develo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING  REUNION EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Reunion East Community Development District will be held on Thursday, December 11, 2025, at 10:30 AM, or as shortly thereafter as reasonably possible, at the Heritage Crossing Community Center, 7715 Heritage Crossing Way, Reunion, FL 34747. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  A copy of the agenda for this meeting may be obtained by contacting Tricia Adams at the District Managers office at Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC, at 219 East Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801, by telephone at (407) 841-5524, by email at tadams@gmscfl.com , or by visiting the Districts website at https://reunioneastcdd.com/ . This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this meeting is asked to advise the District Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting by contacting the District Manager at (407) 841-5524. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Tricia Adams Governmental Management Services  Central Florida District Manager   12/08/2025 7905473</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11417556</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11417554</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING  REUNION WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Reunion West Community Develo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING  REUNION WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Reunion West Community Development District will be held on Thursday, December 11, 2025, at 10:30 AM, or as shortly thereafter as reasonably possible, at the Heritage Crossing Community Center, 7715 Heritage Crossing Way, Reunion, FL 34747. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  A copy of the agenda for this meeting may be obtained by contacting Tricia Adams at the District Managers office at Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC, at 219 East Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801, by telephone at (407) 841-5524, by email at tadams@gmscfl.com , or by visiting the Districts website at https://reunionwestcdd.com/ . This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this meeting is asked to advise the District Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting by contacting the District Manager at (407) 841-5524. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.   12/08/2025 7905449</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11417554</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/97/11416897.pdf</link>
      <description>12/07/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  NOTICE OF LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE AMENDMENT  CITY OF OVIEDO, FLORIDA  The City of Oviedo proposes to consider th...


--- Full Notice Text ---
12/07/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  NOTICE OF LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE AMENDMENT  CITY OF OVIEDO, FLORIDA  The City of Oviedo proposes to consider the following ordinance:  ORDINANCE NO. 1762  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF OVIEDO, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE OF THE CITY OF OVIEDO, SPECIFICALLY ARTICLE II ADMINISTRATION, ARTICLE III DEVELOPMENT AGREEMENTS, ORDERS, AND PERMITS, ARTICLE IV ZONING DISTRICTS AND REGULATIONS, ARTICLE V OTHER SPECIFIC USES AND STRUCTURES, ARTICLE VII NON-CONFORMING SITUATIONS, ARTICLE XI. STREETS AND SIDEWALKS, ARTICLE XII LANDSCAPING, TREE PLANTING, AND BUFFER REQUIREMENTS, ARTICLE XIII PARKING, ARTICLE XIV SIGNS, ARTICLE XV ENVIRONMENTAL PRESERVATION, ARTICLE XVII RECREATIONAL FACILITIES AND OPEN SPACE, ARTICLE XVIII BASIC DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATIONS; PROVIDING FOR LEGISLATIVE FINDINGS AND INTENT; CONFLICTS; SEVERABILITY; CODIFICATION AS WELL AS THE CORRECTION OF SCRIVENER'S ERRORS; AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE  LOCATION MAP  A public hearing will be held on Tuesday, December 16, 2025, before the City of Oviedo Local Planning Agency beginning at 6:30 PM. The public hearing will be held in the City of Oviedo City Council Chambers, 400 Alexandria Boulevard, Oviedo, Florida. All interested parties may appear at the public hearing and be heard. The ordinance and its supporting documents may be reviewed on or after Thursday, December 11, 2025, at the Development Services Department, City Hall Annex Building, 320 Alexandria Boulevard, weekdays from 8:00 AM to 5:00 PM, except holidays. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in this proceeding should contact the ADA Coordinator at (407) 971-5523, at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting. ADVICE TO THE PUBLIC: If any person decides to appeal a decision with respect to any matter considered at the above meeting or hearing, he/she will need a verbatim record of all proceedings including the testimony and evidence, which record is not provided by the City of Oviedo (F.S. 286.0105). For any further questions, comments, or concerns; please contact the Planning Division, at 407-971-5776. 7904601</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416897</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11416897.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416892</link>
      <description>notice   A Public Hearing will be held by the City of Orlando Board of Zoning Adjustment on December 16, 2025 @ 2:00 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   A Public Hearing will be held by the City of Orlando Board of Zoning Adjustment on December 16, 2025 @ 2:00 p.m., or shortly thereafter, in Orlando City Hall, Council Chambers, 2nd Floor of City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. This meeting will also be available for viewing at the following link: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/85198088494. The following variance requests will be considered: 1) 3219 Chelsea St.  (A) Variance to allow to allow dirt and mulch piles in the front yard; (B) Variance to allow an increased fence height; and, (C) Variance to allow a second shed to be within the front yard setback, where accessory structures are not allowed [case# VAR2025-10047]; 2) 13871 Briand Ave.  (A) Variance to allow a reduced street side yard setback for a pergola, and (B) Variance to allow a reduced street side yard setback for an attached screen room [case# VAR2025-10048]; and 3) 950 Bennett Rd.  Variance to allow a reduced distance separation between open storage (commercial vehicles) and office-zoned property [case# VAR2025-10049].  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerk, 407.246.2251, 24 hours in advance of the meeting. For a person desiring to appeal any decision with respect to any matter considered at this meeting, such person will need to ensure a verbatim record of the proceedings is made to include the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based.   12/07/2025 7903410</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416892</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416890</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF A REGULAR NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES MEETING Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Regular M...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF A REGULAR NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES MEETING Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Regular Meeting of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities will be held by the Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida, on Monday, December 15, 2025, at 3:00 p.m.* at 200 Canal Street, 3 rd FL  DeBerry Room. (*After Preliminary Public Hearings Nos. 1 &amp; 2)  Copies of the agenda will be posted on the doors of the first floor of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities office at 200 Canal Street and on the NSBUs website - www.nsbufl.com. A full agenda package will also be posted on the NSBUs website.  Pursuant to section 286.0105 of the Florida Statutes, if an individual decides to appeal any decision made by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities, with respect to any matter considered at a meeting, that individual will need a record of the proceedings and will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made.  The transcription of such a verbatim will be provided to an individual at a cost to be determined by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities in accordance with the full cost to reproduce such transcriptions and copies.  In accordance with the American with Disabilities Act, persons with disabilities needing a special accommodation to participate in these proceedings should contact the individual or agency sending the notice; if possible no later than five days prior to the proceeding at the address given on notice. 7903237 12-7-25</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416890</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416889</link>
      <description>Notice at 536 N

Location: 536 N

--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   A Public Hearing will be held by the Municipal Planning Board, City of Orlando, on TUESDAY, December 16, 2025 @ 9:00 a.m. or shortly thereafter, in City Council Chambers, 400 S. Orange Ave. This meeting will also be available for viewing at the following link: https://orlando-gov.zoom.us/j/95054325064. The following items will be considered: 1) 536 North Westmoreland Light Retail Use  Approximately 0.4 acres located at 536 N. Westmoreland Dr. A) Conditional Use Permit to allow a light retailing use in the I-G zoning district within the Parramore Heritage Overlay (Case #CUP2025-10016). 2) St. Phillip Catholic Church Parish Hall  Approximately 5.9 acres located at 15 W. Par St. A) Conditional Use Permit to allow Parish Hall expansion with additional overflow parking in recently added parcels (Case #CUP2025-10022). 3) Terrawatt EV Parking Lot  Approximately 2.1 acres located at 5500 Lee Vista Blvd. A) Conditional Use Permit for principal use parking with an electric vehicle charging station (Case #CUP2025-10023). 4) Storey Park Multi-Family  Approximately 12.0 acres located at 12165 Dowden Rd. A) Master Plan to allow a 306-unit multifamily development (Case #MPL2025-10037). B) PD Amendment to the existing Wewahootee PD to convert office entitlements to residential entitlements (Case #ZON2025-10009). 5) Starwood Meridian Parks Neighborhood 9A and Portion of 9C  Approximately 114.2 acres located at 13131 Wewahootee Rd. A) Master Plan for development with 159 single-family homes and 95 townhome units (Case #MPL2025-10055). 6) Caravan Hotel Addition  Approximately 7.3 acres located at 5905 S. Kirkman Rd. A) Master Plan Amendment to add a second 19-story hotel with restaurants and other ancillary uses. The request includes an intensity bonus (Case #MPL2025-10057).  Copies of the proposed amendments are available for public inspection Mon.-Fri. 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., in the Economic Development Dept., City Planning Division, 6th Floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave. Any interested parties may appear in City Council Chambers &amp; be heard regarding this matter. For instructions regarding participation/viewing in-person or viewing virtually, visit orlando.gov/mpb or contact cityplanning@orlando.gov or 407.246.2269 &amp; select Option 1. Persons wishing to appeal any decision made during the hearing will need a record of the proceedings &amp; may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including testimony &amp; evidence upon which the appeal is based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in this public hearing should contact the City Clerks Office @ 407.246.2251 at least 24 hours in advance of the hearing.   12/07/2025 7903203</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416889</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416344</link>
      <description>Notice at 307 E

Meeting: Tuesday, December 16, 2025 at 7:30 p.m.
Location: 307 E

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING (2 ND READING)   AMENDING DIVISION 2 OF ARTICLE VI, CODE ENFORCEMENT, OF CHAPTER 2, ADMINISTRATION, OF THE TOWNS CODE OF ORDINANCES, TO DISSOLVE THE CODE ENFORCEMENT BOARD AND ESTABLISH PROVISIONS FOR CODE ENFORCEMENT SPECIAL MAGISTRATE  BY THE TOWN COUNCIL OF THE TOWN OF EATONVILLE, FLORIDA, NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN to hear the proposed Ordinance 2025-8 Amending Division 2 of Article VI, Code Enforcement, of Chapter 2, Administration, of The Towns Code of Ordinances, To Dissolve The Code Enforcement Board and Establish Provisions For Code Enforcement Special Magistrate at the second public hearing scheduled by the Town Council of the Town of Eatonville, Florida, on Tuesday, December 16, 2025 at 7:30 p.m., or as soon thereafter as this matter can be heard, at the Town of Eatonville Town Hall, located at 307 E. Kennedy Blvd., FL 32751.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE TOWN OF EATONVILLE, FLORIDA, AMENDING DIVISION 2 OF ARTICLE VI, CODE ENFORCEMENT, OF CHAPTER 2, ADMINISTRATION, OF THE TOWNS CODE OF ORDINANCES, TO DISSOLVE THE CODE ENFORCEMENT BOARD AND ESTABLISH PROVISIONS FOR CODE ENFORCEMENT SPECIAL MAGISTRATE; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  At the aforementioned public hearing, all interested parties may appear to be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance 2025-8 Amending Division 2 of Article VI, Code Enforcement, of Chapter 2, Administration, of The Towns Code of Ordinances, To Dissolve The Code Enforcement Board and Establish Provisions For Code Enforcement Special Magistrate.  Copies of the proposed Ordinance 2025-8 are available for public inspection at the Town Hall, located at 307 E. Kennedy Boulevard, Eatonville, Florida, during regular business hours, 8:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m., Monday  Friday.  Any person requiring reasonable accommodation to participate in this meeting should contact the Office of the Town Clerk at (407) 623-8910 at least three days in advance so arrangements can be made. All persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at the above referenced public hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.   12/06/2025 7905279</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416344</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11416343</link>
      <description>Notice at 307 E

Meeting: Tuesday, December 16, 2025 at 7:30 p.m.
Location: 307 E

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING (2 ND READING)   AMENDING CHAPTER 20, ARTICLE II, DIVISION 1 OF THE TOWN CODE TO ESTABLISH A LOCAL BUSINESS PREFERENCE IN THE ACQUISITION OF GOODS AND SERVICES  BY THE TOWN COUNCIL OF THE TOWN OF EATONVILLE, FLORIDA, NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN to hear the proposed Ordinance 2025-06 Amending Chapter 20, Article II, Division 1 of The Town Code To Establish A Local Business Preference In The Acquisition of Goods And Services at the second public hearing scheduled by the Town Council of the Town of Eatonville, Florida, on Tuesday, December 16, 2025 at 7:30 p.m., or as soon thereafter as this matter can be heard, at the Town of Eatonville Town Hall, located at 307 E. Kennedy Blvd., FL 32751.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE TOWN OF EATONVILLE, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 20, ARTICLE II, DIVISION 1 OF THE TOWN CODE TO ESTABLISH A LOCAL BUSINESS PREFERENCE IN THE ACQUISITION OF GOODS AND SERVICES; PROVIDING DEFINITIONS; ESTABLISHING EXCEPTIONS FROM LOCAL BUSINESS PREFERENCE; PROVIDING FOR THE APPLICATION AND ENFORCEMENT OF LOCAL BUSINESS PREFERENCE; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION, CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. At the aforementioned public hearing, all interested parties may appear to be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance 2025-06 Amending Chapter 20, Article II, Division 1 of The Town Code To Establish A Local Business Preference In The Acquisition of Goods And Services. These public hearings may be continued to one or more future dates.  Copies of the proposed Ordinance 2025-06 are available for public inspection at the Town Hall, located at 307 E. Kennedy Boulevard, Eatonville, Florida, during regular business hours, 8:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m., Monday  Friday.  Any person requiring reasonable accommodation to participate in this meeting should contact the Office of the Town Clerk at (407) 623-8910 at least three days in advance so arrangements can be made. All persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at the above referenced public hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.   12/06/2025 7905275</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11416343</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11415823</link>
      <description>CITY OF EDGEWOOD Notice of Public Hearing 2 nd and Final Reading of Ordinance   On Tuesday, December 16, 2025, at 6:30 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF EDGEWOOD Notice of Public Hearing 2 nd and Final Reading of Ordinance   On Tuesday, December 16, 2025, at 6:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, the Edgewood City Council will hold a Public Hearing in the City Hall Council Chamber, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL 32809 on the following ordinance:  ORDINANCE NO. 2025-12 - AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF EDGEWOOD, FLORIDA, RELATING TO THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE; AMENDING CHAPTER 134 TO ADD CODE OF ORDINANCES SECTION 134-40 ESTABLISHING A PROCESS FOR THE REVIEW OF REASONABLE ACCOMMODATION REQUESTS FOR CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES PURSUANT TO FLORIDA STATUTES SECTION 397.487; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Ordinances may be inspected by the public in the Office of the City Clerk, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL. Interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the Ordinance. Persons wishing to appeal any decision made during the hearing will need a record of the proceedings and may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including the testimony and evidence on which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance or an interpreter to participate in this public hearing should contact Sandra Riffle, City Clerk, at (407) 851-2920, at least 24 hours in advance of the meeting. The public hearing may be continued to a time and date certain by announcement at this scheduled hearing without any further published notice.   12/05/2025 7903711</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11415823</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11415822</link>
      <description>CITY OF EDGEWOOD Notice of Public Hearing 2 nd and Final Reading of Ordinance   On Tuesday, December 16, 2025, at 6:30 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF EDGEWOOD Notice of Public Hearing 2 nd and Final Reading of Ordinance   On Tuesday, December 16, 2025, at 6:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, the Edgewood City Council will hold a Public Hearing in the City Hall Council Chamber, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL 32809 on the following ordinance:  ORDINANCE NO. 2025-13 - AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF EDGEWOOD, AMENDING CHAPTER 126, SUBDIVISIONS, OF THE CODE OF ORDINANCES, CITY OF EDGEWOOD, TO REVISE THE MANDATORY REPAVING REQUIREMENT FOR PRIVATE STREETS IN GATED NEIGHBORHOODS TO A MANDATORY PAVING NEEDS ASSESSMENT REQUIREMENT; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION, SEVERABILITY, CONFLICTS AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Ordinances may be inspected by the public in the Office of the City Clerk, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL. Interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the Ordinance. Persons wishing to appeal any decision made during the hearing will need a record of the proceedings and may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including the testimony and evidence on which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance or an interpreter to participate in this public hearing should contact Sandra Riffle, City Clerk, at (407) 851-2920, at least 24 hours in advance of the meeting. The public hearing may be continued to a time and date certain by announcement at this scheduled hearing without any further published notice.   12/05/2025 7903716</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11415822</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11415815</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING   OLYMPUS  COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTThe Board of Supervisors of the Olympus Community Development District (District) will hold a special meeting on Friday, December 12, 2025, at 2:00 p.m. at the Holiday Inn Express at 1810 S Hwy 27, Clermont 34711. A copy of the agenda for the meeting can be obtained from the District Office at PFM Group Consulting LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, FL 32817 or by phone at (407) 723-5935.  Additionally, a copy of the agenda, along with any meeting materials available in an electronic format, may be obtained at http://olympuscdd.com/.  The public meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida law. Copies of the agenda may be obtained at the office of the District Manager, located at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Phone: (407) 723-5935 (the District Managers Office), during normal business hours. The public meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when staff or board members may participate by speaker telephone.  Any person requiring special accommodations in order to access and participate in the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the Meetings is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Lynne Mullins District Manager 7902297 12/5/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11415815</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414496</link>
      <description>Notice of Adoption
NOTICE OF ADOPTION
PETITION TO VACATE # 25-05-013
WHEREAS, pursuant to procedures adopted by the Board of County Commissioners, ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Adoption
NOTICE OF ADOPTION
PETITION TO VACATE # 25-05-013
WHEREAS, pursuant to procedures adopted by the Board of County Commissioners, a petition was filed with the Board to vacate that certain 30-foot-wide drainage and utility easement along the west property line of their residential lot located within the Cape/Orlando Estates Unit 31A subdivision containing approximately 0.19 acres in Orange County, Florida (the legal property description is on file in the office of the Comptroller Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners).
WHEREAS, notice of a public hearing before the Board of County Commissioners on November 18, 2025, was published in the Orlando Sentinel, a newspaper of general circulation in Orange County, Florida, one time at least two weeks prior to the date for the hearing; and
WHEREAS, the Board finds that the vacating of that certain 30-foot-wide drainage and utility easement along the west property line of their residential lot located within the Cape/Orlando Estates Unit 31A subdivision containing approximately 0.19 acres will not operate to the detriment of Orange County or the public.
THEREFORE, BE IT RESOLVED BY THE BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF ORANGE COUNTY: The county road, right-of-way, easement, or park described above is vacated as of this date and Orange County renounces any rights in it.
RESOLVED THIS EIGHTEENTH DAY OF NOVEMBER 2025.
Phil Diamond, County Comptroller
As Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners
Orange County, Florida
December 5, 2025
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414496</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/06/11414806.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 101 East Central Boulevard

Location: 101 East Central Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
12.04.2025  PUBLIC NOTICE  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING AND PUBLIC COMMENT PERIOD  TO ALL INTERESTED ORGANIZATIONS,  AGENCIES AND PERSONS  ORANGE COUNTY HOUSING AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DIVISION CONSOLIDATED ANNUAL PERFORMANCE AND EVALUATION REPORT  For Fiscal Year 2024-2025  Funding Opportunity Number: B24UC120003; M24UC120213; E24UC120003;  E25UW120003; B20UW120003; M21UP120213  The Orange County Housing and Community Development Division will submit the 2024-2025 Consolidated Annual Performance and Evaluation Report (CAPER) to the United States Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) on or about December 30, 2025. The CAPER is an annual report of the projects and activities implemented with Community Development Block Grant (CDBG), HOME Investment Partnerships Program (HOME), Emergency Solutions Grant (ESG) and other federally funded programs administered by Orange Countys Housing and Community Development Division during Fiscal Year that started on October 1, 2024, and ended on September 30, 2025. Additionally, the 2024-2025 CAPER reports on projects and activities related to prevention, preparation for, and response to the coronavirus pandemic, which were completed during Fiscal Year 2024-2025 with CDBG-CV funds authorized by the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security Act (CARES Act). Furthermore, the 2024-2025 CAPER reports on projects and activities that address the need for housing and supportive services for homeless persons and those with the greatest risk of housing instability and implemented with HOME-American Rescue Plan funds (HOME-ARP). Finally, the 2024-2025 CAPER provides details on projects and activities funded by the ESG Rapid Unsheltered Survivor Housing Program (ESG-RUSH) to address the needs of individuals and households who were homeless or at risk of homelessness during the Hurricane Helene and Hurricane Milton events. The draft CAPER will be available for review by the public from Thursday, December 4, 2025, through Thursday, December 19, 2025, at the following link: http://www.ocfl.net/NeighborsHousing/CommunityDevelopment.aspx. The draft document will also be available for review at the following locations: Orlando Public Library main branch, Community Relations Department, Third Floor, located at 101 East Central Boulevard, Orlando, Florida 32801; and at the Orange County Housing and Community Development Divisions office located at 525 East South Street, Orlando, FL 32801. A public hearing to receive citizen input on the CAPER will be conducted on Wednesday, December 17, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. at the Internal Operations Center, Largo Training Room, First Floor, located at 450 E. South Street, Orlando, Florida 32801. Comments about the CAPER may be submitted in writing during the public comment period via email to the attention of Janna Souvorova at Janna.Souvorova@ocfl.net, or by mail to:  Housing and Community Development Division Attn: CAPER Public Comments  525 E. South Street, Orlando, Florida 32801  For more information or questions concerning the CAPER, please contact the Orange County Housing and Community Development Division at (407) 836-0963, or via e-mail to Janna.Souvorova@ocfl.net. Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  Orange County does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, sex, age, religion, disability or family status. Those with questions or concerns about nondiscrimination, those requiring special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), and those requiring language assistance (free of charge) should contact the Title VI/Nondiscrimination Coordinator at access@ocfl.net or by calling 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  If you are hearing or speech impaired, you may reach the phone numbers above by dialing 711. 7904234</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414806</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11414806.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414804</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold public hearings on the following:ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold public hearings on the following:ORDINANCE NO. 36-2025  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF DELTONA, FLORIDA, AMENDING SECTION 110-814, ADDITIONAL REGULATIONS FOR CERTAIN PERMITTED PRINCIPAL USES AND STRUCTURES, OF CHAPTER 110, ZONING, AND CHAPTER 74, ADMINISTRATION, OF THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE UPDATING PROCEDURES AND REGULATIONS RELATED TO CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES IN COMPLIANCE WITH FLORIDA STATUTES; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Public hearings will be held as follows:  Planning and Zoning Board  December 17, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. City Commission (First Reading)  January 5, 2026, at 6:30 p.m. City Commission (Adoption Hearing  January 20, 2026, at 6:30 p.m.  at City Hall, 2345 Providence Boulevard, Deltona, Florida.  All interested parties are invited to provide their comments, views and objections to the Deltona Planning and Zoning Board and/or City Commission as part of the Public Hearing. The failure of a person to appear during said public hearing and to object either in person or in writing to said case may severely restrict the ability of such a person to contest it at a later date.  The associated paperwork may be inspected by the public at the Deltona City Hall, 2345 Providence Blvd., Deltona, Florida, Monday  Friday, 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m.  For further information, contact the City Clerks Office at (386) 878-8500.  The date, time and place of any continuance of the above scheduled public hearing will be announced at said public hearing and no further notice regarding said continuance is required to be published.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Deltona City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. The City does not provide this verbatim record.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact City Clerk Joyce Raftery 48 hours in advance of the meeting date and time at (386) 878-8500.  All parties in interest and persons for or against aforementioned items will be given an opportunity to be heard at said Public Hearing.  Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona  If you should have any questions regarding the above ad, please contact my office at (386) 878-8500. Thank you.  Sincerely,  /s/ Joyce Raftery Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona   12/4/2025 7901963</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414804</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414802</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULEMAKING FOR PARKING AND TOWING ENFORCEMENT BY  REUNION WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A public hearing will be conducted by the...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING FOR PARKING AND TOWING ENFORCEMENT BY  REUNION WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Reunion West Community Development District (District) on Thursday, January 8, 2026, at 10:30 a.m., at the Heritage Crossing Community Center, 7715 Heritage Crossing Way, Reunion, Florida 34747.  In accordance with Chapters 190 and 120, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its Rule Chapter V  Parking and Towing Rules, the Amended and Restated Rules Relating to Parking and Parking Enforcement (Policy) to regulate parking on District property with penalties including, but not limited to, towing and suspension of access to amenities. The purpose and effect of the Policy is to provide for efficient District  operations as provided for in Chapter 190, Florida Statutes. Specific legal authority for the Policy includes Sections 190.011, 190.012(2), 715.07, 190.012 and 120.54, Florida Statutes. Prior Notice of Rule Development was published in the Orlando Sentinel on December 4, 2025.  The public hearing will provide an opportunity for the public to address the Policy. A copy of the Policy and any material proposed to be incorporated by reference may be obtained by contacting the District Manager, Tricia Adams, c/o Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC, 219 East Livingston Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, by phone during regular business hours at (407) 841-5524, or by e-mail at tadams@gmscfl.com (District Managers Office).   Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes, must do so in writing within twenty-one (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.  The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the public hearing. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at the public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the public hearing, one or more Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.  Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this hearing is asked to advise the District Manager at least three (3) business days before the hearing by contacting the District Managers Office. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) or 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.  Tricia Adams, District Manager Reunion West Community Development District   12/11/2025 7900243</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414802</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/00/11414800.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 175 W

Meeting: Monday, December 15, 2025 at 6:00 P.M.
Location: 175 W

--- Full Notice Text ---
12/4/2025 NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN BY THE CITY OF LONGWOOD, FLORIDA, that the City Commission will conduct a public hearing on Ordinance No. 25-2278, on Monday, December 15, 2025 at 6:00 P.M., or as soon thereafter as possible in the Longwood City Commission Chambers, 175 West Warren Avenue, Longwood, Florida.  The purpose of the public hearing is to receive public comment and to consider the proposed amendment.  The proposed amendment affects the use of land within the municipal limits of the City of Longwood.  ORDINANCE NO. 25-2278  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF LONGWOOD, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE LONGWOOD CITY CODE SECTION 2-2 (j) GOVERNING APPEALS OF TRESPASS WARNINGS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.At this meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the request.  This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is complete.  A copy of the proposed Longwood City Code Amendment is available for review at City Hall between the hours of 8:00 A.M. to 5:00 P.M. during regular work days.  The office is located at 175 W. Warren Avenue, Longwood, Florida, or you may call the office at 407-260-3440. NOTICE:  All persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at the meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record to include the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based (per Sec. 286.0105, Florida Statutes).  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these meetings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator at 407-260-3466 at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  Publish: Thursday, November 20, 2025  CITY OF LONGWOOD, FL CITY COMMISSION NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING LONGWOOD CITY CODE AMENDMENT  7896969</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414800</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11414800.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/99/11414799.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
7896701 12/4/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER THE ADOPTION OF THE FY 2026 BUDGET; NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER THE IMPOSITION OF OPERATIONS AND MAINTENANCE SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS, ADOPTION OF AN ASSESSMENT ROLL, AND THE LEVY, COLLECTION, AND ENFORCEMENT OF THE SAME; AND NOTICE OF REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETING. 	The Board of Supervisors (Board) for the Sunbridge Stewardship District (District) will hold the following public hearings and a regular meeting:  DATE: TIME:   December 18, 2025 9:00 a.m. LOCATION: 6900 Tavistock Lakes Boulevard, Suite 200 Orlando, Florida 32817The first public hearing is being held pursuant to Chapter 2017-220 and 2025-245, Laws of Florida and Chapter 189, Florida Statutes, to receive public comment and objections on the Districts proposed imposition of operations and maintenance special assessments (O&amp;M Assessments) upon certain lands located within the District, to fund the Proposed Budget for FY 2026; to consider the adoption of an assessment roll; and, to provide for the levy, collection, and enforcement of assessments. At the conclusion of the hearing, the Board will, by resolution, levy O&amp;M Assessments as finally approved by the Board. A Board meeting of the District will also be held where the Board may consider any other District business.   Description of Assessments The District imposes O&amp;M Assessments on benefitted property within the District for the purpose of funding the Districts general administrative, operations, and maintenance budget.  A geographic depiction of the property potentially subject to the proposed O&amp;M Assessments is identified in the map attached hereto.  The schedule of the proposed O&amp;M Assessments, which are subject to change at the hearing, is not to exceed $54.65 per equivalent residential unit (ERU) on each certain property within the District, per year.  Please note that assessments in any year prior to final build out will be less. . For FY 2026, the District intends to collect the assessments imposed on certain benefitted property by sending out a bill.  It is important to pay your assessment because failure to pay will may result in a foreclosure action, which also may result in a loss of title.  The Districts decision to collect assessments on the tax roll or by direct billing does not preclude the District from later electing to collect those or other assessments in a different manner at a future time. Additional Provisions The public hearing and meeting are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law.  A copy of the Budget, proposed assessment roll, and the agenda for the hearings and meeting may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, located at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Ph: (407) 723-5900 (District Managers Office), during normal business hours or on the Districts website at https://sunbridgesd.com.  The public hearing and meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing or meeting.  There may be occasions when staff or board members may participate by speaker telephone.   	Any person requiring special accommodations at the public hearings and meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.   Please note that all affected property owners have the right to appear at the public hearings and meeting and may also file written objections with the District Managers Office within twenty days of publication of this notice.  Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the public hearings or meeting is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. 							 							District Manager  SUNBRIDGE STEWARDSHIP DISTRICT</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414799</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11414799.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414798</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Myrtle Creek and Midtown Improvement Districts and the ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Myrtle Creek and Midtown Improvement Districts and the Poitras East Community Development DistrictThe Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Myrtle Creek and Midtown Improvement Districts and the Poitras East Community Development District will be meeting on Thursday, December 11, 2025, at 3:30 p.m. at 6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd, Ste 200, Orlando, FL 32827.   The Construction Committee will discuss and review the status of current and future Infrastructure Improvements, Requests for Qualifications, Requests for Proposals, etc., related to the Districts.  The meeting will be open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.  There may be occasions when one or more members of the Committee and/or District Staff will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at these meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at 407-723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that the person will need a record of the proceedings and that, accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jennifer Walden District Manager 7894186 12/4/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414798</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414590</link>
      <description>EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater Wes...


--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater West Community Development District (District), will hold a Regular Meeting on December 15, 2025, at 9:15 a.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, https://edgewaterwestcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
December 4, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414590</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414575</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2025-82


Notice is hereby given that the Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on December 11, 2025, in the St. Cloud Community Center at 3101 17th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:00 p.m., will consider the issue and make a recommendation to the City Council relative to enactment of Ordinance No. 2025-82 entitled:


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2025-82 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, ASSIGNING A FUTURE LAND USE DESIGNATION OF APPROXIMATELY +/- 785.68 ACRES IDENTIFIED AS WHALEY PLATT PROJECT #CPA25-00011, GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF LAKE TOHOPEKALIGA, EAST OF OSCEOLA ROAD, SOUTH OF KISSIMMEE PARK ROAD, AND WEST OF LAKE TOHOPEKALIGA ROAD; FROM MXD MIXED USE (COUNTY) TO MIX MIXED USE (CITY), PROVIDING FOR AMENDING THE OFFICIAL FUTURE LAND USE MAP OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, APPLICABILITY AND EFFECT, SEVERABILITY, COPIES ON FILE AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Christy Depuy, Planning Commission Secretary
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, FL 34769
Telephone: 407) 957-7297


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
December 4, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414575</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414560</link>
      <description>Notice at 8 Broadway

Location: 8 Broadway

--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater East Community Development District (District) will hold a Regular Meeting on December 15, 2025, at 9:00 a.m., at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., located at 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, http://edgewatereastcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
December 4, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414560</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11414555</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2025-83


Notice is hereby given that the Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on December 11, 2025, in the St. Cloud Community Center at 3101 17th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:00 p.m., will consider the issue and make a recommendation to the City Council relative to enactment of Ordinance No. 2025-83 entitled:


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on January 8, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2025-83 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, PROVIDING FOR THE ZONING AMENDMENT OF THE ZONING MAP OF THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, SPECIFICALLY CHANGING THE ZONING DESIGNATION OF APPROXIMATELY +/- 785.68 ACRES IDENTIFIED AS WHALEY PLATT, PROJECT #ZMA25-00014, FROM MXD MIXED USE (COUNTY) TO MIX MIXED USE (CITY), GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF LAKE TOHOPEKALIGA, EAST OF OSCEOLA ROAD, SOUTH OF KISSIMMEE PARK ROAD, AND WEST OF LAKE TOHOPEKALIGA ROAD; PROVIDING FOR ENTERING THE DESIGNATION ON THE OFFICIAL ZONING MAP, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, SEVERABILITY, AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Christy Depuy, Planning Commission Secretary
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, FL 34769
Telephone: (407) 957-7297


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-
December 4, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11414555</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/95/11413195.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2025-81
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud
Florida</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11413195</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11413195.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11413368</link>
      <description>Notice at the northeast corner of N

Location: the northeast corner of N

--- Full Notice Text ---
PLANNING AND ZONING COMMISSION / LOCAL PLANNING AGENCY  PUBLIC HEARING AGENDA December 18, 2025DEAR PROPERTY OWNER OR INTERESTED PARTY:  At 9:00 a.m. on Thursday, December 18, 2025, or as soon thereafter as the matters may be considered, the Orange County Planning and Zoning Commission (PZC) / Local Planning Agency (LPA) shall hold a public hearing to consider the rezoning requests listed below and public hearing for an ordinance as described below.  Also, at 9:00 a.m. on Thursday, December 18, 2025, or as soon thereafter as the matters may be considered, the Orange County PZC / Local Planning Agency (LPA) shall hold public hearings to consider the adoption of Small-Scale Development Amendments to the Orange County Comprehensive Plan (CP), as authorized by Chapter 163, Florida Statutes and pursuant to Sections 163.3187(2) and 125.66, Florida Statutes.  PZC / LPA public hearings are held in the Board of County Commissioners Chambers located on the 1st Floor of the Orange County Administration Building, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida.   The staff report book and meeting agenda will also be available for public viewing on the Orange County website (www.orangecountyfl.net) one week prior to the public hearing.  Please be advised that this notice is published in accordance with the Orange County Code, Section 30-1(d)(6) and Section 30-40 as well as the provisions of the Orange County Comprehensive Plan and applicable state law.  Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), if any person with a disability as defined by the ADA needs special accommodations to participate in this proceeding, then not later than two (2) business days prior to the proceedings, he or she should contact the Government Service Center at (407) 836-3111.  Alberto A. Vargas  Planning Manager  Para mas informacion referente a esta vista publica, favor comunicarse al Departamento de Planificacion al numero 407-836-5600. Pou plis enfomasyon an Kreyol souple rele (407)836-3111. AGENDA:  9:00 A.M.  Pledge of Allegiance, review of the November 20, 2025, PZC/LPA meeting minutes, and public comment.  The following public hearings will occur after public comment:  A. Privately Initiated Rezoning Request:  RZ-25-11-023 APPLICANT: Ali Assadi, 50 Investment Group LLC  OWNER: Ali Assadi, 50 Investment Group LLC  REQUEST: To rezone from C-1 (Retail Commercial District) to C-3 (Wholesale Commercial District) LOCATION: 18966 E. Colonial Drive; generally located south of E Colonial Drive west of Union Street, east of Gloucester Street and north of Lansing Street LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 1.72 gross acre DISTRICT: 5  RZ-25-12-025 APPLICANT: Fernando Tata, Astro Auto LLC OWNER: Fernando Tata, Astro Auto LLC  REQUEST: To rezone from C-1 (Retail Commercial District) to C-2 (General Commercial District) LOCATION: 4200 S Orange Blossom Trial; generally located north of 43rd Street, south of 42ND Street, east of S Nashville Ave and west of S Orange Blossom Trail  LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.49 gross acres DISTRICT: 6  LUP-23-03-106 APPLICANT: Jeremy Anderson, Common Oak Engineering LLC  OWNER: Hartzog Homes LLC PROJECT NAME Hartzog Homes Land Use Plan  REQUEST: To rezone from R-T-2 (Combination Mobile Home and Single Family Dwelling District) to PD (Planned Development District)  LOCATION: North of Lake Gifford Way, east of Tollcross Way   LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 8.91 gross acres DISTRICT: 1  B. Privately Initiated Small-Scale Future Land Use Element Map Amendments to Change the Designation of Lands within Unincorporated County, and Where Expressly Noted Below, Concurrent Rezoning Requests  SS-25-11-013 &amp; RZ-25-11-013 APPLICANT: Juan Manuel Vasquez   OWNER: Vasquez Homes LLC REQUEST: To change the Future Land Use Map designation from Low Density Residential (LDR) to Commercial (C) and to rezone from R-1A (Single-Family Dwelling District) to C-1 (Retail Commercial District)  LOCATION: 7501 Liverpool Blvd; generally located at the northeast corner of N. Goldenrod Rd. and Liverpool Blvd.  LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.27 gross acre DISTRICT: 5  SS-25-12-024 APPLICANT: Lucille Ghioto, Habitat for Humanity Greater Orlando and Osceola CountyOWNER: Habitat for Humanity Greater Orlando and Osceola CountyREQUEST: To change Future Land Use from Low Density Residential (LDR) to Medium Density Residential (MDR)  LOCATION: 1709 Wakulla Way; generally located on the north side of Wakulla Way, south of Michael Terrace, west of Rio Grande Ave., and east of Tampa Ave. LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.33-gross acre DISTRICT: 6  SS-25-12-019 APPLICANT: M. Rebecca Wilson, Esq., Lowndes, Drosdick, Doster, Kantor &amp; Reed, P.A.  OWNER: ZES International, LLC REQUEST: To change the Future Land Use Map designation from Activity Center Residential (ACR) to Activity Center Mixed Use (ACMU)  LOCATION: 14445 State Road 535; generally located east of State Road 535, north of World Center Drive, and south of Lake Bryan Beach Boulevard LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 5.93 gross acres DISTRICT: 1  SS-25-12-028 APPLICANT: Rebecca Wilson, Esq., Lowndes, Drosdick, Doster, Kantor &amp; Reed, P.A.  OWNER: 1600 Columbia St, LLC REQUEST: To change the Future Land Use Map designation from Low-Medium Density Residential (LMDR) to Commercial (C)  LOCATION: 1600 Columbia Street; generally located south of Columbia Street, west of S Rio Grande Avenue, and north of Grand Street LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.45 gross acre DISTRICT: 6  SS-25-11-017 &amp; RZ-25-11-017 APPLICANT: Mary D. Solik, Doty Solik Law   OWNER: DEO Towing LLC REQUEST: To change the Future Land Use Map designation from Low Density Residential (LDR) to Commercial (C) and to rezone from C-3 (Wholesale Commercial District) to C-3 Restricted (Wholesale Commercial District)  LOCATION: 5176 Busby Ave; generally located on the west side of Busby Ave., north of Clarcona Ocoee Rd., south of National St., and east of Journal Ave. LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.32 gross acre DISTRICT: 2  SS-25-12-021 APPLICANT: Lucille Ghioto, Habitat for Humanity Greater Orlando and Osceola CountyOWNER: Habitat for Humanity Greater Orlando and Osceola CountyREQUEST: To change Future Land Use from Commercial (C) to Low Density Residential (LDR) LOCATION: 4911 La Grange Ave; generally north of eastern terminus of La Grange Ave LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division TRACT SIZE: 0.34 gross acre DISTRICT: 6 7901932 12/3/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11413368</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11413364</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SHINGLE CREEK TRANSIT AND UTILITY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTThe Board of Superviso...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SHINGLE CREEK TRANSIT AND UTILITY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTThe Board of Supervisors (the Board) of the Shingle Creek Transit and Utility Community Development District (the District) will hold a regular meeting of its Board on Wednesday, December 10, 2025, at 2:00 p.m., at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 197, Orlando, Florida 32817. At such time, the Board is so authorized and may consider any business that may properly come before it. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained by contacting the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Phone (407) 723-5900.  The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors will participate by telephone.   Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this meeting is asked to advise the District Manager, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 7-1-1 or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY), or 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), who can aid you in contacting the District Manager.  A person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that such person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.Jennifer Walden District Manager   12/3/2025 7894174</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11413364</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11411945</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING GROUND TRANSPORTATION COMMITTEE OF THE GREATER ORLANDO AVIATION AUTHORITY   Notice is hereby given that the Ground Transpo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING GROUND TRANSPORTATION COMMITTEE OF THE GREATER ORLANDO AVIATION AUTHORITY   Notice is hereby given that the Ground Transportation Committee (the Committee) of the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority will hold a Notice of Violation Meeting at the Orlando International Airport (MCO) scheduled for Thursday, December 11, 2025, at 1:00 p.m. will be held in the Carl T. Langford Board Room of the Aviation Authority offices in the main terminal building at the Orlando International Airport, One Jeff Fuqua Boulevard, Orlando, FL 32827.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in these proceedings should contact the Aviation Authority offices at 407-825-2001 - 48 hours in advance of the public hearing. Additional information may be obtained from the Manager of Parking &amp; Ground Transportation Services, Zulai Perez, at 5855 Cargo Road, Orlando, Florida 32827, email: zperez@goaa.org, phone 407-825-2389, or at https://flymco.com/airport-business/sunshine-meetings/   12/2, 12/5/2025 7899637</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11411945</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11411337</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETINGOSCEOLA COUNTY  HOUSING FINANCE AUTHORITYA meeting of the Members of the Osceola County Housing Finance Authority will be held on ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETINGOSCEOLA COUNTY  HOUSING FINANCE AUTHORITYA meeting of the Members of the Osceola County Housing Finance Authority will be held on December 9, 2025 at 1:00 pm at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 E. Dakin Avenue, Roseada Room, Kissimmee, FL 34741. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law. Immediately following the adjournment of the Authority Meeting will be an Audit Committee meeting of the Osceola County Housing Finance Authority. A copy of the meeting agenda may be obtained from the Authoritys Manager at 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801. This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.  There may be occasions when one or more Members, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone.Any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the Authority Office at (407) 841-5524 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the Authority Office.  George S. Flint Authority Manager Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC 7902213 12/1/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11411337</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11411336</link>
      <description>Notice at the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue

Location: the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING   For the purposes of Section 147(f) of the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, as amended (the Code), notice is hereby given that the Florida Local Government Finance Commission (the Issuer) will hold a public hearing on December 8, 2025, at 10:00 A.M., or as soon thereafter as practicable. In accordance with Internal Revenue Service Revenue Procedure 2022-20, this public hearing will be held by telephone conference. Interested persons are encouraged to attend the telephone conference using the following instructions:  TELEPHONE CONFERENCE INSTRUCTIONS: TOLL-FREE DIAL IN NUMBER: 1 (877) 304-9269 PASSCODE: 359237#  The public hearing is being conducted for the purpose of receiving comments and hearing discussion concerning the proposed adoption by the Issuer of a resolution approving the issuance and sale by the Issuer of not exceeding $17,000,000 of its Florida Local Government Finance Commission Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds (Cornerstone Charter Academy Project) to be issued in one or more tax-exempt and/or taxable series of qualified 501(c)(3) bonds, as defined in Section 145 of the Code (collectively, the Bonds), pursuant to a plan of finance.  The proceeds of the Bonds, when and if issued, will be loaned to Cornerstone Charter Academy, Inc., a Florida not-for-profit corporation and an organization described under Section 501(c)(3) of the Code, or one of its affiliates (the Borrower). The proceeds will be used by the Borrower for the purposes of: (a) financing and refinancing all or a portion of the costs of acquiring, constructing, equipping, and/or improving of certain educational facilities located at the following addresses: (i) 906 Waltham Avenue, (ii) 5903 Randolph Avenue, (iii) 6300 Hansel Avenue, (iv) 6049 Randolph Avenue, (v) 5929 Hansel Avenue and (vi) 942 Fairlane Avenue, each in the City of Belle Isle, Orange County, Florida, 32809 (the Project); (b) funding necessary reserves and capitalized interest related to the Bonds, if deemed necessary or desirable; and (c) paying certain costs of issuance associated with the Bonds.  The Project will continue to be owned by the Borrower and will continue to be operated as a public charter school by the Borrower (or an entity or entities affiliated with or designated thereby pursuant to one or more qualified use or management agreements).  The Bonds shall be payable solely from the revenues derived by the Issuer from a loan agreement, mortgage and security agreement and other financing documents entered into by and between the Issuer and the Borrower prior to or contemporaneously with the issuance of the Bonds. Such Bonds and the interest thereon shall not constitute an  indebtedness or pledge of the general credit or taxing power, if any, of the Issuer, Brevard County, Charlotte County, Lee County, Osceola County, Sarasota County, St. Johns County, the State of Florida, or any political subdivision or agency thereof (including Orange County and the School District of Orange County). The Issuer has no taxing power.  Issuance of the Bonds shall be subject to several conditions including satisfactory documentation, the approval by bond counsel as to the tax-exempt status of the interest on all or a portion of the Bonds and receipt of necessary approvals for the financing. The aforementioned hearing shall be a public hearing and all persons in attendance will be given an opportunity to be heard and to express their views on the proposed issuance of the Bonds and the location and nature of the Project by accessing the telephone conference as indicated above. Written comments may also be submitted prior to the hearing to the Florida Local Government Finance Commission c/o Nabors Giblin &amp; Nickerson, P.A. at 2502 N. Rocky Point Drive, Suite 1060, Tampa, Florida 33607, directed to Issuers Counsel or via email sent to the following email address: rharb@ngn-tampa.com. Comments made at the hearing are for the consideration of the party(ies) providing an approval of the Bonds but will not bind the Issuer or such party(ies) as to any action it may take.  ALL PERSONS FOR OR AGAINST SAID APPROVAL CAN BE HEARD AT SAID TIME AND PLACE. IF A PERSON DECIDES TO APPEAL ANY DECISION MADE BY THE ISSUER WITH RESPECT TO SUCH HEARING OR MEETING, (S)HE WILL NEED TO ENSURE THAT A VERBATIM RECORD OF SUCH HEARING OR MEETING IS MADE (AT THEIR SOLE COST AND EXPENSE), WHICH RECORD INCLUDES THE TESTIMONY AND EVIDENCE UPON WHICH THE APPEAL IS BASED.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is requested to advise the Issuer at least twenty-four (24) hours prior to the meeting by contacting counsel to the Issuer at (813) 281-2222 or via email sent to the following email address: rharb@ngn-tampa.com.  By order of the Florida Local Government Finance Commission.  FLORIDA LOCAL GOVERNMENT FINANCE COMMISSION  /s/ Nicole Jovanovski Chair   10/01/2025 7901680</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11411336</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/30/11411330.pdf</link>
      <description>7896457 12/1/2025 Pursuant to Chapter 13, Section 7 of the Charter of the City of Orlando, notice is hereby given that a public hearing will be hel...


--- Full Notice Text ---
7896457 12/1/2025 Pursuant to Chapter 13, Section 7 of the Charter of the City of Orlando, notice is hereby given that a public hearing will be held on Monday, December 8, 2025, at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chambers, 2nd Floor, City Hall, 400 S. Orange Avenue, Orlando, FL 32801, concerning the Citys proposed disposition of the 1.6-acre vacant City-owned land on W. Jefferson St and N. Orange Blossom Trail in Orlando, Florida, as more particularly shown on the map below, for redevelopment as an affordable rental housing community.  The Citys estimate of the fair market value of the property is $1,544,000.  The proposed purchaser of the Property is Blossom Trail Housing Partners, LP, whose address is 9200 Belvedere Road, Suite 209, Royal Palm Beach, FL 33411. The seller is the City of Orlando, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, FL 32801.  To encourage and incentivize much needed affordable housing the proposed purchase price is $1.00. Anyone wishing to be heard regarding this matter should plan to attend the public hearing.  Please note that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Council with respect to this matter, he/she will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons with disabilities needing a special accommodation to participate in the proceeding should contact the City Clerks Office at (407) 246-2251, 24 hours in advance of the meeting. NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING FOR PROPOSED DISPOSITION OF REAL PROPERTY BY THE CITY OF ORLANDO</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11411330</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11411330.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11409730</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF A PRELIMINARY PUBLIC HEARING NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF A PRELIMINARY PUBLIC HEARING NO. 2 BY NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Preliminary Public Hearing No. 2 of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities will be held by the Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida, on Monday, December 15, 2025, at 3:00 p.m.* at 200 Canal Street on the third floor, in the DeBerry Room regarding Proposed Modifications (Increases) for NSBUs Electric Service Rates, Charges and Fees. (*immediately following Public Hearing No. 1)  A final public hearing no. 2 will also be conducted in January regarding this matter and will then be considered at the Regular NSBUC Meeting immediately following both final public hearings on January 26, 2026, at 3:00 pm at 200 Canal Street on the third floor in the DeBerry Room, New Smyrna Beach, Florida.  Copies of the agenda will be posted on the doors of the first floor of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities office at 200 Canal Street and on the NSBUs website - www.nsbufl.com. A full agenda package will also be posted on the NSBUs website.  All interested parties may appear at the scheduled Public Hearings and also arrange to inspect documents regarding the matters available at the NSBU office at 200 Canal Street, NSB and also located on NSBUs website  NSBUFL.COM  Pursuant to section 286.0105 of the Florida Statutes, if an individual decides to appeal any decision made by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities, with respect to any matter considered at a meeting, that individual will need a record of the proceedings and will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made. The transcription of such a verbatim will be provided to an individual at a cost to be determined by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities in accordance with the full cost to reproduce such transcriptions and copies.  In accordance with the American with Disabilities Act, persons with disabilities needing a special accommodation to participate in these proceedings should contact the individual or agency sending the notice; if possible no later than five days prior to the proceeding at the address given on notice. 7901097 11-30-25</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11409730</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11409729</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF A PRELIMINARY PUBLIC HEARING NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF A PRELIMINARY PUBLIC HEARING NO. 1 BY NEW SMYRNA BEACH UTILITIES Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida   Notice is hereby given a Preliminary Public Hearing No. 1 of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities will be held by the Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida, on Monday, December 15, 2025, at 3:00 p.m. at 200 Canal Street on the third floor, in the DeBerry Room, regarding Proposed Modifications to NSBUs Rates, Charges and Fees (Increases)  for Water, Wastewater and Reclaimed Water Services.  A final public hearing no. 1 will also be conducted in January regarding this matter and will then be considered at the Regular NSBUC Meeting immediately following both final public hearings on January 26, 2026, at 3:00 pm at 200 Canal Street on the third floor in the DeBerry Room, New Smyrna Beach, Florida.  Copies of the agenda will be posted on the doors of the first floor of the New Smyrna Beach Utilities office at 200 Canal Street and on the NSBUs website - www.nsbufl.com. A full agenda package will also be posted on the NSBUs website.  All interested parties may appear at the scheduled Public Hearings and also arrange to inspect documents regarding this matter available at the NSBU office at 200 Canal Street, NSB and also located on NSBUs website  NSBUFL.COM  Pursuant to section 286.0105 of the Florida Statutes, if an individual decides to appeal any decision made by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities, with respect to any matter considered at a meeting, that individual will need a record of the proceedings and will need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made. The transcription of such a verbatim will be provided to an individual at a cost to be determined by the New Smyrna Beach Utilities in accordance with the full cost to reproduce such transcriptions and copies.  In accordance with the American with Disabilities Act, persons with disabilities needing a special accommodation to participate in these proceedings should contact the individual or agency sending the notice; if possible no later than five days prior to the proceeding at the address given on notice. 7901085 11-30-25</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11409729</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/01/11409701.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 101 East Central Boulevard

Location: 101 East Central Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/30/2025 PUBLIC NOTICE  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING AND PUBLIC COMMENT PERIOD  TO ALL INTERESTED ORGANIZATIONS,  AGENCIES AND PERSONS  ORANGE COUNTY HOUSING AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DIVISION CONSOLIDATED ANNUAL PERFORMANCE AND EVALUATION REPORT  For Fiscal Year 2024-2025  Funding Opportunity Number: B24UC120003; M24UC120213; E24UC120003;  E20UW120003; B20UW120003; M21UP120213  The Orange County Housing and Community Development Division will submit the 2024-2025 Consolidated Annual Performance and Evaluation Report (CAPER) to the United States Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) on or about December 30, 2025. The CAPER is an annual report of the projects and activities implemented with Community Development Block Grant (CDBG), HOME Investment Partnerships Program (HOME), Emergency Solutions Grant (ESG) and other federally funded programs administered by Orange Countys Housing and Community Development Division during Fiscal Year that started on October 1, 2024, and ended on September 30, 2025. Additionally, the 2024-2025 CAPER reports on projects and activities related to prevention, preparation for, and response to the coronavirus pandemic, which were completed during Fiscal Year 2024-2025 with CDBG-CV funds authorized by the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security Act (CARES Act). Furthermore, the 2024-2025 CAPER reports on projects and activities that address the need for housing and supportive services for homeless persons and those with the greatest risk of housing instability and implemented with HOME-American Rescue Plan funds (HOME-ARP). Finally, the 2024-2025 CAPER provides details on projects and activities funded by the ESG Rapid Unsheltered Survivor Housing Program (ESG-RUSH) to address the needs of individuals and households who were homeless or at risk of homelessness during the Hurricane Helene and Hurricane Milton events. The draft CAPER will be available for review by the public from Wednesday, December 3, 2025, through Thursday, December 18, 2025, at the following link: http://www.ocfl.net/NeighborsHousing/CommunityDevelopment.aspx. The draft document will also be available for review at the following locations: Orlando Public Library main branch, Community Relations Department, Third Floor, located at 101 East Central Boulevard, Orlando, Florida 32801; and at the Orange County Housing and Community Development Divisions office located at 525 East South Street, Orlando, FL 32801. A public hearing to receive citizen input on the CAPER will be conducted on Wednesday, December 17, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. at the Internal Operations Center, Largo Training Room, First Floor, located at 450 E. South Street, Orlando, Florida 32801. Comments about the CAPER may be submitted in writing during the public comment period via email to the attention of Janna Souvorova at Janna.Souvorova@ocfl.net, or by mail to:  Housing and Community Development Division Attn: CAPER Public Comments  525 E. South Street, Orlando, Florida 32801  For more information or questions concerning the CAPER, please contact the Orange County Housing and Community Development Division at (407) 836-0963, or via e-mail to Janna.Souvorova@ocfl.net. Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  La Seccin 286.0105 de los Estatutos de la Florida establece que si una persona decide apelar cualquier decisin tomada por una junta, agencia o comisin con respecto a cualquier asunto considerado en una reunin o audiencia, necesitar un registro de los procedimientos y que, para tal fin, es posible que deba asegurarse de que se haga un registro literal de los procedimientos. cuyo expediente incluye los testimonios y las pruebas en que se basar la apelacin.  Seksyon 286.0105, Lwa Florida, deklare ke si yon moun deside f apl kont nenpt desizyon ki te pran pa yon tablo, ajans, oswa komisyon ki gen rap ak nenpt pwoblm konsidere nan yon reyinyon oswa yon odyans, li pral bezwen yon dosye sou pwosedi yo, e ke, pou rezon sa yo, li ka bezwen asire ke yon dosye vbal nan pwosedi yo ft, ki dosye gen ladan temwayaj ak prv ki montre apl la dwe baze.  Orange County does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, sex, age, religion, disability or family status. Those with questions or concerns about nondiscrimination, those requiring special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), and those requiring language assistance (free of charge) should contact the Title VI/Nondiscrimination Coordinator at access@ocfl.net or by calling 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  If you are hearing or speech impaired, you may reach the phone numbers above by dialing 711.  El Condado de Orange no discrimina por motivos de raza, color, origen nacional, sexo, edad, religin, discapacidad o situacin familiar. Aquellos que tengan preguntas o inquietudes sobre la no discriminacin, aquellos que requieran asistencia especial segn la Ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades (ADA) y aquellos que requieran asistencia lingstica (gratuita) deben comunicarse con el Coordinador de No Discriminacin/Ttulo VI en access@ocfl.net o llamando 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  Si tiene problemas de audicin o del habla, puede comunicarse con los nmeros de telfono anteriores marcando 711.  Orange County pa f diskriminasyon sou baz ras, koul, orijin nasyonal, sks, laj, relijyon, andikap oswa sitiyasyon fanmi. Moun ki gen kesyon oswa enkyetid konsnan non diskriminasyon, moun ki bezwen asistans espesyal dapre Lwa Ameriken andikape yo (ADA), ak moun ki bezwen asistans nan lang (gratis) ta dwe kontakte Kowdonat Tit VI/Nondiscrimination nan access@ocfl.net oswa l yo rele 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  Si w gen pwoblm pou tande oswa pou w pale, ou ka kontakte nimewo telefn ki anwo yo l w konpoze 711. Housing available to all, without discrimination. 7899537</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11409701</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11409701.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11409696</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETINGS SCHEDULE OLYMPUS  COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT FISCAL YEAR 2025-2026The Board of Supervisors of the Olympus Community Developm...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETINGS SCHEDULE OLYMPUS  COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT FISCAL YEAR 2025-2026The Board of Supervisors of the Olympus Community Development District will hold their regular meetings for Fiscal Year 2025/2026 at Holiday Inn Express at 1810 S Hwy 27, Clermont 34711 at 11:00 a.m. as follows:  October 31, 2025 November 14, 2025 December 12, 2025 January 9, 2026 February 20, 2026 March 12, 2026 April 17, 2026 May 15, 2026 June 12, 2026 July 24, 2026 August 21, 2026 September 18, 2026  The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.  A copy of the agenda for these meetings may be obtained from PFM Group Consulting LLC or by calling (407) 723-5900.  There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (407) 723-5900 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Lynne Mullins District Manager 7892448 11/30/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11409696</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/55/11407855.pdf</link>
      <description>11/27/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: 	NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Planning and Zoning Commission will hold a public...


--- Full Notice Text ---
11/27/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: 	NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Planning and Zoning Commission will hold a public hearing to consider the enactment of an ordinance entitled:FLU 25-01 AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, TO AMEND THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY COMPREHENSIVE PLAN BY PROVIDING FOR A CHANGE OF THE FUTURE LAND USE DESIGNATION FROM LOW DENSITY RESIDENTIAL (LDR) TO LOW INTENSITY NONRESIDENTIAL (LINR) FOR FIVE PARCELS GENERALLY LOCATED SOUTH OF THE GENEVA SCHOOL AT 1775 SEMINOLA BOULEVARD, AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION I OF THIS ORDINANCE; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The property known as: Parcel ID Number Address 26-20-30-5AR-0D00-1480 26-20-30-5AR-0D00-148C 26-20-30-5AR-0D00-148D 26-20-30-5AR-0D00-148E 10-21-30-5BQ-0000-004B 1490 Azalea Avenue N/A N/A N/A N/A  *Insert Map Here*  	This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, and the Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida, as amended and supplemented. 	The Planning and Zoning Commission will consider the proposed Ordinance on December 10, 2025, at 6:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the Commission. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk, and the same may be inspected by the public.  Publish Date: November 27, 2025			Donna G. Gardner, CMC, City Clerk  Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262-7700, Ext. 1150.  CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA 	NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER FUTURE LAND USE MAP AMENDMENT  7899627</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407855</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407855.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/54/11407854.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at THE SOUTHEAST CORNER OF OXFORD ROAD AND STATE ROAD 436 IDENTIFIED AS

Location: THE SOUTHEAST CORNER OF OXFORD ROAD AND STATE ROAD 436 IDENTIFIED AS

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/27/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: 	NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Planning and Zoning Commission will hold a public hearing to consider the enactment of an ordinance entitled:PUD 25-03 AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE CITYS OFFICIAL ZONING MAP FROM PMX-MID (PLANNED MIXED-USE: MEDIUM RISE) TO PMX-MID FOR TWO PARCELS LOCATED AT THE SOUTHEAST CORNER OF OXFORD ROAD AND STATE ROAD 436 IDENTIFIED AS PARCEL 17-21-30-510-0000-001A AND PARCEL 17-21-30-510-0000-001B, TOTALING APPROXIMATELY 4.48 ACRES, AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION I OF THIS ORDINANCE, AND APPROVING AN AMENDED PLANNED UNIT DEVELOPMENT (PUD) AGREEMENT AND CONCEPT PLAN FOR A MULTITENANT COMMERCIAL DEVELOPMENT; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The property known as: Parcel ID Number Address 17-21-30-510-0000-001A 17-21-30-510-0000-001B 201 S.R. 436 205 S.R. 436  *Insert Map Here*  	This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, and the Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida, as amended and supplemented. 	The Planning and Zoning Commission will consider the proposed Ordinance on December 10, 2025, at 6:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the Commission. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk, and the same may be inspected by the public.  Publish Date: November 27, 2025			Donna G. Gardner, CMC, City Clerk  Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262-7700, Ext. 1150. 7899620 CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA 	NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ZONING MAP AMENDMENT</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407854</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407854.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/53/11407853.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 380 S

Location: 380 S

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/27/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Planning and Zoning Commission will hold a public hearing to consider the enactment of an ordinance entitled:  PUD 25-02  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE CITYS OFFICIAL ZONING MAP AND CHANGING THE ZONING CLASSIFICATION FROM PMX-MID (PLANNED MIXED- USE: MEDIUM RISE) TO PMX-MID (PLANNED MIXED-USE: MEDIUM RISE) FOR ONE (1) PARCELS GENERALLY LOCATED AT 380 S.R. 436 AND DESCRIBED WITH PARCEL IDENTIFICATION NUMBER 17-21- 30-537-0000-0010, TOTALING APPROXIMATELY 1.03 ACRES, AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION I OF THIS ORDINANCE; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The property known as:  Parcel ID Number Address 17-21-30-537-0000-0010 380 S.R. 436  *Insert Map Here*  This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, and the Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida, as amended and supplemented. The Planning and Zoning Commission will consider the proposed Ordinance on December 10, 2025, at 6:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the Commission. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk, and the same may be inspected by the public. Publish Date: November 27, 2025 Donna G. Gardner, CMC, City Clerk Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262- 7700, Ext. 1150.  CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER  ZONING MAP AMENDMENT  7899615</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407853</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407853.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/52/11407852.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
7896696 11/27/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER THE ADOPTION OF THE FY 2026 BUDGET; NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER THE IMPOSITION OF OPERATIONS AND MAINTENANCE SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS, ADOPTION OF AN ASSESSMENT ROLL, AND THE LEVY, COLLECTION, AND ENFORCEMENT OF THE SAME; AND NOTICE OF REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETING. 	The Board of Supervisors (Board) for the Sunbridge Stewardship District (District) will hold the following public hearings and a regular meeting:  DATE: TIME:   December 18, 2025 9:00 a.m. LOCATION: 6900 Tavistock Lakes Boulevard, Suite 200 Orlando, Florida 32817The first public hearing is being held pursuant to Chapter 2017-220 and 2025-245, Laws of Florida and Chapter 189, Florida Statutes, to receive public comment and objections on the Districts proposed imposition of operations and maintenance special assessments (O&amp;M Assessments) upon certain lands located within the District, to fund the Proposed Budget for FY 2026; to consider the adoption of an assessment roll; and, to provide for the levy, collection, and enforcement of assessments. At the conclusion of the hearing, the Board will, by resolution, levy O&amp;M Assessments as finally approved by the Board. A Board meeting of the District will also be held where the Board may consider any other District business.   Description of Assessments The District imposes O&amp;M Assessments on benefitted property within the District for the purpose of funding the Districts general administrative, operations, and maintenance budget.  A geographic depiction of the property potentially subject to the proposed O&amp;M Assessments is identified in the map attached hereto.  The schedule of the proposed O&amp;M Assessments, which are subject to change at the hearing, is not to exceed $54.65 per equivalent residential unit (ERU) on each certain property within the District, per year.  Please note that assessments in any year prior to final build out will be less. . For FY 2026, the District intends to collect the assessments imposed on certain benefitted property by sending out a bill.  It is important to pay your assessment because failure to pay will may result in a foreclosure action, which also may result in a loss of title.  The Districts decision to collect assessments on the tax roll or by direct billing does not preclude the District from later electing to collect those or other assessments in a different manner at a future time. Additional Provisions The public hearing and meeting are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law.  A copy of the Budget, proposed assessment roll, and the agenda for the hearings and meeting may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, located at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Ph: (407) 723-5900 (District Managers Office), during normal business hours or on the Districts website at https://sunbridgesd.com.  The public hearing and meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing or meeting.  There may be occasions when staff or board members may participate by speaker telephone.   	Any person requiring special accommodations at the public hearings and meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.   Please note that all affected property owners have the right to appear at the public hearings and meeting and may also file written objections with the District Managers Office within twenty days of publication of this notice.  Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the public hearings or meeting is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. 							 							District Manager  7896696 SUNBRIDGE STEWARDSHIP DISTRICT</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407852</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407852.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407616</link>
      <description>Notice at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard

Location: 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
THE WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA
NOTICE OF CANCELLATION OF BOARD MEETING
SCHEDULED FOR DECEMBER 3, 2025


The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Board of Supervisors meeting scheduled for December 3, 2025, has been cancelled. The next meeting of the Board of Supervisors is scheduled for January 7, 2026, at 2:00 PM and will be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Water Authority administration building located at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741. Contact Administration Office (t: 407-944-5130 or administrativeoffice@tohowater.com for further assistance.
November 27, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407616</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407599</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED 
AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE AND AMENDED POLICIES &amp; RATES OF THE ANTHEM PARK
 COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED 
AND RESTATED RULES OF PROCEDURE AND AMENDED POLICIES &amp; RATES OF THE ANTHEM PARK
 COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors of the Anthem Park Community Development District (District) on January 7, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Anthem Park Clubhouse, 2090 Continental St., St. Cloud, Florida 34769.


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes,the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, Rule No. 1, and Amended District Policies &amp; Rates, Rule No. 2. The purpose and effect of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure and Amended Policies &amp; Rates is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. Prior notice of rule development was published in the Osceola News-Gazette on November 20, 2025.


The Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure may address topics such as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings and competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings, as well as any other area of the general operation of the District. The Amended Policies &amp; Rates will address such topics as the rates and fees associated with use of the Districts Amenities.


Specific legal authority for the adoption of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure and Amended Policies &amp; Rates includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes (2025). The specific laws implemented in the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 189.053, 189.069(2)(a)(15), 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011(3), 190.011(5), 190.011(15), 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0992, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes (2025).


A copy of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure and Amended Policies &amp; Rates and any material proposed to be incorporated by reference may be obtained by contacting Andy Mendenhall at the District Managers Office by mail at 2502 N. Rocky Point Drive, Suite 1000, Tampa, Florida 33607, by telephone at 813-565-4663, or by email at andy@hikai.com.


Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes,must do so in writing within twentyone (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.


This public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at a public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least three (3) business days prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1800-955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.


District Manager
Anthem Park Community Development District
November 27, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407599</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407055</link>
      <description>notice   A G E N D A  BOARD MEETING OF KISSIMMEE UTILITY AUTHORITY TO BE HELD WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 3, 2025 AT 3:30 PM, BRINSON BOARD ROOM, JAMES C

Meeting: WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 3, 2025 at 3:30 PM

--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   A G E N D A  BOARD MEETING OF KISSIMMEE UTILITY AUTHORITY TO BE HELD WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 3, 2025 AT 3:30 PM, BRINSON BOARD ROOM, JAMES C. WELSH ADMINISTRATION BUILDING, 1701 WEST CARROLL STREET, KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA  A. MEETING CALLED TO ORDER B. PLEDGE OF ALLEGIANCE TO THE FLAG C. APPROVAL OF AGENDA D. AWARDS AND PRESENTATIONS  1. FLORIDA MUNICIPAL ELECTRIC ASSOCIATION (FMEA) BUILDING STRONG COMMUNITIES AWARD  2. DEGREE RECOGNITION  TRACEY CORZO, CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST, CUSTOMER SERVICE, SOUTHERN NEW HAMPSHIRE UNIVERSITY, BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CONCENTRATION: LEADERSHIP  3. 15-YEAR SERVICE AWARD  CORY GLEE, ELECTRIC METER TECHNICIAN I, CUSTOMER SERVICE  4. 25-YEAR SERVICE AWARD  CHRIS REIGLE, APPLICATIONS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER, INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY  5. 25-YEAR SERVICE AWARD  JEF GRAY, VICE PRESIDENT OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY  6. EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH FOR DECEMBER 2025  HECTOR DE LOS SANTOS, INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SUPPORT SPECIALIST, INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY  E. HEAR THE AUDIENCE F. CONSENT AGENDA  1. APPROVAL OF MINUTES FOR NOVEMBER 5, 2025 BOARD MEETING 2. APPROVAL OF EXPENDITURE FOR THE ANNUAL CIS INFINITY SOFTWARE MAINTENANCE AND SUPPORT SERVICES 3. HELP NOW OF OSCEOLA SPONSORSHIP 4. KISSIMMEE VALLEY LIVESTOCK SHOW &amp; OSCEOLA COUNTY FAIR SPONSORSHIP  5. APPROVAL OF SUBORDINATION OF UTILITY INTEREST TO OSCEOLA COUNTY PLANNED UNIT DEVELOPMENT (PUD) LAKESIDE ESTATES  G. PUBLIC HEARING  1. UPDATES TO THE ELECTRIC SERVICE TARIFFS  H. INFORMATIONAL PRESENTATIONS (REQUIRING NO ACTION)  1. HELP NOW OF OSCEOLA  2. INFORMATIONAL UPDATE ON TERMINATION OF KUAS OWNERSHIP INTEREST IN STANTON ENERGY CENTER UNIT 1  I. OLD BUSINESS  J. NEW BUSINESS  1. FISCAL YEAR 2025 BUDGET AMENDMENT  2. APPROVAL OF KUAS STRATEGIC PLAN GOALS FOR CALENDAR YEAR 2026  3. APPROVAL OF AWARD FOR RFP 25-064-RM TO SPATIAL BUSINESS SYSTEMS FOR AUTOMATED UTILITY DESIGN SOFTWARE  4. APPROVAL OF ENGINEERING SERVICES TASK AWARD TO POWER ENGINEERS FOR RECONDUCTORING OF 69KV TRANSMISSION LINES 04-0410 AND 04-0710  K. STAFF REPORTS  1. FINANCE &amp; ADMINISTRATION - UNAUDITED YEAR END FINANCIAL STATEMENTS  L. HEAR ATTORNEY, GENERAL MANAGER, DIRECTORS  M. ADJOURNMENT  STATISTICAL REPORTS AND OTHER INFORMATIONAL ITEMS 1. CUSTOMER SERVICE REPORT 2. COPCA REPORT &amp; SALES 3. PENSION FUND INVESTMENT UPDATE 4. RELIABILITY REPORT 5. KUA IDENTITY THEFT PREVENTION PROGRAM POLICY ANNUAL REPORT 6. LINE EXTENSIONS 7. HUMAN RESOURCES DEMOGRAPHICS 8. ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT CONTRACTS 9. PURCHASE ORDERS 10. RATE COMPARISON 11. SPONSORSHIPS REPORT 12. BOARD CALENDAR 13. FLORIDA PROMPT PAYMENT ACT REPORT  IN ACCORDANCE WITH FLORIDA STATUTES 286.0105, ANY PERSON WISHING TO APPEAL ANY DECISION MADE BY THE KUA BOARD OF DIRECTORS WITH RESPECT TO ANY MATTER CONSIDERED AT SUCH MEETING OR HEARING WILL NEED A RECORD OF THE PROCEEDINGS, AND FOR SUCH PURPOSE MAY NEED TO ENSURE THAT VERBATIM RECORD OF THE PROCEEDINGS IS MADE, WHICH RECORD INCLUDES THE TESTIMONY AND EVIDENCE UPON WHICH THE APPEAL IS MADE. IN ACCORDANCE WITH FLORIDA STATUTES 286.26, PERSONS NEEDING ASSISTANCE TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY OF THESE PROCEEDINGS SHOULD CONTACT THE OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT AND GENERAL MANAGER, 1701 W CARROLL STREET, KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA, 34741, AND (407) 933-7777, EXT. 6100.   11/26/2025 7901708</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407055</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407048</link>
      <description>SEMINOLE COUNTY INDUSTRIAL DEVELOPMENT AUTHORITY  NOTICE OF SCHEDULING OF REGULAR MEETINGS   The Seminole County Industrial Development Authority (...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SEMINOLE COUNTY INDUSTRIAL DEVELOPMENT AUTHORITY  NOTICE OF SCHEDULING OF REGULAR MEETINGS   The Seminole County Industrial Development Authority (the Authority) has adopted the third Tuesday of each month (except November/December if it conflicts with holidays) as the day, 8:30 a.m. as the time, and the Seminole State College building at Heathrow, 1055 AAA Drive, Seminole County Economic Development Hub, Heathrow, FL 32746, as the place for its Regular Meetings to be held (on an as needed basis) as follows:  DATE TIME LOCATION January 20, 2026 8:30 a.m. Seminole County Economic Development Hub February 17, 2026   March 17, 2026   April 21, 2026   May 19, 2026   June 16, 2026   July 21, 2026   August 18, 2026   September 15, 2026   October 20, 2026   November 17, 2026   December 15, 2026     If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Authority with respect to any matter considered at a meeting of the Authority, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purposes, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  This Notice of Scheduling of Regular Meetings has been prepared and filed with the Board of County Commissioners of Seminole County, Florida in compliance with Section 189.417 (1) of the Florida Statutes.  SEMINOLE COUNTY INDUSTRIAL DEVELOPMENT AUTHORITY ESTEBAN SALDARRIAGA, SECRETARY IRMA STENMAN, ASSISTANT SECRETARY   11/26/2024 7901196</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407048</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407047</link>
      <description>Notice at 17404 Sixth Street

Location: 17404 Sixth Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing - Town of Montverde   The Town of Montverde Planning and Zoning Board will hold a public hearing on Wednesday, December 10, 2025, at 6:30 p.m., and the Town Council will hold a public hearing on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, at 7:00 p.m., at the Town Hall Auditorium located at 17404 Sixth Street, Montverde, Florida to deliberate on the following:  RESOLUTION 2025-199  A RESOLUTION OF THE TOWN COUNCIL OF THE TOWN OF MONTVERDE, FLORIDA, GRANTING MINOR SITE PLAN APPROVAL TO MONTVERDE ACADEMY FOR CONSTRUCTION OF PARKING IMPROVEMENTS ON ACADEMY LANE; PROVIDING FOR CONDITIONS; AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE  Interested parties may appear at the public hearings and be heard with respect to the proposed resolution.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in this proceeding should contact the Town Clerk at least 48 hours before the meetings at 407-469-2681. This resolution is available at the Town Clerks Office, at Town Hall located at 17404 Sixth Street, Montverde, Florida, for inspection on Monday through Thursday, from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.   Persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at this meeting, they will need a record of the proceeding, and for such purposes, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Paul Larino, Town Manager Town of Montverde11/26/2025 7901167</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407047</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11407046</link>
      <description>Notice at 17404 Sixth Street

Location: 17404 Sixth Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGS - TOWN OF MONTVERDE   The Town of Montverde Planning and Zoning Board will hold a public hearing on Wednesday, December 10, 2025, at 6:30 p.m., and the Town Council will hold a public hearing on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, at 7:00 p.m., at the Town Hall Auditorium located at 17404 Sixth Street, Montverde, Florida to deliberate on the following: RESOLUTION 2025-198  A RESOLUTION OF THE TOWN COUNCIL OF THE TOWN OF MONTVERDE, FLORIDA, GRANTING A VARIANCE FROM SECTION 10-81 IN CHAPTER 10 OF THE MONTVERDE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE FROM THE SIDE YARD SETBACK FOR REPLACEMENT OF AN EXISTING RETAINING WALL FOR THE REAL PROPERTY LOCATED AT 16319 MAGNOLIA BLUFF DRIVE, MONTVERDE, FLORIDA, OWNED BY JAMES P. MANAHAN AND DANEY C. ORDONEZ; PROVIDING FOR CONDITIONS; AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Interested parties may appear at the public hearings and be heard with respect to the proposed resolution.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in this proceeding should contact the Town Clerk at least 48 hours before the meetings at 407-469-2681. This resolution is available at the Town Clerks Office, at Town Hall located at 17404 Sixth Street, Montverde, Florida, for inspection on Monday through Thursday, from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.   Persons are advised that if they decide to appeal any decision made at this meeting, they will need a record of the proceeding, and for such purposes, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes.11/26/2025 7901163</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407046</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/44/11407044.pdf</link>
      <description>11/26/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Commission will hold a public hearing to consider ...

Meeting: Monday, December 8, 2025 at 5:30 p.m.

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/26/2025 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the Commission will hold a public hearing to consider the adoption of an ordinance entitled: ORDINANCE 25-1627  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, ACKNOWLEDGING THE TERMINATION AND DISSOLUTION OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AGENCY ON DECEMBER 11, 2025, PURSUANT TO THE TERMS OF THE SEMINOLE COUNTY RESOLUTION 2016-R-184; ACCEPTING THE CONVEYANCE OF REAL PROPERTY AND ANY TANGIBLE PERSONAL PROPERTY AND REMAINING FUNDS FROM THE AGENCY TO THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY IN FURTHERANCE OF THE AGENCYS TERMINATION AND DISSOLUTION; CREATING A CENTRAL CITY REINVESTMENT FUND FOR PURPOSES OF MAINTAINING THE REMAINING UNENCUMBERED FUNDS FROM THE COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT TRUST FUND IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE DELEGATION OF AUTHORITY RECEIVED FROM THE SEMINOLE COUNTY BOARD OF COMMISSIONERS; REPEALING CHAPTER 2, ARTICLE I, SECTION 2-5 AND ARTICLE IV, DIVISION 4  COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AGENCY OF THE CODE OF ORDINANCES OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA; AMENDING CHAPTER 14, ARTICLE III, SECTION 14-67 REGARDING PURPOSE AND FINDINGS RELATED TO REGULATION OF ADULT ENTERTAINMENT ESTABLISHMENTS TO RECOGNIZE THE TERMINATION AND DISSOLUTION OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AGENCY; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION WHERE DESIGNATED HEREIN, CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida as amended and supplemented. The Commission will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 25-1627 on Monday, December 8, 2025 at 5:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the Commission. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk and the same may be inspected by the public. Publish Date: November 26, 2025 Donna G. Gardner, CMC, FCPC  City Clerk  "Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes." "Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262-7700, Ext. 1150."  CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE  7899941</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407044</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407044.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/43/11407043.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL

Meeting: THURSDAY, DECEMBER 4, 2025 at 5:30 P.M.
Location: WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/26/2025 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS  NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN THAT THE CITY COMMISSION PROPOSE  TO CONSIDER THE FOLLOWING: ORDINANCE NO. 2025-17  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COMMISSION OF THE CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA; AMENDING CHAPTER 20, ZONING, ARTICLE V, SUPPLEMENTAL DISTRICT REGULATIONS, OF THE CITY OF WINTER SPRINGS CODE OF ORDINANCES TO ADD PROCEDURES FOR PROCESSING REQUESTS FOR REASONABLE ACCOMMODATION FROM THE CITYS LAND DEVELOPMENT REGULATIONS, WHICH SHALL ALSO BE APPLICABLE TO CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES IN ORDER TO COMPLY WITH FLORIDA STATUTES SECTION 397.487; AMENDING ARTICLE III, ESTABLISHMENT OF DISTRICTS, TO ESTABLISH CERTIFIED RECOVERY RESIDENCES AS PERMITTED OR CONDITIONAL USES IN CERTAIN ZONING DISTRICTS; PROVIDING FOR THE REPEAL OF PRIOR INCONSISTENT ORDINANCES AND RESOLUTIONS, INCORPORATION INTO THE CODE, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. PLANNING AND ZONING/LPA PUBLIC HEARINGS WILL BE HELD ON THURSDAY, DECEMBER 4, 2025 AT 5:30 P.M. OR SOON THEREAFTER IN THE COMMISSION CHAMBERS LOCATED AT WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL, 1126 EAST STATE ROAD 434, WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA CITY COMMISSION PUBLIC HEARINGS FOR FIRST READING WILL BE HELD ON MONDAY, DECEMBER 8, 2025 AT 6:30 PM OR SOON THEREAFTER IN THE COMMISSION CHAMBERS LOCATED AT WINTER SPRINGS CITY HALL, 1126 EAST STATE ROAD 434, WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA THE CITY COMMISSION RESERVES THE RIGHT TO POSTPONE OR CONTINUE THE PUBLIC HEARING ON THIS ORDINANCE AT THIS MEETING WITHOUT FURTHER NOTICE. The proposed ordinance may be obtained by interested parties between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m., Monday through Friday, from the office of the City Clerk, located at 1126 E. SR 434, Winter Springs, Florida. For more information, call (407) 327-1800 #237. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Employee Relations Department Coordinator, 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 327-1800, #236. This is a public hearing. Interested parties are advised that they may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed resolutions. If you decide to appeal any recommendation or decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at this meeting, you will need a  record of the proceedings, and for such purposes, you may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made upon which the appeal is based. 7899740 OAK FOREST ASSESSMENT AREA  WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA NOTICE OF HEARING TO INCREASE MAINTENANCE ASSESSMENT</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11407043</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11407043.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
