<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:29:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11495218</link>
      <description>Notice at 8 Broadway

Location: 8 Broadway

--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER EAST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater East Community Development District (District) will hold a Regular Meeting on March 20, 2026, at 9:00 a.m., at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., located at 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, http://edgewatereastcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
February 26, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11495218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11495205</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the South Lake Toho Community Development Di...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the South Lake Toho Community Development District (District) will hold a regular meeting on March 5, 2026, at 10:00 a.m., at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, First Floor, Room 120, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider any business which may properly come before it. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida law. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained by contacting the offices of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (561) 571-0010, during normal business hours.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (561) 571-0010 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
February 26, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11495205</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11495190</link>
      <description>Notice at 8 Broadway

Location: 8 Broadway

--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETINGS


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater West Community Development District (District), will hold a Regular Meeting on March 5, 2026, at 9:15 a.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741 for the purpose of considering any business that may be lawfully considered.


The Board will hold a Special Meeting on March 20, 2026, at 9:15 a.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., located at 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741 for the purpose of adopting a supplemental assessment resolution with delegated authority as well as consider any other business that may be lawfully considered.


The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meetings. A copy of the agenda for the meetings may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, https://edgewaterwestcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at the meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meetings with respect to any matter considered at the meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
February 26, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11495190</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11495182</link>
      <description>Notice at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard

Location: 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
THE WATER COOPERATIVE 
OF CENTRAL FLORIDA
NOTICE OF CANCELLATION 
OF BOARD MEETING
SCHEDULED FOR 
MARCH 4, 2026
The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Board of Supervisors meeting scheduled for March 4, 2026, has been cancelled. The next meeting of the Board of Supervisors is scheduled for April 1, 2026, at 2:00 PM and will be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Water Authority administration building located at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741. Contact Administration Office (t: 407-944-5130 or administrativeoffice@tohowater.com for further assistance.
February 26, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11495182</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11495181</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 1...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE RULES OF PROCEDURE OF THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its proposed Rules of Procedure (the Proposed Rule). The Proposed Rule number is 2026-1. Prior notice of rule development relative to the Proposed Rule was published in the Osceola News Gazette on February 19, 2026.


A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors (the Board) of the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) on April 2, 2026, at 10:00 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, First Floor, Room 120 - HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741, relative to the adoption of the Proposed Rule. Pursuant to Sections 190.011(5) and 190.012(3), Florida Statutes, the Proposed Rule will not require legislative ratification.


The purpose and effect of the Proposed Rule is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida Law. The specific grant of rulemaking authority for the adoption of the Proposed Rule includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes. The specific laws implemented in the Proposed Rule include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 120.542, 120.5435, 120.56, 120.69, 120.81, 189.053, 189.069, 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011, 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.012, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes.


A statement of estimated regulatory costs, as defined in Section 120.541(2), Florida Statutes, has not been prepared relative to the Proposed Rule. Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes, must do so in writing within twenty one (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office (as defined herein).


For more information regarding the public hearing, the Proposed Rule, or for a copy of the Proposed Rule and the related incorporated documents, if any, please contact the District Manager c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, torrese@whhassociates.com (the District Managers Office).


This public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at the public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the public hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this public hearing because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the public hearing. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1 800-955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.


Ernesto Torres, District Manager
South Lake Toho Community Development District

February 26, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11495181</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11488983</link>
      <description>HARMONY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors ( Board of the Harmony Commu...


--- Full Notice Text ---
HARMONY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF PUBLIC MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors ( Board of the Harmony Community Development District ( District will hold a regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors on February 26, 2026, at 6:00 p.m. , at the Su Mesa Caf at 7250 Harmony Sq Dr S, Harmony, FL 34773. A copy of the agenda for the meeting can be obtained from the District Office at PFM Group Consulting LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, FL 32817 or by phone at (407) 723-5900. Additionally, a copy of the agenda, along with any meeting materials available in an electronic format, may be obtained at https://harmonycdd.org/ 


The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law for community development districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Any person requiring special accommodations at the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Lynne Mullins
District Manager
February 19, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11488983</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/45/11487645.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Osceola County Planning Commission
Adoption of Ordinances
Osceola County, Florida



--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Osceola County Planning Commission
Adoption of Ordinances
Osceola County, Florida
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11487645</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11487645.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/57/11481057.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2026-03
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11481057</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11481057.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477262</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF CONSIDERATION OF BUDGET
AMENDMENT FOR
GREATER ORLANDO AVIATION AUTHORITY
Notice is hereby given pursuant to Orlando City Charter Chapter ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF CONSIDERATION OF BUDGET
AMENDMENT FOR
GREATER ORLANDO AVIATION AUTHORITY
Notice is hereby given pursuant to Orlando City Charter Chapter 16, Section 12, that on February 18, 2026, at 2:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as practicable, the Greater Orlando Aviation Authority Board will consider an amendment to its budget for Fiscal Year 2026 in the Aviation Authority Board room (Carl T. Langford Board Room) at One Jeff Fuqua Boulevard, Orlando, Florida 32827-4399.  A memorandum describing the budget amendment may be inspected on the Aviation Authoritys website following the posting of the agenda for the February 18, 2026, Board meeting. 
24784
2/6/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477262</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477251</link>
      <description>CITY OF EDGEWOOD NOTICE OF 
PUBLIC HEARING
SECOND AND FINAL READING OF ORDINANCE
On Tuesday, February 17, 2026, at 6:30 pm or as soon thereafter as...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF EDGEWOOD NOTICE OF 
PUBLIC HEARING
SECOND AND FINAL READING OF ORDINANCE
On Tuesday, February 17, 2026, at 6:30 pm or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, the Edgewood City Council will hold a Public Hearing in the City Hall Council Chamber, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL 32809, on the following ordinance:
ORDINANCE NO 2026-01
AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF EDGEWOOD, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 134 OF THE CODE OF ORDINANCES TO CORRECT A SCRIVENERS ERROR RELATED TO TATTOO ESTABLISHMENTS AND BODY PIERCING; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION, CONFLICTS, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.
Ordinances may be inspected by the public in the Office of the City Clerk, 405 Bagshaw Way, Edgewood, FL. 8 a.m. to 4 p.m. Monday - Thursday and 8 a.m. to 12 noon on Friday or send a request for an email copy to sriffle@edgewood-fl.gov. Interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the Ordinance. Persons wishing to appeal any decision made during the hearing will need a record of the proceedings and may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including the testimony and evidence on which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance or an interpreter to participate in this public hearing should contact Sandra Riffle, City Clerk, at (407) 8512920, at least 24 hours in advance of the meeting. 
21811
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477251</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11475868</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2026-01


Notice is hereby given that the Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on February 17, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:00 p.m., will consider the issue and make a recommendation to the City Council relative to enactment of Ordinance No. 2026-01 entitled:


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on March 12, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2026-01 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, ASSIGNING A FUTURE LAND USE DESIGNATION OF APPROXIMATELY +/- 20.39 ACRES IDENTIFIED AS NEOCITY SOUTH PHASE 1, PROJECT #CPA25-00018, GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF THE FUTURE NOLTE ROAD TURNPIKE INTERCHANGE, SOUTHEAST OF CROSS PRAIRIE PARKWAY AND WEST OF THE FLORIDAS TURNPIKE, FROM MDR MEDIUM DENSITY RESIDENTIAL TO IND INDUSTRIAL, PROVIDING FOR AMENDING THE OFFICIAL FUTURE LAND USE MAP OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, APPLICABILITY AND EFFECT, SEVERABILITY, COPIES ON FILE AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Christy Depuy, Planning Commission Secretary
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, FL 34769
Telephone: (407) 957-7297


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11475868</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11475864</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2026-04


Notice is hereby given that the Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on February 17, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:00 p.m., will consider the issue and make a recommendation to the City Council relative to enactment of Ordinance No. 2026-04 entitled:


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on March 12, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2026-04 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, ASSIGNING A FUTURE LAND USE DESIGNATION OF APPROXIMATELY +/- 5.26 ACRES IDENTIFIED AS BUR OAK BOULEVARD, PROJECT #CPA25-00013, GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF BUR OAK BOULEVARD, EAST OF TAY WES DRIVE, SOUTH OF EAST IRLO BRONSON MEMORIAL HIGHWAY, AND WEST OF LIVE OAK LAKE ROAD, FROM COM COMMERCIAL (COUNTY) TO COM COMMERCIAL (CITY), PROVIDING FOR AMENDING THE OFFICIAL FUTURE LAND USE MAP OF THE COMPREHENSIVE PLAN, FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, APPLICABILITY AND EFFECT, SEVERABILITY, COPIES ON FILE AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Christy Depuy, Planning Commission Secretary
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, FL 34769
Telephone: (407) 957-7297


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11475864</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11475834</link>
      <description>EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater Wes...


--- Full Notice Text ---
EDGEWATER WEST COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF MEETING


Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Edgewater West Community Development District (District), will hold a Special Meeting on February 18, 2026 at 9:00 a.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, at the offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, Inc., 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the meeting is for the Board to consider updated financing plans for the next bond issuance, as well as any business that may be lawfully considered. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provision of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (877) 276-0889, during normal business hours or by visiting the districts website, https://edgewaterwestcdd.net/.


There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors or staff will participate by telephone. Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (877) 276-0889 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made at the meeting with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


District Manager
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11475834</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11475823</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
ORDINANCE NO. 2026-05


Notice is hereby given that the Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on February 17, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:00 p.m., will consider the issue and make a recommendation to the City Council relative to enactment of Ordinance No. 2026-05 entitled:


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on March 12, 2026, in their Chamber at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Ordinance No. 2026-04 entitled:


AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, PROVIDING FOR THE ZONING AMENDMENT OF THE ZONING MAP OF THE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, SPECIFICALLY CHANGING THE ZONING DESIGNATION OF APPROXIMATELY +/- 5.26 ACRES IDENTIFIED AS BUR OAK BOULEVARD, PROJECT #PUD26-00001 FORMERLY ZMA25-00017, FROM PD PLANNED DEVELOPMENT (COUNTY) TO A PUD PLANNED UNIT DEVELOPMENT / PRELIMINARY MASTER PLAN (PUD/PMP ) (CITY) ZONING DESIGNATION, WITH A COMMERCIAL FUTURE LAND USE DESIGNATION ADOPTED BY ORDINANCE NO. 2026-04, GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF BUR OAK BOULEVARD, EAST OF TAY WES DRIVE, SOUTH OF EAST IRLO BRONSON MEMORIAL HIGHWAY, AND WEST OF LIVE OAK LAKE ROAD, PROVIDING FOR ENTERING THE DESIGNATION ON THE OFFICIAL ZONING MAP; FILING OF THE PLANNING COMMISSION RECOMMENDATION AND PROOF OF PUBLICATION, SEVERABILITY, AND EFFECTIVE DATE.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this ORDINANCE is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed ORDINANCE at the Public Hearing thereon. This ORDINANCE, in its entirety can be reviewed at the Community Development Department between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 4:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Christy Depuy, Planning Commission Secretary
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, FL 34769
Telephone: (407) 957-7297


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11475823</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/09/11474009.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2026-02
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud
Florida</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11474009</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11474009.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/08/11474008.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2026-02
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud
Florida</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11474008</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11474008.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/07/11474007.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Hearing
Ordinance No. 2026-03
Planning Commission of the City of St. Cloud
Florida</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11474007</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11474007.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477236</link>
      <description>PLANNING AND ZONING COMMISSION / LOCAL PLANNING AGENCY
PUBLIC HEARING AGENDA
February 19, 2026
DEAR PROPERTY OWNER OR INTERESTED PARTY:
At 9:00 a


--- Full Notice Text ---
PLANNING AND ZONING COMMISSION / LOCAL PLANNING AGENCY
PUBLIC HEARING AGENDA
February 19, 2026
DEAR PROPERTY OWNER OR INTERESTED PARTY:
At 9:00 a.m. on Thursday, February 19, 2026, or as soon thereafter as the matters may be considered, the Orange County Planning and Zoning Commission (PZC) / Local Planning Agency (LPA) shall hold a public hearing to consider the rezoning requests listed below and public hearing for an ordinance as described below.
Also, at 9:00 a.m. on Thursday, February 19, 2026, or as soon thereafter as the matters may be considered, the Orange County PZC / Local Planning Agency (LPA) shall hold public hearings to consider the adoption of Small-Scale Development Amendments to the Orange County Comprehensive Plan (CP), as authorized by Chapter 163, Florida Statutes and pursuant to Sections 163.3187(2) and 125.66, Florida Statutes.
PZC / LPA public hearings are held in the Board of County Commissioners Chambers located on the 1st Floor of the Orange County Administration Building, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. 
The staff report book and meeting agenda will also be available for public viewing on the Orange County website (www.orangecountyfl.net) one week prior to the public hearing.
Please be advised that this notice is published in accordance with the Orange County Code, Section 30-1(d)(6) and Section 30-40 as well as the provisions of the Orange County Comprehensive Plan and applicable state law.
Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.
In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), if any person with a disability as defined by the ADA needs special accommodations to participate in this proceeding, then not later than two (2) business days prior to the proceedings, he or she should contact the Government Service Center at (407) 836-3111.
Alberto A. Vargas 
Planning Manager
Para mas informacion referente a esta vista publica, favor comunicarse al Departamento de Planificacion al numero 407-836-5600.
Pou plis enfomasyon an Kreyol souple rele (407)836-3111.
                                                                                            AGENDA:
9:00 A.M.  Pledge of Allegiance, review of the January 15, 2026, PZC/LPA meeting minutes, and public comment.  The following public hearings will occur after public comment:
Privately Initiated Rezoning Request:
RZ-26-02-042
APPLICANT: Arthur Stagg  
OWNER: Arthur Stagg
REQUEST: To rezone from R-1A (Single-Family Dwelling District) to R-1 (Single-Family Dwelling District) 
LOCATION: 1111 Timor Ave; generally located north of W. Fairbanks Ave, west of Adanson Street, east of Fairview Ave, and south of Carlson Drive 
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 0.15 gross acres
DISTRICT: 5
RZ-26-02-044
APPLICANT: Aldo Maldonado
OWNER: Gold Millie Estate   
REQUEST: To rezone from A-2 (Farmland Rural District) to R-2 (Residential  District)
LOCATION: 7409 and 7429 Restful Street; generally located north of Restful Street, south of University Boulevard, east of Wilde Avenue, and west of Goldenrod Road 
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 1.96 gross acres
DISTRICT: 5
RZ-26-02-046
APPLICANT: Mohammad Rahman 
OWNER: Rahman Mohammad Sohel
REQUEST: To rezone from A-2 (Farmland Rural District) to I-1/I-5 (Industrial District-Light) 
LOCATION: 7152 Memory Lane; generally located south of Memory Lane, east of N. Forsyth Road, west of Greshan Drive, and north of Partridge Lane
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 0.38 gross acre
DISTRICT: 5
RZ-26-01-034
APPLICANT: Duc Hien Nguyen 
OWNER: Duc Hien Nguyen
REQUEST: To rezone from A-2 (Farmland Rural District) to R-2 (Residential District) 
LOCATION: 8206, 8224, and 8236 Curry Ford Road; generally located south of Curry Ford Road, east of Autumn Run Place, and west of Los Amigos Drive.
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 3.82 gross acres
DISTRICT: 3
RZ-26-01-038
APPLICANT: Ho Ho Van
OWNER: Nghia Nguyen
REQUEST: To rezone from R-T-2 (Combination Mobile Home and Single-Family Dwelling District) to R-T-1 (Mobile Home Subdivision District) 
LOCATION: 526 and 528 Shepard Road; generally north of Mercury Road, east of Story Partin Road, west of S. County Road 13, and south of E. Colonial Drive 
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 0.62 gross acre
DISTRICT: 5
Privately Initiated Small-Scale Future Land Use Element Map Amendments to Change the Designation of Lands within Unincorporated County, and Where Expressly Noted Below, Concurrent Rezoning Requests
SS-26-02-039 
APPLICANT: Lonnie Mack Caldwell, Caldwell Design Build, LLC 
OWNER: KHJ Investments, LLC   
REQUEST: To change the Future Land Use Map designation from Low Density Residential (LDR) to Low-Medium Density Residential (LMDR)
LOCATION: 6606 Winegard Road; generally located on the west side of Winegard Road, south of W. Lancaster Road, north of Orwell Avenue, and east of Beret Road 
LEGAL: Legal description on file in the Planning Division
TRACT SIZE: 0.83 gross acre
DISTRICT: 3
Public Hearing 
AN ORDINANCE PERTAINING TO THE BUILDING AND CONSTRUCTION REGULATIONS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA; AMENDING CERTAIN PROVISIONS OF CHAPTER 9 (BUILDING AND CONSTRUCTION REGULATIONS) OF THE ORANGE COUNTY CODE BY UPDATING SECTION 9-4 (BUILDING CODES BOARD OF ADJUSTMENTS AND APPEALS (BCBAA); CREATION; MEMBERSHIP; MEETINGS; QUORUM; POWERS AND DUTIES); AMENDING ARTICLE II (BUILDING CODE); BY REVISING SECTION 9-33 (FLORIDA BUILDING CODE, BUILDING, ADOPTED) AND SECTION 9-39 (FLORIDA BUILDING CODE, EXISTING BUILDING, ADOPTED) FOR CONSISTENCY; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.
22673
2/4/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477236</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477007</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee of the Sunbridge Stewardship District
Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 1:30 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee of the Sunbridge Stewardship District
Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 1:30 p.m.The Construction Committee of the Sunbridge Stewardship District will be meeting on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 1:30 p.m. at 6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd, Ste 200, Orlando, FL 32827. 
The Construction Committee will discuss and review the status of current and future Infrastructure Improvements, Requests for Qualifications, Requests for Proposals, etc., related to the District.  The meeting will be open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.
There may be occasions when one or more members of the Committee and/or District Staff will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at these meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at 407-723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.
Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that the person will need a record of the proceedings and that, accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.
Lynne Mullins
District Manager
7916159 
2/3/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477007</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477006</link>
      <description>Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee
of the Sunbridge Stewardship District
The Construction Committee of the Sunbridge Stew...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Meeting Dates of the Construction Committee
of the Sunbridge Stewardship District
The Construction Committee of the Sunbridge Stewardship District will be meeting on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 1:30 p.m. at 6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd, Ste 200, Orlando, FL 32827. 
The Construction Committee will discuss and review the status of current and future Infrastructure Improvements, Requests for Qualifications, Requests for Proposals, etc., related to the District.  The meeting will be open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.
There may be occasions when one or more members of the Committee and/or District Staff will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at these meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at 407-723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.
Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that the person will need a record of the proceedings and that, accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.
Lynne Mullins
District Manager
19591
2/3/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477006</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476996</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE
MetroPlan Orlando, The Metropolitan Planning Organization for the Orlando Urban Area, announces the following public meeting of the ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE
MetroPlan Orlando, The Metropolitan Planning Organization for the Orlando Urban Area, announces the following public meeting of the Transportation Disadvantaged Local Coordinating Board (TDLCB), to which all persons are invited:
Date: Thursday, February 12, 2026
Time: 10:00 a.m.
Place: MetroPlan Orlando
250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200
Orlando, FL 32801
Purpose: Regularly Scheduled TDLCB Meeting
A copy of the detailed agendas for these meetings may be obtained by contacting Ms. Rachel Frederick, Board Services Coordinator, MetroPlan Orlando, 250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200, Orlando, FL 32801, 407-481-5672, E-mail: 
Rachel.Frederick@MetroPlanOrlando.gov 
Public participation is conducted without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, age, disability, religion, or family status. Persons wishing to express concerns, who require special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act, or who require language services (free of charge) should contact MetroPlan Orlando by phone at (407) 481-5672 or by email at info@metroplanorlando.gov at least three business days prior to the event.
Anuncio de Reunin
MetroPlan Orlando  la organizacin de planificacin metropolitana (MPO) de los condados Orange, Osceola y Seminole  anuncia la siguiente hbrido reunin pblica de la Junta de Coordinacin Local para Personas con Desventaja de Transporte (TDLCB), la cual todos estn invitados: 
Dia: el jueves, 12 de febrero del 2026
Hora: 10:00 a.m.
Lugar: MetroPlan Orlando
250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200
Orlando, FL 32801
Propsito: Reunin Regularmente Programada
Para obtener copias de la agenda de esta reunin por favor contacten a la Sra. Rachel Frederick, asistente administrativa, MetroPlan Orlando, 250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200, Orlando, FL 32801, 407-481-5672, email: Rachel.Frederick@MetroPlanOrlando.gov 
La participacin pblica se lleva a cabo sin distincin de raza, color, origen nacional, sexo, edad, discapacidad, religin o estado familiar. Las personas que deseen expresar inquietudes, que requieran asistencia especial bajo la Ley de Americanos con Discapacidad (ADA) o que requieran servicios de traduccin (sin cargo) deben ponerse en contacto con MetroPlan Orlando por telfono (407) 481-5672 (marcar 0) o por correo electrnico info@metroplanorlando.gov por lo menos tres das antes del evento.
Publish Date:  Orlando Sentinel Legal Notices  Monday, February 2, 2026
21766
2/2/26</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476996</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476992</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT PLAN (CDP)
TEXT AMENDMENT
CITY OF MAITLAND, FLORIDA
The City Council of the City of Maitland, Fl...

Meeting: Monday, February 23, 2026 at 6:30 P.M.

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT PLAN (CDP)
TEXT AMENDMENT
CITY OF MAITLAND, FLORIDA
The City Council of the City of Maitland, Florida, proposes to adopt an ordinance to amend the CDP. The proposed CDP amendment ordinance #1446 is entitled:
AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF MAITLAND, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE CDP - FUTURE LAND USE ELEMENT, CORRIDOR DISTRICT, AREA OF SPECIAL CONSIDERATION  MAITLAND CONCOURSE NORTH, TABLE 1.1.3.11, MAITLAND CONCOURSE NORTH, PROPERTY OVERALL LAND USE MIX, LAND USE TYPE, AMENDING THE RESIDENTIAL USE TYPE TO CATEGORIZE EXISTING 350 UNITS AS MULTI-FAMILY UNITS AND TO ADD 85 TOWNHOMES TO THE RESIDENTIAL USE TYPE AND EXCLUDE RESIDENTIAL PARKING GARAGES FROM FLOOR AREA RATIO CALCULATIONS AND AMENDING STANDARD 1.1.3.10 TO EXCLUDE RESIDENTIAL PARKING GARAGES FROM FLOOR AREA RATIO CALCULATIONS, AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE.
A public hearing on the ordinance will be held by the City Council of the City of Maitland, Florida, on Monday, February 23, 2026 at 6:30 P.M., or as soon thereafter as is reasonably possible in the Maitland City Hall Council Chambers, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida 32751. The purpose of the public hearing is to take public comment, both written and oral, and to consider adoption of the ordinance to amend the City of Maitland (CDP), in accordance with F.S. 163, Part II.
A proposed amendment to the City of Maitlands Comprehensive Development Plan has been submitted by Kimley-Horn and Associates, Inc., 200 S. Orange Avenue., Suite 600, Orlando, Florida 32801. The property owner is BPL Maitland Concourse North, LLC., P.O. Box 3010, Winter Park, Florida 32790. 
The applicant requests a text amendment to the CDP - Future Land Use Element, Corridor District, Area of Special Consideration  Maitland Concourse North, Table 1.1.3.11, Maitland Concourse North, Property Overall Land Use Mix, Land Use Type to recognize the existing 350 units as multi-family and to add 85 townhomes to the residential use type; and to exclude residential parking garages from floor area ratio calculations.
A complete copy of the ordinance and proposed CDP Amendment may be inspected by any interested person, Monday-Thursday, 7:00 A.M.- 6:00 P.M., in the Community Development Department, 1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida 32751. Interested parties may attend the public hearing to be heard by the City Council or may submit written comments at or before the public hearing to the attention of the Community Development Department of the City of Maitland, Florida. Questions concerning the notice of public hearing may be directed to the Community Development Department at (407) 539-6212. The hearing may be continued from time to time.
Please be advised that in accordance with State Law, any person who desires to appeal any decision made at these meetings or hearings will need a record of the proceedings and, for this purpose, may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disability needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerk's office (407) 539-6219 48 hours in advance of the meeting.
Sara Blanchard
Chief Planner
City of Maitland
21429
2/2/26</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476992</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471581</link>
      <description>Notice at cityofwinterpark

Location: cityofwinterpark

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICENotice is hereby given that a public hearing will be held by the City Commission of the City of Winter Park, Florida, on Wednesday, February 11, 2026, at 3:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter at Winter Park City Hall at 401 S. Park Avenue, Winter Park, Florida. In lieu of physically attending in person, members of the public may participate in this meeting by attending virtually by following the instructions located at cityofwinterpark.org/government/board-public-meetings/. You may contact the City Clerks Office at 407-599-3277 for assistance in setting up virtual attendance of the meeting.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 2, ARTICLE III, OF THE CITY CODE RELATING TO SUBSIDIARY BOARDS OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK; AMENDING SECTIONS 2-46 THROUGH 2-2-49 TO REVISE GENERAL PROVISIONS GOVERNING THE ESTABLISHMENT, APPOINTMENT, TERMS, PROCEDURES, AND OPERATIONS OF CITY BOARDS AND AD HOC COMMITTEES; AMENDING SECTIONS 2-62, 2-63, 2-64, 2-65, 2-67, AND 2-74 TO REVISE AND CLARIFY THE COMPOSITION, DUTIES, AND PROCEDURES OF CERTAIN ADVISORY BOARDS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.   AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, APPROVING THE TERMINATION OF THE DISTRIBUTION EASEMENT RECORDED AT OFFICIAL RECORDS BOOK 3941, PAGE 4149 WITHIN THE BOUNDARIES OF THE PROPERTY LOCATED AT 817  ANTONETTE AVENUE AND HAVING ORANGE COUNTY TAX PARCEL NUMBER 07-22-30-1490-02-090; AND AUTHORIZING THE EXECUTION AND RECORDING OF THE NECESSARY TERMINATION OF EASEMENT INSTRUMENT; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS,  SEVERABILITY, AN EFFECTIVE DATE AND RECORDING.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, APPROVING AND AUTHORIZING THE LEASE OF CERTAIN REAL PROPERTY LOCATED AT 947, 955, 959 WEST FAIRBANKS AVENUE TO COLLANTES HOLDINGS, LLC FOR USE AS A RESTAURANT, PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  All interested parties are invited to attend and be heard. Additional information is available on the Citys website at www.cityofwinterpark.org so that citizens may acquaint themselves with each issue.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he/she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he/she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  (F.S. 286.0105)   Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office (407-599-3277) at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  /s/ Rene S. Cranis, City Clerk   2/1/2026 7925661</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471581</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471544</link>
      <description>notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, at 2 pm at Sumter County Service Center, 7375 Powell Road, Room 102, Wildwood, FL. 7920345 2/01/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471544</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471543</link>
      <description>notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, at 2 pm at Sumter County Service Center, 7375 Powell Road, Room 102, Wildwood, FL.   2/01/2026 7920345</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471543</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/42/11471542.pdf</link>
      <description>7916873 2/1/2026 NOTICE BY ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM ASSESSME...


--- Full Notice Text ---
7916873 2/1/2026 NOTICE BY ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM ASSESSMENT  The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will hold a public hearing on February 10, 2026 at 2 p.m., at the Orange County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida.  You are invited to attend and be heard regarding a request to consider the adoption of a Resolution authorizing the Orange County Board of County Commissioners to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem assessments levied by the Orange County Board of County Commissioners as provided in Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.  IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS PUBLIC HEARING NOTICE, CONTACT ORANGE COUNTY COMPTROLLER SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS  407-836-5770  E-MAIL: Special.Assessments@occompt.com  SI USTED TIENE ALGUNA PREGUNTA REFERENTE A ESTA VISTA PBLICA, FAVOR DE COMUNICARSE CON LAS OFICINAS DE FINANZAS DEL CONDADO ORANGE, AL NUMERO DE TELEFONO  407-836-5715  Notice is hereby given to all owners of lands located within the boundaries of Orange County Florida that the Orange County Board of County Commissioners intends to use the uniform method for collection of non-ad valorem assessments levied by the Orange County Board of County Commissioners as set forth in Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.  Take notice that pursuant to the provisions of Section 125.01 (1) (q), Florida Statutes, the Orange County Board of County Commissioners of Orange County, Florida, has received requests for the establishment and / or amendments of Municipal Service Benefit Units (MSBU's) for all the listed properties encompassing the boundaries as set forth in the detailed attachment.  The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will hold public hearings to consider resolutions at a future date and which may adopt the MSBU's in accordance with Section 197.3632, and Section 125.01 (1) (q), Florida Statutes.  The purpose of this public hearing is not to impose a rate or levy an assessment, but rather to consider the adoption of a Resolution authorizing the Board to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem assessments.  Interested parties may appear at the Public Hearing to be heard regarding the use of the uniform method of collecting such non-ad valorem assessments.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting, you will need a record of the proceedings.  You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-3111 no later than two (2) business days prior to the hearing for assistance.  Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Americanos con Incapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  The information contained in this Notice is correct and accurate to the best of our knowledge as of this date.  The properties subject to the proposed resolution are listed in Exhibit A and Exhibit B hereto.   Phil Diamond As Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida   Publish:	January 11, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  January 18, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  January 25, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  February 1, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)   Certify:		MSBU for Notice of Intent Public Hearing  c:	All Board Members Offices (e-mail) 	County Attorneys Office, BCC (e-mail to Angela Diaz) 	Jon Weiss, Deputy County Administrator, BCC (e-mail) 	Ann Curtis, Special Assessments (e-mail) 	Cheryl Gillespie, Agenda Development (e-mail) 	Mike Seif, Orange TV, BCC (e-mail) James Jerome, Program Coordinator, BCC (e-mail)Notice of Intent  November 2026 Exhibit A  Subdivision Name(s)  MSBU Description  Plat Book / Page(s) Section Township Range  Property Boundaries Avalon Woods Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 118/121-128 17-23-27 Lots 1-182 Hamlin Meadows at Hamlin  Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/66-72 30-23-27 Lots 1-165 Tract FD-1 Future Development Harvest at Ovation Area Harvest at Ovation Phase 2 Harvest at Ovation Phase 3A   Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  117/82-85 119/83-88  29-24-27 29-24-27  Lots 167-232 Lots 233-306 Lake Roberts / Lake Reaves Watercrest at Windermere Amend Lake Maintenance  118/50-55  01-23-27  Lots 19-24 Lake Star at Ovation Area Lake Star at Ovation Phase  1B Amend Streetlighting  Retention Pond Maintenance  119/23-28  19-24-27  Lots 56-115 Lakeview Pointe at Horizon West Area, Ravenna Area and Mezzano Shoppes at Lakeview Amend Streetlighting 118/10-11   34-23-27   Lot 1 Lakeview Pointe at Horizon West Area, Ravenna Phase 3 Shoppes at Lakeview Amend Retention Pond   118/10-11   34-23-27   Lot 1 Northlake at Ovation Area Northlake at Ovation Phase 2 and 3 Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  119/60-63  19-24-27  Lots 186-290 Sagewood Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/126-129 02-21-28 Lots 1-71 Serenade at Ovation Area Serenade at Ovation Phase 3 Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/113-116 30-24-27 Lots 121-227 Silverleaf Area Silverleaf Oaks at Hamlin Phase 3B Amending Streetlighting119/1-12  30-23-27  Lots 529-766 Silverleaf Area Silverleaf Oaks at Hamlin Phase 3B Hamlin Meadows at Hamlin Amending Retention Pond  119/01-12 119/66-72  30-23-27 30-23-27  Lots 529-766 Lots 1-165 Tract FD-1 Future Development Stoneybrook Hills Master Road Foothills at Mount Dora Phase 4-2 Amend Streetlighting  118/32-43  03-20-27  Lots 126-226 Watercrest at WindermereEstablish Streetlighting Retention Pond 118/50-55 01-23-27 Lots 1-41 Waterleigh Area Waterleigh Kiddie Academy Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  113/57-58  07-24-27  Lot 1 Wekiva Springs Cove Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 117/105-106 01-21-28 Lots 1-13 Woodside Preserve  Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 117/54-57 25-22-30 Lots 1-53 World Design Center Area World Design Center Phase 3 Parcel 1 Replat World Design Center Phase 3 Parcel 5 Replat Amend  Retention Pond  115/18-20 115/48-53  33-23-29 04-24-29  Lots 1B and 1C Lots 5A, 5B, and 5D Yucatan Gardens Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/64-65 27-22-30 Lots 1-52 Notice of Intent 2026 Establish Lot Cleaning Exhibit B LC 24-0256 24-22-28-6164-06-010 LC 25-0002 24-24-29-6000-26-130 LC 25-0005 26-24-29-0000-00-005 LC 25-0006 11-23-30-6851-00-005 LC 25-0007 18-22-31-1200-00-490 LC 25-0008 30-22-29-9228-17-050 LC 25-0032 24-22-31-1052-03-030 LC 25-0037 03-22-29-0552-01-180 LC 25-0039 25-22-28-1812-03-441 LC 25-0040 07-22-29-5566-01-260 LC 25-0043 15-21-28-0932-02-050 LC 25-0049 10-23-29-0296-00-171 LC 25-0061 36-24-29-6723-00-400 LC 25-0062 12-22-30-3378-02-040 LC 25-0066 25-22-28-1812-06-361 LC 25-0068 19-22-29-6976-08-100 LC 25-0069 24-21-28-5076-00-091 LC 25-0070 19-22-29-0000-00-041 LC 25-0074 36-22-28-6416-04-230 LC 25-0076 17-22-29-7802-00-870 LC 25-0080 13-22-28-8058-00-040 LC 25-0081 03-23-29-0183-10-170 LC 25-0082 03-23-29-0183-10-180 LC 25-0083 27-23-29-8085-02-200 LC 25-0086 21-22-30-7204-15-111 LC 25-0087 02-21-28-8308-00-061 LC 25-0090 15-23-30-5306-01-200 LC 25-0091 16-21-28-0000-00-059 LC 25-0092 22-22-32-0712-19-600 LC 25-0093 14-22-28-0000-00-018 LC 25-0095 34-22-33-1327-03-030 LC 25-0097 07-23-30-9492-04-010 LC 25-0098 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0101 12-22-28-7413-09-010 LC 25-0102 03-22-29-8476-04-150 LC 25-0104 03-23-29-0180-19-040 LC 25-0105 03-22-29-8476-04-190 LC 25-0107 03-23-29-0180-41-110 LC 25-0108 30-24-30-4950-10-000 LC 25-0111 15-23-29-0146-00-040 LC 25-0112 21-22-32-0734-00-870 LC 25-0114 06-22-29-2450-02-090 LC 25-0115 36-22-28-6416-02-115 LC 25-0116 33-21-29-0899-00-860 LC 25-0117 18-22-31-0232-02-920 LC 25-0120 07-22-29-6974-04-090 LC 25-0121 21-22-30-3932-17-230 LC 25-0122 19-22-31-0000-00-024 LC 25-0124 16-23-29-9430-01-290 LC 25-0125 13-22-28-8058-00-460 LC 25-0126 10-23-29-7434-12-010 LC 25-0127 01-22-28-2858-00-040 LC 25-0128 03-23-29-0182-95-110 LC 25-0129 03-23-29-0182-94-240 LC 25-0131 10-23-29-7420-05-120 LC 25-0134 30-22-29-9228-16-060 LC 25-0135 03-23-29-0180-27-170 LC 25-0136 03-23-29-0183-15-030 LC 25-0138 27-22-28-4880-01-210 LC 25-0139 10-23-29-0000-00-039 LC 25-0140 25-22-28-4484-01-060 LC 25-0141 13-22-28-8058-00-040 LC 25-0142 12-22-28-7051-07-140 LC 25-0143 18-22-31-8744-02-231 LC 25-0148 26-22-30-0000-00-086 LC 25-0149 21-22-29-2540-03-010 LC 25-0151 36-20-27-9612-02-040 LC 25-0153 14-23-28-3552-00-120 LC 25-0157 06-24-30-7268-00-310 LC 25-0158 24-22-28-6164-06-010 LC 25-0159 32-21-29-6080-00-062 LC 25-0162 15-22-28-4716-00-152 LC 25-0163 34-22-29-8748-01-100 LC 25-0164 02-22-29-8472-02-180 LC 25-0166 12-22-28-0000-00-003 LC 25-0167 19-22-31-3887-00-002 LC 25-0168 02-22-29-8472-02-190 LC 25-0169 14-21-28-0000-00-043 LC 25-0171 01-23-29-3834-00-740 LC 25-0173 07-22-29-5564-00-210 LC 25-0174 18-22-29-8509-02-090 LC 25-0175 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0176 24-22-28-0000-00-078 LC 25-0177 25-22-28-1810-06-020 LC 25-0180 03-23-29-3292-00-040 LC 25-0181 01-21-27-0000-00-038 LC 25-0182 18-22-30-4748-00-010 LC 25-0185 14-21-28-2590-05-030 LC 25-0187 24-22-28-0614-04-080 LC 25-0191 20-23-29-1137-02-070 LC 25-0192 03-23-29-0180-72-170 LC 25-0193 07-22-29-6936-01-390 LC 25-0195 15-21-28-0932-03-250 LC 25-0196 15-21-28-0000-00-045 LC 25-0198 15-21-28-0932-02-050 LC 25-0200 02-22-29-2996-06-070 LC 25-0204 27-23-29-0000-00-056 LC 25-0208 30-21-29-1832-06-200 LC 25-0209 16-21-28-0000-00-088 LC 25-0210 16-21-28-0000-00-172 LC 25-0212 34-22-33-1327-03-110 LC 25-0213 34-22-33-1327-03-100 LC 25-0214 22-22-32-0712-41-039 LC 25-0215 25-23-29-8486-02-080 LC 25-0220 22-24-29-2982-00-360 LC 25-0221 19-22-31-0000-00-024 LC 25-0225 21-21-28-0020-00-100 LC 25-0227 09-21-28-0197-10-241 LC 25-0228 09-21-28-0197-10-321 LC 25-0231 26-22-28-2894-01-165 LC 25-0232 25-22-28-4484-03-240 LC 25-0240 34-23-27-0000-00-017 LC 25-0242 22-22-32-0712-19-600 LC 25-0243 34-22-33-1327-02-350 LC 25-0245 07-22-29-6974-04-090 LC 25-0247 10-23-29-6152-04-210 LC 25-0248 24-22-30-8240-00-070 LC 25-0249 18-22-29-9580-05-210 LC 25-0254 35-21-28-1408-00-020 LC 25-0255 21-22-30-4316-04-010 LC 25-0257 19-22-29-6960-02-010 LC 25-0261 15-24-28-6186-03-001 LC 25-0264 03-23-29-1402-06-140 LC 25-0266 36-20-27-0000-00-084 LC 25-0267 03-23-29-7436-07-030 LC 25-0268 18-22-29-2534-05-210 LC 25-0269 19-22-29-6978-15-050 LC 25-0271 20-23-29-1162-01-170 LC 25-0276 03-23-29-0182-96-011 LC 25-0277 03-23-29-7435-03-030 LC 25-0278 01-22-28-9484-00-080 LC 25-0279 28-21-29-7476-05-140 LC 25-0281 03-23-29-0180-06-050 LC 25-0287 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0290 29-21-29-2386-02-140 LC 25-0296 34-22-29-1382-02-110 LC 25-0297 15-23-29-0000-00-091 LC 25-0298 12-22-28-7051-07-140 LC 25-0301 13-22-28-8058-00-460 LC 25-0304 25-22-28-1812-03-441 LC 25-0305 03-23-29-0182-74-100 LC 25-0307 14-23-28-4658-00-190 LC 25-0308 18-22-30-4748-00-010 LC 25-0309 06-23-30-5364-00-040 LC 25-0312 17-22-31-0000-00-010 LC 25-0313 03-23-29-7430-01-310 LC 25-0315 03-23-29-0180-72-170 LC 25-0321 25-22-30-6836-01-140 LC 25-0327 24-23-29-3400-00-112 LC 25-0329 22-22-27-1084-02-020 LC 25-0331 26-22-28-9218-00-040 LC 25-0333 25-22-28-1812-06-361 LC 25-0334 36-22-28-6416-04-180 LC 25-0340 01-22-28-2860-00-130 LC 25-0366 19-22-31-3887-00-002 LC 25-0372 12-22-30-3378-02-040 LC 25-0373 05-23-30-1624-04-150 LC 25-0387 01-24-29-8516-81-103 LC 25-0393 21-22-30-4312-11-081 LC 25-0394 14-22-30-8646-01-200 LC 25-0395 17-22-31-7775-02-390 LC 25-0412 02-23-30-6424-00-050 LC 25-0429 14-23-28-3552-00-120 LC 25-0430 08-20-27-8559-02-120  7916873 ORANGE COUNTY NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING Orange County</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471542</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11471542.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471538</link>
      <description>Notice at cityofwinterpark

Location: cityofwinterpark

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICENotice is hereby given that a public hearing will be held by the City Commission of the City of Winter Park, Florida, on Wednesday, February 11, 2026, at 3:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter at Winter Park City Hall at 401 S. Park Avenue, Winter Park, Florida. In lieu of physically attending in person, members of the public may participate in this meeting by attending virtually by following the instructions located at cityofwinterpark.org/government/board-public-meetings/. You may contact the City Clerks Office at 407-599-3277 for assistance in setting up virtual attendance of the meeting.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 2, ARTICLE III, OF THE CITY CODE RELATING TO SUBSIDIARY BOARDS OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK; AMENDING SECTIONS 2-46 THROUGH 2-2-49 TO REVISE GENERAL PROVISIONS GOVERNING THE ESTABLISHMENT, APPOINTMENT, TERMS, PROCEDURES, AND OPERATIONS OF CITY BOARDS AND AD HOC COMMITTEES; AMENDING SECTIONS 2-62, 2-63, 2-64, 2-65, 2-67, AND 2-74 TO REVISE AND CLARIFY THE COMPOSITION, DUTIES, AND PROCEDURES OF CERTAIN ADVISORY BOARDS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.   AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, APPROVING THE TERMINATION OF THE DISTRIBUTION EASEMENT RECORDED AT OFFICIAL RECORDS BOOK 3941, PAGE 4149 WITHIN THE BOUNDARIES OF THE PROPERTY LOCATED AT 817  ANTONETTE AVENUE AND HAVING ORANGE COUNTY TAX PARCEL NUMBER 07-22-30-1490-02-090; AND AUTHORIZING THE EXECUTION AND RECORDING OF THE NECESSARY TERMINATION OF EASEMENT INSTRUMENT; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS,  SEVERABILITY, AN EFFECTIVE DATE AND RECORDING.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, APPROVING AND AUTHORIZING THE LEASE OF CERTAIN REAL PROPERTY LOCATED AT 947, 955, 959 WEST FAIRBANKS AVENUE TO COLLANTES HOLDINGS, LLC FOR USE AS A RESTAURANT, PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  All interested parties are invited to attend and be heard. Additional information is available on the Citys website at www.cityofwinterpark.org so that citizens may acquaint themselves with each issue.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he/she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he/she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  (F.S. 286.0105)   Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office (407-599-3277) at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  /s/ Rene S. Cranis, City Clerk   2/1/2026 7925661</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471538</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471502</link>
      <description>notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, at 2 pm at Sumter County Service Center, 7375 Powell Road, Room 102, Wildwood, FL. 7920345 2/01/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471502</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471501</link>
      <description>notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the Districts 5 &amp; 24 Medical Examiner Advisory Committee will hold a meeting on Thursday, February 19, 2026, at 2 pm at Sumter County Service Center, 7375 Powell Road, Room 102, Wildwood, FL.   2/01/2026 7920345</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471501</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/73/11469273.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 380 STATE ROAD 436

Location: 380 STATE ROAD 436

--- Full Notice Text ---
1/29/2026 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the City Commission will hold a public hearing to consider the enactment of an ordinance entitled:  ORDINANCE 26-1629  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, PROVIDING FOR THE AMENDMENT OF THE PLANNED UNIT DEVELOPMENT (PUD) AGREEMENT AND CONCEPT PLAN FOR THE ICON COMMONS PUD ESTABLISHED VIA ORDINANCE NO. 21-1553 AND NO. 23-1582, FOR ONE PARCEL, TOTALING APPROXIMATELY 1.04 ACRES, LOCATED AT 380 STATE ROAD 436, AS DESCRIBED IN SECTION I OF THIS ORDINANCE; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The property is known as:  Parcel ID Number Address 17-21-30-537-0000-0010 380 S.R. 436  *Insert Map Here*  This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, and the Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida, as amended and supplemented. The City Commission will consider the proposed Ordinance on Monday, February 9, 2026, at 5:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until the Commission takes final action. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk, and the same may be inspected by the public. Publish Date: January 29, 2026 Donna G. Gardner, CMC, City Clerk Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262- 7700, Ext. 1150.  7923670 CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING  TO CONSIDER ZONING MAP AMENDMENT</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469273</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11469273.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/72/11469272.pdf</link>
      <description>1/29/2026 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the City Commission will hold a public hearing to consi...

Meeting: Monday, February 9, 2026 at 5:30 p.m.

--- Full Notice Text ---
1/29/2026 TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN: NOTICE IS GIVEN by the City of Casselberry, Florida, that the City Commission will hold a public hearing to consider adoption of the following ordinance:  ORDINANCE 26-1628  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 86, UTILITIES, ARTICLE II, SEWERS, AND ARTICLE III, WATER, TO ESTABLISH NEW SEWER, WATER, AND RECLAIMED WATER FEES AND CHARGES FOR ALL RESIDENTIAL, COMMERCIAL AND MULTIFAMILY RESIDENTIAL SEWER, WATER, AND RECLAIMED WATER SERVICE PROVIDED BY THE CITY OF CASSELBERRY; PROVIDING FOR ANNUAL ADJUSTMENT OF RATES; CHANGING REFERENCES FROM THE PUBLIC WORKS DEPARTMENT TO THE UTILITIES DEPARTMENT WHERE APPLICABLE; AMENDING ANNEXATION REQUIREMENTS TO RECEIVE WATER AND SEWER SERVICE OUTSIDE CITY LIMITS; MODIFYING PROVISIONS RELATED TO DEPOSIT REFUNDS; ELIMINATING THE 60 DAY EFFECTIVE DATE FOR ADJUSMENTS FOR THE BASE SEWER VARIABLE RATE FLOW CHARGE; UPDATING PROVISIONS RELATED TO THE INSTALLATION, USE, AND PAYMENT FOR PUBLIC FIRE HYDRANTS; AMENDING REGULATIONS RELATED TO WATER IRRIGATION USE RESTRICTIONS AND EMERGENCY RESTRICTIONS ON WATER USE; MAKING ADDITIONAL HOUSEKEEPING AMENDMENTS; PROVIDING FOR CODIFICATION, CONFLICTS, SEVERABILITY AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. This notice is pursuant to the provisions of Chapter 166, Florida Statutes, and the Charter and Ordinances of the City of Casselberry, Florida, as amended and supplemented. The City Commission will consider adoption of Ordinance 26-1628 on Monday, February 9, 2026 at 5:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Casselberry City Hall Commission Chambers, 95 Triplet Lake Drive, Casselberry, Florida. At the meeting, interested parties may appear and be heard with respect to the proposed Ordinance. This hearing may be continued from time to time until final action is taken by the City Commission. Copies of the proposed Ordinance are available at City Hall with the City Clerk and the same may be inspected by the public. Publish Date: January 29, 2026 Donna G. Gardner, CMC, City Clerk Persons are advised that, if they decide to appeal any decision made at these meetings/hearings, they will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose, they may need to insure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, per Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes. Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the A.D.A. Coordinator 48 hours in advance of the meeting at (407) 262-7700 Ext. 1150.  7923669 CITY OF CASSELBERRY, FLORIDA NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING TO CONSIDER ADOPTION OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469272</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11469272.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469132</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION OF PRIVILEGES RULE OF THE ANTHEM PARK COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DIST...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING REGARDING THE AMENDED AND RESTATED SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION OF PRIVILEGES RULE OF THE ANTHEM PARK COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors of the Anthem Park Community Development District (District) on March 4, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Anthem Park Clubhouse, 2090 Continental St., St. Cloud, Florida 34769.


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt its proposed Amended and Restated Suspension and Termination of Privileges Rule, Rule No. 3. The purpose and effect of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. Prior notice of rule development was published in the Osceola News-Gazette on January 22, 2026.


The Amended and Restated Suspension and Termination of Privileges Rule will address such topics as the consequences for violating the Districts Amenities &amp; Policies.


Specific legal authority for the adoption of the proposed Amended and Restated Suspension and Termination of Privileges Rule includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes (2025). The specific laws implemented in the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 189.053, 189.069(2)(a)(15), 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011(3), 190.011(5), 190.011(15), 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0992, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes (2025).


A copy of the proposed Amended and Restated Suspension and Termination of Privileges Rule and any material proposed to be incorporated by reference may be obtained by contacting Andy Mendenhall at the District Managers Office by mail at 2502 N. Rocky Point Drive, Suite 1000, Tampa, Florida 33607, by telephone at 813-565-4663, or by email at andy@hikai.com.


Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes,must do so in writing within twentyone (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.


This public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at a public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least three (3) business days prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1800-955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.


District Manager
Anthem Park Community
 Development District
January 29, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469132</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469109</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING
RESOLUTION NO. 2026-003R


Notice is hereby given that the City Council of the City of St. Cloud, Florida, at a meeting to be held on February 12, 2026, in the Council Chambers at City Hall, 1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida at 6:30 p.m., will consider the adoption of Resolution No. 2026-003R entitled:


A RESOLUTION OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ST. CLOUD, FLORIDA, GRANTING A SITE VARIANCE (#VAR25-00001) TO REDUCE REQUIRED OPEN SPACE FROM APPROXIMATELY +/- .048 ACRES TO +/- .017 ACRES ON THE PREVIOUSLY APPROVED SITE DEVELOPMENT PLAN IN THE HIGHWAY BUSINESS HB ZONING DISTRICT ON THE +/- 5.94 ACRES OF LAND KNOWN AS NARCOOSSEE COMMONS SOUTH (# 18-75.04); ALLOWING THE OPEN COURTYARD BETWEEN UNITS 1386 AND 1388 TO ACT AS AN OUTDOOR PLAY SPACE FOR ADVENTURE WORLD KIDS A CHILD CARE CENTER, AS DESCRIBED IN THE BODY OF THIS RESOLUTION.


Interested parties may appear at the meeting at which time this RESOLUTION is to be considered and shall be heard with respect to the proposed RESOLUTION at the Public Hearing thereon. This RESOLUTION in its entirety can be reviewed at the City Clerk's office between the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 2:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m. Monday through Friday.


If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee/Board, with respect to any matter considered at such hearing/meeting, such person will need a record of the proceedings and that, for this purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based, and which record is not provided by the City of St. Cloud. (FS 286.0105)


In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Secretary/Clerk of the Committee/Board (listed below), prior to the meeting. (FS 286.26)


Ivy Llauro, City Clerk
1300 9th Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769
Telephone: 407-957-7300
January 29, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469109</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11467695</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING   OSCEOLA COUNTY HOUSING FINANCE AUTHORITYA meeting of the Members of the Osceola County Housing Finance Authority will be held o...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING   OSCEOLA COUNTY HOUSING FINANCE AUTHORITYA meeting of the Members of the Osceola County Housing Finance Authority will be held on February 6, 2026 at 1:00 pm at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 E. Dakin Avenue, Room 120, Kissimmee, FL 34741. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law. A copy of the meeting agenda may be obtained from the Authoritys Manager at 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801. This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.  There may be occasions when one or more Members, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone.Any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the Authority Office at (407) 841-5524 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the Authority Office.  George S. Flint Authority Manager Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC 7924470 1/28/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11467695</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11466171</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING  PRESTON COVE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTA regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Preston Cove Community Developme...

Meeting: Tuesday, February 3, 2026 at 10:30 AM

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING  PRESTON COVE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTA regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Preston Cove Community Development District will be held on Tuesday, February 3, 2026 at 10:30 AM, at the Offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, FL 34741. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  A copy of the agenda for this meeting may be obtained from the Districts website: https://prestoncovecdd.com/ or from the District Manager at 219 East Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801; (407) 841-5524. This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone.  Pursuant to the provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this meeting is asked to advise the District Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting by contacting the District Manager at (407) 841-5524. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jeremy LeBrun Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC District Manager   1/27/26 7924304</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11466171</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11466164</link>
      <description>NOTICE TO TAXING AUTHORITIES ANDNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGNotice is hereby given in accordance with the provisions of Section 163


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE TO TAXING AUTHORITIES ANDNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGNotice is hereby given in accordance with the provisions of Section 163.346, Florida Statutes, as amended, that the City Council of the City of Orlando, Florida (the City Council) will consider the adoption of a resolution approving and authorizing the issuance of redevelopment revenue bonds by the Community Redevelopment Agency of the City of Orlando, Florida (the Agency) under Section 163.385, Florida Statutes, in one or more series including, but not limited to, the issuance by the Agency of its Tax Increment Revenue Bond (Downtown District), Series 2026A or by such different name and series designation as directed by the Agencys Chairman (the Bond). Such resolution will be considered by City Council at a meeting to be held on February 9, 2026, at 2:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, in the Council Chambers, Second Floor, City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida 32802. The governing body of the Agency will consider the adoption of its bond resolution authorizing the issuance of the Bond at its meeting to be held at the same location and on the same date and approximate time as the City Council meeting. Proceeds of the Bond will finance various improvements throughout the Downtown Orlando Community Redevelopment Area which may include but are not limited to initiatives such as the Canopy (formerly Under-I), converting various streets in Downtown Orlando from one-way to two-way streets, right-of-way improvements including festival streets, upgraded sidewalks, enhanced civic spaces, various affordable housing projects, and improvements to Lake Eola Park and the surrounding area.  The Title of the City resolution reads as follows:  A RESOLUTION OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, APPROVING THE SUPPLEMENTAL BOND RESOLUTION OF THE COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AGENCY OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA (THE AGENCY) APPROVING AND AUTHORIZING THE ISSUANCE AND SALE BY THE AGENCY OF ITS TAX INCREMENT REVENUE BOND (DOWNTOWN DISTRICT), SERIES 2026A, IN AN ORIGINAL PRINCIPAL AMOUNT NOT TO EXCEED $160,000,000 FOR THE PURPOSE OF FINANCING VARIOUS IMPROVEMENTS THROUGHOUT THE DOWNTOWN ORLANDO COMMUNITY REDEVELOPMENT AREA; PROVIDING CERTAIN COVENANTS AND AUTHORIZATIONS OF THE CITY AND OTHER MATTERS WITH RESPECT THERETO; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Any interested person may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed resolution. Persons wishing to appeal any decision made by the City with respect to any matter relating to the above-referenced resolution considered during the noticed public hearing will need a record of the proceedings and may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Persons with disabilities needing assistance or an interpreter to participate in the public hearing should contact the City Clerks Office at (407) 246-2251 at least 24 hours in advance of the public hearing.  A draft of the proposed resolution may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk, City Hall, Second Floor, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida 32802 during regular working hours from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday.  DATED this 27th day of January, 2026. City of Orlando By: /s/ Buddy Dyer, Mayor   1/27/2026 7923628</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11466164</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11465529</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF MEETING DATES WESTSIDE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT Fiscal Year 2026The Board of Supervisors of the Westside Community Development Dist...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF MEETING DATES WESTSIDE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT Fiscal Year 2026The Board of Supervisors of the Westside Community Development District will hold their regularly scheduled public meetings for Fiscal Year 2026 at 11:00 am at the Hart Memorial Central Library, 211 E. Dakin Ave., Kissimmee, FL 34741, on the first Tuesday of each month as follows, unless otherwise indicated below:October 7, 2025 November 4, 2025 December 2, 2025 January 6, 2026 February 3, 2026** 11:30 AM March 3, 2026** 11:30 AM April 7, 2026 May 5, 2026 June 2, 2026 July 7, 2026 August 4, 2026 September 1, 2026  The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts.  A copy of the agenda for a particular meeting may be obtained from the District Manager at 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801; or by calling (407) 841-5524, during normal business hours, or via the Districts website at https://westsidecdd.com.A meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place as evidenced by motion of the majority of Board Members participating at that meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors will participate by telephone.Any person requiring special accommodations at these meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (407) 841-5524 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jason M. Showe District Manager Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC 7919962 1/26/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11465529</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11465528</link>
      <description>Notice at 1450 Diamond Loop Drive

Location: 1450 Diamond Loop Drive

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULEMAKING BY  TOWN OF KINDRED COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   In accordance with Chapters 190 and 120, Florida Statutes, the District hereby gives the public notice of its intent to adopt proposed revised Amenity Rules and Rates (Proposed Rules and Rates). The proposed rule number is 2026-1. Prior notice of rule development was published in The Orlando Sentinel on January 19 th , 2026.  A public hearing will be conducted by the Board of Supervisors of the Town of Kindred Community Development District (the District) on March 5 th , 2026, at 2:00 p.m. at the Town of Kindred Clubhouse, located at 1450 Diamond Loop Drive, Kissimmee, Florida 34744. relative to the adoption of the Proposed Rules and Rates. Pursuant to Sections 190.011(5) and 190.012(3), Florida Statutes, the Proposed Rules and Rates will not require legislative ratification.  The specific grant of rulemaking authority for the adoption of the Proposed Rules and Rates includes Sections 190.035(2), 190.011(5) and 120.54, Florida Statutes. The specific laws implemented in the Proposed Rules and Rates include, but are not limited to Section 190.035, Florida Statutes.  A statement of estimated regulatory costs, as defined in Section 120.541(2), Florida Statutes, has not been prepared relative to the Proposed Rules and Rates. Any person who wishes to provide the District with a proposal for a lower cost regulatory alternative as provided by Section 120.541(1), Florida Statutes, must do so in writing within twenty-one (21) days after publication of this notice to the District Managers Office.  For more information regarding the public hearing, the Proposed Rules and Rates, or for a copy of the Proposed Rule and the related incorporated documents, if any, please contact the District Manager c/o Rizzetta &amp; Company, Inc., 8529 South Park Circle, Suite 330, Orlando, Florida 32819, or BMendes@rizzetta.com (hereinafter, the District Managers Office).  The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the hearing without additional notice. If anyone chooses to appeal any decision of the Board with respect to any matter considered at the public hearing, such person will need a record of the proceedings and should accordingly ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based. At the public hearing, staff or Supervisors may participate in the public hearing by speaker telephone.  Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this hearing is asked to advise the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the public hearing. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 or 1-800-955-8770, who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.  Brian Mendes, District Manager Town of Kindred Community Development District   1/26/2026 7914782</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11465528</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464890</link>
      <description>Notice at 1299 Harding Street

Meeting: Wednesday, February 11, 2026 at 9:00 a.m.
Location: 1299 Harding Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF WINTER PARK401 Park Avenue, South  Winter Park, Florida 32789NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that a public hearing will be held by the Historic Preservation Board of the City of Winter Park on the requests described below on Wednesday, February 11, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, at 401 Park Avenue, South, Winter Park, Florida. Public participation and comment on these matters must be in-person. Further information is available at cityofwinterpark.org/government/board-public-meetings/, including staff reports within 5 days of the meetings.  COR 26-02. Request by Karen and Armando Martorelli for approval to construct a new one-story rear addition, make modifications to the front elevation of the residence including a minor front setback variance of one foot eight inches, and undertake minor alterations to the rear detached structure at the property located at 1299 Harding Street, zoned R-1AA.  NOTE: If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. (F.S. 286.0105). Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Planning Department at 407-599-3324 at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  /s/: Mary Jean, Board Clerk 7923090 1/25/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464890</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464886</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

--- Full Notice Text ---
MAGIC PLACE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT NOTICE OF REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETINGThe Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Magic Place Community Development District (District) will hold a regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors on February 2, 2026 at 10:00 a.m. at Magic Village Views, 7430 Brooklyn Dr, Kissimmee, FL 34747. The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the pertinent provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.  A copy of the agenda for the meetings may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, located at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, or by phone (407) 723-5900 (District Managers Office), during normal business hours or from the districts website online: http://magicplacecdd.com/.  Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.  Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jane Gaarlandt District Manager 7922293 1/25/26</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464886</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464885</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Blvd

--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Public Meeting  Magic Reserve Community Development DistrictThe Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Magic Reserve Community Development District (District) will hold a regular meeting of the Board of Supervisors on February 2, 2026 at 10:00 a.m. at Magic Village Views, 7430 Brooklyn Dr, Kissimmee, FL 34747. The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the pertinent provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.  A copy of the agenda for the meetings may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, located at 3501 Quadrangle Blvd., Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, or by phone (407) 723-5900 (District Managers Office), during normal business hours or from the districts website online: http://magicreservecdd.com/.  Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5900 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.  Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Jane Gaarlandt District Manager 7922290 1/25/26</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464885</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464877</link>
      <description>ORANGE COUNTYNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on February 10, 2026, at 2 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTYNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on February 10, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the following proposed ordinance:  AN ORDINANCE OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA PERTAINING TO ANIMAL SERVICES AMENDING ARTICLE II, CHAPTER 5 OF THE ORANGE COUNTY CODE; AMENDING SECTION 5-29 (DEFINITIONS); AMENDING SECTION 5-32 (CLASSIFICATION OF DOGS AS DANGEROUS; CONFINEMENT AND QUARANTINE REQUIREMENTS OF DANGEROUS DOGS; EXEMPTIONS; REQUIREMENTS FOR OWNERS OF DANGEROUS DOGS; CONDUCT OF SPECIAL MAGISTRATE HEARINGS; AND APPEALS) AMENDING SECTION 5-32.1 (ATTACK OR BITE BY DANGEROUS DOG; ATTACK BY UNCLASSIFIED DOG THAT CAUSES DEATH; PENALTIES; APPEALS; CONFISCATION; DESTRUCTION) AMENDING SECTION 5-34 (IMPOUNDMENT OF ANIMALS; COMPULSORY STERILIZATION); AMENDING SECTION 5-35 (DISPOSITION OF IMPOUNDED ANIMALS); AMENDING SECTION 5-41 (TRAPPING; EXPOSING POISON) AMENDING SECTION 5-50 (VIOLATIONS; CONSTRUCTION OF ARTICLE) CREATING A NEW SECTION 5-54 (MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS AND WARRANTY REQUIREMENTS FOR SALE OF DOGS AND CATS); CREATING A NEW SECTION 5-55 (COMMUNITY CAT MANAGEMENT PROGRAM); AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  You may examine the notice and the proposed ordinance at the office of the Comptroller Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Fourth Floor; Orlando, Florida; between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m., Monday through Friday.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS NOTICE, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY ANIMAL SERVICES DIVISION, 407-254-9125, Email: Diane.Summers@ocfl.net  PARA MAS INFORMACION EN ESPAOL ACERCA DE ESTAS REUNIONES PUBLICAS O DE CAMBIOS POR SER EFECTUADOS, FAVOR DE LLAMAR A LA OFICINA DE LOS ABOGADOS DEL CONDADO, ELFRIDA RAMOS, AL 407-836-7320.  POU W KA JWENN PLIS ENFMASYON AN KREYL AYISYEN SOU REYINYON PIBLIK SA YO OSWA SOU CHANJMAN KAP FT YO, TANPRI RELE 407-836-3111.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7922037 1/25/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464877</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464876</link>
      <description>ORANGE COUNTYNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on February 10, 2026, at 2 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
ORANGE COUNTYNOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARINGThe Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on February 10, 2026, at 2 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commission Chambers, First Floor, County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida. You are invited to attend and be heard regarding the following request by:  Applicant: Anthony Lasala Life Estate, Shanda F Lasala Life Estate, REM: Anthony Lasala Trust 50% INT, REM: Shanda F Lasala Trust 50% INT Consideration: Request for a Shoreline Alteration/Dredge and Fill Permit SADF # 25-07-018 to repair an existing seawall on Big Sand Lake, pursuant to Orange County Code, Chapter 15, Article VI, Shoreline Alteration Dredge and Fill Location: District 1; on property located adjacent to Big Sand Lake, 10102 Brandon Circle, Orlando, FL 32836; Orange County, Florida (legal property description on file in Environmental Protection Division)  You may obtain a copy of the legal property description by calling the Orange County Environmental Protection Division; 407-836-1400; or pick one up at 3165 McCrory Place, Suite 200; Orlando, Florida.  IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS NOTICE, CONTACT THE ORANGE COUNTY ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION DIVISION, 407-836-1400, Email: Elizabeth.Johnson@ocfl.net  PARA MS INFORMACIN, REFERENTE A ESTA VISTA PUBLICA CON RESPECTO A UNA AUDIENCIA PUBLICA SOBRE PROPIEDAD EN SU AREA/VECINDAD, FAVOR COMUNICARSE CON LA DIVISIN DE ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION, AL NUMERO, 407-836-1400.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting you will need a record of the proceedings. You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-5631 no later than two business days prior to the hearing for assistance. Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  Phil Diamond, County Comptroller As Clerk of the  Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida ORG 7922034 1/25/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464876</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/68/11464868.pdf</link>
      <description>1/25/26 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, at 2:00 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/25/26 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will conduct a public hearing on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, at 2:00 p.m., or as soon thereafter as possible, in the County Commissioners' Chambers, First Floor, Orange County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida, to consider recognition of encumbrance rollovers, grant rollovers, fund balance adjustments, capital improvement adjustments, and to make other necessary adjustments. All interested parties are invited to attend and be heard. If you have any questions regarding the public hearing, please contact the Orange County Office of Management and Budget, 407-836-7390. Any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the Orange County Board of County Commissioners at this meeting will need a record of the proceedings. For that purpose, such person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), if any person with a disability as defined by the ADA needs special accommodations to participate in this proceeding, he or she should contact the Orange County Communications Division at 407-836-5328, no later than two (2) business days prior to the proceeding. Fund Balance Amendment: Sources: Fund Balance $266,068,004 Interfund Transfers 1,008,357 Miscellaneous Revenue 106,947,250 Total Sources $374,023,611 Uses: Personal Services $5,229,868 Operating Expenses 15,499,943 Capital Outlay 11,287,000 Debt Services 0 Reserves 296,843,701 Interfund Transfers 1,008,357 Miscellaneous 44,154,742  Total Uses $374,023,611 Encumbrance Rollovers: Sources: Fund Balance $454,327,621 Total Sources $454,327,621 Uses: Operating Expenses $207,726,770 Capital Outlay 220,259,751 Grants 23,539,984 Other 2,801,116 Total Uses $454,327,621 Grant Rollovers: Sources: Intergovernmental Revenue $441,219,083 Grant Income 3,486,467 Non-Revenue 2,519,557 Total Sources $447,225,107 Uses: Personal Services $16,446,793 Operating Expenses 186,564,972 Capital Outlay 207,687,052 Grants 34,093,980 Other 2,432,310 Total Uses $447,225,107 Capital Improvements Adjustments: Uses: CIP Projects $294,649,120 Provision for Rebudgets (40,142,312) Reserves (254,506,808) Total Uses $0  To obtain a complete detail listing of fund balance adjustments, encumbrance rollovers, grant rollovers, and capital improvement adjustments, please contact the Office of Management and Budget at 407-836-7390.  7921468 NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464868</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11464868.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464860</link>
      <description>Notice at cityofwinterpark

Location: cityofwinterpark

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICENotice is hereby given that a public hearing will be held by the City Commission of the City of Winter Park, Florida, on Wednesday, January 28, 2026 and February 11, 2026, at 3:30 p.m. or as soon thereafter at Winter Park City Hall at 401 S. Park Avenue, Winter Park, Florida. In lieu of physically attending in person, members of the public may participate in this meeting by attending virtually by following the instructions located at cityofwinterpark.org/government/board-public-meetings/. You may contact the City Clerks Office at 407-599-3277 for assistance in setting up virtual attendance of the meeting.  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF WINTER PARK, FLORIDA, APPROVING THE PARTIAL TERMINATION OF THE PLAT DEDICATED SIX FOOT WIDE UTILITY EASEMENT CREATED BY THE DOMMERICH COVE PLAT RECORDED AT PLAT BOOK Z, PAGE 21, PUBLIC RECORDS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA WITHIN THE BOUNDARIES OF THE PROPERTY LOCATED AT 2923 COVE TRAIL AND HAVING ORANGE COUNTY TAX PARCEL NUMBER 29-21-30-2122-00-140; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS,  SEVERABILITY, AN EFFECTIVE DATE AND RECORDING.  Further, this advertisement constitutes a notice of the applicants intent to seek a partial vacation of a plat pursuant to Section 177.101, Florida Statutes. This notice is deemed to be attached to the applicants petition.All interested parties are invited to attend and be heard.  Additional information is available on the Citys website at www.cityofwinterpark.org so that citizens may acquaint themselves with each issue.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he/she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he/she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  (F.S. 286.0105)   Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office (407-599-3277) at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting.  /s/ Rene S. Cranis, City Clerk 7919972 1/25, 2/1/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464860</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/58/11464858.pdf</link>
      <description>7916872 1/25/2026 NOTICE BY ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM ASSESSM...


--- Full Notice Text ---
7916872 1/25/2026 NOTICE BY ORANGE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS OF INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM ASSESSMENT  The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will hold a public hearing on February 10, 2026 at 2 p.m., at the Orange County Administration Center, 201 South Rosalind Avenue, Orlando, Florida.  You are invited to attend and be heard regarding a request to consider the adoption of a Resolution authorizing the Orange County Board of County Commissioners to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem assessments levied by the Orange County Board of County Commissioners as provided in Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.  IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS REGARDING THIS PUBLIC HEARING NOTICE, CONTACT ORANGE COUNTY COMPTROLLER SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS  407-836-5770  E-MAIL: Special.Assessments@occompt.com  SI USTED TIENE ALGUNA PREGUNTA REFERENTE A ESTA VISTA PBLICA, FAVOR DE COMUNICARSE CON LAS OFICINAS DE FINANZAS DEL CONDADO ORANGE, AL NUMERO DE TELEFONO  407-836-5715  Notice is hereby given to all owners of lands located within the boundaries of Orange County Florida that the Orange County Board of County Commissioners intends to use the uniform method for collection of non-ad valorem assessments levied by the Orange County Board of County Commissioners as set forth in Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.  Take notice that pursuant to the provisions of Section 125.01 (1) (q), Florida Statutes, the Orange County Board of County Commissioners of Orange County, Florida, has received requests for the establishment and / or amendments of Municipal Service Benefit Units (MSBU's) for all the listed properties encompassing the boundaries as set forth in the detailed attachment.  The Orange County Board of County Commissioners will hold public hearings to consider resolutions at a future date and which may adopt the MSBU's in accordance with Section 197.3632, and Section 125.01 (1) (q), Florida Statutes.  The purpose of this public hearing is not to impose a rate or levy an assessment, but rather to consider the adoption of a Resolution authorizing the Board to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem assessments.  Interested parties may appear at the Public Hearing to be heard regarding the use of the uniform method of collecting such non-ad valorem assessments.  If you wish to appeal any decision made by the Board of County Commissioners at this meeting, you will need a record of the proceedings.  You should ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  If you require special accommodations under the Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990, please call 407-836-3111 no later than two (2) business days prior to the hearing for assistance.  Si usted requiere ayuda especial bajo la ley de Americanos con Incapacidades de 1990, por favor llame al 407-836-3111.  The information contained in this Notice is correct and accurate to the best of our knowledge as of this date.  The properties subject to the proposed resolution are listed in Exhibit A and Exhibit B hereto.   Phil Diamond As Clerk of the Board of County Commissioners Orange County, Florida   Publish:	January 11, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  January 18, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  January 25, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)  February 1, 2026		Orlando Sentinel Public Record (Orange Extra all zones)   Certify:		MSBU for Notice of Intent Public Hearing  c:	All Board Members Offices (e-mail) 	County Attorneys Office, BCC (e-mail to Angela Diaz) 	Jon Weiss, Deputy County Administrator, BCC (e-mail) 	Ann Curtis, Special Assessments (e-mail) 	Cheryl Gillespie, Agenda Development (e-mail) 	Mike Seif, Orange TV, BCC (e-mail) James Jerome, Program Coordinator, BCC (e-mail)Notice of Intent  November 2026 Exhibit A  Subdivision Name(s)  MSBU Description  Plat Book / Page(s) Section Township Range  Property Boundaries Avalon Woods Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 118/121-128 17-23-27 Lots 1-182 Hamlin Meadows at Hamlin  Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/66-72 30-23-27 Lots 1-165 Tract FD-1 Future Development Harvest at Ovation Area Harvest at Ovation Phase 2 Harvest at Ovation Phase 3A   Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  117/82-85 119/83-88  29-24-27 29-24-27  Lots 167-232 Lots 233-306 Lake Roberts / Lake Reaves Watercrest at Windermere Amend Lake Maintenance  118/50-55  01-23-27  Lots 19-24 Lake Star at Ovation Area Lake Star at Ovation Phase  1B Amend Streetlighting  Retention Pond Maintenance  119/23-28  19-24-27  Lots 56-115 Lakeview Pointe at Horizon West Area, Ravenna Area and Mezzano Shoppes at Lakeview Amend Streetlighting 118/10-11   34-23-27   Lot 1 Lakeview Pointe at Horizon West Area, Ravenna Phase 3 Shoppes at Lakeview Amend Retention Pond   118/10-11   34-23-27   Lot 1 Northlake at Ovation Area Northlake at Ovation Phase 2 and 3 Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  119/60-63  19-24-27  Lots 186-290 Sagewood Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/126-129 02-21-28 Lots 1-71 Serenade at Ovation Area Serenade at Ovation Phase 3 Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/113-116 30-24-27 Lots 121-227 Silverleaf Area Silverleaf Oaks at Hamlin Phase 3B Amending Streetlighting119/1-12  30-23-27  Lots 529-766 Silverleaf Area Silverleaf Oaks at Hamlin Phase 3B Hamlin Meadows at Hamlin Amending Retention Pond  119/01-12 119/66-72  30-23-27 30-23-27  Lots 529-766 Lots 1-165 Tract FD-1 Future Development Stoneybrook Hills Master Road Foothills at Mount Dora Phase 4-2 Amend Streetlighting  118/32-43  03-20-27  Lots 126-226 Watercrest at WindermereEstablish Streetlighting Retention Pond 118/50-55 01-23-27 Lots 1-41 Waterleigh Area Waterleigh Kiddie Academy Amend Streetlighting Retention Pond  113/57-58  07-24-27  Lot 1 Wekiva Springs Cove Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 117/105-106 01-21-28 Lots 1-13 Woodside Preserve  Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 117/54-57 25-22-30 Lots 1-53 World Design Center Area World Design Center Phase 3 Parcel 1 Replat World Design Center Phase 3 Parcel 5 Replat Amend  Retention Pond  115/18-20 115/48-53  33-23-29 04-24-29  Lots 1B and 1C Lots 5A, 5B, and 5D Yucatan Gardens Establish Streetlighting Retention Pond 119/64-65 27-22-30 Lots 1-52 Notice of Intent 2026 Establish Lot Cleaning Exhibit B LC 24-0256 24-22-28-6164-06-010 LC 25-0002 24-24-29-6000-26-130 LC 25-0005 26-24-29-0000-00-005 LC 25-0006 11-23-30-6851-00-005 LC 25-0007 18-22-31-1200-00-490 LC 25-0008 30-22-29-9228-17-050 LC 25-0032 24-22-31-1052-03-030 LC 25-0037 03-22-29-0552-01-180 LC 25-0039 25-22-28-1812-03-441 LC 25-0040 07-22-29-5566-01-260 LC 25-0043 15-21-28-0932-02-050 LC 25-0049 10-23-29-0296-00-171 LC 25-0061 36-24-29-6723-00-400 LC 25-0062 12-22-30-3378-02-040 LC 25-0066 25-22-28-1812-06-361 LC 25-0068 19-22-29-6976-08-100 LC 25-0069 24-21-28-5076-00-091 LC 25-0070 19-22-29-0000-00-041 LC 25-0074 36-22-28-6416-04-230 LC 25-0076 17-22-29-7802-00-870 LC 25-0080 13-22-28-8058-00-040 LC 25-0081 03-23-29-0183-10-170 LC 25-0082 03-23-29-0183-10-180 LC 25-0083 27-23-29-8085-02-200 LC 25-0086 21-22-30-7204-15-111 LC 25-0087 02-21-28-8308-00-061 LC 25-0090 15-23-30-5306-01-200 LC 25-0091 16-21-28-0000-00-059 LC 25-0092 22-22-32-0712-19-600 LC 25-0093 14-22-28-0000-00-018 LC 25-0095 34-22-33-1327-03-030 LC 25-0097 07-23-30-9492-04-010 LC 25-0098 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0101 12-22-28-7413-09-010 LC 25-0102 03-22-29-8476-04-150 LC 25-0104 03-23-29-0180-19-040 LC 25-0105 03-22-29-8476-04-190 LC 25-0107 03-23-29-0180-41-110 LC 25-0108 30-24-30-4950-10-000 LC 25-0111 15-23-29-0146-00-040 LC 25-0112 21-22-32-0734-00-870 LC 25-0114 06-22-29-2450-02-090 LC 25-0115 36-22-28-6416-02-115 LC 25-0116 33-21-29-0899-00-860 LC 25-0117 18-22-31-0232-02-920 LC 25-0120 07-22-29-6974-04-090 LC 25-0121 21-22-30-3932-17-230 LC 25-0122 19-22-31-0000-00-024 LC 25-0124 16-23-29-9430-01-290 LC 25-0125 13-22-28-8058-00-460 LC 25-0126 10-23-29-7434-12-010 LC 25-0127 01-22-28-2858-00-040 LC 25-0128 03-23-29-0182-95-110 LC 25-0129 03-23-29-0182-94-240 LC 25-0131 10-23-29-7420-05-120 LC 25-0134 30-22-29-9228-16-060 LC 25-0135 03-23-29-0180-27-170 LC 25-0136 03-23-29-0183-15-030 LC 25-0138 27-22-28-4880-01-210 LC 25-0139 10-23-29-0000-00-039 LC 25-0140 25-22-28-4484-01-060 LC 25-0141 13-22-28-8058-00-040 LC 25-0142 12-22-28-7051-07-140 LC 25-0143 18-22-31-8744-02-231 LC 25-0148 26-22-30-0000-00-086 LC 25-0149 21-22-29-2540-03-010 LC 25-0151 36-20-27-9612-02-040 LC 25-0153 14-23-28-3552-00-120 LC 25-0157 06-24-30-7268-00-310 LC 25-0158 24-22-28-6164-06-010 LC 25-0159 32-21-29-6080-00-062 LC 25-0162 15-22-28-4716-00-152 LC 25-0163 34-22-29-8748-01-100 LC 25-0164 02-22-29-8472-02-180 LC 25-0166 12-22-28-0000-00-003 LC 25-0167 19-22-31-3887-00-002 LC 25-0168 02-22-29-8472-02-190 LC 25-0169 14-21-28-0000-00-043 LC 25-0171 01-23-29-3834-00-740 LC 25-0173 07-22-29-5564-00-210 LC 25-0174 18-22-29-8509-02-090 LC 25-0175 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0176 24-22-28-0000-00-078 LC 25-0177 25-22-28-1810-06-020 LC 25-0180 03-23-29-3292-00-040 LC 25-0181 01-21-27-0000-00-038 LC 25-0182 18-22-30-4748-00-010 LC 25-0185 14-21-28-2590-05-030 LC 25-0187 24-22-28-0614-04-080 LC 25-0191 20-23-29-1137-02-070 LC 25-0192 03-23-29-0180-72-170 LC 25-0193 07-22-29-6936-01-390 LC 25-0195 15-21-28-0932-03-250 LC 25-0196 15-21-28-0000-00-045 LC 25-0198 15-21-28-0932-02-050 LC 25-0200 02-22-29-2996-06-070 LC 25-0204 27-23-29-0000-00-056 LC 25-0208 30-21-29-1832-06-200 LC 25-0209 16-21-28-0000-00-088 LC 25-0210 16-21-28-0000-00-172 LC 25-0212 34-22-33-1327-03-110 LC 25-0213 34-22-33-1327-03-100 LC 25-0214 22-22-32-0712-41-039 LC 25-0215 25-23-29-8486-02-080 LC 25-0220 22-24-29-2982-00-360 LC 25-0221 19-22-31-0000-00-024 LC 25-0225 21-21-28-0020-00-100 LC 25-0227 09-21-28-0197-10-241 LC 25-0228 09-21-28-0197-10-321 LC 25-0231 26-22-28-2894-01-165 LC 25-0232 25-22-28-4484-03-240 LC 25-0240 34-23-27-0000-00-017 LC 25-0242 22-22-32-0712-19-600 LC 25-0243 34-22-33-1327-02-350 LC 25-0245 07-22-29-6974-04-090 LC 25-0247 10-23-29-6152-04-210 LC 25-0248 24-22-30-8240-00-070 LC 25-0249 18-22-29-9580-05-210 LC 25-0254 35-21-28-1408-00-020 LC 25-0255 21-22-30-4316-04-010 LC 25-0257 19-22-29-6960-02-010 LC 25-0261 15-24-28-6186-03-001 LC 25-0264 03-23-29-1402-06-140 LC 25-0266 36-20-27-0000-00-084 LC 25-0267 03-23-29-7436-07-030 LC 25-0268 18-22-29-2534-05-210 LC 25-0269 19-22-29-6978-15-050 LC 25-0271 20-23-29-1162-01-170 LC 25-0276 03-23-29-0182-96-011 LC 25-0277 03-23-29-7435-03-030 LC 25-0278 01-22-28-9484-00-080 LC 25-0279 28-21-29-7476-05-140 LC 25-0281 03-23-29-0180-06-050 LC 25-0287 24-24-29-6000-28-110 LC 25-0290 29-21-29-2386-02-140 LC 25-0296 34-22-29-1382-02-110 LC 25-0297 15-23-29-0000-00-091 LC 25-0298 12-22-28-7051-07-140 LC 25-0301 13-22-28-8058-00-460 LC 25-0304 25-22-28-1812-03-441 LC 25-0305 03-23-29-0182-74-100 LC 25-0307 14-23-28-4658-00-190 LC 25-0308 18-22-30-4748-00-010 LC 25-0309 06-23-30-5364-00-040 LC 25-0312 17-22-31-0000-00-010 LC 25-0313 03-23-29-7430-01-310 LC 25-0315 03-23-29-0180-72-170 LC 25-0321 25-22-30-6836-01-140 LC 25-0327 24-23-29-3400-00-112 LC 25-0329 22-22-27-1084-02-020 LC 25-0331 26-22-28-9218-00-040 LC 25-0333 25-22-28-1812-06-361 LC 25-0334 36-22-28-6416-04-180 LC 25-0340 01-22-28-2860-00-130 LC 25-0366 19-22-31-3887-00-002 LC 25-0372 12-22-30-3378-02-040 LC 25-0373 05-23-30-1624-04-150 LC 25-0387 01-24-29-8516-81-103 LC 25-0393 21-22-30-4312-11-081 LC 25-0394 14-22-30-8646-01-200 LC 25-0395 17-22-31-7775-02-390 LC 25-0412 02-23-30-6424-00-050 LC 25-0429 14-23-28-3552-00-120 LC 25-0430 08-20-27-8559-02-120  7916872 ORANGE COUNTY NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING Orange County</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464858</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11464858.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
