<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:59:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PUD-25-0014 - 2001 Yates Road</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/16/11381716.pdf</link>
      <description>Planned Unit Development at 2001 Yates Road: OS (Open Space) → PUD (Planned Unit Development)

Type: Planned Unit Development (PUD)
Meeting: Tuesday, November 18, 2025 at 6:00 p.m.
Location: 2001 Yates Road
Zoning: OS (Open Space) → PUD (Planned Unit Development)
Parcel ID: 18-25-29-0000- 0180-0000 and 18-25-29-0000-0185-0000
Reference: PUD-25-0014

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/3/2026 The City Commission will consider a request to amend the Official Zoning Map referenced in Ordinance No. 3110 known as the Land Development Code of the City of Kissimmee rezoning the property hereinafter described as follows: FROM: OS (Open Space)  City TO: PUD (Planned Unit Development)  City The subject property is located at 2001 Yates Road Parcel IDs: 18-25-29-0000- 0180-0000 and 18-25-29-0000-0185-0000 Legal Descriptions: N1/2 OF: BEG AT SW COR OF NE 1/4 OF SW 1/4, N 672 FT, E TO SHINGLE CREEK, S ALONG SHINGLE CREEK TO S/L OF SAID QUARTER, W TO POB And S1/2 OF: BEG AT SW COR OF NE 1/4 OF SW 1/4, N 672 FT, E TO SHINGLE CREEK, S ALONG SHINGLE CREEK TO S/L OF SAID QUARTER, W TO POB PROPOSED ORDINANCE #25-19: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING ORDINANCE NO. 3110 KNOWN AS THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE, REZONING THE PROPERTY HEREINAFTER DESCRIBED, REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The City Commission will hold a Public Hearing on Tuesday, November 18, 2025 at 6:00 p.m. in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida, and will consider the adoption of an Ordinance to rezone the above described property following the public hearing. A copy of the proposed Ordinance may be inspected in the office of the Development Services Department at City Hall, 101 Church Street. All interested parties may appear and be heard on the above date. Written opinion will be received until 5:30 p.m., Tuesday, November 18, 2025. Any questions may be directed to the Development Services Department at (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov. Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or meeting may be heard by participating in person.  Reference # PUD-25-0014 CITY COMMISSION Armstrong Zoning KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA  In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the City Clerk (407) 518-2308 prior to the meeting. (FS286.26) In accordance with Florida Statues 286.0105: Any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the Planning Advisory Board with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made.  NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING CITY COMMISSION  7890714</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11381716</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11381716.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRC - 2001 Yates RD</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/14/11381714.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice at 2001 Yates RD: REC (Recreation) - → INST (Institutional) -

Location: 2001 Yates RD
Zoning: REC (Recreation) - → INST (Institutional) -
Parcel ID: 18-25-29-0000-0180-0000 and 18-25-29-0000-0185-0000
Reference: DRC

--- Full Notice Text ---
11/3/2026 The City of Kissimmee proposes to adopt the following ordinance that would change the use of land as described below. A public hearing on this proposal will be held by the City of Kissimmee City Commission to consider the first reading of the proposed ordinance on Tuesday, November 18, 2025, at 6:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Commission Chambers of City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida. PROPOSED ORDINANCE# 25-18: AN ORDINANCE AMENDING ORDINANCE NO. 3050 KNOWN AS THE ORDINANCE ADOPTING THE COMPREHENSIVE DEVELOPMENT PLAN FOR THE CITY OF KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA, UNDER THE AUTHORITY OF FLORIDA STATUTE 163.3184; DIRECTING THE CITY MANAGER TO AMEND THE COMPREHENSIVE LAND USE PLAN AS HEREIN PROVIDED AFTER THE PASSAGE OF THIS ORDINANCE; PROVIDING FOR A PUBLIC HEARING AS REQUIRED BY LAW; REPEALING ALL ORDINANCES IN CONFLICT HEREWITH; AND PROVIDING AN EFFECTIVE DATE. The purpose of this Public Hearing is to make a recommendation to the City Commission concerning the request to amend Ordinance No. 3050. The proposed Ordinance would amend the 2025 Future Land Use Map of the Kissimmee Comprehensive Plan by changing the land use classification for the area described below as follows: FROM: REC (Recreation) - City TO: INST (Institutional) - City The subject property is located at 2001 Yates RD. Legal Description: Parcel 1: 18-25-29-0000-0180-0000 N1/2 OF: BEG AT SW COR OF NE 1/4 OF SW 1/4, N 672 FT, E TO SHINGLE CREEK, S ALONG SHINGLE CREEK TO S/L OF SAID QUARTER, W TO POB Together with Parcel 2: 18-25-29-0000-0185-0000 S1/2 OF: BEG AT SW COR OF NE 1/4 OF SW 1/4, N 672 FT, E TO SHINGLE CREEK, S ALONG SHINGLE CREEK TO S/L OF SAID QUARTER, W TO POB The purpose of this public hearing is to consider a proposed amendment to Ordinance 3050, known as the Comprehensive Development Plan, which would change the 2025 Future Land Use Map of the Kissimmee Comprehensive Plan. The proposed amendment and the supporting documents, including a parcel description, may be inspected in the Development Services Department, City Hall, 101 Church Street, Kissimmee, Florida, between 8:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday. Please direct any questions to the Development Services Department, (407) 518-2140 or planning@kissimmee.gov .  Any interested party wanting to be heard on this issue may submit testimony to be read into the official record to CityClerkEmail@kissimmee.gov prior to the start of the meeting or may be heard by participating in person.  Reference # DRC LUPA-25-0003 CITY COMMISSION Yates Road KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA In accordance with Florida Statutes 286.0105: any person wishing to appeal any decision made by the City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing will need a record of the proceedings, and for such purposes may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is made. In accordance with Florida Statute 286.26, persons needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the Office of the  CITY OF KISSIMMEE NOTICE OF PUBLIC HEARING NOTICE OF LAND USE CHANGE  7890710</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11381714</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11381714.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
