<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:23:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11451749</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENTOn Monday, January 26, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2026-1, entitled: AN ORDINANCE ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENTOn Monday, January 26, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2026-1, entitled: AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, VACATING,  CLOSING, AND ABANDONING APPROXIMATELY 91 FEET OF WEST ILLIANA STREET,  GENERALLY LOCATED EAST OF CSX RAILROAD, SOUTH OF WEST MICHIGAN STREET, WEST  OF TAYLOR AVENUE AND NORTH OF WEST PINELOCH AVENUE, AS DESCRIBED IN THE PLAT  OF GEORGE GREENMORES SUBDIVISION, AS RECORDED IN PLAT BOOK G, PAGE 79 AND IN  THE CARLTON TERRACE PLAT, AS RECORDED IN PLAT BOOK O, PAGE 38 IN THE PUBLIC  RECORDS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA, AND COMPRISED OF 0.126 ACRES OF LAND, MORE  OR LESS; PROVIDING FOR CONDITIONS OF ABANDONMENT; THE EXECUTION OF EFFECTING  DOCUMENTS, SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE  DATE.. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00  p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties  may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information  about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/council meeting at least  3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may  participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in  advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the  designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed  ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S.  Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision  made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the  proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is  committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with  disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24  hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov. 7918877 1/13/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11451749</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11451745</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETING  TAPESTRY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTA meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Tapestry Commun...

Meeting: Thursday, January 29, 2026 at 10:00 AM

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF REGULAR BOARD OF SUPERVISORS MEETING  TAPESTRY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICTA meeting of the Board of Supervisors of the Tapestry Community Development District will be held on Thursday, January 29, 2026 at 10:00 AM at the Offices of Hanson, Walter &amp; Associates, 8 Broadway, Suite 104, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.  Anyone wishing to participate in the meetings telephonically on the above date and time must call (305) 224-1968 and when prompted, enter meeting ID: 892 1126 0282 or via computer at https://us06web.zoom.us/j/89211260282. Additional information regarding this meeting may be obtained from the Districts website https://tapestrycdd.com or by contacting the District Manager, Tricia Adams, at tadams@gmscfl.com or by calling 407-841-5524.  The meetings are open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. A copy of the meeting agendas may be obtained from the District Manager at 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, FL 32801; (407) 841-5524. Either or both meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting.  There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors, Staff or other individuals will participate by telephone or Zoom webinar.Any person requiring special accommodations at this meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at (407) 841-5524 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service 1-800-955-8770, for aid in contacting the District Office.  Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at these meetings is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.  Tricia L. Adams Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC District Manager 7918666 1/13/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11451745</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11451163</link>
      <description>ORDER TO SHOW CAUSE   IN THE CIRCUIT COURT OF THE SECOND JUDICIAL CIRCUIT IN AND FOR LEON COUNTY, FLORIDA CASE NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
ORDER TO SHOW CAUSE   IN THE CIRCUIT COURT OF THE SECOND JUDICIAL CIRCUIT IN AND FOR LEON COUNTY, FLORIDA CASE NO. 2025-CA-001796  VALIDATION OF NOT TO EXCEED $750,000,000 FLORIDA MUNICIPAL LOAN COUNCIL REVENUE BONDS (VARIOUS SERIES)  FLORIDA MUNICIPAL LOAN COUNCIL, a public body corporate and politic pursuant to the Florida Interlocal Cooperation Act of 1969, Plaintiff, vs. THE STATE OF FLORIDA, AND THE SEVERAL PROPERTY OWNERS, TAXPAYERS AND CITIZENS OF THE CITY OF STUART, FLORIDA, THE CITY OF DELAND, FLORIDA, AND THE CITY OF ROCKLEDGE, FLORIDA, INCLUDING NON-RESIDENTS OWNING PROPERTY OR SUBJECT TO TAXATION THEREIN AND ALL OTHERS HAVING OR CLAIMING ANY RIGHT, TITLE, OR INTEREST IN PROPERTY TO BE AFFECTED BY THE ISSUANCE OF THE BONDS HEREIN DESCRIBED, OR TO BE AFFECTED THEREBY, Defendants.  TO: THE STATE OF FLORIDA, THROUGH THE STATE ATTORNEYS FOR THE SECOND JUDICIAL CIRCUIT OF FLORIDA, THE SEVENTH JUDICIAL CIRCUIT OF FLORIDA, THE EIGHTEENTH JUDICIAL CIRCUIT OF FLORIDA, AND THE NINETEENTH JUDICIAL CIRCUIT OF FLORIDA AND TO THE SEVERAL PROPERTY OWNERS, TAXPAYERS, AND CITIZENS OF THE STATE OF FLORIDA AND OF THE CITY OF STUART, FLORIDA, THE CITY OF DELAND, FLORIDA, AND THE CITY OF ROCKLEDGE, FLORIDA, INCLUDING NON- RESIDENTS OWNING PROPERTY OR SUBJECT TO TAXATION THEREIN, AND ALL OTHERS HAVING OR CLAIMING ANY RIGHT, TITLE, OR INTEREST IN PROPERTY TO BE AFFECTED BY THE ISSUANCE OF THE BONDS HEREINAFTER MORE PARTICULARLY DESCRIBED OR TO BE AFFECTED IN ANY WAY THEREBY:  Plaintiff, the Florida Municipal Loan Council (Plaintiff), having filed its Complaint for Validation (Complaint) in this action pursuant to chapter 75, Florida Statutes, seeking to determine the authority of the Plaintiff to issue its Revenue Bonds (Various Series), in the amount of not to exceed $750,000,000 (Bonds) (a more particular description of the Bonds being contained in the Complaint), to determine the legality of the proceedings had and taken in connection therewith, and the legality of the provisions, covenants, and agreements contained therein and the revenues pledged to the payment thereof, and seeking a judgment of this Court to validate the proceedings for the Bonds, the revenues pledged for the payment thereof, and the Bonds when issued pursuant thereto, and the Complaint now having been presented to this Court, for entry of an Order to Show Cause pursuant to chapter 75, Florida Statutes, and the Court being fully advised in the premises: IT IS ORDERED AND ADJUDGED that the State of Florida, through the State Attorney of the Second Judicial Circuit of Florida, through its State Attorney for the Seventh Judicial Circuit of Florida, through its State Attorney for the Eighteenth Judicial Circuit of Florida and through its State Attorney for the Nineteenth Judicial Circuit of Florida, and the several taxpayers, property owners, and citizens of the City of Stuart, Florida, the City of DeLand, Florida, and the City of Rockledge, Florida, including non-residents owning property or subject to taxation therein, and others claiming any right, title, or interest in property to be affected by the issuance of the Bonds or to be affected in any way thereby, shall appear on March 4, 2026, at 1:00 p.m. Eastern Time, before the Honorable Judge John C. Cooper,  to be determined by remote video conference using the meeting instructions below, and show cause, if any there be, why the prayers of the Complaint should not be granted and why the proceedings for the Bonds when issued pursuant thereto and the revenues pledged to the payment thereof should not be validated and confirmed as requested in the Complaint. The foregoing hearing in this matter will be conducted remotely using the Zoom videoconferencing platform (www.zoom.us). There are no fees for attending this court hearing via the Zoom videoconferencing platform. The Zoom platform also allows individuals to appear via telephone instead of internet videoconferencing. At the designated hearing time, anyone interested in this bond validation proceeding may participate in the show cause hearing through Zoom at the following internet address: Topic: 25-CA-1796 Florida Municipal Loan Council vs. State of Florida Time: March 4, 2026, 1:00 PM Eastern Time  Join Zoom Meeting https://zoom.us/j/99313193767?pwd=KAY4WYjQswiUt2OaJLj6zLdl1cdcSc.1  Meeting ID: 993 1319 3767 Passcode: 685935  Dial in audio only  1 786 635 1003  AND IT IS FURTHER ORDERED AND ADJUDGED that this Order to Show Cause be published in the manner required by section 75.06, Florida Statutes. AND IT IS FURTHER ORDERED AND ADJUDGED that by such publication of this Order to Show Cause all taxpayers, property owners, and citizens of the City of Stuart, Florida, the City of DeLand, Florida, and the City of Rockledge, Florida, including non-residents owning property or subject to taxation therein, and all others having or claiming any right, title, or interest in property to be affected by the issuance of the Bonds or to be affected in any way thereby, or the validity of the Bonds, or of any revenues pledged for payment thereof, or of the proceedings authorizing the issuance of the Bonds, including any remedies provided for their collection, be and they are made parties defendant to this proceeding, and that this Court shall have jurisdiction of them to the same extent as if named as defendants in the Complaint and personally served with process in this cause.  If you are a person with a disability who needs any accommodation in order to participate in this proceeding, you are entitled, at no cost to you, to the provision of certain assistance. Please contact ADA Coordinator, 301 South Monroe Street, Tallahassee, FL 32301, 850.606.4400, at least seven (7) days before your scheduled court appearance, or immediately upon receiving this notification if the time before the scheduled appearance is less than seven (7) days; if you are hearing or voice impaired, call 711. 7908348 1/12/26 and 1/19/26</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11451163</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11450280</link>
      <description>Notice at 4974 ORL Tower Road

Location: 4974 ORL Tower Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
INVITATION TO BID   CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY (CFX) ORLANDO, FLORIDASealed Electronic Bids for the work generally described below will be received on February 18, 2026, until 1:30p.m., Orlando local time, as shown on the CFX website. The CFX website will serve as the official instrument to determine when a bid is received.  A submittal that is received after the date/time specified will be rejected. Rejection of a submittal under those circumstances shall not be the basis of a protest pursuant to the CFX Procedure for Resolution of Protests.  Bid opening at CFXs Headquarters Building located at 4974 ORL Tower Road, Orlando, FL. 32807, shall immediately follow the bid submittal deadline. Such bid opening will additionally be accessible by online stream by use of the web-conference information provided in the full version of this invitation to bid.  SYSTEMWIDE GUARDRAIL PROTECTION IMPROVEMENTS SOLICITATION NO. 251202, PROJECT NO. 599-170E  The work consists of Systemwide Guardrail Protection Improvements along State Roads 408, 417, 429, 528, and 538 at 16 locations that require water body protection. The scope includes the removal of existing guardrail, clearing and grubbing, installing new guardrail, placing miscellaneous asphalt, earthwork, and lighting improvements. The work is located in Orange County, Florida.  For a full version of the invitation for this project including additional information regarding availability of the Bidding Documents, pre-qualification requirements, pre-bid meeting, protest procedure, and bonding requirements refer to CFXs web site at www.CFXWay.com.  CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY  Aneth Williams Director of Procurement 7917337 1/11/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11450280</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/77/11450277.pdf</link>
      <description>1/11/2026 Orange County invites the community to LPA &amp; BCC hearings regarding the University Boulevard Pedestrian/ Cyclist Safety Study


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/11/2026 Orange County invites the community to LPA &amp; BCC hearings regarding the University Boulevard Pedestrian/ Cyclist Safety Study. Orange County is evaluating concepts to address the safety and needs of the pedestrians, cyclists, and transit users along the study corridor, while observing the current efficiency of the 1.25-mile roadway segment of University Boulevard, from Semoran Boulevard to Goldenrod Road. The purpose of this meeting is to provide an update of the completed study activities to date, and to present the Recommended Improvement Concept to the public for review and comment.  The LPA hearing will be held on August 21, 2025.  The BCC hearing will be held on August 26, 2025. Both hearings will be held at the Orange County Commission Chambers (201 S. Rosalind Ave., Orlando, FL 32801). The LPA hearing will begin at 9 a.m. and the BCC at 2 p.m., or shortly thereafter. The public will have opportunities to ask questions and provide comments after presentations. Project information is available on the project website at www.universityboulevardpedestriancyclistsafetystudy.com or on the Orange County website at www.ocfl.net.  For more information, please contact: Blanche Hardy, P.G., ARM Orange County Project Manager Transportation Planning Division Phone: 407-836-0257 Email: blanche.hardy@ocfl.net Para informacin en Espaol, llame a: Esther Fernndez, Ingeniera II Departamento de Obras Pblicas del Condado de Orange Divisin de Ingeniera Telfono: 407-836-7982 Correo Electrnico: esther.fernandez@ocfl.net  Public participation is solicited without regard to race, color, national origin, age, sex, religion, income, disability, or familial status. Persons who require language translation or interpretive services, which are provided at no cost, should contact Orange County Title VI/Nondiscrimination Coordinator Richard Dicks Jr. at 407-836-5379 or richard.dicksjr@ocfl.net at least seven (7)  days prior to the meeting. Persons requiring special accommo- dations under the American with Disabilities Act of 1990 (ADA)  may request assistance from County ADA Coordinator Nicola Norton at 407-836-6568 or nicola.norton@ocfl.net at least seven (7) days prior to the meeting.  What LPA Hearing BCC Hearing When 08/21/2025, at 9 a.m. 08/26/2025, at 2 p.m. Where 201 S. Rosalind Ave., Orlando, FL 32801   PUBLIC NOTICE  University Boulevard Pedestrian/Cyclist Safety Study Local Planning Agency (LPA) &amp; Board of County Commissioners (BCC) Hearings  7917027</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11450277</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11450277.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/54/11450254.pdf</link>
      <description>1/11/26 1


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/11/26 1. Call to Order 2. Roll Call 3. Election of Officers of the Board of Trustees 4. Presentation and approval of minutes of the meeting held on September 25 and September 30, 2025 5. Presentation of the annual report of the Board of Trustees 6. Quarterly Agreed-Upon Procedures Process Review 7. Transaction of any business that may properly be brought before the Board a. Reaffirmation of Resolution 98-1 b. Scheduling of Meetings January 22, 2026  Annual meeting  confirmed  May 21,2026 Preliminary Budget Workshop  July 16, 2026 Funding Requests/Preliminary Budget September 10, 2026 Tentative Budget Hearing  September 24, 2026 Final Budget Hearing  8. Public Comment 9. Any other matter necessary to achieve the aforementioned goals 10. Adjournment  PERSONS WITH DISABILITIES NEEDING ASSISTANCE TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY OF THESE PROCEEDINGS SHOULD CONTACT BRANDON RICHTER AT 352-732-4260 extension 129 AT LEAST 48 HOURS BEFORE THE DATE OF THE SCHEDULED MEETING. If a person decides to appeal any decision or recommendation made by council with respect to any matter considered at this meeting, he/she will need record of the proceedings, and that for such purposes he may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. This agenda is provided to the North Lake County Hospital District only as a guide, and in no way limits their consideration to the items contained hereon. The North Lake County Hospital District has the sole right to determine those items they will discuss, consider, or act upon. Changes or amendments to this Agenda may occur at any time prior to, or during the scheduled meeting. It is recommended that if you have an interest in the meeting, you make every attempt to attend the meeting. This Agenda is provided only as a courtesy, and such provision in no way infers or conveys that the Agenda appearing here is or will be the Agenda considered at the meeting.   AGENDA  NORTH LAKE COUNTY HOSPITAL DISTRICT MEETING ON JANUARY 22, 2026 ANNUAL MEETING  LAKE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS ROOM  7908943</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11450254</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11450254.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/17/11449117.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11449117</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11449117.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11449039</link>
      <description>Notice at 2090 Continental Street

Location: 2090 Continental Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING  GRAMERCY FARMS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   The Board of Supervisors of the Gramercy Farms Community Development District will hold a meeting on January 16, 2026, at 9:00 a.m., at the Anthem Park Clubhouse, located at 2090 Continental Street, St. Cloud, Florida 34769.  A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the office of the District Manager, Rizzetta &amp; Company, Inc., located at 8529 South Park Circle, Suite 330, Orlando, Florida 32819, (407) 472-2471, during normal business hours. Additionally, a copy of the agenda, along with any meeting materials available in an electronic format, may be obtained at (www.gramercyfarmscdd.org).  The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.  Any person requiring special accommodations at the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1- 800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.  Brian Mendes District Manager   01/09/2026 7914521</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11449039</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11449007</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1972 Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of BEN HABRIT 
(An Irrevocable Express Trust ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1972 Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of BEN HABRIT 
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP STATE OF GEORGIA COUNTY OF HENRY) I, GOLIGHTLY, HAJJI also known as DAWID HAJJI TER'EL SAR OF CINCINNATI (affiant), a Ohioan National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of MCDONOUGH, County of HENRY, State of GEORGIA, which he recognizes and intends to maintain as his permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 1 Courthouse Square, McDonough, GA 30253, and that he formerly resided at 4777 E. Galbraith Rd, Cincinnati, OH 45236 (city) CINCINNATI (state) OHIO, but that his abode in Georgia constitutes his predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that he affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (Hajji Golightly) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (Hajji Golightly), providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (Hajji Golightly) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. H11522120, dated September 23rd, 2025. Affiant further declares that Hajji Golightly or the HAJJI FAMILY OF GOLIGHTLY ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Georgia, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile. I, Golightly, Hajji also known as DAWID HAJJI TER'EL SAR OF CINCINNATI, declare, state, verify under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America, that the above statements are true and correct, and with nothing further to state, I have affixed my seal, mark or signature below.
Golightly,Hajji(Affiant) Date 1201/25
January 9, 16, 2026
#COL-528</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11449007</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11448096</link>
      <description>INVITATION TO BID - WINTER SPRINGS EAST WATER RECLAMATION FACILITY (WRF)   Wharton-Smith, Inc


--- Full Notice Text ---
INVITATION TO BID - WINTER SPRINGS EAST WATER RECLAMATION FACILITY (WRF)   Wharton-Smith, Inc., the Construction Manager at Risk (CMAR) for the Winter Springs East WRF Project with the City of Winter Springs, invites you to submit a competitive bid for the following Bid Packages: Master Plant Contractor, Sitework, Fencing, Concrete, Pipeline, Demolition, Pre-Engineered Metal Building, Roofing, HVAC, Doors, Finishes, Steel Truss &amp; Metal Decking Supplier &amp; Erector, Flooring, Plumbing, Coatings, Instrumentation &amp; Controls, Electrical, Submersible Pumps, Slide Gates, Screen &amp; Compactors, Grit System, Large Bubble Mixing System, Rotary Lobe Blower, Submersible IR Propeller Pumps, Fine Bubble Aeration System, Coarse Bubble Diffusers, Clarifier System, Scum Pumps, RAS/WAS Pumps, Disk Filters, Vertical Turbine Pumps, Sodium Hypo System, Polyethylene Tanks, Mobile Sludge Dewatering System, and Diesel Generators. Wharton-Smith, Inc. and the City of Winter Springs will receive electronic bids for the project until the date and time specified below. All questions and bid proposals must be submitted electronically to the email address below and received by the deadlines provided. Bid Questions Deadline: 01/23/26 at 5:00 PM EST; Bid Due Date: 02/10/26 at 2:00 PM EST; Email for Submission: watergmpbids@whartonsmith.com; Pre-Bid Meeting &amp; Site Visit: A nonmandatory pre-bid meeting and site visit will be held for all bidders.; Date &amp; Time: 01/16/26 at 9:00 AM EST; For access to the contract documents, pre-bid site location, and all bid-related questions, please contact: Dwayne Kreidler; Wharton-Smith, Inc. watergmpbids@whartonsmith.com; 407-321-8410</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11448096</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11448095</link>
      <description>CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY 2026 BOARD MEETINGS NOTICE   The Central Florida Expressway Authority (CFX) announces the following Board Meet...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY 2026 BOARD MEETINGS NOTICE   The Central Florida Expressway Authority (CFX) announces the following Board Meetings to which all persons are invited.  February 12, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. April 9, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. June 11, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. August 13, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. October 8, 2026 at 9:00 a.m. December 10, 2026 at 9:00 a.m.  Meeting location unless otherwise notified: 4974 ORL Tower Road, Boardroom, Orlando, FL 32807.  For Further Information Contact: Central Florida Expressway Authority Mimi Lamaute 4974 ORL Tower Road, Orlando, FL 32807 Phone 407-690-5000 Website: www.CFXway.com  The agenda for each meeting will be posted on the CFX website seven (7) days in advance of the meeting.  Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), if any person with a disability as defined by the ADA needs special accommodation to participate in this proceeding, then not later than two (2) business days prior to the proceeding, he or she should contact the Central Florida Expressway Authority at 407-690-5000.  Persons who require translation services, which are provided at no cost, should contact CFX at 407-690-5000 x5316 or by email at Malaya.Bryan@CFXway.com at least three business days prior to the event.   1/08/2026 7916878</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11448095</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11447929</link>
      <description>951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL
www


--- Full Notice Text ---
951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL
www.tohowater.com 407.944.5000


PUBLIC NOTICE
WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA
2026 APPROVED BOARD MEETING DATES


The Water Cooperative of Central Florida approved the 2026 Board Meeting Schedule as: January 7, February 4, March 4, April 1, May 6, June 3, July 1, August 5, September 2, October 7, November 4 and December 2.
The purpose of these meetings is to act upon and approve any proposed regional water supply projects. Any changes to this schedule will be published for notification at least 7 days before subsequent adjustments.
The meetings will take place from 2:00pm to 3:00pm and be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Administration Building, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741.
Anyone interested in obtaining more information about these meetings may contact Todd Swingle at 407-944-5131. Any person requiring special accommodation at the meetings, because of a disability or physical impairment, should contact the Toho Executive Office at 407-944-5130.
January 8, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11447929</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11447928</link>
      <description>Notice at the self-service storage facility for rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property

Location: the self-service storage facility for rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC SALE
Pursuant to the Florida Self Storage Lien Act, the owner of a self-storage facility has a lien upon all personal property located at the self-service storage facility for rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property. Due to the failure to pay the rent, the owner is enforcing its lien and intends to sell or otherwise dispose of the personal property located in the rented spaces listed in this notice. THIS NOTICE IS BEING PROVIDED PURSUANT TO FLORIDA STATE LAW BEFORE the sale, the tenants listed may pay the amount necessary to satisfy the lien and the reasonable expenses incurred to redeem the personal property.
ADVERTISEMENT OF SALE: Notice is hereby given that the personal property located in the following storage units will be sold by competitive bidding.
Facility Name:
iStorage - Store 2512
Facility Address: 932 Dyer Blvd, Kissimmee, FL 34741
Facility Phone:(321) 343-4563
Derrick Tyson-Bed, chairs, bed frame, furniture, office chair, boxes, dresser, and books. David Higgins-Treadmill, pillows, boxes, cones, books, papers, tote bags, basket, wiring, shoes, misc items. Victor Poupart-matters, art, table, ironing board, neck massager, cabinet, misc items. Tashana Warner-Chair, table, toys, backpack, suitcase, desk, bedding, beach chair, bed frame, misc items. Dolores Eileen Donnell-bags, boxes, tubs, basket, black tote bags, stackable plastic drawers, dcor ginger bread house. Dolores Eileen Donnell-Chair, table, boxes tubs, rattan chair, side tables, misc items. Shimara Ayala-boxes, bags, basket, table, tubs, books, misc items. Christian Hernandez-Double unit chairs, building materials, bike, side table, chemicals, stove, freezer. Christopher Boturla-bins, chair, table, lamps, suitcase, bag, cabinet, misc items. Nigeria Newberry-bags, boxes, clothes, shoes and toys.
Description: Bidding:
All bidding will take place online at StorageTreasures.com on 01/27/2026, at 9:00 A.M. Property will be sold to the highest bidder.
January 8, 15, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11447928</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11447918</link>
      <description>Notice at Section 13

Location: Section 13

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE
Notice is hereby provided that the South Florida Water Management District, on December 30, 2025, issued an Environmental Resource Permit #49-114582-P, Application #250821-56211 to Forestar (USA) Real Estate Group, Inc., authorizing construction and operation of stormwater management system serving the residential development known as Thomason Estates, Osceola County, located at Section 13, Township 26, Range 30. The project will develop 30 single family lots and associated stormwater infrastructure serving 10.31 acres of residential development. A copy of the permit can be obtained by contacting the Regulatory Records Management Section, during normal business hours, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday, except legal holidays, at 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, FL 33406, Regulation Division, by telephone at 561-682-6911, by e-mail at permits@sfwmd.gov, or by accessing the permit directly from the Districts website (www.sfwmd.gov) using the Application/Permit Search on the ePermitting page.
The District's agency action is final unless a timely petition for an administrative hearing is filed under Sections 120.569 and 120.57 of the Florida Statutes before the deadline for filing a petition.
As required by Sections 120.569 and 120.60(3), Fla. Stat., the following is notice of the opportunities which may be available for administrative hearing or judicial review when the substantial interests of a party are determined by an agency. Please note that this Notice of Rights is not intended to provide legal advice. Not all of the legal proceedings detailed below may be an applicable or appropriate remedy. You may wish to consult an attorney regarding your legal rights.
RIGHT TO REQUEST ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
A person whose substantial interests are or may be affected by the South Florida Water Management Districts (SFWMD or District) action has the right to request an administrative hearing on that action pursuant to Sections 120.569 and 120.57, Fla. Stat. Persons seeking a hearing on a SFWMD decision which affects or may affect their substantial interests shall file a petition for hearing with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD, in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein, within 21 days of receipt of written notice of the decision, unless one of the following shorter time periods apply: (1) within 14 days of the notice of consolidated intent to grant or deny concurrently reviewed applications for environmental resource permits and use of sovereign submerged lands pursuant to Section 373.427, Fla. Stat.; or (2) within 14 days of service of an Administrative Order pursuant to Section 373.119(1), Fla. Stat. "Receipt of written notice of agency decision" means receipt of written notice through mail, electronic mail, or posting that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action, or publication of notice that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action. Any person who receives written notice of a SFWMD decision and fails to file a written request for hearing within the timeframe described above waives the right to request a hearing on that decision.
If the District takes final agency action which materially differs from the noticed intended agency decision, persons who may be substantially affected shall, unless otherwise provided by law, have an additional Rule 28-106.111, Fla. Admin. Code, point of entry.
Any person to whom an emergency order is directed pursuant to Section 373.119(2), Fla. Stat., shall comply therewith immediately, but on petition to the board shall be afforded a hearing as soon as possible.
A person may file a request for an extension of time for filing a petition. The SFWMD may, for good cause, grant the request. Requests for extension of time must be filed with the SFWMD prior to the deadline for filing a petition for hearing. Such requests for extension shall contain a certificate that the moving party has consulted with all other parties concerning the extension and that the SFWMD and any other parties agree to or oppose the extension. A timely request for an extension of time shall toll the running of the time period for filing a petition until the request is acted upon.
FILING INSTRUCTIONS
A petition for administrative hearing must be filed with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD. Filings with the Office of the District Clerk may be made by mail, hand-delivery, or e-mail. Filings by facsimile will not be accepted. A petition for administrative hearing or other document is deemed filed upon receipt during normal business hours by the Office of the District Clerk at SFWMD headquarters in West Palm Beach, Florida. The Districts normal business hours are 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m., excluding weekends and District holidays. Any document received by the Office of the District Clerk after 5:00 p.m. shall be deemed filed as of 8:00 a.m. on the next regular business day. Additional filing instructions are as follows:
 * Filings by mail must be addressed to the Office of the District Clerk, 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, Florida 33406.
 * Filings by hand-delivery must be delivered to the Office of the District Clerk. Delivery of a petition to the SFWMD's security desk does not constitute filing. It will be necessary to request that the SFWMD's security officer contact the Office of the District Clerk. An employee of the SFWMD's Clerk's office will receive and file the petition.
 * Filings by e-mail must be transmitted to the Office of the District Clerk at clerk@sfwmd.gov. The filing date for a document transmitted by electronic mail shall be the date the Office of the District Clerk receives the complete document. A party who files a document by e-mail shall (1) represent that the original physically signed document will be retained by that party for the duration of the proceeding and of any subsequent appeal or subsequent proceeding in that cause and that the party shall produce it upon the request of other parties; and (2) be responsible for any delay, disruption, or interruption of the electronic signals and accepts the full risk that the document may not be properly filed.
INITIATION OF AN ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
Pursuant to Sections 120.54(5)(b)4. and 120.569(2)(c), Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.201 and 28-106.301, Fla. Admin. Code, initiation of an administrative hearing shall be made by written petition to the SFWMD in legible form and on 8  by 11 inch white paper. All petitions shall contain:
 1. Identification of the action being contested, including the permit number, application number, SFWMD file number or any other SFWMD identification number, if known.
 2. The name, address, any email address, any facsimile number, and telephone number of the petitioner and petitioners representative, if any.
 3. An explanation of how the petitioners substantial interests will be affected by the agency determination.
 4. A statement of when and how the petitioner received notice of the SFWMDs decision.
 5. A statement of all disputed issues of material fact. If there are none, the petition must so indicate.
 6. A concise statement of the ultimate facts alleged, including the specific facts the petitioner contends warrant reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 7. A statement of the specific rules or statutes the petitioner contends require reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 8. If disputed issues of material fact exist, the statement must also include an explanation of how the alleged facts relate to the specific rules or statutes.
 9. A statement of the relief sought by the petitioner, stating precisely the action the petitioner wishes the SFWMD to take with respect to the SFWMDs proposed action.
MEDIATION
The procedures for pursuing mediation are set forth in Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.111 and 28-106.401.405, Fla. Admin. Code. The SFWMD is not proposing mediation for this agency action under Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., at this time.
RIGHT TO SEEK JUDICIAL REVIEW
Pursuant to Section 120.68, Fla. Stat., and in accordance with Florida Rule of Appellate Procedure 9.110, a party who is adversely affected by final SFWMD action may seek judicial review of the SFWMD's final decision by filing a notice of appeal with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein within 30 days of rendition of the order to be reviewed, and by filing a copy of the notice with the clerk of the appropriate district court of appeal.
January 8, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11447918</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11446532</link>
      <description>WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA 2026 APPROVED BOARD MEETING DATES   The Water Cooperative of Central Florida approved the 2026 Board Meeting S...


--- Full Notice Text ---
WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA 2026 APPROVED BOARD MEETING DATES   The Water Cooperative of Central Florida approved the 2026 Board Meeting Schedule as: January 7, February 4, March 4, April 1, May 6, June 3, July 1, August 5, September 2, October 7, November 4 and December 2.  The purpose of these meetings is to act upon and approve any proposed regional water supply projects. Any changes to this schedule will be published for notification at least 7 days before subsequent adjustments.  The meetings will take place from 2:00pm to 3:00pm and be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Administration Building, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741.  Anyone interested in obtaining more information about these meetings may contact Todd Swingle at 407-944-5131. Any person requiring special accommodation at the meetings, because of a disability or physical impairment, should contact the Toho Executive Office at 407-944-5130.   1/07/2026 7916181</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11446532</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11446530</link>
      <description>EVEREST GMR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT NOTICE OF SPECIAL MEETING AND ATTORNEY-CLIENT SESSION   Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervi...


--- Full Notice Text ---
EVEREST GMR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT NOTICE OF SPECIAL MEETING AND ATTORNEY-CLIENT SESSION   Notice is hereby given that the Board of Supervisors of the Everest GMR Community Development District (the District) will conduct a special meeting and hold an attorney-client session on:  Date: Wednesday, January 14, 2026 Time: 11:00 a.m. Place: 8298 W Irlo Bronson Memorial Highway Orlando, Florida 32817  Attorney-client session is being conducted to discuss settlement negotiations or strategy related to litigation expenditures concerning the ongoing litigation entitled Everest GMR Community Development District v. WBA Portfolio Owner NLP Galaxy, LLC, et. al., Circuit Court of the Ninth Judicial Circuit in and for Osceola County, Florida, Case No. 2024-CA-003324 ED.  The special meeting and/or the attorney-client session may be continued to a date, time and place approved by the Board on the record at the meeting without additional publication of notice. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors will participate by telephone.  The special meeting, which is open to the public, will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law for Community Development Districts. The purpose of the meeting is to address the ongoing litigation referenced above and for the CDD Board to conduct all business authorized by law. At such time, the CDD Board is so authorized and may consider any business that may properly come before it. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained from the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting, LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Phone: (407) 723-5900.  The attorney-client session, which also begins at or shortly after 11:00 a.m. and is closed to the public, will address settlement negotiations and strategy sessions relating to litigation expenditures. These meetings are being held pursuant to Section 286.011(8), Florida Statutes. The following persons are anticipated to attend such attorney-client session: Jane Gaarlandt, Kwame Jackson, Johnathan Johnson, Dan Langley, Tom Callan, David B. Portwood, Sr., Emy Orellana, Sean Palmer, Raquel Marte-Lluberes, David Reed, and a court reporter. The attorney-client session is expected to last approximately thirty minutes.  Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in any portion of the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at least forty-eight (48) hours before the meeting by contacting the District Manager at (407) 723-5900. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), who can aid you in contacting the District Office.  A person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that the person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based.  Everest GMR CDD Jane Gaarlandt, District Manager   1/07/2026 7914649</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11446530</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11446528</link>
      <description>Bid Notices   The Orange County Board of County Commissioners is soliciting bids (IFBs) and proposals (RFPs) for goods, services, construction and ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Bid Notices   The Orange County Board of County Commissioners is soliciting bids (IFBs) and proposals (RFPs) for goods, services, construction and professional services. Interested parties may obtain documents and subscribe to notifications at www.ocfl.net/eprocurement. For assistance, email procurement@ocfl.net or call 407-836-5635.   Jan 7, 14, 21, 28, 2026 7906425</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11446528</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/29/11445129.pdf</link>
      <description>7912671 1/6/2026 On Monday, January 12, 2026  the Orlando City Council will consider proposed Ordinance #2025-46, entitled: AN ORDINANCE OF THE CIT...


--- Full Notice Text ---
7912671 1/6/2026 On Monday, January 12, 2026  the Orlando City Council will consider proposed Ordinance #2025-46, entitled: AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, ANNEXING THE JENNIE JEWEL DRIVE RIGHT OF WAY FROM ORANGE AVENUE TO SOUTH ROSALIND AVENUE AND THE SOUTH ROSALIND AVENUE RIGHT OF WAY FROM JENNIE JEWEL DRIVE TO HIGHWAY PLACE (VACATED) COMPRISED OF APPROXIMATELY 1.24 ACRES OF LAND INTO THE CORPORATE LIMITS OF THE CITY; PROVIDING  AMENDMENT OF THE CITYS BOUNDARY DESCRIPTION, AND FOR AMENDMENT OF THE CITYS OFFICIAL MAPS; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.   A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/councilmeeting at least 3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24 hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov.  7912671 Notice of Proposed Enactment</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11445129</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11445129.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/31/11443731.pdf</link>
      <description>1/4/2026 On Thursday, January 15, 2026, beginning at 9:00 A


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/4/2026 On Thursday, January 15, 2026, beginning at 9:00 A.M., or as soon thereafter as the matter may be heard, the Orange County Planning and Zoning Commission (PZC)/Local Planning Agency (LPA) shall conduct a public hearing in the Orange County Administration Center at 201 S. Rosalind Ave., 1st Floor, in downtown Orlando, FL, regarding the transmittal of the 2026-1 Regular Cycle Amendment to the Orange County Comprehensive Plan (CP), as it has been amended, as authorized by Chapter 163, Florida Statutes, for the following matter: A. Privately Initiated Future Land Use Element Map Amendment to Change the Designation of Lands within Areas Identified on Map Set Forth Below  1. 2026-1-A-4-1: C and LMDR to MHDR  Parcel ID#: 21-22-31-0000-00-009; 10850 E. Colonial Dr.; Generally located south of E. Colonial Dr.; west of Park Manor Dr.; north of Genevieve St., and east of Grayson Dr.  14.06 gross ac. ABBREVIATIONS INDEX: IND-Industrial; C-Commercial; O-Office; LDR-Low Density Residential; LMDR-Low-Medium Density Residential; MDR-Medium Density Residential; MHDR-Medium-High Density Residential; HDR-High Density Residential; PD-Planned Development; EDU-Educational; CONS-Wetland/Conservation; PR/OS-Parks/Recreation/Open Space; OS-Open Space; CONS-Conservation; PRES-Preservation; R-Rural/Agricultural; RS-Rural Settlement; RS 1/1-Rural Settlement 1/1; RS 1/2-Rural Settlement 1/2; RSLD 2/1-Rural Settlement Low Density; INST-Institutional; ACMU-Activity Center Mixed Use; ACR-Activity Center Residential; GC-Growth Center; PD-Planned Development; USA-Urban Service Area; WB-Water Body; CP-Comprehensive Plan; FLUM-Future Land Use Map; FLUE-Future Land Use Element; GOPS-Goals, Objectives, and Policies; OBJ-Objective; SR-State Road; AC-Acres Any interested party may appear at the public hearing and be heard regarding the consideration of the above described Comprehensive Plan Amendment, and submit written comments to the address below prior to the public hearing. The public hearing may be continued on the date of the public hearing to a future date or dates. Any interested party is hereby advised that the date, time, and place of any continuation of the public hearing shall be announced during the public hearing and that no further notices regarding these matters will be published. To obtain more detailed information, or to inspect the proposed amendment package, or any part thereof, any interested party may appear between 8:00 A.M. and 5:00 P.M., Monday through Friday, at the Orange County Planning Division, 201 S. Rosalind Ave., 2nd Floor, Orlando, FL, 32801, or telephone during those same hours at 407-836-5600, or send an email to planning@ocfl.net. In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), if any person with a disability as defined by the ADA needs special accommodation to participate in this proceeding, then not later than two (2) business days prior to the proceeding, that person should contact the Orange County Communications Division, 3 rd Floor, Orange County Administration Center, 201 S. Rosalind Ave., Orlando, FL, or telephone that department at (407) 836-6568.  PARA MAS INFORMACION, REFERENTE A ESTAS AUDIENCIAS PUBLICA, FAVOR COMMUNICARSE CON LA DIVISION DE  PLANIFICACION URBANA AL NUMERO, 407-836-5600. POU PLIS ENFMASYON AN KREYL, SOUPLE RELE (407) 836-3111.  NOTICE OF CHANGE TO THE ORANGE COUNTY COMPREHENSIVE PLAN  PUBLIC HEARING  7910271</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11443731</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11443731.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/28/11443728.pdf</link>
      <description>1/4/26 1


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/4/26 1. Call to Order 2. Roll Call 3. Election of Officers of the Board of Trustees 4. Presentation and approval of minutes of the meeting held on September 25 and September 30, 2025 5. Presentation of the annual report of the Board of Trustees 6. Quarterly Agreed-Upon Procedures Process Review 7. Transaction of any business that may properly be brought before the Board a. Reaffirmation of Resolution 98-1 b. Scheduling of Meetings January 22, 2026  Annual meeting  confirmed  May 21,2026 Preliminary Budget Workshop  July 16, 2026 Funding Requests/Preliminary Budget September 10, 2026 Tentative Budget Hearing  September 24, 2026 Final Budget Hearing  8. Public Comment 9. Any other matter necessary to achieve the aforementioned goals 10. Adjournment  PERSONS WITH DISABILITIES NEEDING ASSISTANCE TO PARTICIPATE IN ANY OF THESE PROCEEDINGS SHOULD CONTACT BRANDON RICHTER AT 352-732-4260 extension 129 AT LEAST 48 HOURS BEFORE THE DATE OF THE SCHEDULED MEETING. If a person decides to appeal any decision or recommendation made by council with respect to any matter considered at this meeting, he/she will need record of the proceedings, and that for such purposes he may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. This agenda is provided to the North Lake County Hospital District only as a guide, and in no way limits their consideration to the items contained hereon. The North Lake County Hospital District has the sole right to determine those items they will discuss, consider, or act upon. Changes or amendments to this Agenda may occur at any time prior to, or during the scheduled meeting. It is recommended that if you have an interest in the meeting, you make every attempt to attend the meeting. This Agenda is provided only as a courtesy, and such provision in no way infers or conveys that the Agenda appearing here is or will be the Agenda considered at the meeting.   AGENDA  NORTH LAKE COUNTY HOSPITAL DISTRICT MEETING ON JANUARY 22, 2026 ANNUAL MEETING  LAKE COUNTY BOARD OF COUNTY COMMISSIONERS ROOM  7908941</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11443728</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11443728.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11443227</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF BID  ORLANDO GIFTED ACADEMY EARLY SITE &amp; BUILDING DEMOLITION PROJECT  PROJECT NO


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF BID  ORLANDO GIFTED ACADEMY EARLY SITE &amp; BUILDING DEMOLITION PROJECT  PROJECT NO. 2025103 CONTRACT NO. RFQ 2412CM   Pirtle Construction, the Construction Manager for Orange County Public Schools, Orlando Gifted Academy Early Site &amp; Building Demolition, Project No. RFQ 2412CM is soliciting bids from qualified subcontractors and vendors. An Outreach/Pre-Bid Site Visit Meeting is scheduled at the project site on 1/13/2026 at 10:00 AM. A prequalification package is available to interested subcontractors and vendors upon request at preconstruction@pirtleconstruction.com. The project is at 1121 N. Fern Creek Avenue, Orlando, FL, 32803. The project will consist of the complete demolition of the 9 +/- acre existing campus, including the removal of existing buildings, site infrastructure, utilities, &amp; miscellaneous other items. The Project will also include remedial grading and site preparation for new building pads to support construction of the new campus. All bidders must submit their bids via email to preconstruction@pirtleconstruction.com by 5:00 PM on or before January 29, 2026. Pirtle reserves the right to reject any bids, waive informalities and irregularities in bidding, and accept bids that Pirtle considers to be in the projects best interest. If you are interested in bidding or have any pre-bid Requests for Information, please contact Matt Swieringa at mswieringa@pirtleconstruction.com. Pirtle is an Equal Opportunity Employer, License #CGC055033.   1/03 1/04 1/10 1/11/2026 7911371</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11443227</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11442793</link>
      <description>Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1972- Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
BEN HABRIT (An Irrevocable Express ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1972- Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
BEN HABRIT (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) MISCELLANEOUS AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Georgia &amp; Florida:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on September 27, 1990, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST. The TRUSTEE shall:
 1. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
 2. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust. WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING: BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a Hajji Golightly BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a Terrell Golightly BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a GOLIGHTLY, HAJJI BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a GOLIGHTLY, TERRELL BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a HAJJI FAMILY OF GOLIGHTLY ESTATE BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a Hajji Golightly BANKRUPTCY ESTATE BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DAWID HAJJI TER'EL SAR OF CINCINNATI BEN HABRIT EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a BET DAWID TRUST ENTERPRISE
BET DAWID TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a Hajji Golightly
BET DAWID TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a DAWID HAJJI TER'EL SAR OF CINCINNATI HEADQUARTERS: 4777 E. Galbraith Rd, Cincinnati, OH 45236
PRINCIPAL: 5415 Park St N, Saint Petersburg, FL 33709
MAILING: 50 Lincoln RD, STE C 1011, McDonough, GA, 30253 AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH, IS AS FOLLOWS: NAME: INTEREST: SIGNATURE:


Acua, Ana Isabel, Sole Trustee 100% Hajji Golightly, Manager 0%


January 2, 2026
#COL-531</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11442793</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11442789</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable E...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 8:20 AM:


The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of FLATHEAD LAKE, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on August 22, 2014 at 5:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigration officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlors declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:


P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality


I, Norred, Scott Edward (creditor) d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD NORRED (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my CALIFORNIA Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.
I declare that my name is Norred, Scott Edward also known as LORD DEBUYS. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Californian National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Montana republic of the United States of America  (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4. 
T A K E J U D I C I A L N O T I C E, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Montana Forms, County Municipality Forms, all MT DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission. I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1978  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or
Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


I, Norred, Scott Edward, born in the land of CALIFORNIA United States of America, territory of GLENDORA, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Norred, Scott Edward being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States (Public Law 94-241  March 24, 1976  Article III.  90 STAT. 266  Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.


Place of Meeting: 100 Main Street, Kalispell, Montana, 59901



There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 8:25 AM


__________________________________________
Norred, Scott Edward Settlor/Trust Protector



_________________________________________
Lozano, Harol M. Sole Trustee

January 2, 2026
#COL-529</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11442789</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11442788</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1996
Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Georgia &amp; Florida: The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on December 26, 2015, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a AVERY, DONOVAN JORDAN
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN FAMILY OF AVERY ESTATE
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY BANKRUPTCY ESTATE SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELOHIM DJA HIGH LORD OF ATLANTA
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PHI DEI TRUST ENTERPRISE
PHI DEI TRUST ENTERPTISE d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY
PHI DEI TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a ELOHIM DJA HIGH LORD OF ATLANTA
HEADQUARTERS: 1000 MEDICAL CENTER BLVD. LAWRENCEVILLE, GA 30245
PRINCIPAL: 5515 Vista View Way, Oviedo, FL 32765
MAILING: 267 LANGELY DR, UNIT 1202 LAWRENCEVILLE, GA 30046-6907
January 2, 2026
#COL-527</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11442788</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11442787</link>
      <description>Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Exp...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT


To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Montana &amp; Florida:


The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on August 22, 2014, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.


Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST.


The TRUSTEE shall:
 1. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
 2. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.


WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:


FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD NORRED
FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a NORRED, SCOTT EDWARD
FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD FAMILY OF NORRED ESTATE
FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD NORRED BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LORD DEBUYS
FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LAKESHORE HOLDINGS
LAKESHORE HOLDINGS TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD NORRED
LAKESHORE HOLDINGS TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a LORD DEBUYS


HEADQUARTERS: 150 W Rte 66, Glendora, CA 91740
PRINCIPAL: 1150 Douglas Avenue, Altamonte Springs, FL 32714
MAILING: 100 Main Street, Kalispell, MT, 59901


AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH, IS AS FOLLOWS:


NAME:
INTEREST:
SIGNATURE:





Lozano, Harol M. , Sole Trustee


100% OWNER





SCOTT EDWARD NORRED, Manager


0%

January 2, 2026
#COL-530</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11442787</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11442017</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF 2026 CFTOD REGULAR BOARD MEETINGS   Please take notice that the Board of Supervisors of the Central Florida Tourism Oversight District wi...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF 2026 CFTOD REGULAR BOARD MEETINGS   Please take notice that the Board of Supervisors of the Central Florida Tourism Oversight District will meet in regular session at 1900 Hotel Plaza Boulevard, Lake Buena Vista, Florida, commencing at 10:30 a.m. (unless otherwise indicated below) on the following 2026 calendar year dates to conduct its regular board meetings:  January 23 February 27 March 27 April 24 May 29 June 26 July 24 August 28 September 11 @5:05pm (Budget-1st Reading) September 25 @5:05pm (Budget-Final reading) October 23 November 20 December 18  Interested parties may appear at the public meeting(s) to be heard with respect to the proposed resolution(s) and other matters on the agenda(s). If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.   1/01/2026 7906003</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11442017</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441784</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASS...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS


Notice is hereby given that the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) intends to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments to be levied by the District pursuant to Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.


The Board of Supervisors of the District will conduct a public hearing on January 8, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room  HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the public hearing is to consider the adoption of a resolution authorizing the District to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments (the Uniform Method) to be levied by the District on properties located on land included in, or to be added to, the District.


The District may levy non-ad valorem special assessments for the purpose of financing, acquiring, maintaining and/or operating community development facilities, services, and improvements within and without the boundaries of the District, to consist of, among other things, onsite and offsite sanitary sewer collection, onsite and offsite water distribution, master stormwater management system, electrical service system (underground), conservation mitigation, onsite and offsite public roadway improvements, landscape/irrigation wells and distribution/hardscape within master public roads, and/or any other lawful improvements or services of the District.


Owners of the properties to be assessed and other interested parties may appear at the public hearing and be heard regarding the use of the Uniform Method. This hearing is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and location to be specified on the record at the hearing. There may be occasions when Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the hearing and/or meeting is asked to contact the District Managers office at c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the hearing and/or meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the hearing is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 25, 2025
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441784</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441782</link>
      <description>TOHO BOARD OF SUPERVISORS 2026 MEETING SCHEDULE


Please be advised pursuant to Section 189


--- Full Notice Text ---
TOHO BOARD OF SUPERVISORS 2026 MEETING SCHEDULE


Please be advised pursuant to Section 189.417 Florida Statutes that, the Board of Supervisors of the Tohopekaliga Water Authority, an independent special district of the State of Florida ("TOHO"), has adopted a schedule of regular meetings for calendar year 2026 as set forth below, on the second Wednesday of each month, excluding January and November.


These regular meetings of TOHO, and the two Budget Workshops, will be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Boardroom, First Floor, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida, commencing at 5.00 pm.
JANUARY 21
FEBRUARY 11
MARCH 11
APRIL 8
MAY 13
JUNE 10
JUNE 24 (Capital Budget Workshop)
JULY 8
AUGUST 12
AUGUST 26 (Operating Budget Workshop)
SEPTEMBER 9
OCTOBER 14
NOVEMBER 18
DECEMBER 9


The purpose of these meetings will be to consider any matter deemed appropriate by TOHO, with the two Workshop dates also focused on Capital / Operating Budget as indicated above.


Any person deciding to appeal any decision of the Tohopekaliga Water Authority Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at these meetings will need a record of the proceedings. For such purpose, he/she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.


Copies of proposed Resolutions of TOHO, as well as the Agendas, may be obtained from the Executive Office, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


Any person requiring special accommodations at the public meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the Tohopekaliga Water Authority at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida 34741, (407) 944-5000
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441782</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441779</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
EVEREST GMR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF BOARD OF SUPERVISORS' MEETING


A regular Board of Supervisors meeting of the Everest GMR Community Development District will be held on Wednesday, January 14, 2026, at 11:00 a.m. at 8298 W Irlo Bronson Memorial Hwy, Kissimmee, FL 34747. A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, located at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, (407) 723-5900, during normal business hours. Additionally, a copy of the agenda may be obtained at http://everestgmrcdd.com/.


The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the pertinent provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5940 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Jane Gaarlandt
District Manager
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441779</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/96/11438396.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Neptune...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Neptune Middle School</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438396</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11438396.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/95/11438395.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Neptune...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Neptune Middle School</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438395</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11438395.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/94/11438394.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Oakwood...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Oakwood Drive</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438394</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11438394.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/93/11438393.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Cypress...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Finding of No Significant Impact and Notice of Intent to Request Release of Funds
Osceola County Housing and Community Services
Cypress Parkway</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438393</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11438393.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441305</link>
      <description>notice   Orange County Library District Board of Trustees FY 2026 The Orange County Library System Board of Trustees will meet at 6:00 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   Orange County Library District Board of Trustees FY 2026 The Orange County Library System Board of Trustees will meet at 6:00 p.m. on January 8, 2026: Orlando Public Library Albertson Room, 3rd floor 101 E Central Boulevard Orlando, Florida 32801 Subject: Board Meeting   Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, states that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by a board, agency, or commission with respect to any matter considered at a meeting or hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  La Seccin 286.0105 de los Estatutos de la Florida establece que si una persona decide apelar cualquier decisin tomada por una junta, agencia o comisin con respecto a cualquier asunto considerado en una reunin o audiencia, necesitar un registro de los procedimientos y que, para tal fin, es posible que deba asegurarse de que se haga un registro literal de los procedimientos. cuyo expediente incluye los testimonios y las pruebas en que se basar la apelacin.  Seksyon 286.0105, Lwa Florida, deklare ke si yon moun deside f apl kont nenpt desizyon ki te pran pa yon tablo, ajans, oswa komisyon ki gen rap ak nenpt pwoblm konsidere nan yon reyinyon oswa yon odyans, li pral bezwen yon dosye sou pwosedi yo, e ke, pou rezon sa yo, li ka bezwen asire ke yon dosye vbal nan pwosedi yo ft, ki dosye gen ladan temwayaj ak prv ki montre apl la dwe baze.  Orange County does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, sex, age, religion, disability or family status. Those with questions or concerns about nondiscrimination, those requiring special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), and those requiring language assistance (free of charge) should contact the Title VI/Nondiscrimination Coordinator at access@ocfl.net or by calling 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  If you are hearing or speech impaired, you may reach the phone numbers above by dialing 711.  El Condado de Orange no discrimina por motivos de raza, color, origen nacional, sexo, edad, religin, discapacidad o situacin familiar. Aquellos que tengan preguntas o inquietudes sobre la no discriminacin, aquellos que requieran asistencia especial segn la Ley de Estadounidenses con Discapacidades (ADA) y aquellos que requieran asistencia lingstica (gratuita) deben comunicarse con el Coordinador de No Discriminacin/Ttulo VI en access@ocfl.net o llamando 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  Si tiene problemas de audicin o del habla, puede comunicarse con los nmeros de telfono anteriores marcando 711.  Orange County pa f diskriminasyon sou baz ras, koul, orijin nasyonal, sks, laj, relijyon, andikap oswa sitiyasyon fanmi. Moun ki gen kesyon oswa enkyetid konsnan non diskriminasyon, moun ki bezwen asistans espesyal dapre Lwa Ameriken andikape yo (ADA), ak moun ki bezwen asistans nan lang (gratis) ta dwe kontakte Kowdonat Tit VI/Nondiscrimination nan access@ocfl.net oswa l yo rele 3-1-1 (407-836-3111).  Si w gen pwoblm pou tande oswa pou w pale, ou ka kontakte nimewo telefn ki anwo yo l w konpoze 711.   12/31/2025 7914845</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441305</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11441299</link>
      <description>Notice at 1844 Westfall Dr

Meeting: Wednesday, January 14, 2026 at 6:00 pm
Location: 1844 Westfall Dr

--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Community Meeting   Notice is hereby given that the Office of Student Enrollment of Orange County Public Schools, Florida, will have the following community meetings:  Wednesday, January 14, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Union Park Middle School located at 1844 Westfall Dr, Orlando, FL 32817 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Union Park MS consolidation with Discovery MS, Glenridge MS, Legacy MS, Odyssey MS, Roberto Clemente MS, and Union Park MS potentially impacted.  Thursday, January 15, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Bonneville Elementary School located at 14700 Sussex Dr, Orlando, FL 32826 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Bonneville ES consolidation with Bonneville ES, Columbia ES, and East Lake ES potentially impacted.  Thursday, January 15, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Orlo Vista Elementary School located at 3 S Hastings St, Orlando, FL 32835 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Orlo Vista ES consolidation with Eagles Nest ES, Eccleston ES, Ivey Lane ES, Oak Hill ES, Orlo Vista ES, and Washington Shores ES potentially impacted.  Wednesday, January 21, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Chickasaw Elementary School located at 6900 Autumnvale Dr, Orlando, FL 32822 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Chickasaw ES consolidation with Chickasaw ES, Deerwood ES, and Engelwood ES potentially impacted.  Wednesday, January 21, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Eccleston Elementary School located at 1500 Aaron Ave, Orlando, FL 32811 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Eccleston ES consolidation with Eagles Nest ES, Eccleston ES, Ivey Lane ES, Oak Hill ES, Orlo Vista ES, and Washington Shores ES potentially impacted.  Thursday, January 22, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at McCoy Elementary School located at 5225 S Semoran Blvd, Orlando, FL 32822 for a rezoning option(s) review session. McCoy ES consolidation with Lake George ES, McCoy ES, Shenandoah ES, and Ventura ES potentially impacted.  Thursday, January 22, 2026 at 6:00 pm, at Meadow Woods Elementary School located at 5225 S Semoran Blvd, Orlando, FL 32822 for a rezoning option(s) review session. Meadow Woods ES consolidation with Oakshire ES, Meadow Woods ES, Southwood ES, and Wyndham Lakes ES potentially impacted.  These are informational sessions where no formal action will be taken. In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities, Act persons needing a special accommodation to participate in this proceeding should contact the Office of Student Enrollment at 407.317.3342 at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting. Additional information may be obtained by contacting Staci Neal, Senior Director of Student Enrollment, at 407.317.3200 Ext. 2022189 or schoolrezoning@ocps.net.  Notice is hereby given that the Office of Student Enrollment of Orange County Public Schools, Florida, will have a School Board Work Session: Tuesday, January 27, 2026 at 1:00PM, at the Ronald Blocker Educational Leadership Center located at 445 W Amelia St., Orlando, FL, 32801 for a rezoning option(s) school board work session. The Office of Student Enrollment will present the rezoning option(s) for rezoning consolidations for these areas: Bonneville ES consolidation with Bonneville ES, Columbia ES, and East Lake ES potentially impacted. Chickasaw ES consolidation with Chickasaw ES, Deerwood ES, and Engelwood ES potentially impacted. Eccleston ES consolidation with Eagles Nest ES, Eccleston ES, Ivey Lane ES, Oak Hill ES, Orlo Vista ES, and Washington Shores ES potentially impacted. Orlo Vista ES consolidation with Eagles Nest ES, Eccleston ES, Ivey Lane ES, Oak Hill ES, Orlo Vista ES, and Washington Shores ES potentially impacted. McCoy ES consolidation with Lake George ES, McCoy ES, Shenandoah ES, and Ventura ES potentially impacted. Meadow Woods ES consolidation with Oakshire ES, Meadow Woods ES, Southwood ES, and Wyndham Lakes ES potentially impacted. Union Park MS consolidation with Discovery MS, Glenridge MS, Legacy MS, Odyssey MS, Roberto Clemente MS, and Union Park MS potentially impacted.  This is an informational session where no formal action will be taken. The school board work session is public; however, there is no input from the public at this meeting. Additional information may be obtained by contacting Staci Neal, Senior Director of Student Enrollment, at 407.317.3200 Ext. 2022189 or schoolrezoning@ocps.net.   12/31/2025 7911190</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11441299</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11438404</link>
      <description>TOHO BOARD OF SUPERVISORS 2026 MEETING SCHEDULE   Please be advised pursuant to Section 189


--- Full Notice Text ---
TOHO BOARD OF SUPERVISORS 2026 MEETING SCHEDULE   Please be advised pursuant to Section 189.417 Florida Statutes that, the Board of Supervisors of the Tohopekaliga Water Authority, an independent special district of the State of Florida (TOHO), has adopted a schedule of regular meetings for calendar year 2026 as set forth below, on the second Wednesday of each month, excluding January and November.  These regular meetings of TOHO, and the two Budget Workshops, will be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Boardroom, First Floor, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida, commencing at 5.00pm.  JANUARY 21 FEBRUARY 11 MARCH 11 APRIL 8 MAY 13 JUNE 10 JUNE 24 (Capital Budget Workshop) JULY 8 AUGUST 12 AUGUST 26 (Operating Budget Workshop) SEPTEMBER 9 OCTOBER 14 NOVEMBER 18 DECEMBER 9 The purpose of these meetings will be to consider any matter deemed appropriate by TOHO, with the two Workshop dates also focused on Capital / Operating Budget as indicated above.  Any person deciding to appeal any decision of the Tohopekaliga Water Authority Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at these meetings will need a record of the proceedings. For such purpose, he/she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  Copies of proposed Resolutions of TOHO, as well as the Agendas, may be obtained from the Executive Office, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.  Any person requiring special accommodations at the public meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the Tohopekaliga Water Authority at 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, Florida 34741, (407) 944-5000.   12/30/2025 7913612</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438404</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11438403</link>
      <description>Notice of Proposed Enactment   On Monday, January 12, 2026 the Orlando City Council will consider proposed Ordinance #2025-42, entitled AN ORDINANC...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Proposed Enactment   On Monday, January 12, 2026 the Orlando City Council will consider proposed Ordinance #2025-42, entitled AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE CITYS GROWTH MANAGEMENT PLAN TO CHANGE THE FUTURE LAND USE MAP DESIGNATION FOR CERTAIN LAND GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF PARK LAKE STREET, EAST OF HIGHLAND AVENUE SOUTH OF MARKS STREET AND WEST OF BROADWAY AVENUE COMPRISED OF 0.56 ACRES OF LAND, MORE OR LESS, FROM OFFICE LOW TO RESIDENTIAL MEDIUM INTENSITY; DELETING SUBAREA POLICY S.14.7; PROVIDING FOR AMENDMENT OF THE CITYS GROWTH MANAGEMENT PLAN; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/councilmeeting at least 3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24 hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov. 7910947 12/30/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438403</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11438402</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, January 12, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2025-45, entitled: AN ORDINA...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, January 12, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2025-45, entitled: AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, REZONING CERTAIN LAND GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF PARK LAKE STREET, EAST OF HIGHLAND AVENUE, SOUTH OF MARKS STREET AND WEST OF BROADWAY AVENUE AND COMPRISED OF 2.2 ACRES OF LAND, MORE OR LESS, FROM LOW INTENSITY OFFICE-RESIDENTIAL WITH THE TRADITIONAL CITY OVERLAY DISTRICT, TO PLANNED DEVELOPMENT WITH THE TRADITIONAL CITY OVERLAY DISTRICT, PROVIDING A DEVELOPMENT PLAN AND SPECIAL LAND DEVELOPMENT REGULATIONS OF THE PLANNED DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, PERMIT DISCLAIMER, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/council meeting at least 3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24 hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov.   12/30/2025 7908634</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11438402</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437884</link>
      <description>Notice at 19950 Nugent Street

Location: 19950 Nugent Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
RANGER DRAINAGE DISTRICT   2025-2026 YEARLY MEETING DATES AND TIMESThe meetings will be held at the Ranger Drainage District office located at 19950 Nugent Street, Orlando, Florida 32833 on the following dates:   Wednesday August 6, 2025  6:00 PM  Wednesday September 3, 2025 6:00 PM  Wednesday October 1, 2025  6:00 PM  Wednesday November 5, 2025  6:00 PM  Wednesday December 3, 2025  6:00 PM  Wednesday January 7, 2026  6:30 PM  Wednesday February 4, 2026  6:30 PM  Wednesday March 4, 2026  6:30 PM  Wednesday April 1, 2026  6:30 PM  Wednesday May 6, 2026  6:30 PM  Wednesday June 3, 2026  6:30 PM (Annual Landowners Meeting)  Wednesday June 3, 2026  7:30 PM (Regular Meeting)  Wednesday July 8, 2026  6:30 PM   12/29/25 7908886</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437884</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437883</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE   The Bay Lake City Council will hold its regular meeting at the CFTOD first floor boardroom, 1900 Hotel Plaza Blvd, Lake Buena Vist...


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE   The Bay Lake City Council will hold its regular meeting at the CFTOD first floor boardroom, 1900 Hotel Plaza Blvd, Lake Buena Vista, FL on January 7, 2026 at 8:30 am.  The agenda will be accessible on the city website in advance of the meeting or by contacting the City Clerk at a.iennaco@cityofbaylakefl.gov. Any person requiring special accommodations to access and participate in the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the City Clerk at least 48 hours prior to the meeting.12/29/2025 7907957</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437883</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437881</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE   The Lake Buena Vista City Council will hold its regular meeting at the CFTOD first floor boardroom, 1900 Hotel Plaza Blvd, Lake Bu...


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE   The Lake Buena Vista City Council will hold its regular meeting at the CFTOD first floor boardroom, 1900 Hotel Plaza Blvd, Lake Buena Vista, FL on January 7, 2026 at 9:00 am.  The agenda will be accessible on the city website in advance of the meeting or by contacting the City Clerk at a.iennaco@cityoflakebuenavistafl.gov Any person requiring special accommodations to access and participate in the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the City Clerk at least 48 hours prior to the meeting.   12/29/2025 7907920</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437881</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437880</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE ENACTMENT  CITY OF MAITLAND FLORIDA   PUBLIC NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the City of Maitland City Council will hold a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ORDINANCE ENACTMENT  CITY OF MAITLAND FLORIDA   PUBLIC NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the City of Maitland City Council will hold a Public Meeting on Monday January 12, 2026, at 6:30 P.M., or as soon thereafter as is reasonably possible, in the Council Chambers of Maitland City Hall,1776 Independence Lane, Maitland, Florida, to consider the following:  ORDINANCENO. 1453  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF MAITLAND, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE OFFICIAL ZONING MAP, A PART OF ARTICLE 1 OF THE MAITLAND LAND DEVELOPMENT CODE, BY CHANGING THE ZONING CLASSIFICATION OF PROPERTY GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF MAITLAND BOULEVARD AND WEST OF TRELAGO WAY, FURTHER DESCRIBED HEREIN, FROM PLANNED DEVELOPMENT TO PLANNED DEVELOPMENT; APPROVING A CONCEPTUAL DEVELOPMENT PLAN FOR LOT 3 OF MAITLAND CONCOURSE NORTH; AND PROVIDING FOR AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Interested parties may appear at said hearing and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. Any person who decides to appeal any decision of the City Council with respect to any matter considered at this hearing will need a record of the proceedings and for such purpose may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which appeal is to be based.  In accordance with Section 286.26, Florida Statutes, persons with disabilities requiring accommodations to participate in these proceedings should contact the City Clerks Office (407) 539-6219 at least 48 hours prior.  /s/ Lori Hollingsworth City Clerk   12/29/2025 78961237906955</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437880</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437059</link>
      <description>Public Notice   All interested parties within Orange, Osceola, and Seminole Counties are hereby advised that the Central Florida Regional Transport...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Public Notice   All interested parties within Orange, Osceola, and Seminole Counties are hereby advised that the Central Florida Regional Transportation Authority (LYNX) is applying to the Florida Department of Transportation for a capital grant under Section 5310 of the Federal Transit Act of 1991, as amended, for the purchase of ten (10) paratransit vehicles to be used for the provision of public transit services within rural areas of Orange, Osceola, and Seminole Counties. The wheelchair accessible vehicles will include on-board mobile data terminals, at an estimated total cost of $1,900,000.  Additionally, LYNX is applying to the Florida Department of Transportation for a capital grant under Section 5339 of the Federal Transit Act of 1991, as amended, for the purchase of two (2) Compressed Natural Gas (CNG) buses to be used for the provision of public transit services within rural areas of Orange and Osceola Counties. The wheelchair accessible vehicles will include on-board mobile data terminals and fareboxes, at an estimated total cost of $2,400,000.  This public notice is to provide an opportunity for Public Hearings for both projects listed above, and to advise all interested parties of the service intended if grant funds are awarded to ensure that those services will not represent a duplication of current or proposed services provided by existing transit or paratransit operators in the area.  This hearing will be conducted if and only if a written request is received by January 5, 2026, by 5:00pm EST. Requests for a hearing must be addressed to LYNX, 455 N Garland Ave. Orlando, FL 32801, Attention: Prahallad Vijayvargiya, and a copy sent to Florida Department of Transportation  District 5, 420 W Landstreet Rd., Orlando, FL 32824, Attention: Jo Santiago.  Florida Law and Title VI of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 Prohibits Discrimination in Public accommodation on the basis of race, color, sex, religion, sex, national origin, disability, income or of marital status. Persons believing they have been discriminated against on these conditions may file a complaint with the Florida Commission on Human Relations at 850-488-7082 or 800-342-8170 (voice messaging).   12/28/2025 7913271</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437059</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437058</link>
      <description>notice   1

Meeting: Monday, January 12, 2026 at 1:00 PM

--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   1. PS-26-15567-LA - Architectural and Engineering Services For The Osceola County Solid Waste Transfer Station. The solicitation document and any addenda can be accessed and downloaded from VendorLink at the following web address: Vendorlink.osceola.org. There will be a VIRTUAL NON-MANDATORY PRE-PROPOSAL CONFERENCE held on Monday, January 12, 2026 at 1:00 PM Local Time. Dial in at 407-906-2344, and when prompted, enter the following conference code: 852 500 276#. Please note the meeting will be audio recorded. The deadline for questions is Friday, January 16, 2026 at 4:00 PM Local Time. DUE DATE: Tuesday, February 3, 2026 at 2:00 PM Local Time. Contact: Luis Aviles (407) 742-0937.  FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT OSCEOLA COUNTYS VENDORLINK WEB SITE AT http://vendorlink.osceola.org.   12/28/2025 7912932</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437058</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437041</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Point Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Point Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year beginning October 1, 2025, at the Osceola County Administration Building, Lake Toho Conference Room, 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 1304, Kissimmee, FL 34741 starting at 11:00 A.M. or soon thereafter. These regular quarterly meetings will be on the following dates in 2026: February 19, April 16, July 16, and November 19. All meetings are open to the public.  In accordance with Chapter 286, Florida Statutes, the public is advised that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at this hearing, that person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. All meeting facilities are accessible in accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act. Individuals with disabilities requiring accommodations (i.e., sign language interpreter or materials in accessible format) or individuals with Limited English Proficiency requiring language interpreters to participate in County sponsored meetings, please contact the Countys ADA/Title VI Coordinator, at (407) 742-1200 (TTY Users Dial: 711 for the Florida Relay System) or cfd@osceola.org , at least five (5) business days prior to the meeting.   12/28/2025 7910609</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437041</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437040</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Creek Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Creek Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year beginning October 1, 2025, at the Osceola County Administration Building, Lake Toho Conference Room, 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 1304, Kissimmee, FL 34741 starting at 12:00 P.M. or soon thereafter. These regular quarterly meetings will be on the following dates in 2026: January 14, May 13, August 12, and November 4. All meetings are open to the public.  In accordance with Chapter 286, Florida Statutes, the public is advised that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at this hearing, that person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. All meeting facilities are accessible in accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act. Individuals with disabilities requiring accommodations (i.e., sign language interpreter or materials in accessible format) or individuals with Limited English Proficiency requiring language interpreters to participate in County sponsored meetings, please contact the Countys ADA/Title VI Coordinator, at (407) 742-1200 (TTY Users Dial: 711 for the Florida Relay System) or cfd@osceola.org , at least five (5) business days prior to the meeting.   12/28/2025 7910605</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437040</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437039</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Creek Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Creek Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year beginning October 1, 2025, at the Osceola County Administration Building, Lake Toho Conference Room, 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 1304, Kissimmee, FL 34741 starting at 12:00 P.M. or soon thereafter. These regular quarterly meetings will be on the following dates in 2026: January 14, May 13, August 12, and November 4. All meetings are open to the public.  In accordance with Chapter 286, Florida Statutes, the public is advised that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at this hearing, that person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. All meeting facilities are accessible in accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act. Individuals with disabilities requiring accommodations (i.e., sign language interpreter or materials in accessible format) or individuals with Limited English Proficiency requiring language interpreters to participate in County sponsored meetings, please contact the Countys ADA/Title VI Coordinator, at (407) 742-1200 (TTY Users Dial: 711 for the Florida Relay System) or cfd@osceola.org , at least five (5) business days prior to the meeting.   12/28/2025 7910461</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437039</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11437038</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Ridge Villas Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fisca...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF QUARTERLY MEETING SCHEDULE   The Indian Ridge Villas Common Facilities District will conduct its regular quarterly meetings for the fiscal year beginning October 1, 2025, at the Osceola County Administration Building, Lake Toho Conference Room, 1 Courthouse Square, Suite 1304, Kissimmee, FL 34741 starting at 6:00 P.M. or soon thereafter. These regular quarterly meetings will be on the following dates in 2026: January 8, April 9, July 9, and October 8. All meetings are open to the public.  In accordance with Chapter 286, Florida Statutes, the public is advised that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Board of Supervisors with respect to any matter considered at this hearing, that person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. All meeting facilities are accessible in accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act. Individuals with disabilities requiring accommodations (i.e., sign language interpreter or materials in accessible format) or individuals with Limited English Proficiency requiring language interpreters to participate in County sponsored meetings, please contact the Countys ADA/Title VI Coordinator, at (407) 742-1200 (TTY Users Dial: 711 for the Florida Relay System) or cfd@osceola.org , at least five (5) business days prior to the meeting.   12/28/2025 7910451</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437038</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/78/11437878.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11437878</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11437878.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11436050</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1996
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 11:40 AM:
The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANTIS, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on December, 26 2015 at 5:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of FERN PARK, SEMINOLE COUNTY FLORIDA, JEWISH HERITAGE NEWSPAPER PUBLICATION, (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality"
I, Avery, Donovan Jordan (creditor) d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my Georgia Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.
I declare that my name is Avery, Donovan Jordan also known as Elohim DJA High Lord of Atlanta. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Georgian National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Georgia republic of the United States of America - (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4.
TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Georgia Forms, County Municipality Forms, all "GA" DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; "all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission." I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1996 - "concluded"
-
Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or
Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
I, Avery, Donovan Jordan, born in the land of Georgia United States of America, territory of Gwinnett, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that "I, Avery. Donovan Jordan being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States (Public Law 94-241 - March 24, 1976  Article III. - 90 STAT. 266 - Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.
December 26, 2025
#COL-525</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11436050</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11436049</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1996
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP
STATE OF GEORGIA)
COUNTY OF GWINNETT)
I, AVERY, DONOVAN JORDAN also known as ELOHIM DJA HIGH LORD OF ATLANTA (affiant), a Georgian National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of LAWRENCEVILLE, County of GWINNETT, State of GEORGIA, which he recognizes and intends to maintain as his permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 75 Langley Dr, Lawrenceville, Georgia, and that he formerly resided at 1000 MEDICAL CENTER BLVD (city) LAWRENCEVILLE (state) GEORGIA, but that his abode in Georgia constitutes his predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that he affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY)providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. 25064129-1, dated AUGUST 13, 2025. Affiant further declares that DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY or the DONOVAN JORDAN FAMILY OF AVERY ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Georgia, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.
December 26, 2025
#COL-524</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11436049</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11435046</link>
      <description>UBLIC HEARING NOTICE FOR REQUESTS BEFORE THE CITY OF DELTONA CITY COMMISSIONThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold a public hearing(s) on the follo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
UBLIC HEARING NOTICE FOR REQUESTS BEFORE THE CITY OF DELTONA CITY COMMISSIONThe City of Deltona, Florida will hold a public hearing(s) on the following:ORDINANCE NO. 02-2026  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY OF DELTONA, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE GENERAL ORDINANCES, CHAPTER 66, TRAFFIC AND VEHICLES, TO UPDATE REGULATIONS RELATED TO MICROMOBILITY DEVICES IN ACCORDANCE WITH FLORIDA STATUTES; PROVIDING FOR CONFLICTS, CODIFICATION, SEVERABILITY, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE.  Public hearing(s) will be held as follows:	  City Commission (First Reading)  January 20, 2026, at 6:30 p.m.  at City Hall, 2345 Providence Boulevard, Deltona, Florida.  All interested parties are invited to provide their comments, views and objections to the Deltona City Commission as part of the public hearing(s). The failure of a person to appear during said public hearing(s) and to object either in person or in writing to said case may severely restrict the ability of such a person to contest it at a later date.  The associated paperwork may be inspected by the public at the Deltona City Hall, 2345 Providence Blvd., Deltona, Florida, Monday  Friday, 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m. For further information, contact the City Clerks Office at (386) 878-8500.  The date, time and place of any continuance of the above scheduled public hearing(s) will be announced at said public hearing(s) and no further notice regarding said continuance is required to be published.  If a person decides to appeal any decision made by the Deltona City Commission with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing(s), he or she will need a record of the proceedings, for such purpose, he or she may need to insure that a verbatim record of the proceeding is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  The City does not provide this verbatim record.  Individuals with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Manager in writing at CityManager@deltonafl.gov or to Deltona City Hall, 2345 Providence Blvd., Deltona, FL 32725 at least 48 hours prior to the meeting at which the person wishes to attend. The City is not permitted to provide the use of human physical assistance to physically handicapped persons in lieu of the construction or use of ramps or other mechanical devices in order to comply with Florida law. If proper accommodations for handicapped access cannot be made at a particular public meeting venue pursuant to a timely written request under Section 286.26 F.S., the City Manager shall change the venue of that meeting to a location where those accommodations can be provided.  All parties in interest and persons for or against aforementioned items will be given an opportunity to be heard at said Public Hearing(s).  Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona  If you should have any questions regarding the above ad, please contact my office at (386) 878-8500. Thank you.  Sincerely, /s/ Joyce Raftery Joyce Raftery, CMC, MMC City Clerk, City of Deltona   12/25/2025 7904345</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11435046</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434839</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASS...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS


Notice is hereby given that the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) intends to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments to be levied by the District pursuant to Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.


The Board of Supervisors of the District will conduct a public hearing on January 8, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room  HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the public hearing is to consider the adoption of a resolution authorizing the District to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments (the Uniform Method) to be levied by the District on properties located on land included in, or to be added to, the District.


The District may levy non-ad valorem special assessments for the purpose of financing, acquiring, maintaining and/or operating community development facilities, services, and improvements within and without the boundaries of the District, to consist of, among other things, onsite and offsite sanitary sewer collection, onsite and offsite water distribution, master stormwater management system, electrical service system (underground), conservation mitigation, onsite and offsite public roadway improvements, landscape/irrigation wells and distribution/hardscape within master public roads, and/or any other lawful improvements or services of the District.


Owners of the properties to be assessed and other interested parties may appear at the public hearing and be heard regarding the use of the Uniform Method. This hearing is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and location to be specified on the record at the hearing. There may be occasions when Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the hearing and/or meeting is asked to contact the District Managers office at c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the hearing and/or meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the hearing is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 25, 2025
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434839</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434832</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the S...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the South Lake Toho Community Development District (District) hereby gives notice of its intention to develop Rules of Procedure to govern the operations of the District. The proposed rule number is 2026-1.


The Rules of Procedure will address such areas as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings, competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings, as well as any other area of the general operation of the District.


The purpose and effect of the Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. The specific grant of rulemaking authority for the adoption of the proposed Rules of Procedure includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes. The specific laws implemented in the proposed Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 120.542, 120.5435, 120.56, 120.69, 120.81, 189.053, 189.069, 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011, 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.012, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes.


A copy of the proposed Rules of Procedure and the related incorporated documents, if any, may be obtained by contacting the District Manager, c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, torrese@whhassociates.com.


Ernesto Torres, District Manager
South Lake Toho Community Development District
December 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434832</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/26/11434326.pdf</link>
      <description>St


--- Full Notice Text ---
St. Cloud City Council Advisory Committee &amp; Board Members Needed
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434326</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11434326.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434262</link>
      <description>Legal AdThis is notification that the St


--- Full Notice Text ---
Legal AdThis is notification that the St. Johns River Water Management District (District) has received  the Individual Consumptive Use Permit (CUP) permit application(s) listed below:   City of Winter Park, 401 S Park Ave, Winter Park, FL 32789-4386 Consumptive Use Permit  application #7624-7, received October 10, 2025. The applicant proposes the use of 14.24  million gallons per day (mgd) of groundwater from the Lower Floridan aquifer for public supply  use. The withdrawals used by this project will consist of Groundwater from FAS - Lower Floridan aquifer via 8 active wells in Orange and Seminole Counties, located in Section 2, Township 22  South, Range 29 East; Sections 3 and 6, Township 22 South, Range 30 East; and Section 33,  Township 21 South, Range 30 East. This project is known as City of Winter Park.The file(s) containing the permit application(s) are available at www.sjrwmd.com/permitting and  then click on Regulatory Permit Search.  The District issues two types of Individual consumptive use permits (CUPs)  staff-issued CUPs and Governing Board-issued CUPs. Decisions on Individual CUP application(s) will be made at  either a District service center (if staff issued) or at Districts Governing Board meeting where  permit applications that have not been delegated to District staff will be acted upon. The  Governing Board normally meets on the second Tuesday of the month.   Objections, comments, questions, or information regarding an application for an Individual CUP  must be made in writing and received by the Office Director, Office of Records and Regulatory  Support, P.O. Box 1429, Palatka, FL 32178-1429, or by e-mail at applicationsupport@sjrwmd. com, as soon as possible after the notification of the application receipt. The Permit Application  Number or the Project Name should be included in the objection. If the District receives a timely  substantial objection, the objector will receive written notice of the Districts decision (or intended decision) on the permit application.   A Notice of Decision (or Notice of Intended District Decision) will be provided to persons who  timely requested individual notice. A request for individual notice must be received by the Office  Director, Office of Records and Regulatory Support, prior to the date of the Notice of Decision  (or Notice of Intended District Decisions) is generated. Please note that filing a written objection  does not entitle you to a Chapter 120, Florida Statutes, administrative hearing. For more  information, call (386) 329-4570.   12/24/2025 7912790</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434262</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434261</link>
      <description>Legal AdThis is notification that the St


--- Full Notice Text ---
Legal AdThis is notification that the St. Johns River Water Management District (District) has received  the Individual Consumptive Use Permit (CUP) permit application(s) listed below:   City of Mascotte, 100 E Myers Blvd, Mascotte, FL 34753-9766 Consumptive Use Permit  application #2453-9, received December 01, 2025. The applicant proposes the use of 2.84 mgd  of groundwater for public supply use. The withdrawals used by this project will consist of  groundwater from the Lower Floridan aquifer via two active wells and groundwater from the  Upper Floridan aquifer via three active wells in Lake County, located in Sections 14 and 15,  Township 22 South, Range 24 East for a project known as City of Mascotte.The file(s) containing the permit application(s) are available at www.sjrwmd.com/permitting and  then click on Regulatory Permit Search.  The District issues two types of Individual consumptive use permits (CUPs)  staff-issued CUPs and Governing Board-issued CUPs. Decisions on Individual CUP application(s) will be made at  either a District service center (if staff issued) or at Districts Governing Board meeting where  permit applications that have not been delegated to District staff will be acted upon. The  Governing Board normally meets on the second Tuesday of the month.   Objections, comments, questions, or information regarding an application for an Individual CUP  must be made in writing and received by the Office Director, Office of Records and Regulatory  Support, P.O. Box 1429, Palatka, FL 32178-1429, or by e-mail at applicationsupport@sjrwmd. com, as soon as possible after the notification of the application receipt. The Permit Application  Number or the Project Name should be included in the objection. If the District receives a timely  substantial objection, the objector will receive written notice of the Districts decision (or intended decision) on the permit application.   A Notice of Decision (or Notice of Intended District Decision) will be provided to persons who  timely requested individual notice. A request for individual notice must be received by the Office  Director, Office of Records and Regulatory Support, prior to the date of the Notice of Decision  (or Notice of Intended District Decisions) is generated. Please note that filing a written objection  does not entitle you to a Chapter 120, Florida Statutes, administrative hearing. For more  information, call (386) 329-4570.   12/24/2025 7912787</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434261</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11434259</link>
      <description>Legal AdThis is notification that the St


--- Full Notice Text ---
Legal AdThis is notification that the St. Johns River Water Management District (District) has received  the Individual Consumptive Use Permit (CUP) permit application(s) listed below:   City of Winter Garden, 300 W Plant St, Winter Garden, FL 34787-3009 Consumptive Use  Permit application #3368-7, received June 05, 2025. The applicant requests the use of 8.79  million gallons per day (mgd) of groundwater from the Upper and Lower Floridan aquifers for  public supply use. The withdrawals used by this project will consist of Groundwater from FAS -  Lower Floridan Aquifer via 2 active wells; Groundwater from FAS - Upper Floridan Aquifer via 5  wells (4 active, 1 proposed) in Orange County, located in Sections 12, and 23, Township 22  South, Range 27 East; and Section 3, Township 23 South, Range 27 East. This project is  known as City of Winter Garden.The file(s) containing the permit application(s) are available at www.sjrwmd.com/permitting and  then click on Regulatory Permit Search.  The District issues two types of Individual consumptive use permits (CUPs)  staff-issued CUPs and Governing Board-issued CUPs. Decisions on Individual CUP application(s) will be made at  either a District service center (if staff issued) or at Districts Governing Board meeting where  permit applications that have not been delegated to District staff will be acted upon. The  Governing Board normally meets on the second Tuesday of the month.   Objections, comments, questions, or information regarding an application for an Individual CUP  must be made in writing and received by the Office Director, Office of Records and Regulatory  Support, P.O. Box 1429, Palatka, FL 32178-1429, or by e-mail at applicationsupport@sjrwmd. com, as soon as possible after the notification of the application receipt. The Permit Application  Number or the Project Name should be included in the objection. If the District receives a timely  substantial objection, the objector will receive written notice of the Districts decision (or intended decision) on the permit application.   A Notice of Decision (or Notice of Intended District Decision) will be provided to persons who  timely requested individual notice. A request for individual notice must be received by the Office  Director, Office of Records and Regulatory Support, prior to the date of the Notice of Decision  (or Notice of Intended District Decisions) is generated. Please note that filing a written objection  does not entitle you to a Chapter 120, Florida Statutes, administrative hearing. For more  information, call (386) 329-4570.   12/24/2025 7912740</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11434259</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432195</link>
      <description>REQUEST FOR QUALIFICATIONS FOR ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   The Enterprise Community Development Distri...


--- Full Notice Text ---
REQUEST FOR QUALIFICATIONS FOR ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   The Enterprise Community Development District (District), located in Osceola County, Florida, announces that professional engineering services will be required on a continuing basis for the Districts utility and stormwater improvements and other public improvements authorized by Chapter 190, Florida Statutes. The engineering firm selected will act in the general capacity of District Engineer and provide District engineering services, as required.  Any firm or individual (Applicant) desiring to provide professional services to the District must: 1) hold applicable federal, state and local licenses; 2) be authorized to do business in Florida in accordance with Florida law; and 3) furnish a statement (Qualification Statement) of its qualifications and past experience on U.S. General Service Administrations Architect-Engineer Qualifications, Standard Form No. 330, with pertinent supporting data. Among other things, Applicants must submit information relating to: a) the ability and adequacy of the Applicants professional personnel; b) whether the Applicant is a certified minority business enterprise; c) the Applicants willingness to meet time and budget requirements; d) the Applicants past experience and performance, including but not limited to past experience as a District Engineer for any community development districts and past experience with Osceola County; e) the geographic location of the Applicants headquarters and offices; f) the current and projected workloads of the Applicant; and g) the volume of work previously awarded to the Applicant by the District. Further, each Applicant must identify the specific individual affiliated with the Applicant who would be handling District meetings, construction services, and other engineering tasks.  The District will review all Applicants and will comply with Florida law, including the Consultants Competitive Negotiations Act, Chapter 287, Florida Statutes (CCNA). All applicants interested must submit eight (8) copies of Standard Form No. 330 and Qualification Statement by 12:00 p.m. on Wednesday, December 31, 2025 to the attention of Angel Montagna, Inframark, IMS, 313 Campus Street, Celebration, Florida 34747 (District Managers Office).  The Board shall select and rank the Applicants using the requirements set forth in the CCNA and the evaluation criteria on file with the District Manager, and the highest ranked Applicant will be requested to enter into contract negotiations. If an agreement cannot be reached between the District and the highest ranked Applicant, negotiations will cease and begin with the next highest ranked Applicant, and if these negotiations are unsuccessful, will continue to the third highest ranked Applicant.  The District reserves the right to reject any and all Qualification Statements. Additionally, there is no express or implied obligation for the District to reimburse Applicants for any expenses associated with the preparation and submittal of the Qualification Statements in response to this request.  Any protest regarding the terms of this Notice, or the evaluation criteria on file with the District Manager, must be filed in writing, within seventy-two (72) calendar hours (excluding Saturdays, Sundays, and state holidays) after the publication of this Notice. The formal protest setting forth with particularity the facts and law upon which the protest is based shall be filed within seven (7) calendar days (including Saturdays, Sundays, and state holidays) after the initial notice of protest was filed. Failure to timely file a notice of protest or failure to timely file a formal written protest shall constitute a waiver of any right to object or protest with respect to aforesaid Notice or evaluation criteria provisions. Any person who files a notice of protest shall provide to the District, simultaneous with the filing of the notice, a protest bond with a responsible surety to be approved by the District and in the amount of Ten Thousand Dollars ($10,000.00). Additional information and requirements regarding protests are set forth in the Districts Rules of Procedure, which are available from the District Manager.  ENTERPRISE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT DISTRICT ENGINEER PROPOSALS COMPETITIVE SELECTION CRITERIA  1) Ability and Adequacy of Professional Personnel (Weight: 25 Points) Consider the capabilities and experience of key personnel within the firm including certification, training, and education; affiliations and memberships with professional organizations; etc.  2) Consultants Past Performance (Weight: 25 Points) Past performance for other Community Development Districts in other contracts; amount of experience on similar projects; character, integrity, reputation, of respondent; etc.  3) Geographic Location (Weight: 20 Points) Consider the geographic location of the firms headquarters, offices and personnel in relation to the project.  4) Willingness to Meet Time and Budget Requirements (Weight: 15 Points) Consider the consultants ability and desire to meet time and budget requirements including rates, staffing levels and past performance on previous projects; etc.  5) Certified Minority Business Enterprise (Weight: 5 Points) Consider whether the firm is a Certified Minority Business Enterprise. Award either all eligible points or none.  6) Recent, Current and Projected Workloads (Weight: 5 Points) Consider the recent, current and projected workloads of the firm.  7) Volume of Work Previously Awarded to Consultant by District (Weight: 5 Points) Consider the desire to diversify the firms that receive work from the District; etc.   12/23/2025 7907422</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432195</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432194</link>
      <description>Notice of A Regular Meeting Celebration Community Development District   The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Celebration Community Development ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of A Regular Meeting Celebration Community Development District   The Board of Supervisors (Board) of the Celebration Community Development District (District) will hold a regular meeting on Tuesday, January 20, 2026, at 5:00 p.m. at the District Office, 313 Campus Street, Celebration, Florida 34747. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained by contacting the offices of the District Manager at 407-566-1935 or by visiting the Districts website at www.celebrationcdd.org. The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law for community development districts. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. Staff or Board members may participate by speaker telephone or communications media technology. Any person requiring special accommodations at the meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office. Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.   12/23/2025 Kerry Satterwhite, District Manager</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432194</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432188</link>
      <description>notice   On October 1, 2025, the Pennsylvania State Real Estate Commission accepted the voluntary surrender of Christina P


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   On October 1, 2025, the Pennsylvania State Real Estate Commission accepted the voluntary surrender of Christina P. Myers, license no. RS321972, of Orlando, Florida, because Myers failed to comply with continuing education requirements during the June 1, 2022 - May 31, 2024, biennial period.   12/23/2025 7911828</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432188</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11432182</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, January 12, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance no


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, January 12, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance no.: 2025-41, entitled AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, AMENDING CHAPTER 9, CODE OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, ENTITLED BUILDING SECURITY CODE; AMENDING ARTICLE I, SECTION 9.12 ENTITLED DEFINITIONS; AMENDING ARTICLE II, SECTION 9.14 ENTITLED DOORS AND SECTION 9.15 ENTITLED DOORS-LOCKING DEVICES; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CODIFICATION, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chambers, 2 nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. If a person decides to appeal any decision made by Council with respect to any matter considered at the hearing, he or she will need a record of the proceedings, and that, for such purpose, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, which record includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. The proposed ordinance may be inspected by the public at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2 nd floor of Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Qualified persons with disabilities needing auxiliary aid or service, or other assistance, so they can participate equally in this meeting should contact the Office of the City Clerk at (407) 246-2251 as soon as possible but no later than 48 hours before the meeting.   12/23/2025 7908635</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11432182</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11431368</link>
      <description>notice   On June 18, 2025, the Pennsylvania State Board of Nursing indefinitely suspended the license of Garry Roger Dormevil, RN, PA license no


--- Full Notice Text ---
notice   On June 18, 2025, the Pennsylvania State Board of Nursing indefinitely suspended the license of Garry Roger Dormevil, RN, PA license no. RN577888, last known of Mount Dora and Orlando, Florida. The Board took this action based on disciplinary action being taken against his license by the proper licensing authority of another state.   12/22/2025 7910807</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11431368</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11430551</link>
      <description>Notice at Vesta District Services

Meeting: Tuesday, January 6, 2026 at 10:00 a.m.
Location: Vesta District Services

--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of Workshop Change for the Avalon Groves Community Development District Board of Supervisors   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN by the Avalon Groves Community Development District that the Board of Supervisors (Board) will hold its January workshop on Tuesday, January 6, 2026 at 10:00 a.m. at the Palms at Serenoa Clubhouse, 17244 Bay Cedar Way, Clermont, FL 34714. At such times the Board may discuss any business that may properly come before it, but will not take any action outside of a regular Board meeting.  A copy of the agenda may be obtained by contacting the offices of the District Manager, located at Vesta District Services, 205 International Parkway, Suite 208, Lake Mary, FL 32746, Ph: (321) 263-0132 during normal business hours or on the Avalon Groves Community Development Districts website: www.avalongrovescdd.org seven days in advance of the meeting.  The workshop is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The workshop may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the workshop. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District staff may participate by speaker telephone.  Any person requiring special accommodations at the workshop because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the workshop. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.   12/21/2025 7906023</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11430551</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/29/11429429.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11429429</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11429429.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11429383</link>
      <description>Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certifica...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GRAY, DUKE OF ELYON, and INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS, and INVICTUS VERITAS d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE TUFTS.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE TUFTS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS TUFTS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS, THOMAS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE FAMILY OF TUFTS ESTATE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS TUFTS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GREY, DUKE OF ELYON
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GRAY
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS TRUST ENTERPRISE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS EQUIPMENT CONSULTANTS


HEADQUARTERS: 209 NORTH OAK AVENUE, SANFORD, FLORIDA 32771
PRINCIPAL: 1275 SHILOH ROAD, BLDG. 2750, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
MAILING: 2090 BAKER ROAD, 304-169, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Mationschek, Volker Michael, Sole Trustee 
100% EQUITABLE INTEREST/OWNER
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Tufts, Thomas Wayne, Settlor/Witness 
0% EQUITABLE INTEREST

December 12, 19, 2025
#COL-522</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11429383</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11429382</link>
      <description>Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certifica...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU, THE DUCHESS OF ELYON, and VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a VIA VERITAS, and VIA VERITAS d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TUFTS.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TUFTS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a VIA VERITAS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA TUFTS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS, CYNTHIA
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE FAMILY OF TUFTS ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE CHASTAIN
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE FAMILY OF CHASTAIN ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA TUFTS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU, THE DUCHESS OF ELYON
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA DUTCHESS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TRUST ENTERPRISE
HEADQUARTERS: 209 NORTH OAK AVENUE, SANFORD, FLORIDA 32771
PRINCIPAL: 1275 SHILOH ROAD, BLDG. 2750, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
MAILING: 2090 BAKER ROAD, 304-169, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Gordon-Jones, Daniel James, Sole Trustee 
100% EQUITABLE INTEREST/OWNER
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Tufts, Cynthia Marie, Settlor/Witness 
0% EQUITABLE INTEREST

December 12, 19, 2025
#COL-520</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11429382</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428238</link>
      <description>Notice at Section 12

Location: Section 12

--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE
Notice is hereby provided that the South Florida Water Management District, on November 21, 2025 issued an Environmental Resource Permit #49-112324-P, Application #250912-56991 to Forestar (USA) Real Estate Group, Inc., 1064 Greenwood Blvd, Suite 200, Lake Mary, FL 32746, authorizing construction and operation of stormwater management system serving 17.88 acres for a 43 lot single-family residential subdivision development known as Travis Landing Construction Plans in Osceola County, located at Section 12, Township 26, Range 28. A copy of the permit can be obtained by contacting the Regulatory Records Management Section, during normal business hours, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday, except legal holidays, at 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, FL 33406, Regulation Division, by telephone at 561-682-6911, by e-mail at permits@sfwmd.gov, or by accessing the permit directly from the Districts website (www.sfwmd.gov) using the Application/Permit Search on the ePermitting page. The District's agency action is final unless a timely petition for an administrative hearing is filed under Sections 120.569 and 120.57 of the Florida Statutes before the deadline for filing a petition. As required by Sections 120.569 and 120.60(3), Fla. Stat., the following is notice of the opportunities which may be available for administrative hearing or judicial review when the substantial interests of a party are determined by an agency. Please note that this Notice of Rights is not intended to provide legal advice. Not all of the legal proceedings detailed below may be an applicable or appropriate remedy. You may wish to consult an attorney regarding your legal rights.
RIGHT TO REQUEST ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
A person whose substantial interests are or may be affected by the South Florida Water Management Districts (SFWMD or District) action has the right to request an administrative hearing on that action pursuant to Sections 120.569 and 120.57, Fla. Stat. Persons seeking a hearing on a SFWMD decision which affects or may affect their substantial interests shall file a petition for hearing with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD, in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein, within 21 days of receipt of written notice of the decision, unless one of the following shorter time periods apply: (1) within 14 days of the notice of consolidated intent to grant or deny concurrently reviewed applications for environmental resource permits and use of sovereign submerged lands pursuant to Section 373.427, Fla. Stat.; or (2) within 14 days of service of an Administrative Order pursuant to Section 373.119(1), Fla. Stat. "Receipt of written notice of agency decision" means receipt of written notice through mail, electronic mail, or posting that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action, or publication of notice that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action. Any person who receives written notice of a SFWMD decision and fails to file a written request for hearing within the timeframe described above waives the right to request a hearing on that decision.
If the District takes final agency action which materially differs from the noticed intended agency decision, persons who may be substantially affected shall, unless otherwise provided by law, have an additional Rule 28-106.111, Fla. Admin. Code, point of entry.
Any person to whom an emergency order is directed pursuant to Section 373.119(2), Fla. Stat., shall comply therewith immediately, but on petition to the board shall be afforded a hearing as soon as possible.
A person may file a request for an extension of time for filing a petition. The SFWMD may, for good cause, grant the request. Requests for extension of time must be filed with the SFWMD prior to the deadline for filing a petition for hearing. Such requests for extension shall contain a certificate that the moving party has consulted with all other parties concerning the extension and that the SFWMD and any other parties agree to or oppose the extension. A timely request for an extension of time shall toll the running of the time period for filing a petition until the request is acted upon.
FILING INSTRUCTIONS
A petition for administrative hearing must be filed with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD. Filings with the Office of the District Clerk may be made by mail, hand-delivery, or e-mail. Filings by facsimile will not be accepted. A petition for administrative hearing or other document is deemed filed upon receipt during normal business hours by the Office of the District Clerk at SFWMD headquarters in West Palm Beach, Florida. The Districts normal business hours are 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m., excluding weekends and District holidays. Any document received by the Office of the District Clerk after 5:00 p.m. shall be deemed filed as of 8:00 a.m. on the next regular business day. Additional filing instructions are as follows:
 * Filings by mail must be addressed to the Office of the District Clerk, 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, Florida 33406.
 * Filings by hand-delivery must be delivered to the Office of the District Clerk. Delivery of a petition to the SFWMD's security desk does not constitute filing. It will be necessary to request that the SFWMD's security officer contact the Office of the District Clerk. An employee of the SFWMD's Clerk's office will receive and file the petition.
 * Filings by e-mail must be transmitted to the Office of the District Clerk at clerk@sfwmd.gov. The filing date for a document transmitted by electronic mail shall be the date the Office of the District Clerk receives the complete document. A party who files a document by e-mail shall (1) represent that the original physically signed document will be retained by that party for the duration of the proceeding and of any subsequent appeal or subsequent proceeding in that cause and that the party shall produce it upon the request of other parties; and (2) be responsible for any delay, disruption, or interruption of the electronic signals and accepts the full risk that the document may not be properly filed.
INITIATION OF AN ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING
Pursuant to Sections 120.54(5)(b)4. and 120.569(2)(c), Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.201 and 28-106.301, Fla. Admin. Code, initiation of an administrative hearing shall be made by written petition to the SFWMD in legible form and on 8  by 11 inch white paper. All petitions shall contain:
 1. Identification of the action being contested, including the permit number, application number, SFWMD file number or any other SFWMD identification number, if known.
 2. The name, address, any email address, any facsimile number, and telephone number of the petitioner and petitioners representative, if any.
 3. An explanation of how the petitioners substantial interests will be affected by the agency determination.
 4. A statement of when and how the petitioner received notice of the SFWMDs decision.
 5. A statement of all disputed issues of material fact. If there are none, the petition must so indicate.
 6. A concise statement of the ultimate facts alleged, including the specific facts the petitioner contends warrant reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 7. A statement of the specific rules or statutes the petitioner contends require reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action.
 8. If disputed issues of material fact exist, the statement must also include an explanation of how the alleged facts relate to the specific rules or statutes.
 9. A statement of the relief sought by the petitioner, stating precisely the action the petitioner wishes the SFWMD to take with respect to the SFWMDs proposed action.
MEDIATION
The procedures for pursuing mediation are set forth in Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.111 and 28-106.401.405, Fla. Admin. Code. The SFWMD is not proposing mediation for this agency action under Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., at this time.
RIGHT TO SEEK JUDICIAL REVIEW
Pursuant to Section 120.68, Fla. Stat., and in accordance with Florida Rule of Appellate Procedure 9.110, a party who is adversely affected by final SFWMD action may seek judicial review of the SFWMD's final decision by filing a notice of appeal with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein within 30 days of rendition of the order to be reviewed, and by filing a copy of the notice with the clerk of the appropriate district court of appeal.
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428238</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428226</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASS...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS


Notice is hereby given that the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) intends to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments to be levied by the District pursuant to Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.


The Board of Supervisors of the District will conduct a public hearing on January 8, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room  HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the public hearing is to consider the adoption of a resolution authorizing the District to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments (the Uniform Method) to be levied by the District on properties located on land included in, or to be added to, the District.


The District may levy non-ad valorem special assessments for the purpose of financing, acquiring, maintaining and/or operating community development facilities, services, and improvements within and without the boundaries of the District, to consist of, among other things, onsite and offsite sanitary sewer collection, onsite and offsite water distribution, master stormwater management system, electrical service system (underground), conservation mitigation, onsite and offsite public roadway improvements, landscape/irrigation wells and distribution/hardscape within master public roads, and/or any other lawful improvements or services of the District.


Owners of the properties to be assessed and other interested parties may appear at the public hearing and be heard regarding the use of the Uniform Method. This hearing is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and location to be specified on the record at the hearing. There may be occasions when Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the hearing and/or meeting is asked to contact the District Managers office at c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the hearing and/or meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the hearing is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 25, 2025
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428226</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428218</link>
      <description>Notice at 2300 Glades Road

Location: 2300 Glades Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF LANDOWNERS MEETING AND ELECTION AND MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT

Notice is hereby given to the public and all landowners within the South Lake Toho Community Development District (District) the location of which is generally described as comprising a parcel or parcels of land containing approximately 529 acres, generally located in Sections 4 and 9, Township 27S, Range 29E; and Sections 33 and 34, Township 26S, Range 29E, and within the unincorporated limits of Osceola County, Florida, advising that a meeting of landowners will be held for the purpose of electing five (5) persons to the District Board of Supervisors.


DATE: January 8, 2026
TIME: 9:30 a.m.
PLACE: Hart Memorial Library
211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room-HMC
Kissimmee, Florida 34741


Each landowner may vote in person or by written proxy. Proxy forms may be obtained upon request at the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, located at 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431; (Ph): 561-571-0010 (District Managers Office). At said meeting each landowner or his or her proxy shall be entitled to nominate persons for the position of Supervisor and cast one vote per acre of land, or fractional portion thereof, owned by him or her and located within the District for each person to be elected to the position of Supervisor. A fraction of an acre shall be treated as one acre, entitling the landowner to one vote with respect thereto. Platted lots shall be counted individually and rounded up to the nearest whole acre. The acreage of platted lots shall not be aggregated for determining the number of voting units held by a landowner or a landowners proxy. At the landowners meeting the landowners shall select a person to serve as the meeting chair and who shall conduct the meeting.


The landowners meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. A copy of the agenda for this meeting may be obtained from the District Office. Any person requiring special accommodations to participate in these meetings is asked to contact the District Office at (PH): 561-571-0010, at least 48 hours before the hearing. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or (800) 955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that such person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11428207</link>
      <description>HARBOR RESERVE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR ANNUAL AUDIT SERVICES


The Harbor Reserve Community Development District h...


--- Full Notice Text ---
HARBOR RESERVE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR ANNUAL AUDIT SERVICES


The Harbor Reserve Community Development District hereby requests proposals for annual financial auditing services. The proposal must provide for the auditing of the Districts financial records for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2025, with an option for four (4) additional annual renewals. The District is a local unit of special-purpose government created under Chapter 190, Florida Statutes, for the purpose of financing, constructing, and maintaining public infrastructure. The District is located in Osceola County, Florida. The District currently has an operating budget of approximately $98,540. The final contract will require that, among other things, the audit for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2025, be completed no later than June 1, 2026.


Each auditing entity submitting a proposal must be authorized to do business in Florida; hold all applicable state and federal professional licenses in good standing, including but not limited to a license under Chapter 473, Florida Statutes, and be qualified to conduct audits in accordance with Government Auditing Standards, as adopted by the Florida Board of Accountancy. Audits shall be conducted in accordance with Florida law and particularly section 218.39, Florida Statutes, and the rules of the Florida Auditor General.


Proposal packages, which include evaluation criteria and instructions to proposers, are available from the District Manager at the address and telephone number listed below.

Proposers must provide one (1) original hard copy and one (1) electronic copy of their proposal to Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC Attn: Jill Burns/Samantha Ham, District Manager/Staff, 219 East Livingston Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, in an envelope marked on the outside Auditing Services  Harbor Reserve Community Development District.


Proposals must be received by 5:00 PM on Friday, January 9, 2026, at the office address listed above. Proposals received after this time will not be eligible for consideration. Please direct all questions regarding this Notice to the District Manager who can be reached at (407) 841-5524.

Jill Burns, District Manager
Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC
December 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11428207</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Miscellaneous - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/46/11426446.pdf</link>
      <description>Notice of 30-Day Comment Period
Submission of Section 108 loan application and substantial amendment to the 2025-2029 consolidated plan and 2025 a...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of 30-Day Comment Period
Submission of Section 108 loan application and substantial amendment to the 2025-2029 consolidated plan and 2025 annual action plan

Aviso de perodo de comentarios de 30 das
presentacin de la solicitud de prestamo de la seccin 108 y enmienda sustancial al plan consolidado 2025-2029 al plan de accin anual 2025
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426446</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11426446.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11426531</link>
      <description>REQUEST FOR LEGAL SERVICES  TOWN OF DUNDEE TOWN COMMISSIONThe Town of Dundee, Florida, is seeking Letters of Interest from qualified attorneys or l...


--- Full Notice Text ---
REQUEST FOR LEGAL SERVICES  TOWN OF DUNDEE TOWN COMMISSIONThe Town of Dundee, Florida, is seeking Letters of Interest from qualified attorneys or law firms to provide municipal legal services. The selected attorney or firm will serve as Town Attorney and provide general legal counsel to the Town Commission, Town Manager, and Town staff.  Interested firms shall send a letter of interest outlining the firms experience in providing municipal legal services and any other specialties applicable to municipal operations. A list of current or past client references shall be included.  All letters of interest and documentation shall be directed to Ken Cassel, Town Manager at 202 E Main Street, Dundee, Florida, 33838. Submittals may be sent electronically to the Town Clerk, Erica Anderson, EAnderson@townofdundee.com. All submissions shall be due to the town Clerk by Monday, January 19, 2026. All responses shall be gathered and presented to the Town Commission for review.  Firms shall be available on February 10, 2026, for a public interview with the Town Commission.  It is anticipated that the Town Commission will make a decision that evening and authorize the mayor to execute an engagement letter and hourly rates with the selected firm.  Any inquiries shall be directed to the Town Manager through the Town Clerk, Erica Anderson, at EAnderson@townofdundee.com or by phone at 863-438-8330 ext. 258 In accordance with the Americans with Disabilities Act and Florida Statute, Section 286.26, persons with disabilities needing special accommodations to participate in this proceeding should contact the Town Clerks Office, P.O. Box 1000, 202 East Main Street, Dundee, FL 33838, in writing not later than 48 hours prior to the proceeding.   7909151 12/17/25, 12/21/25, 12/24/25, 12/28/25, 12/31/25, 1/4/25</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11426531</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424664</link>
      <description>Notice of 2026 Meeting Schedule for City of Orlando Downtown Development Board and Community Redevelopment Agency Advisory BoardThe regular meeting...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of 2026 Meeting Schedule for City of Orlando Downtown Development Board and Community Redevelopment Agency Advisory BoardThe regular meeting schedule for the Downtown Development Board and Community Redevelopment Agency Advisory Board of the City of Orlando for 2026 is as follows: January 28, 2026, February 25, 2026, March 25, 2026, April 22, 2026, May 27, 2026, June 24, 2026, July 22, 2026, August 26, 2026, September 23, 2026, October 28, 2026, November 18, 2026, and December 2, 2026. Unless otherwise specifically noticed in the future, all meetings will take place at 3:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Veterans Conference Room, Second Floor, City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida, 32801. Any person who desires to appeal any decision made during the meeting will need a record of the proceedings, and for this purpose may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Qualified persons with disabilities needing auxiliary aid or service, or other assistance to participate equally in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office as soon as possible, but no later than 24 hours prior to such meeting.   12/16/2025 7907038</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424664</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424663</link>
      <description>Notice of January - June 2026 Meeting Schedule for the City of Orlando Community Redevelopment AgencyThe regular meeting schedule for the Community...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of January - June 2026 Meeting Schedule for the City of Orlando Community Redevelopment AgencyThe regular meeting schedule for the Community Redevelopment Agency of the City of Orlando for January  June of 2026 is as follows: January 12, 2026, January 26, 2026, February 9, 2026, February 23, 2026, March 16, 2026, April 6, 2025, April 20, 2026, May 11, 2026, June 8, 2026, and June 22, 2026. All meetings will take place in City Council Chambers, Second Floor, City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida, 32801 at 2:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible.   Any person who desires to appeal any decision made during the meeting will need a record of the proceedings, and for this purpose may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based.  Persons with disabilities needing assistance to participate in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office at least 24 hours prior to such meeting.   12/16/2025 7907030</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424663</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424662</link>
      <description>Notice of January  June 2026 Meeting Schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District Board of DirectorsThe regular meeting schedu...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of January  June 2026 Meeting Schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District Board of DirectorsThe regular meeting schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District Board of Directors for January-July of 2026 is as follows: January 12, 2026, January 26, 2026, February 9, 2026, February 23, 2026, March 16, 2026, April 6, 2026, April 20, 2026, May 11, 2026, June 8, 2026 and June 22, 2026.  All meetings will take place in City Council Chambers, Second Floor, City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida, 32801 at 2:00 p.m. or as soon thereafter as possible.   Any person who desires to appeal any decision made during the meeting will need a record of the proceedings, and for this purpose may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.  Qualified persons with disabilities needing auxiliary aid or service, or other assistance to participate equally in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office as soon as possible, but no later than 24 hours prior to such meeting.   12/16/2025 7907029</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424662</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424661</link>
      <description>Notice of 2026 Meeting Schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District Advisory CouncilThe regular meeting schedule for the Downt...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Notice of 2026 Meeting Schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District Advisory CouncilThe regular meeting schedule for the Downtown South Neighborhood Improvement District for 2026 is as follows: January 14, 2026, February 11, 2026, March 11, 2026, April 8, 2026, May 13, 2026, June 10, 2026, July 8, 2026, August 12, 2026, September 9, 2026, October 14, 2026, November 11, 2026, and December 9, 2026. Unless otherwise specifically noticed in the future, all meetings will take place at 9:00 a.m. or as soon thereafter as possible, in the Veterans Conference Room, Second Floor, City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, Florida, 32801. Any person who desires to appeal any decision made during the meeting will need a record of the proceedings, and for this purpose may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made which includes testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. Qualified persons with disabilities needing auxiliary aid or service, or other assistance to participate equally in any of these proceedings should contact the City Clerks office as soon as possible, but no later than 24 hours prior to such meeting.   12/16/2025 7907021</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424661</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424660</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE NARCOOSSEE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the Narcoo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE NARCOOSSEE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT   In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the Narcoossee Community Development District (District) hereby gives notice of its intention to develop Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, Chapter 1, to govern the operations of the District.  In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the Narcoossee Community Development District (District) hereby gives notice of its intention to develop Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure, Chapter 1, to govern the operations of the District.  The Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure will address such topics as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings and competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings, as well as any other area of the general operation of the District.  The purpose and effect of the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. The legal authority for the adoption of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure includes sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes (2025). The specific laws implemented in the Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 189.053, 189.069(2)(a)(15), 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011(3), 190.011(5), 190.011(15), 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0525, 255.0992, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes (2025).  A copy of the proposed Amended and Restated Rules of Procedure and any material proposed to be incorporated by reference may be obtained by contacting Jason Showe at the District Managers Office by mail at Governmental Management Services  Central Florida, LLC 219 E. Livingston Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, by telephone at (407) 841-5524, or by email at jshowe@gmscfl.com.  District Manager Narcoossee Community Development District   12/16/2025 7906541</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424660</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424091</link>
      <description>Public Notice   PUBLIC NOTICE: Cellco Partnership and its controlled affiliates doing business as Verizon Wireless (Verizon Wireless) proposes to b...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Public Notice   PUBLIC NOTICE: Cellco Partnership and its controlled affiliates doing business as Verizon Wireless (Verizon Wireless) proposes to build a 45-foot non-utility pole Communications Tower/Structure. Anticipated lighting application is none.  The Site location is 2603 Orlando Drive, Sanford, Seminole County, FL 32771, Lat: [28-46-50.94], Long: [-81-16-23.56].  The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Antenna Structure Registration (ASR, Form 854) filing number is A1325859.   ENVIRONMENTAL EFFECTS  Interested persons may review the application (www.fcc.gov/asr/applications) by entering the filing number.  Environmental concerns may be raised by filing a Request for Environmental Review (www.fcc.gov/asr/environmentalrequest) and online filings are strongly encouraged.  The mailing address to file a paper copy is: FCC Requests for Environmental Review, Attn: Ramon Williams, 445 12th Street SW, Washington, DC 20554.12/15/2025 7907555</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424091</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11423397</link>
      <description>Request for Proposal 04-26 AGENT OF RECORD   The Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida (COMMISSION) is seeking bids from Qualifie...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Request for Proposal 04-26 AGENT OF RECORD   The Utilities Commission, City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida (COMMISSION) is seeking bids from Qualified Vendors for: AGENT OF RECORD.  Proposals will be received electronically through Vendor Link https://www.myvendorlink.com/common/searchsolicitations.aspx?aid=358 until 2:30 P.M. (local time) January 27, 2026.  Those interested in submitting a bid may obtain instructions for obtaining bid forms from the office of the Procurement Manager 200 Canal Street New Smyrna Beach, FL 32168 386 424 3046.  The Utilities Commission reserves the right to waive informalities in any bid, to reject any and all bids in whole or in part, with or without cause, and/or accept bids or portions thereof that in its judgement will be in the best interest of the Utilities Commission.  UTILITIES COMMISSION City of New Smyrna Beach, Florida County of Volusia Maureen Lynch, CPPB Procurement Manager 7903879 12/14/2025</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11423397</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422830</link>
      <description>Notice at Auxiliary Water Treatment Plant ASR

Location: Auxiliary Water Treatment Plant ASR

--- Full Notice Text ---
State of Florida Department of Environmental Protection Notice of Draft Permit   The Department of Environmental Protection hereby provides notice that it has prepared a draft permit for the proposed project as detailed in the application, subject to the conditions specified in the draft permit and summarized below. The applicant, City of Sanford, Brynt Johnson, Public Works and Utilities Director, 300 North Park Avenue, Sanford, Florida  32771 applied on September 9, 2025, for a Class V ASR injection well construction permit modification. The project is located at Auxiliary Water Treatment Plant ASR, 3100 South Orlando Drive, Sanford, Florida 32773, in Seminole County (File 0307357-004-UC/5SR, WACS ID 97848). The permittee will continue to cycle test one non-hazardous Class V injection ASR-1 and associated monitor wells SZMW-1, SZMW-2, and CZMW-1 for the recharge, storage, and recovery of potable water from the Sanford Auxiliary Water Treatment Plant Number 2 and raw groundwater from the Hidden Lakes Wellfield. The ASR well will be tested according to the cycle test table in Specific Condition VI.A.7. The injection well is constructed with 138 feet of 17.4-inch casing reduced to 10.75-inch diameter casing to a depth of 530 feet below land surface (bls), and total depth of 631 feet bls. CZMW-1 is completed in the Upper Floridan aquifer within the confining zone from 430 feet to 480 feet bls. SZMW-1 and SZMW-2 are completed in the Upper Floridan aquifer within the injection zone from 530 feet to 628 feet bls and from 530 feet to 630 feet bls, respectively. The Department has permitting jurisdiction under Chapter 403 of the Florida Statutes and the rules adopted thereunder. The project is not exempt from permitting procedures. The Department has determined that an Underground Injection Control permit is required for the proposed work. Any interested person may submit written comments on the draft permit and may request a public meeting within 30 days after publication of this public notice. A request for a public meeting shall be submitted in writing and shall state the nature of the issues proposed to be raised in the meeting. If a public meeting is later scheduled, there will be another 30-day notice period for that meeting. Written comments or a public meeting request shall be submitted to the Department of Environmental Protection, Aquifer Protection Program, 2600 Blair Stone Road, MS 3530, Tallahassee, Florida 32399-2400, which is the office processing this permit application. All comments received within the 30-day period will be considered in formulation of the Departments final decision regarding permit issuance. The files associated with this order are available for public inspection during normal business hours, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m., Monday through Friday, except state holidays, at the Department of Environmental Protection, Central District, and at the Department of Environmental Protection, Aquifer Protection Program office in Tallahassee. Any additional information concerning this project may be obtained by contacting Jeremy Hart, Professional Geologist II, at 850-245-8657.   12/13/25 7907715</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422830</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424129</link>
      <description>Public Notice
NOTICE
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT FOR ARCHITECTURAL AND ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE ORANGE CENTER K8 CONVERSION REPURPOSE PROJECT
The Schoo...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Public Notice
NOTICE
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT FOR ARCHITECTURAL AND ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE ORANGE CENTER K8 CONVERSION REPURPOSE PROJECT
The School Board of Orange County, Florida, announces that Architectural and Engineering Services are required for the project listed below.
PROJECT NAME AND NUMBER: Orange Center K8 Conversion Repurpose Project, RFQ 2530PS
SERVICES TO BE PROVIDED: Architectural and Engineering Services.
PRE-SUBMITTAL MEETING: December 16, 2025, 10:00 a.m., via WebEx.
Meeting information will be posted on VendorLink.
Attendance is not mandatory.
OCPS CONTACT: Ed Ames, Facilities &amp; Construction Contracting
Orange County Public Schools
PROPOSALS ARE TO BE SUBMITTED: To VendorLink.
PROPOSAL DUE DATE: January 14, 2026, 2:00 p.m.
Requirements: Interested firms are required to comply with all requirements of the Request for Qualification (RFQ). All solicitations for Construction Related Services can be found at the following link: https://vendorlink.ocps.net/common/login.aspx. Furthermore, all Notices concerning this solicitation and award shall be posted to the aforementioned website. These Notices shall include, but are not limited to, shortlisting meeting dates and times, presenting meeting dates and times, presenting the intended decision, and providing decision information.
Equal Employment Opportunity: The School Board of Orange County, Florida, does not discriminate in admission or access to, or treatment or employment in its programs and activities, on the basis of race, color, religion, age, sex, national origin, marital status, disability, genetic information, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, or any other reason prohibited by law. The following individuals at the Ronald Blocker Educational Leadership Center, 445 West Amelia Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, attend to compliance matters: Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) Officer &amp; Title IX Coordinator: Keshara Cowans; ADA Coordinator: Jay Cardinali; Section 504 Coordinator: Tajuana Lee-Wenze. (407.317.3200).
December 12, 2025
December 19, 2025
January 2, 2026
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424129</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11424128</link>
      <description>NOTICE
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT FOR CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT SERVICES FOR THE ORANGE CENTER K8 CONVERSION REPURPOSE PROJECT
The School Board of Orange Co...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT FOR CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT SERVICES FOR THE ORANGE CENTER K8 CONVERSION REPURPOSE PROJECT
The School Board of Orange County, Florida, announces that Construction Management Services are required for the project listed below.
PROJECT NAME AND NUMBER: Orange Center K-8 Conversion Repurpose Project, RFQ 2531CM
SERVICES TO BE PROVIDED: Construction Management Services
PRE-SUBMITTAL MEETING: December 16, 2025, 10:00 a.m., via WebEx.
Meeting information will be posted on VendorLink.
Attendance is not mandatory.
OCPS CONTACT: Ed Ames, Facilities &amp; Construction Contracting
Orange County Public Schools
PROPOSALS ARE TO BE SUBMITTED: To VendorLink.
PROPOSAL DUE DATE: January 15, 2026, 2:00 p.m.
Requirements: Interested firms are required to comply with all requirements of the Request for Qualification (RFQ). All solicitations for Construction Related Services can be found at the following link: https://vendorlink.ocps.net/common/login.aspx. Furthermore, all Notices concerning this solicitation and award shall be posted to the aforementioned website. These Notices shall include, but are not limited to, shortlisting meeting dates and times, presenting meeting dates and times, presenting the intended decision, and providing decision information.
Equal Employment Opportunity: The School Board of Orange County, Florida, does not discriminate in admission or access to, or treatment or employment in its programs and activities, on the basis of race, color, religion, age, sex, national origin, marital status, disability, genetic information, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, or any other reason prohibited by law. The following individuals at the Ronald Blocker Educational Leadership Center, 445 West Amelia Street, Orlando, Florida 32801, attend to compliance matters: Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO) Officer &amp; Title IX Coordinator: Keshara Cowans; ADA Coordinator: Jay Cardinali; Section 504 Coordinator: Tajuana Lee-Wenze. (407.317.3200).
December 12, 2025
December 19, 2025
January 2, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11424128</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/81/11422281.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422281</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11422281.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422237</link>
      <description>DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. February 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2018 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-0000

Copyright Notice No. CR-2018-001
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)

Common Law Copyright Notice: All rights re; common law copyright of trade-name/trademark, JASON CALDWELL FAMILY OF DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS, JASON DAVIS, DAVIS, JASON CALDWELL, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LIBERTAS TRUST ENTERPRISE and DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST as well as any and all derivatives and variations in the spelling of said trade-names/trademarks  Copyright 02/05/2018, by DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST (the natural person). Said trade-names/trademarks, may neither be used, nor reproduced, neither in whole nor in part, nor in any manner whatsoever, without the prior, express, written consent and acknowledgment of DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST (the natural person) as signified by the signature of Acuna, Bercy (the Sole Trustee; non-resident alien) and Davis, Jason Caldwell (the Settlor, Trust Protector). With the intent of being contractually bound, any Juristic Person, as well as the agent of said Juristic, consents and agrees by this Copyright Notice that neither said Juristic Person, nor the agent of said Juristic Person, shall display, nor otherwise use in any manner, the trade-name/trademarks, nor common-law copyright described herein, nor any derivative of, nor any variation in the spelling of, said name without prior, express, written consent and acknowledgement of DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST, herein known as the Secured Party, as signified by Secured Partys signature. Secured Party neither grants, nor implies, nor otherwise gives consent for any unauthorized use of JASON CALDWELL FAMILY OF DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS, JASON DAVIS, DAVIS, JASON CALDWELL, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LIBERTAS TRUST ENTERPRISE and DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST, and all such unauthorized use is strictly prohibited. The Secured Party is not now, nor has ever been an accommodation party, not a surety, for the purported debtor, i.e. JASON CALDWELL FAMILY OF DAVIS ESTATE nor for any derivative of, nor for any variation in the spelling of, said name, nor for any other juristic person, the debtor (JASON CALDWELL DAVIS) is completely under jurisdiction of the Foreign Express Trust, DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST, an Irrevocable Trust Organization for tax treaty purposes associated with the Internal Revenue Service withholding compliances. The Secured Party is the holder of the U.S. Department of State Annexed Security No. 25032199-1, Dated March, 21, 2025; The Florida non-Hague Convention Country Certificate No. 10681726, Dated February, 12, 2025; and the County of PALM BEACH, City of WEST PALM BEACH Certificate of Title No. 1091987-079000 as the Collateral for the Security Interest, known as Equity Secured Promissory Note No. PN-20180205-0001 in the amount of Nine Billion Dollar Lien with interest. See Copyright Depot No. 00093838-1 against all claims, legal actions, orders, warrants, judgements, demands, liabilities, losses, depositions, summons, lawsuits, costs, fines, liens, levies, penalties, damages interest, and expenses whatsoever, both absolute and contingent, as are due and as might come due, now existing and as might hereafter arise, and as might be suffered by, imposed on, and incurred by debtor for any and every reason, purpose, and cause whatsoever. This Notice by Declaration becomes a fully executed copyright notice wherein Davis, Jason Caldwell (The Settlor, Trust Protector) of the DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST, grants the Secured Party security interest in all of the debtors property and interest in property in the sum certain amount of Seven Billion Dollars ($7,000,000,000.00 USD) exercised by a Nine Billion Dollar ($9,000,000,000.00) Lien referenced with the Florida Secretary of State Financing Statement and in the Organic Public Record Orange Records Clerk Office non-Uniform Commercial Code Central Filing. For each trade-name/trademark used, per each occurrence of use (violations/infringement), plus triple damages, plus cost for each such use, as well as for each and every use of any and all derivatives of, and variations in the spelling of JASON CALDWELL FAMILY OF DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS, JASON DAVIS, DAVIS, JASON CALDWELL, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS ESTATE, JASON CALDWELL DAVIS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LIBERTAS TRUST ENTERPRISE and DEI PROVIDENTIA EXPRESS TRUST, the trust office shall refer to the Affidavit of Schedule of Fees for summary judgement granted by any court of record in the matters of equity.
December 5, 12, 2025
#COL-505</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422237</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422233</link>
      <description>Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certifica...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GRAY, DUKE OF ELYON, and INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS, and INVICTUS VERITAS d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE TUFTS.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE TUFTS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS TUFTS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS, THOMAS
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS WAYNE FAMILY OF TUFTS ESTATE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THOMAS TUFTS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GREY, DUKE OF ELYON
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a THADEUS GRAY
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a INVICTUS VERITAS TRUST ENTERPRISE
INVICTUS VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS EQUIPMENT CONSULTANTS


HEADQUARTERS: 209 NORTH OAK AVENUE, SANFORD, FLORIDA 32771
PRINCIPAL: 1275 SHILOH ROAD, BLDG. 2750, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
MAILING: 2090 BAKER ROAD, 304-169, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Mationschek, Volker Michael, Sole Trustee 
100% EQUITABLE INTEREST/OWNER
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Tufts, Thomas Wayne, Settlor/Witness 
0% EQUITABLE INTEREST

December 12, 19, 2025
#COL-522</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422233</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422232</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST Est. July 29th, in the year of our Lord, 1979 Anno Domini
Schedule D: Trustee Minutes 5-1979
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SUI GENERIS NEXUS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PUBLIC NOTICE OF PERMANENT TAX INJUNCTION AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY
Parties:
Sui Generis Nexus Express Trust
d/b/a KEVIN GERRARD MILES (Complainant)
VS.
Cook County Sheriff
Internal Revenue Service Commissioner
United States Department of Justice
Secretary of United States Department of Homeland Security
(Defendant)
INJUNCTION AGAINST ALL PUBLIC OFFICERS AND CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE INVOKING IRREPARABLE
INJURY
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Illinois &amp; North Carolina:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on July 29, 1979, the trustee received the Chattel Papers and Discovery, herein known as Permanent Tax Injunction, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing not limited to The ship Friendship, of Seminole Province, Florida, Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of SUI GENERIS NEXUS EXPRESS TRUST.
To all Parties stated above, a Maritime/Agricultural Termination of Lien is made effective July, 29, 1979 and the issuance of a lien held by preferred mortgage is made effective July, 29, 1979, in the office of Maryland Department of Assessments &amp; Taxation, under Original File Number 181425776, with The Federal Reserve System, E Pluribus Unum The United States of America, U.S. Department of Defense Finance and Accounting Services, Comptroller of Maryland, The United States Department of the Treasury 1789, North American Water and Power Alliance and the U.S. Treasury Department Internal Revenue Service (IRS);. The preferred mortgage lien is filed and recorded with the Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller by way of Memorandum of Trust File No. #COL-122, Dated February 21, 2025. The Chattel Paper is a documented vessel as any vessel of the United States that has been issued a certificate of documentation that might include a register, enrollment, license, or enrollment and license for various trades as prescribed in Section 2101 (10) of Title 46 SHIPPING. A Public Vessel
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. July 29th, in the year of our Lord, 1979 Anno Domini
Schedule D: Trustee Minutes 5-1979-"continuation"
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SUI GENERIS NEXUS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PUBLIC NOTICE OF PERMANENT TAX INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY
means a vessel that is owned, or demised chartered, and operated by the United States Government or a government of a foreign country; and is not engaged in commercial service, as prescribed in 2101 (24)(A)(B) of Title 46 SHIPPING.
The Department of Homeland Security U.S. Customs and Border Protection, has or will receive a LEIN NOTICE ([19 U.S.C. 66, 1564; 19 CFR 141.1120] under OMB Control Number 1651-0012 (CBP Form 3485) in recognition of the preferred mortgage on file by the Secretary of Homeland Security. The Public Vessel described in Certificate of Title is as follows:
Department of State File Number: 25043339-2/ Registered April 17, 2025, with Secretary MARCO RUBIO
State of Illinois State File Number: 112-1961 6046716 / Registered June 02, 1961, with Cook County Registrar FRANKLIN D. YODER
Certificate of Manifest Description:
Name: KEVIN GERRARD MILES Quantity: SINGLE
Weight: 7 pounds
Salvaged Title: Abandoned at BERTH, Lost at Sea
Maritime Informant: BEATRICE CARLICE
Time of Delivery: 04:25AM Military Time Location of Delivery: 365 W Oak, Chicago, Illinois Port of Entry: U.S. Customs and Board Protection Port Name: Illinois International Port District Location Address: 3600 E 95th St, IL 60617 Field Inspection Office: N/A
Manifest Inspector: N/A
Seal of Officer of Naturalization Court: Karen A. Yarbrough and Cook County
The abandoned wreckage (after-birth material) under claim by the 1302 Unam Sanctam Express Trust and all successors, permitted by Article 9 of The Barbary Treaties 1786-1816, Signed at Tunis August 28, 1797, is hereby revoked and subject to the preferred mortgage. The Public Vessel described in the Certificate of Manifest is also known as SUI GENERIS NEXUS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a KEVIN EL, THE BEY OF RALEIGH, which is not a citizen of the United States nor a national of the United States as described in [46 U.S.C.  104]. The Public Vessel, known as SUI GENERIS NEXUS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a KEVIN EL, THE BEY OF RALEIGH is not subject to any exclusive economic zone but under the protection of the Prince Pasha, Bey of Tunis, described in Article 12.
The contents of this Permanent Tax Injunction is public and private law made between HIS HIGHNESS THE HEAVEN- PROTECTED, THE SEID SA'ID SON OF THE SEID SULTAN, DEFENDER OF MASKAT AND ITS DEPENDENCIES, AND THE UNITED STATES, I.E. THE TERRITORY OF AMERICA, FOR THE SAKE OF INTERCOURSE, AND AMITY, AND THE PROMOTION OF TRADE, 1249 Hijrah translated in the Christian era of 1833; further prescribed in the Articles of Confederation, 1781. The SUI GENERIS NEXUS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a KEVIN GERRARD MILES and d/b/a KEVIN EL, THE BEY OF RALEIGH is the beneficial owner of the Public Vessel of the United States, which claims Tax Treaty Benefits, as a resident of Tunis (Tunisian subject), within the meaning of the income MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. July 29th, in the year of our Lord, 1979 Anno Domini
tax treaty between the United States and that country. Special rates and conditions: The beneficial owner is claiming the provisions of Schedule D: Trustee Minutes 5-1979 - "concluded"
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SUI GENERIS NEXUS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PUBLIC NOTICE OF PERMANENT TAX INJUNCTION AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY
Article 3 &amp; 6 (Treaty between the The Seid Sa'id and the United States 1833) and Article 12 (1797 Treaty of Peace and Friendship), paragraph 1, 4; of the treaty previously identified to claim a 0% rate of withholding on vessels of the United States federal and state income tax and real property valuation assessment owned by SUI GENERIS NEXUS EXPRESS TRUST. IT IS WRITTEN, the citizens of America have liberty to enter into any PORT of the PORTS of HIS HIGNESS (Article 2). Vessels of the United States of America, when they arrive at and enter the country which is under the rule of the Sultan, or any country whatever under his rule, shall not be subject to any charge except the import duty of five percent, upon the property, merchandize and lading landed (Article 3). The people of the United States, citizens of America, whenever they wish to resort to any of the provinces of the Sultan for the purposes of selling and buying, have permission so to do; and in landing their property they shall not be opposed; and whenever they wish to reside therein, there shall be no charge upon them for residence, nor any impost, but they shall be on the footing of the nation nearest in friendship (Article 6). The term "vessel of the United States", as used in Title 18, means a vessel belonging in whole or in part to the United States, or ANY CITIZEN THEREOF, or any corporation created by or under the laws of the United States, or of any State, Territory, District, or possession thereof.
Under penalties or perjury under the laws of the United States of America, I declare that I have examined the information on this form and to the best of my knowledge and belief it is true, correct, and complete. I further certify that; I am the individual that is the beneficial owner of all the income or proceeds to which a form W-8BEN relates for chapter 4 purposes and such form relates to income effectively connected with the conduct of a trade or business in the United States but is not subject to tax under an applicable income tax treaty.
SIGNED: Alix Acua Sole Trustee
DATED: October 16, 2025
December 12, 2025
#COL-514</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422232</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422231</link>
      <description>Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certifica...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Trustee approved the initial exchanges of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU, THE DUCHESS OF ELYON, and VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a VIA VERITAS, and VIA VERITAS d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TUFTS.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TUFTS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a VIA VERITAS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA TUFTS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TUFTS, CYNTHIA
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE FAMILY OF TUFTS ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE CHASTAIN
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE FAMILY OF CHASTAIN ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA TUFTS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU, THE DUCHESS OF ELYON
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA DUTCHESS
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ELLA SOPHIA BLEIU
VIA VERITAS EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a CYNTHIA MARIE TRUST ENTERPRISE
HEADQUARTERS: 209 NORTH OAK AVENUE, SANFORD, FLORIDA 32771
PRINCIPAL: 1275 SHILOH ROAD, BLDG. 2750, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
MAILING: 2090 BAKER ROAD, 304-169, KENNESAW, GEORGIA 30144
AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Gordon-Jones, Daniel James, Sole Trustee 
100% EQUITABLE INTEREST/OWNER
NAME:
EXTENT OF INTEREST:
Tufts, Cynthia Marie, Settlor/Witness 
0% EQUITABLE INTEREST

December 12, 19, 2025
#COL-520</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422231</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422230</link>
      <description>DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. March 22, 2018 AT 3:22 PM
Trustee Minutes 1.10-1988:

Other Property Exchange  Non-Real Estate Assets
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST
(an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the States of California or Florida:


The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on March 22, 2018, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to the Seminole County Recorder Office.


Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ALEJANDRO, GRAND DUKE OF RIVERSIDE.


The Trustee shall:
- Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
- Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business, respecting the holders and this Express Trust.


WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:


URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ALEJANDRO LOPEZ TERRAZAS
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LOPEZ TERRAZAS, ALEJANDRO
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ALEJANDRO FAMILY OF LOPEZ TERRAZAS ESTATE
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ALEJANDRO LOPEZ TERRAZAS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ALEJANDRO, GRAND DUKE OF RIVERSIDE
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a URSUS CONVALLIS TR
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a AURA TERRAE UNINC ASSOC
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a AURA TERRAE
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LEXSTYLE LLC
URSI AUREI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LEXSTYLE
URSUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a LEXSTYLE LLC
URSUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a LEXSTYLE
URSUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a AURA TERRAE UNINC ASSOC
URSUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a AURA TERRAE


Place of meeting: 5 Windsormere Way Ste 200, Oviedo, Florida 32765


AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
LUIS MIGUEL LOPEZ GOMEZ, Sole Trustee  100% Interest
ALEJANDRO LOPEZ TERRAZAS, Settlor/Trust Protector  0% Interest


s/ Lopez Gomez, Luis Miguel Sole Trustee
s/ Lopez Terrazas, Alejandro Settlor
December 12, 2025
#COL-516</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422230</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11422227</link>
      <description>DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. June 2, 2015 AT 2:30 PM
Trustee Minutes 1.10-1989:
Other Property Exchange  Non-Real Estate Assets
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST
(an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT


To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the States of California or Florida:


The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on June 2, 2015, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to the San Bernardino County Recorder Office.


Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a EMILY, GRAND DUCHESS OF REDLANDS.


The Trustee shall:
- Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
- Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business, respecting the holders and this Express Trust.


WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:


SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a EMILY ANNE HAID
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a HAID, EMILY ANNE
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a EMILY ANNE FAMILY OF HAID ESTATE
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a EMILY ANNE HAID BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a EMILY, GRAND DUCHESS OF REDLANDS
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SCIURUS CONVALLIS TR
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a AURA TERRAE UNINC ASSOC
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a AURA TERRAE
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ARMOR WEAR CO
SCIURUS AUREAM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a ARMOR WEAR
SCIURUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a AURA TERRAE UNINC ASSOC
SCIURUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a AURA TERRAE
SCIURUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a ARMOR WEAR CO
SCIURUS CONVALLIS TR d/b/a ARMOR WEAR


Place of meeting: 5 Windsormere Way Ste 200, Oviedo, Florida 32765


AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH IS AS FOLLOWS:
LUIS MIGUEL LOPEZ GOMEZ, Sole Trustee  100% Interest
EMILY ANNE HAID, Settlor/Trust Protector  0% Interest


s/ Lopez Gomez, Luis Miguel Sole Trustee
s/ Haid, Emily A. Settlor
December 12, 2025
#COL-517</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11422227</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420497</link>
      <description>REQUEST FOR QUALIFICATIONS FOR ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


RFQ for Engineering Services


The Sou...


--- Full Notice Text ---
REQUEST FOR QUALIFICATIONS FOR ENGINEERING SERVICES FOR THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


RFQ for Engineering Services


The South Lake Toho Community Development District (District), located in Osceola County, Florida, announces that professional engineering services will be required on a continuing basis for the Districts stormwater systems, and other public improvements authorized by Chapter 190, Florida Statutes. The engineering firm selected will act in the general capacity of District Engineer and will provide District engineering services, as required.


Any firm or individual (Applicant) desiring to provide professional services to the District must: 1) hold applicable federal, state and local licenses; 2) be authorized to do business in Florida in accordance with Florida law; and 3) furnish a statement (Qualification Statement) of its qualifications and past experience on U.S. General Service Administrations Architect-Engineer Qualifications, Standard Form No. 330, with pertinent supporting data. Among other things, Applicants must submit information relating to: a) the ability and adequacy of the Applicants professional personnel; b) whether the Applicant is a certified minority business enterprise; c) the Applicants willingness to meet time and budget requirements; d) the Applicants past experience and performance, including but not limited to past experience as a District Engineer for any community development districts and past experience with Osceola County, Florida; e) the geographic location of the Applicants headquarters and offices; f) the current and projected workloads of the Applicant; and g) the volume of work previously awarded to the Applicant by the District. Further, each Applicant must identify the specific individual affiliated with the Applicant who would be handling District meetings, construction services, and other engineering tasks.


The District will review all Applicants and will comply with Florida law, including the Consultants Competitive Negotiations Act, Chapter 287, Florida Statutes (CCNA). All Applicants interested must submit electronic copies of Standard Form No. 330 and the Qualification Statement by 12:00 p.m. on December 29, 2025 to attention of Wrathell, Hunt and Associates, LLC, c/o District Manager, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431; Phone: (561) 571-0010 (District Managers Office).


The Board shall select and rank the Applicants using the requirements set forth in the CCNA and the evaluation criteria on file with the District Manager, and the highest ranked Applicant will be requested to enter into contract negotiations. If an agreement cannot be reached between the District and the highest ranked Applicant, negotiations will cease and begin with the next highest ranked Applicant, and if these negotiations are unsuccessful, will continue to the third highest ranked Applicant.


The District reserves the right to reject any and all Qualification Statements. Additionally, there is no express or implied obligation for the District to reimburse Applicants for any expenses associated with the preparation and submittal of the Qualification Statements in response to this request.


Any protest regarding the terms of this Notice, or the evaluation criteria on file with the District Manager, must be filed in writing, within seventy-two (72) hours (excluding weekends) after the publication of this Notice. The formal protest setting forth with particularity the facts and law upon which the protest is based shall be filed within seven (7) calendar days after the initial notice of protest was filed. Failure to timely file a notice of protest or failure to timely file a formal written protest shall constitute a waiver of any right to object or protest with respect to aforesaid Notice or evaluation criteria provisions. Any person who files a notice of protest shall provide to the District, simultaneous with the filing of the notice, a protest bond with a responsible surety to be approved by the District and in the amount of Twenty Thousand Dollars ($20,000.00).


Any and all questions relative to the RFQ shall be directed in writing by email only to Ernesto Torres at torrese@whhassociates.com with email copies to Michael Eckert at Michael.Eckert@KutakRock.com and Kate John at Kate.John@KutakRock.com. [Kate.John@KutakRock.com]
December 11, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420497</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420491</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASS...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
NOTICE OF THE DISTRICTS INTENT TO USE THE UNIFORM METHOD OF COLLECTION OF NON-AD VALOREM
SPECIAL ASSESSMENTS


Notice is hereby given that the South Lake Toho Community Development District (the District) intends to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments to be levied by the District pursuant to Section 197.3632, Florida Statutes.


The Board of Supervisors of the District will conduct a public hearing on January 8, 2026, at 9:30 a.m. at the Hart Memorial Library, 211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room  HMC, Kissimmee, Florida 34741.


The purpose of the public hearing is to consider the adoption of a resolution authorizing the District to use the uniform method of collecting non-ad valorem special assessments (the Uniform Method) to be levied by the District on properties located on land included in, or to be added to, the District.


The District may levy non-ad valorem special assessments for the purpose of financing, acquiring, maintaining and/or operating community development facilities, services, and improvements within and without the boundaries of the District, to consist of, among other things, onsite and offsite sanitary sewer collection, onsite and offsite water distribution, master stormwater management system, electrical service system (underground), conservation mitigation, onsite and offsite public roadway improvements, landscape/irrigation wells and distribution/hardscape within master public roads, and/or any other lawful improvements or services of the District.


Owners of the properties to be assessed and other interested parties may appear at the public hearing and be heard regarding the use of the Uniform Method. This hearing is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The public hearing may be continued to a date, time, and location to be specified on the record at the hearing. There may be occasions when Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the hearing and/or meeting is asked to contact the District Managers office at c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the hearing and/or meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 1-800-955-8771 who can aid you in contacting the District Managers Office.


Each person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the hearing is advised that person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 25, 2025
January 1, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420491</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420484</link>
      <description>Notice at 2300 Glades Road

Location: 2300 Glades Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF LANDOWNERS MEETING AND ELECTION AND MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT

Notice is hereby given to the public and all landowners within the South Lake Toho Community Development District (District) the location of which is generally described as comprising a parcel or parcels of land containing approximately 529 acres, generally located in Sections 4 and 9, Township 27S, Range 29E; and Sections 33 and 34, Township 26S, Range 29E, and within the unincorporated limits of Osceola County, Florida, advising that a meeting of landowners will be held for the purpose of electing five (5) persons to the District Board of Supervisors.


DATE: January 8, 2026
TIME: 9:30 a.m.
PLACE: Hart Memorial Library
211 East Dakin Avenue, Second Floor, Lillie Room-HMC
Kissimmee, Florida 34741


Each landowner may vote in person or by written proxy. Proxy forms may be obtained upon request at the office of the District Manager, Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, located at 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431; (Ph): 561-571-0010 (District Managers Office). At said meeting each landowner or his or her proxy shall be entitled to nominate persons for the position of Supervisor and cast one vote per acre of land, or fractional portion thereof, owned by him or her and located within the District for each person to be elected to the position of Supervisor. A fraction of an acre shall be treated as one acre, entitling the landowner to one vote with respect thereto. Platted lots shall be counted individually and rounded up to the nearest whole acre. The acreage of platted lots shall not be aggregated for determining the number of voting units held by a landowner or a landowners proxy. At the landowners meeting the landowners shall select a person to serve as the meeting chair and who shall conduct the meeting.


The landowners meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. A copy of the agenda for this meeting may be obtained from the District Office. Any person requiring special accommodations to participate in these meetings is asked to contact the District Office at (PH): 561-571-0010, at least 48 hours before the hearing. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or (800) 955-8770 for aid in contacting the District Office.


A person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that such person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 18, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420484</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11420479</link>
      <description>SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR ANNUAL AUDIT SERVICES


The South Lake Toho Community Development District...


--- Full Notice Text ---
SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR ANNUAL AUDIT SERVICES


The South Lake Toho Community Development District hereby requests proposals for annual financial auditing services. The proposal must provide for the auditing of the Districts financial records for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2026, with an option for additional annual renewals, subject to mutual agreement by both parties. The District is a local unit of special-purpose government created under Chapter 190, Florida Statutes, for the purpose of financing, constructing, and maintaining public infrastructure. The District is located in Osceola County, Florida, and has an annual operating budget of approximately $81,619. The final contract will require that, among other things, the audit for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2026, be completed no later than June 30, 2027.


The auditing entity submitting a proposal must be duly licensed under Chapter 473, Florida Statutes, and be qualified to conduct audits in accordance with Government Auditing Standards, as adopted by the Florida Board of Accountancy. Audits shall be conducted in accordance with Florida Law and particularly Section 218.39, Florida Statutes, and the rules of the Florida Auditor General. Proposal packages, which include evaluation criteria and instructions to proposers, are available from the District Manager at the address and telephone number listed below.


Proposers must provide one (1) electronic and one (1) unbound copy of their proposal to the District Manager, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431, (561) 571-0010 in an envelope marked on the outside Auditing Services, South Lake Toho Community Development District. Proposals must be received by 12:00 p.m., on December 22, 2025, at the office of the District Manager.


Please direct all questions regarding this Notice to the District Manager.


Ernesto Torres
District Manager
December 11, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11420479</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
