<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board - Public Notices</title>
    <link>https://kissimmee.fyi</link>
    <description>Public notices for Kissimmee Planning Advisory Board meetings and proceedings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:51:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/62/11490462.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490462</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11490462.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490416</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1987


Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Tr...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1987


Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP


STATE OF NEW YORK

COUNTY OF RICHMOND


I, ERHABOR, EKIROGUAGHEN OSAROBO also known as OSAROBO OSANOBUA OF RICHMOND (affiant), a New Yorker National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of NEW JERSEY, County of UNION, State of NEW JERSEY, which he recognizes and intends to maintain as his permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 26 Central Ave, Staten Island, NY 10301, and that he formerly resided at 355 Bard Avenue, Staten Island New York 10313 (city) STATEN ISLAND (state) NEW YORK, but that his abode in New York constitutes his predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that he affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor), providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the SAPIENTIA DEI EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. 24057054-1, dated January 1st, 2004. Affiant further declares that Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor or the EKIROGUAGHEN OSAROBO FAMILY OF ERHABOR ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of New York, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.


I, Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo also known as OSAROBO OSANOBUA OF RICHMOND, declare, state, verify under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America, that the above statements are true and correct, and with nothing further to state, I have affixed my seal, mark or signature below.

February 20, 2026
#COL-567</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490416</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490415</link>
      <description>ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est. January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am
SCHEDULE A: TRUSTEE MINUTES ARD-005-2025
LITERARY MINUTES OF MEETING OF ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST
Date: Wednesday January 29, 2025
Time: 12:00pm Adjourned Time 12:35pm
OTHER PROPERTY EXCHANGE- NON-REAL PROPERTY
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To the Governing Bodies of this Express Trust, All Corporation Soles, but not limited to the State of Nevada, State of California, State of Texas, State of Florida.
The Sole Trustee called the meeting to order and affirmed officially on January 29,2025 the Trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to the County of Clark County.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a Aishyah Malkah Ali Yahudah El Bey
The Trustee shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings.
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the Holders of this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED BEING DULY SWORN DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THE NAMES OF THE ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHA KAMILAH JENKINS
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A JENKINS, AISHA KAMILAH ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A JENKINS, AISHA K ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHA K JENKINS ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHA JENKINS
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A JENKINS, AISHA
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHA KAMILAH FAMILY OF JENKINS ESTATE ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHA JENKINS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A OSHER OPHIR TRUST ENTERPRISE
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A WHOLISTICLY YOU LLC ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A MY TRANSFORMATION PROJECT
24
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est. January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A NACHALAH VENTURES
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A NACHALAH MANAGEMENT GROUP ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AMERICAN DIPPER LAND TRUST ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A EPIC ADVENTURES
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A AISHYAH MALKAH ALI YAHUDAH EL BEY ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST D/B/A JENKINS PSYCHOTHERAPY SERVICES
HEADQUARTERS: 111 N. SANDERS STREET, ST. HELENA, MONTANA 59601 PRINICIPAL ADDRESS: 360 S. RAMPART BLVD STE 110B LAS VEGAS, NV 89145 MAILING ADDRESS: 1170 W. CHARLESTON AVE #170-468 LAS VEGAS, NEVADA 89135
25
25
February 20, 27, March 6, 2026
#COL-566</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490415</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490414</link>
      <description>ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est. January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am
SCHEDULE B: TRUSTEE MINUTES: ARD-005-2025
LITERARY MINUTES OF MEETING OF ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST MISCELLANEOUS AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE
Date: Wednesday January 29, 2025
Time:
10:00 am
Adjourned: 12:13 pm
Location: 360 S Rampart Blvd Ste 110B Las Vegas, NV [89145]
Persons Present: Settlor &amp; Sole Trustee
STATE OF NEVADA
COUNTY OF CLARK
} }
I, Aisha Kamilah Jenkins, an Aboriginal Moor Montanan National of Yashar' al of the House of Yahudah from the Tribes of Yamassee, declare, state and verify before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn under oath deposes and says that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of Las Vegas, County of Clark, State of Nevada, which she recognizes and intends to maintain as her permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 11700 W. Charleson Apt 170-468 Las Vegas, Nevada and that she formerly resided at 111 N. Sanders Street, St. Helena, Montana, but that her abode in Nevada constitutes her predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that she affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to the registered owner named AISHA JENKINS in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner AISHA JENKUNS, providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that she is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said birth certificate of title, and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner AISHA JENKINS as having attained the age of majority at a date of 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above and Certificate of Title No 25013211-1 dated December 30, 2024. Affiant further declares that AISHA JENKINS of the AISHA KAMILAH FAMILY OF JENKINS ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Nevada and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.
I Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah, declare, state, verify under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America, that the above statements are true and correct, and with nothing further to state, I have affixed my seal and mark or signature below.
1/29/2025
Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah
26
26
Date
February 20, 2026
#COL-572</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490414</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490413</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1987


Copyright Notice
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



T...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1987


Copyright Notice
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust:



The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on January 1st, 2004, at 9:25 AM, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Copyright Notice No. 89 as Exhibit A, as prescribed in Copyright Depot No. 00097559-1 December 16th, 2025 and the Affidavit of Schedule of Fees on the attached Schedule B, is held in trust.


Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of SAPIENTIA DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor.


The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.





Being no other business before the Board, the meeting was adjourned at 9:48 AM.



Place of Meeting: 60 South 31st Street, Kenilworth, New Jersey 07033



Lozano, Harol M. Sole Trustee
February 20, 2026
#COL-570</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490413</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490412</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1987


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Ex...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1987


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 11:20 AM:


The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of SAPIENTIA DEI, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 1st, 2004 at 8:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigration officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlors declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:


P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality


I, Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo (creditor) d/b/a Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my NEW YORK Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.


I declare that my name is Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo also known as OSAROBO OSANOBUA OF RICHMOND. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native New Yorker National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in New York republic of the United States of America  (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4.


TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of New York Forms, County Municipality Forms, all NY DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission. I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,


Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1987  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or


Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


I, Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo, born in the land of NEW YORK United States of America, territory of STATEN ISLAND, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States (Public Law 94-241  March 24, 1976  Article III.  90 STAT. 266  Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.


Place of Meeting: 60 South 31st Street, Kenilworth, New Jersey 07033



There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 12:25 PM


Erhabor, Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Settlor/Trust Protector


Lozano, Harol M. Sole Trustee
February 20, 2026
#COL-568</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490412</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490411</link>
      <description>Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1987


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Expr...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1987


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


Parties:


Sapientia Dei Express Trust
d/b/a Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor
(Complainant)


vs.


RICHMOND County Sheriff
RICHMOND County Board of Commissioners
RICHMOND Superior Court Clerk
New York Governor
(Defendant)


INJUNCTION AGAINST ALL PUBLIC OFFICERS AND CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE INVOKING IRREPARABLE INJURY


COME THIS DAY, the 16th of December, in the year of OUR LORD 2025


NOTICE OF ESTOPPEL AND STIPULATION OF CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE TO ALL New York AND UNITED STATES STATUTES WHERE Retrospective laws are highly injurious, oppressive, and unjust. No such laws, therefore, should be made, either for the decision of civil causes, or the punishment of offenses AND MOTION TO INTERVENE WITH AN INJUNCTION FOR THE NAME SAPIENTIA DEI EXPRESS TRUST doing business as Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor AND OSAROBO OSANOBUA OF RICHMOND  Per Exhibit E8437G8 (Trademark License Agreement)


All constitutional civil officers have given oath to the support the constitution of New York and the United States as prescribed in Article XIII, Section 1 of the New York 1894 Constitution. The Complainant (One of The People of the Territory of New York under Declaration of Express Trust), rights protected by the Constitution (Article I, Section 6) have been injured in the past by the Sheriffs and his/her officers by being compelled to accuse or furnish evidence against himself. Every subject shall have a right to produce all proofs that may be favorable to himself; to meet the witnesses against him face to face, and to be fully heard in his defense, by himself, and counsel. The Complainant, under duress, incurred a force stop and/or force detainment without due process of affidavit of


Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1987  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SAPIENTIA DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


complaint under oath attached to the summons, citation or notice of violation without special designation of the persons or objects of search, arrest, or seizure (Article I, Section 12). As prescribed in CPLR  305, ATTACHMENTS of the Rules of The Supreme Court of the State of New York, (a) Summons; supplemental summons. A summons shall specify the basis of the venue designated and, if based upon the residence of the plaintiff, it shall specify the plaintiffs address, and also shall bear the index number assigned and the date of filing with the clerk of the court. A third-party summons shall also specify the date of filing of the third-party summons with the clerk of the court. The summons in an action arising out of a consumer credit transaction shall prominently display at the top of the summons the words consumer credit transaction and, where a purchaser, borrower, or debtor is a defendant, shall specify the county of residence of a defendant, if one resides within the state, and the county where the consumer credit transaction took place, if it is within the state. Where, upon order of the court or by stipulation of all parties or as of right pursuant to section 1003, a new party is joined in the action and the joinder is not made upon the new partys motion, a supplemental summons specifying the pleading which the new party must answer shall be filed with the clerk of the court and served upon such party. (b) Summons and notice. If the complaint is not served with the summons, the summons shall contain or have attached thereto a notice stating the nature of the action and the relief sought, and, except in an action for medical malpractice, the sum of money for which judgment may be taken in case of default. (c) Amendment. At any time, in its discretion and upon such terms as it deems just, the court may allow any summons or proof of service of a summons to be amended, if a substantial right of a party against whom the summons issued is not prejudiced.


DEMAND FOR RELIEF


FURTHERMORE, I DEMAND, for the RICHMOND County Sheriff to put the name SAPIENTIA DEI EXPRESS TRUST doing business as ERHABOR, EKIROGUAGHEN OSAROBO AND Ekiroguaghen Osarobo Erhabor AND OSAROBO OSANOBUA OF RICHMOND on THE DO NOT STOP, DO NOT DETAIN LIST FOR New York and all OTHER STATES under Full Faith and Credit. The Constitution reserves all rights protected by the above said 1894 Constitution of New York, the Articles of Association and the Articles of Confederation and do not waive any part of my rights; abide by your oaths to it.


TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE THAT THIS WRIT OF INJUNCTION SHALL ALSO SERVE AS YOUR CONTRACT; failure to answer and rebut this Writ is acquiescence and is estoppel; you have 30 days to answer, then this contract is law. No STATE shall pass and Bill of Attainder, ex post facto Law, or Law impairing the Obligation of Contracts  Section 10 of 1787 United States Constitution.


SIGNED: Harol M. LozanoSOLE TRUSTEESIGNED: Ekiroguaghen Osarobo ErhaborSETTLOR/COMPLAINANT





February 20, 2026
#COL-569</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490411</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11490410</link>
      <description>ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est. January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am
SCHEDULE A: TRUSTEE MINUTES: ARD-004-2025
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
LITERARY MINUTES OF MEETING OF ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST
Date Tuesday January 28, 2025
Time: 10:00 am
Adjourned: 12:13 p
Location: 360 S. Rampart Blvd Ste 110B Las Vegas, NV [89145]
Persons Present: Settlor &amp; Sole Trustee
Business Conducted: DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
The Sole Trustee (second party) from the Board of Trustees of Ashar Regnum Dei Express Trust, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am, holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
"P. Law 94-241, Article III. Citizenship &amp; Nationality"
I, Jenkins, Aisha, Kamilah d/b/a AISHA KAMILAH JENKINS hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U. S. National evidenced by my Montana Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Contract.
I declare that my name is Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah d/b/a AISHA KAMILAH JENKINS. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Securities of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Aboriginal Moor Montanan National House of Yahudah from the Yamasee, of the land of America formerly known as Ta'ameri, Amaruka, Al-Moroc, Atzlan, India Superior and Turtle Island pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV, the United Nations Declaration of the Rights of Indigenous Peoples UN/61/195 but not a citizen of the United States, domiciled in Nevada republic of the United States of America (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a "sex tourism" crimes statue, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U. S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4.
20
20
ASHAR REGNUM DEI EXPRESS TRUST (An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization) Est. January 23, 2025 at 10:00 am
Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of NEVADA or any other State Forms, County, Municipality Forms, all NEVADA DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any and or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Las; "all previously signed Federal and State forms are, herby, extinguished by this recission. "I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi, colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.
I, Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah, born in the land of Montana United States of America, territory of Great Falls, declare (or certify, verify, or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America[28 U.S.C. Code  1746(1)] that "I, Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not citizen of the United States" (Public Law 94-241-March 24, 1976- Article III-90 STAT. 266-Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.
There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting was adjourned at time
Amm
Jenkins, Aisha Kamilah
fitte
Settlor/Trust Protector
Yusuf, Liban Yassin
Sole Trustee
21
21
February 20, 2026
#COL-571</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11490410</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11489019</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the S...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT BY THE SOUTH LAKE TOHO COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT


In accordance with Chapters 120 and 190, Florida Statutes, the South Lake Toho Community Development District (District) hereby gives notice of its intention to develop Rules of Procedure to govern the operations of the District. The proposed rule number is 2026-1.


The Rules of Procedure will address such areas as the Board of Supervisors, officers and voting, district offices, public information and inspection of records, policies, public meetings, hearings and workshops, rulemaking proceedings, competitive purchase including procedure under the Consultants Competitive Negotiation Act, procedure regarding auditor selection, purchase of insurance, pre-qualification, construction contracts, goods, supplies and materials, maintenance services, contractual services and protests with respect to proceedings, as well as any other area of the general operation of the District.


The purpose and effect of the Rules of Procedure is to provide for efficient and effective District operations and to ensure compliance with recent changes to Florida law. The specific grant of rulemaking authority for the adoption of the proposed Rules of Procedure includes Sections 190.011(5), 190.011(15) and 190.035, Florida Statutes. The specific laws implemented in the proposed Rules of Procedure include, but are not limited to, Sections 112.08, 112.3143, 112.31446, 112.3145, 119.07, 119.0701, 120.54, 120.542, 120.5435, 120.56, 120.69, 120.81, 189.053, 189.069, 190.006, 190.007, 190.008, 190.011, 190.033, 190.035, 218.33, 218.391, 255.05, 255.0518, 255.0525, 255.20, 286.0105, 286.011, 286.012, 286.0113, 286.0114, 287.017, 287.055, and 287.084, Florida Statutes.


A copy of the proposed Rules of Procedure and the related incorporated documents, if any, may be obtained by contacting the District Manager, c/o Wrathell, Hunt &amp; Associates, LLC, 2300 Glades Road, Suite 410W, Boca Raton, Florida 33431 Ph: 561-571-0010, torrese@whhassociates.com.


Ernesto Torres, District Manager
South Lake Toho Community Development District

February 19, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11489019</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/44/11487644.pdf</link>
      <description>Lake Tohopekaliga Road
PD&amp;E Study Public Meeting
Osceola County, Florida



--- Full Notice Text ---
Lake Tohopekaliga Road
PD&amp;E Study Public Meeting
Osceola County, Florida
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11487644</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11487644.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/81/11484081.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484081</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11484081.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11484039</link>
      <description>Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1980
Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1980
Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Texas &amp; Florida:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on November 09, 2014, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST.
The TRUSTEE shall:

 * Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
 * Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.

WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RITA FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU BANKRUPTCY ESTATE
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RITA LUNA LILIUM LADY OF HONOLULU
LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE
LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU
LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a RITA LUNA LILIUM LADY OF HONOLULU
HEADQUARTERS: 1 Jarrett White Rd, TRIPLER AMC, HI 96859
PRINCIPAL: 2170 W STATE ROAD 434, LONGWOOD, FLORIDA 32779
MAILING: 729 GRAPEVINE HWY, HURST, TEXAS 76022
AND THE EXTENT OF THE INTEREST OF EACH, IS AS FOLLOWS:
NAME:
INTEREST:
SIGNATURE:
Acuna, Ana Isabel, Sole Trustee
100% OWNER
Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan , Manager
0%


February 13, 2026
#COL-563</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484039</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11484038</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1980


Copyright Notice
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



To...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1980


Copyright Notice
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust:



The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on November 9, 2014, at 8:25 AM, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Copyright Notice No. 38 as Exhibit A , as prescribed in Copyright Depot No. 00091877-1 Dtd 11/01/2024 and the Affidavit of Schedule of Fees on the attached Schedule B, is held in trust.


Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU.


The TRUSTEE shall:
 1. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
 2. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.





Being no other business before the Board, the meeting was adjourned at 8:48 AM.



Place of Meeting: 1400 Plaza Place, Southlake, Texas, 76092 (Tarrant County)



___________________________________________
Acuna, Ana Isabel Sole Trustee























Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1980  continuation


Copyright Notice No. 38
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


Common Law Copyright Notice: All rights re; common law copyright of trade-name/trademark, RITA FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE, ESTATE OF RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, BROSSEAU, RITA, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU ESTATE, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE and LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST as well as any and all derivatives and variations in the spelling of said trade-names/trademarks  Copyright Dtd 11/01/2024 , by LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST (the natural person). Said trade-names/trademarks, may neither be used, nor reproduced, neither in whole nor in part, nor in any manner whatsoever, without the prior, express, written consent and acknowledgment of LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST (the natural person) as signified by the signature of Acuna, Ana Isabel (the Sole Trustee; non-resident alien) and Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan (the Settlor, Trust Protector and a Co-Trustee). With the intent of being contractually bound, any Juristic Person, as well as the agent of said Juristic, consents and agrees by this Copyright Notice that neither said Juristic Person, nor the agent of said Juristic Person, shall display, nor otherwise use in any manner, the trade-name/trademarks, nor common-law copyright described herein, nor any derivative of , nor any variation in the spelling of, said name without prior, express, written consent and acknowledgment of LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST, hereinafter known as the Secured Party, as signified by Secured Partys signature. Secured Party neither grants, nor implies, nor otherwise gives consent for any unauthorized use of RITA FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE, ESTATE OF RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, BROSSEAU, RITA, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU ESTATE, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE and LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST, and all such unauthorized use is strictly prohibited. The Secured Party is not now, nor has ever been, an accommodation party, not a surety, for the purported debtor, i.e. RITA FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE nor for any derivative of, nor for any variation in the spelling of, said name, nor for any other juristic person, the debtor (RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU) is completely under jurisdiction of the Foreign Express Trust, LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST, an Irrevocable Trust Organization for tax treaty purposes associated with the Internal Revenue Service withholding compliances. The Secured Party is the holder of the U.S. Department of State Annexed Security No. 151-80007552, Dated June, 23, 1980; and the County of HONOLULU, City of HONOLULU Certificate of Title No.151-80007552 as the Collateral for the Security Interest, known as Equity Secured Promissory Note No. 11.22017 in the amount of a Nine Billion Dollar Lien with interest. See Copyright Depot No. 00091877-1 against all claims, legal actions, orders, warrants, judgments, demands, liabilities, losses, depositions, summons, lawsuits, costs, fines, liens, levies, penalties, damages, interest, and expenses whatsoever, both absolute and contingent, as are due and as might become due, now existing and as might hereafter arise, and as might be suffered by, imposed on, and incurred by debtor for any and every reason, purpose, and cause whatsoever. This Notice by Declaration becomes a fully executed copyright notice wherein Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan  (the Settlor, Trust Protector) of the LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST, grants the Secured Party security interest in all of the debtors property and interest in property in the sum certain amount of Seven Billion Dollars ($7,000,000,000.00 USD) exercised by a Nine Billion Dollar ($9,000,000,000.00) Lien referenced with the Texas Secretary of State Financing Statement and in the Organic Public Record Seminole Recorders Clerk Office non-Uniform Commercial Code Central Filing. For each trade-name/trademark used, per each occurrence of use (violations/infringement), plus triple damages, plus cost for each such use, as well as for each and every use of any and all derivatives of, and variations in the spelling of NICHOLAS FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE, ESTATE OF RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU, BROSSEAU, RITAS, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU ESTATE, RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU BANKRUPTCY ESTATE, LUNA LILIUM TRUST ENTERPRISE and LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST, the trust office shall refer to the Affidavit of Schedule of Fees for summary judgment granted by any court of record in the matters of equity.





Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 3-1980  Exhibit A - concluded


Copyright Notice
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



With nothing more to state, we have adjourned this day;














Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan : Principal ____________________________
Dated ________________________

February 13, 2026
#COL-565</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484038</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11484037</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1980


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Exp...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1980


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 10:20 AM:


The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of LUNA LILIUM, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on November 9th, 2014 at 5:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlors declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:


P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality


I, Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan (creditor) d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my Hawaii Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.
I declare that my name is Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan also known as Rita Luna Lilium Lady of Honolulu. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Hawaii Resident, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Texas republic of the United States of America  (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4. 
T A K E J U D I C I A L N O T I C E, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Texas Forms, County Municipality Forms, all TX DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission. I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1980  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or
Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.


DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY


I, Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan , born in the land of Hawai'i, United States of America, territory of Honolulu, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States (Public Law 94-241  March 24, 1976  Article III.  90 STAT. 266  Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.


Place of Meeting: 1601 Hurst Town Center Drive, Hurst, TX 76054



There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 10:25 AM


__________________________________________
Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan Settlor/Trust Protector



_________________________________________
Acuna, Ana Isabel Sole Trustee

February 13, 2026
#COL-561</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484037</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11484036</link>
      <description>Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1980


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Expre...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1980


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


Parties:


Luna Lilium Express Trust
d/b/a RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU
(Complainant)


vs.


Tarrant County Sheriff
Tarrant County Board of Commissioners
Tarrant Superior Court Clerk
Texas Governor
(Defendant)


INJUNCTION AGAINST ALL PUBLIC OFFICERS AND CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE INVOKING IRREPARABLE INJURY


COME THIS DAY, the 21 st of January, in the year of OUR LORD 2024


NOTICE OF ESTOPPEL AND STIPULATION OF CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE TO ALL TEXAS AND UNITED STATES STATUTES WHERE Retrospective laws are highly injurious, oppressive, and unjust. No such laws, therefore, should be made, either for the decision of civil causes, or the punishment of offenses AND MOTION TO INTERVENE WITH AN INJUNCTION FOR THE NAME LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST doing business as RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU AND RITA LUNA LILIUM LADY OF HONOLULU  Per Exhibit 01.J220 (Trademark License Agreement)


All constitutional civil officers have given oath to support the constitution of Texas and the United States as prescribed in Article 1, Section 11 of the CONSTITUTION OF THE REPUBLIC OF TEXAS 1836. The Complainant (One of The People of the Territory of Texas under Declaration of Express Trust), rights protected by the Constitution (Article 1) have been injured in the past by the Sheriffs and his/her officers by being compelled to accuse or furnish evidence against herself. Every subject shall have a right to produce all proofs that may be favorable to himself; to meet the witnesses against her face to face, and to be fully heard in her defense, by herself, and counsel. The Complainant, under duress, incurred a force stop and/or force detainment without due process of affidavit of


Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1980  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


complaint under oath attached to the summons, citation or notice of violation without special designation of the persons or objects of search, arrest, or seizure (Article 6, Section 6). As prescribed in Rule 106. ATTACHMENTS of the Rules of The Superior Court of the State of Texas, The Method of Service shall be executed under oath by the clerk and accompanied by the citation as well as a copy of the petition. The citation shall (1) be styled "The State of Texas," (2) be signed by the clerk under seal of court, (3) contain name and location of the court, (4) show date of filing of the petition, (5) show date of issuance of citation, Rule 99 - Issuance and Motion, Tex. R. Civ. P. 99 The officer or authorized person to whom process is delivered shall endorse thereon the day and hour on which he received it, and shall execute and return the same without delay. Rule 105 - Duty of Officer or Person Receiving, Tex. R. Civ. P. 105 The Motion to Attach shall be fastened to the Complaint; copies of the Complaint and Summons (Citation/Violation) are then to be given to the sheriff or his or her deputy for service on the defendant; immediately after such service on the defendant; immediately after such service, that Complaint, together with the sheriffs Return of Service, is to be entered with the court Tex. R. Civ. P. 107


DEMAND FOR RELIEF


FURTHERMORE, I DEMAND , for the Tarrant County Sheriff to put the name LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST doing business as BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN AND RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU AND RITA LUNA LILIUM LADY OF HONOLULU on THE DO NOT STOP, DO NOT DETAIN LIST FOR TEXAS and all OTHER STATES under Full Faith and Credit . The Constitution reserves all rights protected by the above said 1836 Constitution of Texas, the Articles of Association and the Articles of Confederation and do not waive any part of my rights; abide by your oaths to it .


TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE THAT THIS WRIT OF INJUNCTION SHALL ALSO SERVE AS YOUR CONTRACT; failure to answer and rebut this Writ is acquiescence and is estoppel; you have 30 days to answer , then this contract is law. No STATE shall pass and Bill of Attainder, ex post facto Law, or Law impairing the Obligation of Contracts  Section 10 of 1787 United States Constitution.


SIGNED: Ana Isabel Acuna SOLE TRUSTEE


SIGNED: Rita Thawng Jan Brosseau SETTLOR/COMPLAINANT

February 13, 2026
#COL-564</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484036</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11484035</link>
      <description>Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1980


Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Tru...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1980


Other Property Exchange  Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
LUNA LILIUM
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)



AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP


STATE OF TEXAS

COUNTY OF TARRANT


I, BROSSEAU, RITA THAWNG JAN also known as RITA LUNA LILIUM LADY OF HONOLULU (affiant), a Hawaii Resident declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of HURST, County of TARRANT, State of TEXAS, which she recognizes and intends to maintain as her permanent home; affiant declares that she also maintains a residence at 417 S King St, Honolulu, HI 96813, and that she formerly resided at 1 Jarrett White Rd, TRIPLER AMC, 96859 HAWAII, but that her abode in Texas constitutes her predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that she affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU), providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that she is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the LUNA LILIUM EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. 151-80007552, dated JUNE 23, 1980. Affiant further declares that RITA THAWNG JAN BROSSEAU or the RITA THAWNG JAN FAMILY OF BROSSEAU ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Texas, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.


I, Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan also known as Rita Luna Lilium Lady of Honolulu, declare, state, verify under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America, that the above statements are true and correct, and with nothing further to state, I have affixed my seal, mark or signature below.


______________________________________
___________________
Brosseau, Rita Thawng Jan (Affiant)
Date

February 13, 2026
#COL-562</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11484035</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11482345</link>
      <description>Notice at 2506 4th Street

Location: 2506 4th Street

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE UNDER
FICTITIOUS NAME LAW
PURSUANT TO
SECTION 865.09
FLORIDA STATUTES
To Whom It May Concern:
Notice is hereby given that the undersigned intends to engage in business under the fictitious name KARAMELO BOARD &amp; DESSERT with its principal place of business located at 2506 4th Street, St. Cloud, FL, in Osceola County, Florida. The said business is owned by KAREN SPA LLC.
This notice is being published in accordance with Section 865.09, Florida Statutes.
DATED at St. Cloud, Osceola County, Florida, on this 28th day of January 2026.
February 12, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11482345</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11482344</link>
      <description>Notice at 211 E Dakin Ave

Location: 211 E Dakin Ave

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF TIME CHANGE FOR THE REGULAR MEETING
OVEROAKS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT

Two regular meetings of the Board of Supervisors of the Overoaks Community Development District previously scheduled to begin at 9:30 a.m., has been rescheduled and will now begin at 6:00 p.m. The meetings will be held on Tuesday, February 24, 2026, and April 28, 2026, at 6:00 p.m. at the Hart Memorial Library located at 211 E Dakin Ave, Kissimmee, FL 34741, to discuss the Agenda and business items of the Overoaks Community Development District.
The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law for community development districts. A copy of the agenda for this special meeting may be obtained by contacting the District Manager by mail at 313 Campus Street, Celebration FL 34747, by telephone at 407-566-1935, or by visiting the Districts website www.overoakscdd.org. This meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the special meeting. There may be occasions when Supervisors or staff will participate by communication media technology.
Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations in order to access and participate in the special meeting because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Managers Office at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the special meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Managers Office.
Each person who decides to appeal any action taken at the meetings is advised that the person will need a record of proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.
Michael Perez,
District Manager
February 12, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11482344</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/48/11476948.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476948</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11476948.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476914</link>
      <description>Document prepared by: Marzuki, Sandriliana
Keraton Express Trust
5840 Red Bug Lake Road #1589
Winter Springs, FL 32708
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
Document prepared by: Marzuki, Sandriliana
Keraton Express Trust
5840 Red Bug Lake Road #1589
Winter Springs, FL 32708
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est. January 1st, in the year of our Lord, 2023 Anno Domini
THIS INDENTURE ("Agreement) made this 1st day of January, 2023 serves as a Declaration of Express Trust and shall continue for a term of twenty-five (25) years from this day, between SANDRILIANA MARZUKI herein known as the Settlor and Trust Protector, (the first party) and DE CLARA ESTER YUDITH Trustee, herein known as the First Trustee, Sole Trustee or Trustee, (the second party), under the name of KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RADEN AYU SANDRILIANA. With this contract, the Parties intend to create an Express Trust Organization for the benefit of the Trust Certificate Unit Holders and to identify, accumulate, purchase and hold any assets that become available and to provide for a prudent administration and distribution system administered by legal persons acting in a fiduciary capacity.
WITNESSETH: Whereas the Settlor, irrevocably assigns and conveys to the Trustee, in trust, specific properties as defined in The Trustee Minutes (1-1973), attached to this document in exchange for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RADEN AYU SANDRILIANA.
Trust: Trust includes an express trust, private or charitable, with additions thereto, wherever and however created. Property: Property means anything that may be the subject of ownership and includes both real and personal property.
Person: Person means any natural person, individual, corporation, government or governmental subdivision or agency, business trust, estate, trust, partnership, limited liability company, association, or other entity.
Settlor: SANDRILIANA MARZUKI of 5840 Red Bug Lake Road #1589 Winter Springs, FL 32708, doing business in Seminole County, Florida of 590 Centerpointe Cir - 1st Floor, Suite 100 Altamonte Springs, FL 32701 - (defined) in law a settlor is a person who settles property in trust law for the benefit of beneficiaries. In some legal systems, a settlor is also referred to as a trustor or occasionally, a grantor or donor... A settlor may create a trust manifesting an intention to create it; grantor is the person who creates the trust.
Trust Protector: SANDRILIANA MARZUKI or other authorized person in the future by settlor, - (defined) appointed under the trust instrument to direct, restrain, remove the trustee(s) or appoint a successor.
Trustee(s): DE CLARA ESTER YUDITH of Perum Cempaka Mas, Blok U Baru, No 14B, Kuta Utara, Badung, Bali 80361, Indonesia - (defined) includes an original, additional, or successor trustee, whether or not appointed or confirmed by a court. A person or firm that holds or administers property or assets for the benefit of a third party and can be given the powers to make investment decisions for the Trust, or vote on the distribution of assets to the beneficiaries and/or has the power to hire persons whether an authorized person or not, including accountants, attorneys, auditors, investment advisers, appraisers or other agents even if they are associated or affiliated with the trustee, to advise or assist the trustee in the performance of administrative duties.
Document prepared by:
Marzuki, Sandriliana
Keraton Express Trust
5840 Red Bug Lake Road #1589
Winter Springs, FL 32708
Beneficial Owner: KERATON EXPRESS TRUST herein known as the First Beneficiary and other beneficiaries to come in future(defined) beneficial owner is where specific property rights ("use and title) in equity belong to a person even though legal title of the property belongs to another person. This often relates where the legal title owner has implied trustee duties to the beneficial owner.
WHEREAS, the Trust Organization is authorized to exist and function through its Board of Trustees, comprised of the total active number of trustees who are legal persons holding fee simple title, not differentiating between legal and equitable, not as individuals, but collectively as the Board, according to the inalienable Common Law rights.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be amendable, as described in the bylaws, and shall be irrevocable by the Settlor or by any other person or entity but said trustee can be fired by the Trust Protector and replace by new trustee appointed by the Trust Protector. It is the intention of the Settlor to make the Beneficiaries, an absolute gift of the Trust Certificate Units (TCUs), in which the Beneficiaries shall not have any vested interest, until the termination of this Trust and final distribution accumulated assets or any early distribution of the assets thereof. There shall be exactly 100 Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) available to the Beneficiaries.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be administered, managed, governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida, being bound to the Articles of Confederation of 1781, Article IV.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be governed by its country's applicable laws known as Muscat (Muskat), Sultanate of Oman, with formation documents governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida to govern the interpretation of the trust. Under the law of the Sultanate of Oman, a court within Oman, is able to exercise primary supervision over the administration of the trust. The Treaty of Marrakesh, the Treaty of Maskat of 1833, the Articles of Association, the Articles of Confederation, and the Uniform Commercial Code (only when and if applicable and/or allowable to remain under the jurisdiction of the Common Law). The domicile of the trust is within the Court of Equity, in Florida in the Republic of the United States of America but shall have full faith and credit in any State as a last resort when everything else fails.
February 6, 2026
#COL-558</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476914</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476913</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 1st, in the year of our Lord, 2023 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1973
Other Property Exchange - Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
KERATON
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To the governing authorities of this Express Trust, including all Corporation Soles, without limitation the State of Florida and the State of Texas: The Sole Trustee formally convened the meeting and confirmed that, effective January 1, 2023, the Trustee accepted custody of certain intangible property, specifically identified as an Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be administered under the trust and published through appropriate local municipal newspaper filings, including but not limited to records maintained by the Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller. The Trustee authorized the initial transfer of the described property in consideration for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, herein designated as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs), to be issued and maintained under this Indenture by the Trustees for the benefit of the Beneficiaries, also referred to as Members of KERATON EXPRESS TRUST.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a) Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b) Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE KERATON EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SANDRILIANA MARZUKI
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a MARZUKI, SANDRILIANA
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SANDRILIANA FAMILY OF MARZUKI ESTATE
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a SANDRILIANA MARZUKI BANKTRUPTCY ESTATE
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a RADEN AYU SANDRILIANA
KERATON EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PURI GRIYA TRUST ENTERPRISE
PURI GRIYA TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a SANDRILIANA MARZUKI
PURI GRIYA TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a RADEN AYU SANDRILIANA
HEADQUARTERS: 6500 CAMPUS CIR DR E, IRVING TX 75063
PRINCIPLE: 590 Centerpointe Cir, 1st Floor Suite 100, Altamonte Springs, FL 32701 MAILING: 5840 Red Bug Lake Road #1589, Winter Springs, FL 32708
February 6, 2026
#COL-555</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476913</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476912</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 1st, in the year of our Lord, 2023 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1973
Other Property Exchange  Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of KERATON
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 8:20 AM:
The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of KERATON, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 1, 2023 at 5:35 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
"P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality"
I, Marzuki, Sandriliana (creditor) d/b/a SANDRILIANA MARZUKI (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my Texas Nation Certificate of Naturalization and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Certificate of Naturalization Contract.
I declare that my name is Marzuki, Sandriliana also known as Raden Ayu Sandriliana. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Texas National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Texas republic of the United States of America - (see 2010 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of
4.
TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Texas Forms, County Municipality Forms, all "Texas" DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; "all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission." I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 1st, in the year of our Lord, 2023 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1973 (concluded)
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
KERATON
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
and all governmental, quasi, colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
I, Marzuki, Sandriliana, naturalized in the land of Texas United States of America, territory of Irving, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Marzuki, Sandriliana being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States" (Public Law 94-241 - March 24, 1976 - Article III. - 90 STAT. 266 - Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.
Place of Meeting: 1 N Fort Lauderdale Beach Blvd, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33304 (Broward County)
February 6, 2026
#COL-556</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476912</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476911</link>
      <description>DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
DECLARATION OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. March 27, 2019, 10:04 AM
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-2001
Other Property Exchange - Non-Real Property Assets Literary Minutes of Meeting of
PAYTON IMAGO DEI
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of California:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on March 27, 2019, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to The County of Seminole Recorder Office.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON IMAGO DEI DUKE OF RIVERSIDE.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON NEHEMIAH DOUGLAS
PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON DOUGLAS
PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DOUGLAS, PAYTON NEHEMIAH
PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON NEHEMIAH FAMILY OF DOUGLAS ESTATE PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON DOUGLAS BANKRUPTCY ESTATE PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON IMAGO DEI DUKE OF RIVERSIDE PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON IMAGO DEI TRUST ENTERPRISE PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PAYTON IMAGO DEI EXPRESS TRUST ENTERPRISE
AT: 2217 KING RICHARDS COURT WINTER PARK FL 32792
February 6, 2026
#COL-554</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476911</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476909</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 1st, in the year of our Lord, 2023 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1973
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of KERATON
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP
STATE OF FLORIDA)
COUNTY OF SEMINOLE)
I, MARZUKI, SANDRILIANA also known as RADEN AYU SANDRILIANA (affiant), a Texas National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of WINTER SPRINGS, FLORIDA, County of SEMINOLE, State of FLORIDA, which she recognizes and intends to maintain as her permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 705 Woodlawn Dr, Winter Springs, Florida, and that she formerly resided at 6500 CAMPUS CIR DR E, (city) IRVING (state) TEXAS, but that her abode in Florida constitutes her predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that she affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official certificate of naturalization pertaining to a registered owner named (SANDRILIANA MARZUKI) in said certificate of title showing the date of naturalization of said registered owner (SANDRILIANA MARZUKI), providing there is attached to said naturalization certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said naturalization certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (SANDRILIANA MARZUKI) as having attained the age of the majority. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the KERATON EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. 44858133, dated DECEMBER 16, 2023. Affiant further declares that SANDRILIANA MARZUKI or the SANDRILIANA FAMILY OF MARZUKI ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Florida, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.
February 6, 2026
#COL-557</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476909</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477253</link>
      <description>Public Notice
Intent to Purchase
Pursuant to Section 2-201 of the City of Deltona Code of Ordinances, notice is hereby given as follows:
The City C...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Public Notice
Intent to Purchase
Pursuant to Section 2-201 of the City of Deltona Code of Ordinances, notice is hereby given as follows:
The City Commission of the City of Deltona will consider the proposed purchase of certain real property located west of Captain Drive, north of Snow Drive, and south of Whitehorse Street in Deltona, Florida
Parcel No. 813035000100.
Legal Description:
TRACT J DELTONA LAKES UNIT 35 MB 27 PGS 150-157 INC PER OR 4020 PG 3720 PER 5477 PG 3543
Parties in Interest: 
Miguel A Gomez and Amanda Gomez, 107 Wax Myrtle Dr., Sanford, Florida 32773
City of Deltona, 2345 Providence Boulevard, Deltona, Florida 32725
Sprint-Florida, Incorporated, 6391 Sprint Parkway, Mailstop KSOPHT0101-Z240, Overland Park, Kansas 66251-2040
Bright House Networks,12405 Powerscourt Drive, St. Louis, MO 63131
Florida Power and Light Company, 700 Universe Blvd., Attn: Corp Gov, Juno Beach, Florida 33408
Date and Time of Meeting:    February 17, 2026, at 6:30 P.M.
Location: City Hall, 2345 Providence Blvd., Deltona, Florida 32725
23971
2/5/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477253</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477246</link>
      <description>Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Midtown &amp; Myrtle Creek Improvement Districts and the Poitras East Community Development Distr...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Midtown &amp; Myrtle Creek Improvement Districts and the Poitras East Community Development District
Fiscal Year 2025-2026
The Construction Committee of the Boggy Creek, Greeneway, Midtown and Myrtle Creek Improvement Districts and the Poitras East Community Development District will be meeting for the remainder of Fiscal Year 2026 in the office of Tavistock Development Company, 6900 Tavistock Lakes Blvd., Suite 200, Orlando, FL 32827 at 3:30 p.m. each month as follows:
February 12, 2026
March 5, 2026
April 9, 2026
May 14, 2026
June 11, 2026
July 9, 2026
August 13, 2026
September 10, 2026
The Construction Committee will discuss and review the status of current and future Infrastructure Improvements, Requests for Qualifications, Requests for Proposals, etc., related to the Districts.  The meetings will be open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with provisions of Florida law for Community Development Districts.  The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meetings. There may be occasions when one or more members of the Committee and/or District Staff will participate by telephone.  
Any person requiring special accommodations at these meetings because of a disability or physical impairment should contact the District Office at 407-723-5900 at least 48 hours prior to the meetings.  If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.
Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Committee with respect to any matter considered at the meetings is advised that the person will need a record of the proceedings and that, accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.
Jennifer Walden
District Manager
19596
2/5/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477246</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477242</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE
YOU WILL PLEASE TAKE NOTICE on Thursday,
February 19, 2026 at 9:30 a

Meeting: Thursday, February 19, 2026 at 9:30 a.m.

--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE
YOU WILL PLEASE TAKE NOTICE on Thursday,
February 19, 2026 at 9:30 a.m., the Pollution Control Board of the
Central Florida Tourism Oversight District will meet in regular
session at the Environmental Sciences Laboratory, 2191 South
Service Lane, Lake Buena Vista, Florida 32830. At that time, the
Board will discuss such business as may properly come before
them.
By: Doreen Johnson
24844
2/04/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477242</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477231</link>
      <description>Bid Notices
The Orange County Board of County Commissioners is soliciting bids (IFBs) and proposals (RFPs) for goods, services, construction and pr...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Bid Notices
The Orange County Board of County Commissioners is soliciting bids (IFBs) and proposals (RFPs) for goods, services, construction and professional services. Interested parties may obtain documents and subscribe to notifications at www.ocfl.net/eprocurement. For assistance, email procurement@ocfl.net or call 407-836-5635.
20775
Feb 4, 11, 18, 25, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477231</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477229</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SHINGLE CREEK TRANSIT AND UTILITY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
The Board of Supervis...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF REGULAR MEETING OF THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS OF THE SHINGLE CREEK TRANSIT AND UTILITY COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
The Board of Supervisors (the Board) of the Shingle Creek Transit and Utility Community Development District (the District) will hold a regular meeting of its Board on Wednesday, February 11, 2026, at 2:00 p.m., at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 197, Orlando, Florida 32817. At such time, the Board is so authorized and may consider any business that may properly come before it. A copy of the agenda for the meeting may be obtained by contacting the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, Phone (407) 723-5900.
The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the provisions of Florida law. The meeting may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at such meeting. There may be occasions when one or more Supervisors will participate by telephone. 
Pursuant to provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in this meeting is asked to advise the District Manager, at least forty-eight (48) hours before the meeting. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service at 7-1-1 or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY), or 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), who can aid you in contacting the District Manager.
A person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that such person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based. 
Jennifer Walden
District Manager
19594
2/4/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477229</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11477010</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT
The Valencia College District Board of Trustees announces that rule development is taking place as follows:
SUBJECT: Pol...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF RULE DEVELOPMENT
The Valencia College District Board of Trustees announces that rule development is taking place as follows:
SUBJECT: Policy 6Hx28: 3C-04 Total Rewards: Recognition of Full-Time Employees for Educational Advancement
Policy 6Hx28: 3D-06.1 Paid Parenting Leave for Full-Time Employees
PURPOSE AND EFFECT: Amend the above referenced policies to comply with current laws, college practices, and maintain consistency with the Colleges mission.
LEGAL AUTHORITY: 1001.64 FS
A copy of the preliminary draft, if available, of the proposed rule change may be obtained by contacting the office of Dr. Kathleen Plinske, Secretary to the District Board of Trustees, Valencia College, Post Office Box 3028, Orlando, Florida 32802.
22911
sfernandezdelpino@valenciacollege.edu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11477010</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476999</link>
      <description>ADVERTISEMENT TO BID FOR CONSTRUCTION
AJAX BUILDING COMPANY LLC, AS CM FOR
STATE OF FLORIDA DEPARTMENT OF CORRECTIONS
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT REQUESTIN...


--- Full Notice Text ---
ADVERTISEMENT TO BID FOR CONSTRUCTION
AJAX BUILDING COMPANY LLC, AS CM FOR
STATE OF FLORIDA DEPARTMENT OF CORRECTIONS
PUBLIC ANNOUNCEMENT REQUESTING BIDS
FROM QUALIFIED SUBCONTRACTORS
Thursday January 29, 2026
PROPOSALS ARE REQUESTED FROM QUALIFIED SUBCONTRACTORS BY AJAX BUILDING COMPANY LLC
ON BEHALF OF FLORIDA DEPARTMENT OF CORRECTIONS.
AJAX PROJECT NUMBER: 50000392
PROJECT NAME: FDC-CM20007 Lake CI Modernization
PROJECT LOCATION: Lake CI, 19225 US 27, Clermont Fl. 34715
PRE-BID MEETING: To be held via Video Call (Teams) on February 12, 2026 at 2:00pm EST. Invitations to all interested bidders.
BID OPENING: To be held at 2:00pm on March 02, 2026 at Ajaxs Jobsite Office (19225 US 27, Clermont, FL. 34715)
ESTIMATED OVERALL CONSTRUCTION BUDGET: $1,750,000.00
BID PACKAGE/SCOPE OF WORK: BP 33.34 Wastewater Treatment Project. Refer to AJAX website (below) for further details.
The award will be made in accordance with Section 255.29, Florida Statutes, and AS DETAILED IN THE SPECIFIC
BID PACKAGE.
Please visit AJAXs website https://www.ajaxbuilding.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2026/01/Website-Project-Info-
Sheet_50000392.-01-29-26.pdf
22668
2/02/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476999</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476991</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE
The Central Florida MPO Alliance (CFMPOA), whose membership is comprised of metropolitan planning organizations including the Lake-S...


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE
The Central Florida MPO Alliance (CFMPOA), whose membership is comprised of metropolitan planning organizations including the Lake-Sumter MPO, MetroPlan Orlando, Ocala/Marion TPO, Polk TPO, the Space Coast TPO, and the Volusia-Flagler TPO announces the following public meeting, to which all persons are invited:
Date: Friday, February 13, 2026
Time: 10:00 a.m.
Place: MetroPlan Orlando
David L. Grovdahl Board Room
250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200
Orlando, FL 32801
Purpose: Regularly scheduled CFMPOA meeting
A copy of the detailed agenda may be obtained by contacting Ms. Lisa Smith, 250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200, Orlando, FL 32801 (407) 481-5672, extension 307. 
Public participation is conducted without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, age, disability, religion, or family status. Persons wishing to express concerns, who require special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act, or who require language services (free of charge) should contact MetroPlan Orlando by phone at (407) 481-5672 or by email at info@metroplanorlando.org at least three business days prior to the event. 
La participacin pblica se lleva a cabo sin distincin de raza, color, origen nacional, sexo, edad, discapacidad, religin o estado familiar. Las personas que deseen expresar inquietudes, que requieran asistencia especial bajo la Ley de Americanos con Discapacidad (ADA) o que requieran servicios de traduccin (sin cargo) deben ponerse en contacto con MetroPlan Orlando por telfono (407) 481-5672 (marcar 0) o por correo electrnico info@metroplanorlando.org por lo menos tres das antes del evento.
Publish Date: - Monday, February 2, 2026 - Orlando Sentinel Legal Notices
21348  
21348  2/2/26</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476991</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476990</link>
      <description>MEETING NOTICE
MetroPlan Orlando, The Metropolitan Planning Organization for the Orlando Urban Area, announces the following meeting of its Governi...


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEETING NOTICE
MetroPlan Orlando, The Metropolitan Planning Organization for the Orlando Urban Area, announces the following meeting of its Governing Board, to which all persons are invited:
Date: Wednesday, February 11, 2026
Time: 9:00 a.m.
Physical Location: 
MetroPlan Orlando
250 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 200
Orlando, FL 32801
Online Access(*): This meeting will also be available via the Zoom platform. For information on accessing the meeting by computer or phone, see: Calendar &amp; Meeting Materials | MetroPlan Orlando
Purpose: Regularly Scheduled Board Meeting
AGENDA/GENERAL SUBJECT MATTER TO BE CONSIDERED:
1. Call to Order
2. Chairpersons Announcements
3. Executive Directors Announcements
4. Public Comments on Action Items
5. Consent Items
6. Other Action Items
7. Information Items for Acknowledgement
8. Other Business
9. Presentations
10. Board Member Comments
11. General Public Comments
12. Adjournment
For information about the meeting and agenda, contact Ms. Lisa Smith, Board Services Coordinator, MetroPlan Orlando, (407) 481-5672 extension 307, email: 
Lisa.Smith@MetroPlanOrlando.gov or visiting
https://metroplanorlando.gov/about-us/.
Public participation is conducted without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, age, disability, religion, or family status. Persons wishing to express concerns, who require special assistance under the Americans with Disabilities Act, or who require language services (free of charge) should contact MetroPlan Orlando by phone at (407) 481-5672 or by email at info@metroplanorlando.org at least three business days prior to the event.
La participacin pblica se lleva a cabo sin distincin de raza, color, origen nacional, sexo, edad, discapacidad, religin o estado familiar. Las personas que deseen expresar inquietudes, que requieran asistencia especial bajo la Ley de Americanos con Discapacidad (ADA) o que requieran servicios de traduccin (sin cargo) deben ponerse en contacto con MetroPlan Orlando por telfono (407) 481-5672 (marcar 0) o por correo electrnico info@metroplanorlando.org por lo menos tres das antes del evento.
As required by Section 286.0105, Florida Statutes, MetroPlan Orlando hereby notifies all interested parties that if a person decides to appeal any decision made by MetroPlan Orlando with respect to any matter considered at such meeting or hearing, he or she may need to ensure that a verbatim record is made to include the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is to be based.
Publish Date:  Orlando Sentinel Legal Notices  Monday February 2, 2026
21309
2/2/26</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476990</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11476987</link>
      <description>Request for Qualifications Continuing Service Contract for  Mechanical, Electrical and Plumbing Design/Engineering Services  RFQ # SDOC-26-Q-058-CH...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Request for Qualifications Continuing Service Contract for  Mechanical, Electrical and Plumbing Design/Engineering Services  RFQ # SDOC-26-Q-058-CH-FPC
The School Board of Osceola County, Florida announces that proposals are being solicited for Continuing Service Contract for Mechanical, Electrical and Plumbing Design/Engineering Services. Submittal deadline is February 11, 2026. The solicitation may be downloaded from the Districts web site: https://vendorlink.osceola.org/common/login.aspx
Should you have questions in regards to this solicitation, please contact:
Cheryl Hood, Supervisor of Purchasing
School District of Osceola County
817 Bill Beck Blvd.
Kissimmee, Florida 34744
Email: cheryl.hood@osceolaschools.net
Phone: 407.870-4627
Fax: 407.870.4616
Hours: 8:00 a.m.-4:30 p.m./Monday-Friday
An Equal Opportunity Agency
7921201
1/19 1/25 2/02/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11476987</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471577</link>
      <description>Notice at 4974 ORL Tower Road

Location: 4974 ORL Tower Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
INVITATION TO BID   CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY (CFX) ORLANDO, FLORIDASealed Electronic Bids for the work generally described below will be received on March 04, 2026, until 1:30p.m., Orlando local time, as shown on the CFX website. The CFX website will serve as the official instrument to determine when a bid is received.  A submittal that is received after the date/time specified will be rejected. Rejection of a submittal under those circumstances shall not be the basis of a protest pursuant to the CFX Procedure for Resolution of Protests.  Bid opening at CFXs Headquarters Building located at 4974 ORL Tower Road, Orlando, FL. 32807, shall immediately follow the bid submittal deadline. Such bid opening will additionally be accessible by online stream by use of the web-conference information provided in the full version of this invitation to bid.  SYSTEMWIDE FY 23 COATINGS OF STEEL BRIDGE &amp; SYSTEMWIDE FY23 COAT RAMP PLAZA BUTTERFLY STRUCTURES SOLICITATION NO. 260101, PROJECT NO. 599-773 &amp; 599-774  The work consists of providing all labor, materials, equipment, and incidentals necessary to clean and coat steel structural elements for nine (9) butterfly trusses and eighteen (18) steel bridges along the CFX System.  Butterfly truss locations are along SR 408: EB Conway Rd (75A031), Andes Ave (75S959), Yucatan Dr (75S961). Locations along SR 417: Lake Nona Blvd (75A057 &amp; 75A058), Curry Ford Rd (75S683 &amp; 75S684), University Blvd (75S685 &amp; 75S686). Four (4) of the above locations are clean, spot repair and overcoat, four (4) are Full removal (coating) and re-coat and one (1) location is cleaning only.  Steel bridge locations are along SR 408: Hiawassee Rd (750396 &amp; 750397), Pine Hills Mainline Toll Plaza pedestrian overpass (759011), WB I-4 Ramp (750571), WB Conway Road (750589), EB Andes Ave (750579), SR 436 (750581). Locations along SR 417: SR 528 WB (750470), SR 528 EB (750374), Colonial Dr (750343 &amp; 750342), University Blvd (750557&amp; 750348). Locations along SR 414: Clarcona Rd (750703), Keene Rd (750705). Hiawassee Rd (750712), Orange Blossom Tr (750743). Locations along SR 429: Porter Rd (750526). Seventeen (17) of the above locations are clean, spot repair and overcoat while one (1) is Full removal (coating) and re-coat. Two (2) locations; 750470 and 750374 include cleaning and coating of existing concrete elements. All work is in Orange County.  For a full version of the invitation for this project including additional information regarding availability of the Bidding Documents, pre-qualification requirements, pre-bid meeting, protest procedure, and bonding requirements refer to CFXs web site at www.CFXWay.com.  CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY  Zulay Millan Director of Procurement 7925317 2/1/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471577</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471576</link>
      <description>CITY OF WINTER GARDEN REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS RFP #26-002 JANITORIAL SERVICES FOR WINTER GARDEN   The City of Winter Garden, Florida, is soliciting p...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF WINTER GARDEN REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS RFP #26-002 JANITORIAL SERVICES FOR WINTER GARDEN   The City of Winter Garden, Florida, is soliciting proposals from qualified vendors that are interested in providing janitorial and floor care services for various buildings and departments.  Proposal packages must be received no later than 4 PM (local time) on Monday, April 13, 2026. Any proposal packages received after the above-noted time will not be accepted under any circumstances. Any uncertainty regarding the time a proposal package is received will be resolved against the Respondent. Proposal packages submitted after this designated time will be returned unopened.  Contractors interested in providing the janitorial services shall submit one (1) original, four (4) copies, and one (1) flash drive containing all original documents of the required response of their proposal to the City of Winter Garden reception desk by the submission deadline to the attention of:  David W. Markland  Facilities Operations Manager City of Winter Garden RFP #26-002 300 W. Plant Street Winter Garden, FL 34787  No faxed or electronic submissions will be accepted.  RFP proposal packages may be obtained Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to 4:30 pm, by emailing David Markland at dmarkland@cwgdn.com . The City of Winter Garden reserves the right to accept or reject, in part or total, any or all proposals and to waive any informalities as deemed in the best interest of the City.  Each proposer must request the RFP package by emailing David Markland. A link to download all pertinent documents will then be provided. Each proposer must download the RFP package before submitting a proposal and ensure a representative attends the MANDATORY PRE-PROPOSAL MEETING. The Mandatory Pre-Proposal Meeting is scheduled for 9:00 a.m. on Thursday March 5 th , 2026, at the Tanner Hall, 29 W. Garden Avenue, Winter Garden, Florida 34787. Proposers who have not purchased an RFP package from the City prior to submitting their proposal and do not have a representative attend the Mandatory Pre-Proposal Meeting shall be disqualified.  All proposals must be marked on the outside of the envelope with the proposers name, project name, and the time and date of opening. It shall be the PROPOSERS responsibility to ensure that proposals are delivered to the above address by the appointed time.  David Markland Facilities Operations Manager   2/01/2026 7925304</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471576</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471573</link>
      <description>NOTICE TO ALL PROPERTY OWNERS AND RESIDENTS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDAPursuant to s


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE TO ALL PROPERTY OWNERS AND RESIDENTS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDAPursuant to s. 1001.372(2)(c), Fla. Stat. and s. 50.0311(6), Fla. Stat., please be notified that all meetings of the Orange County School Board will be advertised on a link located on the Boards homepage of ocps.net. Those desiring to receive legally required advertisements and public notices from the School Board by first-class mail or email must register their name or email address with the School Board.  You may send your request via first-class mail to School Board Clerk, Orange County Public Schools, 445 W. Amelia Street, Orlando, FL 32801.  You may send your request via email to schoolboardclerk@ocps.net.  You must include your name, address and telephone number in case the Clerk has questions.  _____________________ Maria F. Vazquez Superintendent   2/1/2026 7924942</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471573</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471534</link>
      <description>Notice at 4974 ORL Tower Road

Location: 4974 ORL Tower Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
INVITATION TO BID   CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY (CFX) ORLANDO, FLORIDASealed Electronic Bids for the work generally described below will be received on March 04, 2026, until 1:30p.m., Orlando local time, as shown on the CFX website. The CFX website will serve as the official instrument to determine when a bid is received.  A submittal that is received after the date/time specified will be rejected. Rejection of a submittal under those circumstances shall not be the basis of a protest pursuant to the CFX Procedure for Resolution of Protests.  Bid opening at CFXs Headquarters Building located at 4974 ORL Tower Road, Orlando, FL. 32807, shall immediately follow the bid submittal deadline. Such bid opening will additionally be accessible by online stream by use of the web-conference information provided in the full version of this invitation to bid.  SYSTEMWIDE FY 23 COATINGS OF STEEL BRIDGE &amp; SYSTEMWIDE FY23 COAT RAMP PLAZA BUTTERFLY STRUCTURES SOLICITATION NO. 260101, PROJECT NO. 599-773 &amp; 599-774  The work consists of providing all labor, materials, equipment, and incidentals necessary to clean and coat steel structural elements for nine (9) butterfly trusses and eighteen (18) steel bridges along the CFX System.  Butterfly truss locations are along SR 408: EB Conway Rd (75A031), Andes Ave (75S959), Yucatan Dr (75S961). Locations along SR 417: Lake Nona Blvd (75A057 &amp; 75A058), Curry Ford Rd (75S683 &amp; 75S684), University Blvd (75S685 &amp; 75S686). Four (4) of the above locations are clean, spot repair and overcoat, four (4) are Full removal (coating) and re-coat and one (1) location is cleaning only.  Steel bridge locations are along SR 408: Hiawassee Rd (750396 &amp; 750397), Pine Hills Mainline Toll Plaza pedestrian overpass (759011), WB I-4 Ramp (750571), WB Conway Road (750589), EB Andes Ave (750579), SR 436 (750581). Locations along SR 417: SR 528 WB (750470), SR 528 EB (750374), Colonial Dr (750343 &amp; 750342), University Blvd (750557&amp; 750348). Locations along SR 414: Clarcona Rd (750703), Keene Rd (750705). Hiawassee Rd (750712), Orange Blossom Tr (750743). Locations along SR 429: Porter Rd (750526). Seventeen (17) of the above locations are clean, spot repair and overcoat while one (1) is Full removal (coating) and re-coat. Two (2) locations; 750470 and 750374 include cleaning and coating of existing concrete elements. All work is in Orange County.  For a full version of the invitation for this project including additional information regarding availability of the Bidding Documents, pre-qualification requirements, pre-bid meeting, protest procedure, and bonding requirements refer to CFXs web site at www.CFXWay.com.  CENTRAL FLORIDA EXPRESSWAY AUTHORITY  Zulay Millan Director of Procurement 7925317 2/1/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471534</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bid Notices and Requests for Services - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471533</link>
      <description>CITY OF WINTER GARDEN REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS RFP #26-002 JANITORIAL SERVICES FOR WINTER GARDEN   The City of Winter Garden, Florida, is soliciting p...


--- Full Notice Text ---
CITY OF WINTER GARDEN REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS RFP #26-002 JANITORIAL SERVICES FOR WINTER GARDEN   The City of Winter Garden, Florida, is soliciting proposals from qualified vendors that are interested in providing janitorial and floor care services for various buildings and departments.  Proposal packages must be received no later than 4 PM (local time) on Monday, April 13, 2026. Any proposal packages received after the above-noted time will not be accepted under any circumstances. Any uncertainty regarding the time a proposal package is received will be resolved against the Respondent. Proposal packages submitted after this designated time will be returned unopened.  Contractors interested in providing the janitorial services shall submit one (1) original, four (4) copies, and one (1) flash drive containing all original documents of the required response of their proposal to the City of Winter Garden reception desk by the submission deadline to the attention of:  David W. Markland  Facilities Operations Manager City of Winter Garden RFP #26-002 300 W. Plant Street Winter Garden, FL 34787  No faxed or electronic submissions will be accepted.  RFP proposal packages may be obtained Monday through Friday, 8:00 am to 4:30 pm, by emailing David Markland at dmarkland@cwgdn.com . The City of Winter Garden reserves the right to accept or reject, in part or total, any or all proposals and to waive any informalities as deemed in the best interest of the City.  Each proposer must request the RFP package by emailing David Markland. A link to download all pertinent documents will then be provided. Each proposer must download the RFP package before submitting a proposal and ensure a representative attends the MANDATORY PRE-PROPOSAL MEETING. The Mandatory Pre-Proposal Meeting is scheduled for 9:00 a.m. on Thursday March 5 th , 2026, at the Tanner Hall, 29 W. Garden Avenue, Winter Garden, Florida 34787. Proposers who have not purchased an RFP package from the City prior to submitting their proposal and do not have a representative attend the Mandatory Pre-Proposal Meeting shall be disqualified.  All proposals must be marked on the outside of the envelope with the proposers name, project name, and the time and date of opening. It shall be the PROPOSERS responsibility to ensure that proposals are delivered to the above address by the appointed time.  David Markland Facilities Operations Manager   2/01/2026 7925304</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471533</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11471530</link>
      <description>NOTICE TO ALL PROPERTY OWNERS AND RESIDENTS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDAPursuant to s


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE TO ALL PROPERTY OWNERS AND RESIDENTS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDAPursuant to s. 1001.372(2)(c), Fla. Stat. and s. 50.0311(6), Fla. Stat., please be notified that all meetings of the Orange County School Board will be advertised on a link located on the Boards homepage of ocps.net. Those desiring to receive legally required advertisements and public notices from the School Board by first-class mail or email must register their name or email address with the School Board.  You may send your request via first-class mail to School Board Clerk, Orange County Public Schools, 445 W. Amelia Street, Orlando, FL 32801.  You may send your request via email to schoolboardclerk@ocps.net.  You must include your name, address and telephone number in case the Clerk has questions.  _____________________ Maria F. Vazquez Superintendent   2/1/2026 7924942</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11471530</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/13/11470713.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470713</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11470713.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/11/11470711.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470711</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11470711.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11470609</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 07th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 4-1967
Other Property Exchange - Non-Real Estate Assets Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PRIVATE CONTRACT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 2:01 PM:
The Sole Trustee (second party), known as Last, First Middle from the Board of Trustees, of DIVINE HOUSE OF EL, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 07, 2000 at 10:07AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of COUNTY RECORDERS OFFICE IN THE STATE OF FLORIDA, with the County Clerk of Court (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court, Title 8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)) bears witness and holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
"P. Law 99-396  AUG. 27, 1986, Oath of Allegiance"
I declare that my name is Zafinirina, Maria Luciana. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Madagascar National, pursuant to Public Law 99-396  August 27, 1986, Section 16 but not a citizen of the United States, and have entered into a Private Express Trust Contract to manage property known as 1452 W WIGWAM BLVD UNIT 1225 LITCHFIELD PARK AZ, PARCEL 508-13-697, SEC 21/2N/1W, LOT 1225 in the Continental United States of America for the DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST, filed and recorded with the Clerk of Court in the County of Seminole within the State of Florida.
TAKE EQUITABLE NOTICE, the trustee(s) of an Express Trust are protected under the Constitution as citizens throughout the continental United States. The trustee(s) under a will or declaration of an Express Trust are natural persons, "citizens" within the meaning of Article IV, Section 2 of the Constitution, and are therefore entitled to all the privileges and immunities of the same. - Paul v. Virginia, 75 U.S. 168 (1868).
TAKE EQUITABLE NOTICE, 1849 California Constitution - Declaration of Rights - Section 17, Foreigners who are, of who may hereafter become bona fide residents if this State, shall enjoy the same rights in respect to the possession, enjoyment, and inheritance of property, as native born citizens.
TAKE EQUITABLE NOTICE, to all court officials, county officers, city and district representatives, "No State shall enter into any Treaty, Alliance, or Confederation; grant Letters of Marque and Reprisal; coin Money; emit Bills of Credit; make any Thing but gold and silver Coin a Tender in Payment of Debts; pass any Bill of Attainder, ex post facto Law, or Law impairing the Obligation of Contracts, or grant any Title of Nobility  U.S.A. Constitution, Article I, Section 10, Clause 1.
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 07th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 4-1967 - "concluded"
Other Property Exchange - Non-Real Estate Assets Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PRIVATE CONTRACT
There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 2:29 PM
January 30, 2026
#COL-551</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470609</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11470608</link>
      <description>Prepared By: Creflo Holoman
Firm: Via Iure, LLC
1070 Montgomery Road, Suite 2333
Altamonte Springs, FL 32714
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
Prepared By: Creflo Holoman
Firm: Via Iure, LLC
1070 Montgomery Road, Suite 2333
Altamonte Springs, FL 32714
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est. January 7th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
THIS INDENTURE ("Agreement") made this 7th day of March, 2000 serves as a Declaration of Express Trust and shall continue for a term of twenty-five (25) years from this day, between NECOLIOUS HOOKER III herein known as the Settlor and Trust Protector, (the first party) and MARIA LUCIANA ZAFINIRINA Trustee, herein known as the First Trustee, Sole Trustee or Trustee, (the second party), under the name of DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a IMHOTEP ALI EL, PHAROAH OF SAN DIEGO. With this contract, the Parties intend to create an Express Trust Organization for the benefit of the Trust Certificate Unit Holders and to identify, accumulate, purchase and hold any assets that become available and to provide for a prudent administration and distribution system administered by legal persons acting in a fiduciary capacity. WITNESSETH: Whereas the Settlor, irrevocably assigns and conveys to the Trustee, in trust, specific properties as defined in The Trustee Minutes (1-1967), attached to this document in exchange for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a IMHOTEP ALI EL, PHAROAH OF SAN DIEGO. Trust: Trust includes an express trust, private or charitable, with additions thereto, wherever and however created. Property: "Property" means anything that may be the subject of ownership and includes both real and personal property. Person: "Person" means any natural person, individual, corporation, government or governmental subdivision or agency, business trust, estate, trust, partnership, limited liability company, association, or other entity.
Settlor: NECOLIOUS HOOKER III of 14175 West Indian School Rd, Ste B4 PMB #136, Goodyear, Arizona, doing business in Seminole County, Florida of 2170 W State Road 434, Longwood, FL 32779 - (defined) in law a settlor is a person who settles property in trust law for the benefit of beneficiaries. In some legal systems, a settlor is also referred to as a trustor or occasionally, a grantor or donor... A settlor may create a trust manifesting an intention to create it; grantor is the person who creates the trust.
Trust Protector: NECOLIOUS HOOKER III or other authorized person in the future by settlor, - (defined) appointed under the trust instrument to direct, restrain, remove the trustee(s) or appoint a successor.
Trustee(s): MARIA LUCIANA ZAFINIRINA of ANKIRIHIRY NORD, p/lle, 11/52, Toamasina, Madagascar - (defined) includes an original, additional, or successor trustee, whether or not appointed or confirmed by a court. A person or firm that holds or administers property or assets for the benefit of a third party and can be given the powers to make investment decisions for the Trust, or vote on the distribution of assets to the beneficiaries and/or has the power to hire persons whether an authorized person or not, including accountants, attorneys, auditors, investment advisers, appraisers or other agents even if they are associated or affiliated with the trustee, to advise or assist the trustee in the performance of administrative duties. Beneficial Owner: DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST herein known as the First Beneficiary and other beneficiaries to come in future (defined) beneficial owner is where specific property rights ("use and title") in equity belong to a person even though legal title of the property belongs to another person. This often relates where the legal title owner has implied trustee duties to the beneficial owner.
WHEREAS, the Trust Organization is authorized to exist and function through its Board of Trustees, comprised of the total active number of trustees who are legal persons holding fee simple title, not differentiating between legal and equitable, not as individuals, but collectively as the Board, according to the inalienable Common Law rights.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be amendable, as described in the bylaws, and shall be irrevocable by the Settlor or by any other person or entity but said trustee can be fired by the Trust Protector and replace by new trustee appointed by the Trust Protector. It is the intention of the Settlor to make the Beneficiaries, an absolute gift of the Trust Certificate Units (TCUs), in which the Beneficiaries shall not have any vested interest, until the termination of this Trust and final distribution accumulated assets or any early distribution of the assets thereof. There shall be exactly 100 Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) available to the Beneficiaries. WHEREAS, the Trust shall be administered, managed, governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida and Arizona, being bound to the Articles of Confederation of 1781, Article IV.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be governed by its country's applicable laws known as Muscat (Muskat), Sultanate of Oman, with formation documents governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida and Arizona to govern the interpretation of the trust. Under the law of the Sultanate of Oman, a court within Oman, is able to exercise primary supervision over the administration of the trust. The Treaty of Marrakesh, the Treaty of Maskat of 1833, the Articles of Association, the Articles of Confederation, and the Uniform Commercial Code (only when and if applicable and/or allowable to remain under the jurisdiction of the Common Law). The domicile of the trust is within the Court of Equity, in Florida and Arizona in the Republic of the United States of America but shall have full faith and credit in any State as a last resort when everything else fails.
January 30, 2026
#COL-552</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470608</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11470607</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 7th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1967
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP
STATE OF ARIZONA)
COUNTY OF MARICOPA)
I, HOOKER III, NECOLIOUS also known as IMHOTEP ALI EL, PHAROAH OF SAN DIEGO (affiant), a Californian National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of GOODYEAR, County of MARICOPA, State of ARIZONA, which he recognizes and intends to maintain as his permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 14175 West Indian School Road, Ste B4, PMB #136 Goodyear, Arizona, and that he formerly resided at 1600 PACIFIC HWY #160 (city) SAN DIEGO (state) CALIFORNIA, but that his abode in Arizona constitutes his predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that he affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (NECOLIOUS HOOKER III) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (NECOLIOUS HOOKER III), providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (NECOLIOUS HOOKER III) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. 15049893-1, dated AUGUST 13, 2015. Affiant further declares that NECOLIOUS HOOKER III or the NECOLIOUS FAMILY OF HOOKER III ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Arizona, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.
January 30, 2026
#COL-549</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470607</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11470606</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 7th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1967
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 8:20 AM:
The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of DIVINE HOUSE OF EL, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 7, 2000 at 5:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality"
I, Hooker III, Necolious (creditor) d/b/a NECOLIOUS HOOKER III (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my California Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.
I declare that my name is Hooker III, Necolious also known as IMHOTEP Ali El, Pharoah of San Diego Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native Californian National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Arizona republic of the United States of America  (see 2000 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism" crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4.
TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Arizona Forms, County Municipality Forms, all "AZ" DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; "all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission." I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1967 - "concluded"
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or
Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
I, Hooker III, Necolious, born in the land of California United States of America, territory of San Diego, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Hooker III. Necolious being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States" (Public Law 94-241 - March 24, 1976 - Article III. - 90 STAT. 266 - Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.
Place of Meeting: 587 E State Road 434, Longwood, Fl 32750 (Seminole County)
There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 8:25 AM
January 30, 2026
#COL-548</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470606</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11470605</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 7th, in the year of our Lord, 2000 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1967
Other Property Exchange - Intangible Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Arizona &amp; Florida:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on January 07, 2000, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a NECOLIOUS HOOKER III
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a HOOKER III, NECOLIOUS
DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a NECOLIOUS FAMILY OF HOOKER III ESTATE DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a NECOLIOUS HOOKER III BANKRUPTCY ESTATE DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a IMHOTEP ALI EL, PHAROAH OF SAN DIEGO DIVINE HOUSE OF EL EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a DIVINE TRUST ENTERPRISE
DIVINE TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a NECOLIOUS HOOKER III
DIVINE TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a IMHOTEP ALI EL, PHAROAH OF SAN DIEGO
HEADQUARTERS: 1600 PACIFIC HWY #260, SAN DIEGO, CA 92101
PRINCIPAL: 660 CENTURY POINTE, 1ST FLOOR, STE A, LAKE MARY, FL 32746 MAILING: 14175 WEST INDIAN SCHOOL RD. STE B4, PMB #136, GOODYEAR, AZ 85395
January 30, 2026
#COL-550</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11470605</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469138</link>
      <description>Notice at the self-service storage facilityfor rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property

Location: the self-service storage facilityfor rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property

--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PUBLIC SALE
Pursuant to the Florida Self Storage Lien Act, the owner of a self-storage facility has a lien upon all personal property located at the self-service storage facilityfor rent or other charges incurred for the storage of the personal property. Due to the failure to pay the rent, the owner is enforcing its lien and intends to sellor otherwise dispose of the personal property located in the rented spaces listed in this notice. THIS NOTICE IS BEING PROVIDED PURSUANT TO FLORIDA STATE LAW BEFORE the sale, the tenants listed may pay theamount necessary to satisfy the lien and the reasonable expenses incurred to redeem the personal property. 
ADVERTISEMENT OF SALE:
Notice is hereby given that the personal property located in the following storage units will be sold by competitive bidding.
Facility Name: Istorage-932 Dyer Blvd. Kissimmee, FL 34741.
Deontay Beverly- Clothes, Ironing board, Bedding, car part, food, water, Cleaning Supplies, Thread holder, Totes, Boxes.Valeria Ortega- Skateboard, Skates, Totes, Pots, Baskets, Clothes, TV, Blankets, Crafts, Suitcase, Personal, items. Wilmer Inojosa- Bed Frame, Mattress, Fans, Heater, Bike, Jack, Car seat, CarParts, Small Sail boat figurines, Hand tools, Car fluids, Light poll, TV, Tool box,Art.Kutrina Lee- Fan, Table, chairs, Dining Set, Bed Frame, TV, Mattress, Lamps. Dresser, Pictures, Clothes, Rug, Jordan Shoes, Personal Items.Edwin J C Carrero- Popcorn machine, White chair, Desk, Dolly, Skeleton, Totes, Food Containers, Bike, Ladder, Rolling Cart, Deep Freezer, Insulation. Gitza Hernandez- Misc. ItemsEdward Dyer- Misc. Items
All bidding will take place online at StorageTreasures.com on FEBRUARY 13, 2026, at 9:00 A.M. Property will be sold to the highest bidder
January 29, 2026
February 5, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469138</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469127</link>
      <description>PUBLIC NOTICE
WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA
Cancellation of February 4, 2026, Board Meeting
The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Board m...


--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE
WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA
Cancellation of February 4, 2026, Board Meeting
The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Board meeting date of February 4, 2026, is cancelled. The scheduled March 4, 2026, meeting is confirmed as the next WCCF Board meeting.
The purpose of these WCCF Board meetings is to act upon and approve any proposed regional water supply projects. Any changes to this schedule will be published for notification at least 7 days before subsequent adjustments.
The meetings will take place from 2:00 pm to 3:00 pm and be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Administration Building, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741.
Anyone interested in obtaining more information about these meetings may contact Todd Swingle at 407-944-5131. Any person requiring special accommodation at the meetings, because of a disability or physical impairment, should contact the Toho Executive Office at 407-944-5130.
January 29, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469127</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469124</link>
      <description>Notice at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

Location: 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard

--- Full Notice Text ---
EVEREST GMR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT DISTRICT
Notice of Board of Supervisors Meeting


A regular Board of Supervisors meeting of the Everest GMR Community Development District will be held on Wednesday, February 11, 2026, at 11:00 a.m. at 8298 W Irlo Bronson Memorial Hwy, Kissimmee, FL 34747. A copy of the agenda may be obtained at the offices of the District Manager, PFM Group Consulting LLC, located at 3501 Quadrangle Boulevard, Suite 270, Orlando, Florida 32817, (407) 723-5900, during normal business hours. Additionally, a copy of the agenda may be obtained at http://everestgmrcdd.com/.


The meeting is open to the public and will be conducted in accordance with the pertinent provisions of Florida Law for Community Development Districts. The meetings may be continued to a date, time, and place to be specified on the record at the meeting. There may be occasions when Board Supervisors or District Staff may participate by speaker telephone.


Pursuant to the Americans with Disabilities Act, any person requiring special accommodations to participate in the meeting is asked to advise the District Office at (407) 723-5940 at least forty-eight (48) hours prior to the meetings. If you are hearing or speech impaired, please contact the Florida Relay Service by dialing 7-1-1, or 1-800-955-8771 (TTY) / 1-800-955-8770 (Voice), for aid in contacting the District Office.


Any person who decides to appeal any decision made by the Board with respect to any matter considered at the meeting is advised that this same person will need a record of the proceedings and that accordingly, the person may need to ensure that a verbatim record of the proceedings is made, including the testimony and evidence upon which such appeal is to be based.


Jane Gaarlandt
District Manager
January 29, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469124</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11469107</link>
      <description>Notice at Jones Road

Location: Jones Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
SECTION 106PUBLIC NOTICE
Gulfstream Towers proposes to construct a 180-foot-tall Monopine tower located at Jones Road, St. Cloud, Osceola County, FL 34771. Parcel ID: 21-25-31-4260-0001-0650 at Latitude N28 17' 29.82", Longitude W81 12' 41.43". Gulfstream Towers seeks comments from all interested persons on the impact of the tower on any districts, sites, buildings, structures, or objects significant in American history, architecture, archaeology, engineering, or culture, that are listed or eligible for listing in the National Register of Historic Places. Specific information about the project, including the historic preservation reviews that Gulfstream Towers is conducting pursuant to the rules of the Federal Communications Commission (47 C.F.R. Sections 1.1307(4)) and the Advisory Council on Historic Preservation (36 C.F.R. Part 800) will be made available to interested persons who request the information from the contact below. All questions, comments, and correspondence should be directed to Julia Klima at Dynamic Environmental Associates, Inc., 3850 Lake Street, Suite C, Macon, GA 31204, 877-968-4787, Sec106@DynamicEnvironmental.com within 30 days from the date of this publication. Re: 22312031
January 29, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11469107</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11466165</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENTOn Monday, February 9, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2026-1, entitled: AN ORDINANCE ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENTOn Monday, February 9, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2026-1, entitled: AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, VACATING,  CLOSING, AND ABANDONING APPROXIMATELY 91 FEET OF WEST ILLIANA STREET,  GENERALLY LOCATED EAST OF CSX RAILROAD, SOUTH OF WEST MICHIGAN STREET, WEST  OF TAYLOR AVENUE AND NORTH OF WEST PINELOCH AVENUE, AS DESCRIBED IN THE PLAT  OF GEORGE GREENMORES SUBDIVISION, AS RECORDED IN PLAT BOOK G, PAGE 79 AND IN  THE CARLTON TERRACE PLAT, AS RECORDED IN PLAT BOOK O, PAGE 38 IN THE PUBLIC  RECORDS OF ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA, AND COMPRISED OF 0.126 ACRES OF LAND, MORE  OR LESS; PROVIDING FOR CONDITIONS OF ABANDONMENT; THE EXECUTION OF EFFECTING  DOCUMENTS, SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE  DATE. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00  p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties  may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information  about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/council meeting at least  3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may  participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in  advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the  designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed  ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S.  Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision  made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the  proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is  committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with  disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24  hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov. 7923955 1/27/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11466165</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11466162</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, February 9, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2025-48, entitled:  AN ORDIN...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF PROPOSED ENACTMENT   On Monday, February 9, 2026, the Orlando City Council will consider proposed ordinance #2025-48, entitled:  AN ORDINANCE OF THE CITY COUNCIL OF THE CITY OF ORLANDO, FLORIDA, AMENDING THE LAND DEVELOPMENT REGULATIONS OF THE WEWAHOOTEE PLANNED DEVELOPMENT ZONING DISTRICT, SUCH DISTRICT BEING COMPRISED OF APPROXIMATELY 1,262 ACRES AND GENERALLY LOCATED NORTH OF MOSS PARK RD., SOUTH OF STATE ROAD 528, AND EAST  OF STATE ROAD 417; PROVIDING FOR SEVERABILITY, CORRECTION OF SCRIVENERS ERRORS, AND AN EFFECTIVE DATE. A public hearing on this ordinance will be held during Councils regular meeting beginning at 2:00 p.m., in Council Chamber, 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida. Interested parties may appear at the meeting and be heard with respect to the proposed ordinance. All pertinent information about meeting access and participation instructions will be available on orlando.gov/council meeting at least 3 days prior to the meeting. Additionally, interested parties are invited to watch the meeting live and may participate by providing public comment during the meeting or submitting written public comment in advance regarding the proposed ordinance. The opportunity to provide public comment is available until the designated public comment portion of the item is closed. All items received are public record. The proposed ordinance may be inspected at the Office of the City Clerk located on the 2nd floor, Orlando City Hall, 400 S. Orange Ave., Orlando, Florida or online at orlando.gov. Anyone who desires to appeal an official decision made at this meeting, if an appeal is permitted by law, may need to obtain a verbatim record of the proceedings that includes the testimony and evidence upon which the appeal is based. The City of Orlando is committed to reasonably accommodating the communication needs of persons with disabilities. Persons with disabilities who need reasonable accommodations to participate in this meeting, contact no later than 24 hours in advance of the meeting, the Office of the City Clerk at 407.246.2251 or cityclerk@orlando.gov. 7922919 1/27/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11466162</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11465535</link>
      <description>PUBLIC NOTICE  RANGER DRAINAGE DISTRICT BOARD OF SUPERVISORS ATTORNEY - CLIENT SESSIONFEBRUARY 4, 2026  5:30 p


--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE  RANGER DRAINAGE DISTRICT BOARD OF SUPERVISORS ATTORNEY - CLIENT SESSIONFEBRUARY 4, 2026  5:30 p.m.  RANGER DRAINAGE DISTRICT OFFICE  19950 Nugent Street  Orlando, FL 32833   YOU ARE HEREBY NOTIFIED that at the request of the Districts Counsel, an attorney-client session will be held under the Shade Meeting provisions available under Floridas Sunshine Law, Florida Statutes 286.011(8) on February 4, 2026 beginning at 5:30 p.m. and lasting for up to one (1) hour. This meeting shall commence at an open meeting and then will move into the attorney-client session limited in attendance to: the Ranger Drainage District attorneys from Lewis, Longman &amp; Walker, P.A.: Kevin Hennessy, Seth Behn, and John Cavaliere; District Supervisors: David Mauck, Mike Nolan, and Russell Beyersdorf; District General Manager, Dawn Mullins; and, a court reporter who will transcribe the full proceedings. The meeting transcription will be made part of the public record for release at the conclusion of the litigation. The client attorney session will be for the purpose of discussing: settlement negotiations and strategy sessions related to litigation expenditures in the following court case: Ranger Drainage District v. Gary Mittan: Case No. 2024-CA-003664-O, pending in the Circuit Court of the Ninth Judicial Circuit in and for Orange County, Florida. Published January 26, 2026   1/26/26 7922067</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11465535</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/31/11465531.pdf</link>
      <description>1/26/26 NOTICE OF 1 ST PUBLIC HEARING OF THE 2026-2030 CONSOLIDATED PLAN AND 2026 ACTION PLAN AND FUNDING AVAILABILITY 2026-2030 Consolidated Plan ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
1/26/26 NOTICE OF 1 ST PUBLIC HEARING OF THE 2026-2030 CONSOLIDATED PLAN AND 2026 ACTION PLAN AND FUNDING AVAILABILITY 2026-2030 Consolidated Plan In compliance with federal regulations under 25 CFR Part 91, the City of Orlando must develop and submit a five-year Consolidated Plan outlining its housing and community development priorities, based on an evaluation of neighborhood needs. This Plan will identify strategies to support low and moderateincome residents, strengthen neighborhoods, and address the needs of individuals experiencing homelessness and those with special needs. Along with feedback gathered through community surveys, this meeting provides an additional opportunity for residents to share their perspectives on housing and community development needs within the City of Orlando and to help shape the 2026-2030 Consolidated Plan. Residents of the City of Orlando are encouraged to participate in this discussion about housing and community needs and the programs that may address them. Funding to support identified priorities is expected from the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development through the following programs: Community Development Block Grant (CDBG), Emergency Solutions Grant (ESG), HOME Investment Partnerships Program (HOME), and Housing Opportunities for Persons with AIDS (HOPWA). Action Plan FY 2026-2027 Funding Availability The City of Orlando Housing and Community Development Department is anticipating an announcement from the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development regarding the Program Year (PY) 2026- 2027 Community Development Block Grant (CDBG), Emergency Solutions Grant (ESG), HOME Investment Partnerships Program (HOME) and HousingOpportunities for Persons with AIDS Program (HOPWA). The federal funding allocations for PY2025 were $2,522,385 in CDBG, $220,965 in ESG, $1,207,798 in HOME and $5,638,344 in HOPWA. The city anticipates receiving similar funding allocations for PY2026 and is soliciting proposals from non-profit organizations that serve the community. This notice begins the local application process. HOME funding applications are accepted on an ongoing basis. HOPWA funds are administered by Orange County. CDBG program funds are available for the provision of affordable housing, community and economic development activities and assistance for low- and moderate-income persons and special populations within the City of Orlando. The city will give priority to affordable housing and related services. ESG program funds are available for emergency shelters and activities that support rapid re-housing and homelessness prevention.  Activities funded by CDBG and ESG programs must contribute to the goals and objectives of the City of Orlando 2026-2030 Consolidated Plan and meet all applicable federal requirements. All interested non-profit agencies are invited to apply for PY2026 grant funding. A link to the mandatory CDBG pre-application and ESG application will be available on February 9, 2026, on the citys website: orlando.gov/housing. Public Hearing A public hearing to gather input on housing and community development needs for the preparation of the 2026-2030 Consolidated Plan, as well as to conduct an application workshop for the FY 2026-27 Action Plan will be held in the Fairview Room, on the Ninth Floor of Orlando City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, FL 32801, on Monday, February16, 2026, from 9 a.m. to 12 p.m. Final applications for CDBG and ESG program funds will be due at 5 p.m. EDT on Friday, March 27, 2026. Preliminary funding recommendations will be determined in June 2026. A link to the applications, program instructions and eligible activity guidance will be available on the citys website: orlando.gov/housing. For additional general information, or if you require special accommodations, please contact 407.246.4492.  CITY OF ORLANDO CONTRACTOR REGISTRATION MEETING The City of Orlando Housing and Community Development Department (HCD) will hold a Contractor Registration Meeting on Wednesday, March 11, 2026, at 9 a.m. The meeting will be held both in person in the Fairview Room, on the Ninth Floor of Orlando City Hall, 400 South Orange Avenue, Orlando, FL, 32801, and virtually via Zoom. Parking validation will be provided to attendees who park in the City Commons Parking Garage (460 Boone Avenue). The purpose of the meeting is to familiarize General Contractors, Architects, Engineers, and Specialty Subcontractors (HVAC, Electrical, Plumbing, and Roofing), interested in working on city-sponsored residential rehabilitation projects, with the rules, regulations, and specifications of the City of Orlando Housing Rehabilitation Program. Attendance is mandatory for all General Contractors, Architects, Engineers, and Specialty Subcontractors who would like to be added to the HCD Rotating Contractor List for bidding. All General Contractors, Architects, Engineers, and Specialty Subcontractors must have valid licenses, certifications, and insurance and be registered in the State of Florida to be eligible to apply for inclusion on the HCD Rotating Contractor List. Applications for inclusion on the HCD Rotating Contractor List will be available after the meeting. For more information, or to register to attend the meeting virtually, please email: harold.watson@orlando.gov.  7921457 City of Orlando</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11465531</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11465531.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Publications - Notices of Hearings - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464209</link>
      <description>PUBLIC NOTICE  WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA Cancellation of February 4, 2026, Board Meeting   The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Boar...


--- Full Notice Text ---
PUBLIC NOTICE  WATER COOPERATIVE OF CENTRAL FLORIDA Cancellation of February 4, 2026, Board Meeting   The Water Cooperative of Central Florida Board meeting date of February 4, 2026, is cancelled. The scheduled March 4, 2026, meeting is confirmed as the next WCCF Board meeting.  The purpose of these WCCF Board meetings is to act upon and approve any proposed regional water supply projects. Any changes to this schedule will be published for notification at least 7 days before subsequent adjustments.  The meetings will take place from 2:00pm to 3:00pm and be held in the Bruce R. Van Meter Board Room at the Toho Administration Building, 951 Martin Luther King Boulevard, Kissimmee, FL 34741.  Anyone interested in obtaining more information about these meetings may contact Todd Swingle at 407-944-5131. Any person requiring special accommodation at the meetings, because of a disability or physical impairment, should contact the Toho Executive Office at 407-944-5130.   1/24/2026 7922938</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464209</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Orlando</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11464208</link>
      <description>NOTICE OF AGENCY ACTION   Notice is hereby provided that the South Florida Water Management District (SFWMD), on January 7, 2026, issued an Environ...


--- Full Notice Text ---
NOTICE OF AGENCY ACTION   Notice is hereby provided that the South Florida Water Management District (SFWMD), on January 7, 2026, issued an Environmental Resource permit (permit) with conditions Permit Number 49-113947-P, Application Number 250606-53649 to Heuriskein Investments LLC, 8618 Vesta Terrace, Orlando, Florida 32825 for Stonebridge Park, Residential, Osceola County, Section 27, Township 25 South, Range 31 East.  This Permit authorizes construction and operation of a stormwater management (SWM) system and associated SWM infrastructure to serve 28.21 acres and 154 residential lots in Stonebridge Park. The SWM system consists of inlets and storm sewer to collect and convey runoff to a wet detention system with outfall through a control structure to the ditch along Batton Road before discharging through existing cross drains under Jones Road.  A copy of the permit can be obtained by contacting the SFWMD Regulatory Records Management Section, during normal business hours, 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., Monday through Friday, except legal holidays, at 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, FL 33406, Regulation Division, by telephone at 561-682-6911, by e-mail at permits@sfwmd.gov, or by accessing the permit directly from the Districts website (www.sfwmd.gov) using the Application/Permit Search on the RegPermitting page.  The Districts agency action is final unless a timely petition for an administrative hearing is filed under Sections 120.569 and 120.57 of the Florida Statutes before the deadline for filing a petition.  As required by Sections 120.569 and 120.60(3), Fla. Stat., the following is notice of the opportunities which may be available for administrative hearing or judicial review when the substantial interests of a party are determined by an agency. Please note that this Notice of Rights is not intended to provide legal advice. Not all of the legal proceedings detailed below may be an applicable or appropriate remedy. You may wish to consult an attorney regarding your legal rights.  RIGHT TO REQUEST ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING A person whose substantial interests are or may be affected by the South Florida Water Management Districts (SFWMD or District) action has the right to request an administrative hearing on that action pursuant to Sections 120.569 and 120.57, Fla. Stat. Persons seeking a hearing on a SFWMD decision which affects or may affect their substantial interests shall file a petition for hearing with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD, in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein, within 21 days of receipt of written notice of the decision, unless one of the following shorter time periods apply: (1) within 14 days of the notice of consolidated intent to grant or deny concurrently reviewed applications for environmental resource permits and use of sovereign submerged lands pursuant to Section 373.427, Fla. Stat.; or (2) within 14 days of service of an Administrative Order pursuant to Section 373.119(1), Fla. Stat. Receipt of written notice of agency decision means receipt of written notice through mail, electronic mail, or posting that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action, or publication of notice that the SFWMD has or intends to take final agency action. Any person who receives written notice of a SFWMD decision and fails to file a written request for hearing within the timeframe described above waives the right to request a hearing on that decision.  If the District takes final agency action which materially differs from the noticed intended agency decision, persons who may be substantially affected shall, unless otherwise provided by law, have an additional Rule 28-106.111, Fla. Admin. Code, point of entry.  Any person to whom an emergency order is directed pursuant to Section 373.119(2), Fla. Stat., shall comply therewith immediately, but on petition to the board shall be afforded a hearing as soon as possible.  A person may file a request for an extension of time for filing a petition. The SFWMD may, for good cause, grant the request. Requests for extension of time must be filed with the SFWMD prior to the deadline for filing a petition for hearing. Such requests for extension shall contain a certificate that the moving party has consulted with all other parties concerning the extension and that the SFWMD and any other parties agree to or oppose the extension. A timely request for an extension of time shall toll the running of the time period for filing a petition until the request is acted upon.  FILING INSTRUCTIONS A petition for administrative hearing must be filed with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD. Filings with the Office of the District Clerk may be made by mail, hand- delivery, or e-mail. Filings by facsimile will not be accepted. A petition for administrative hearing or other document is deemed filed upon receipt during normal business hours by the Office of the District Clerk at SFWMD headquarters in West Palm Beach, Florida. The Districts normal business hours are 8:00 a.m.  5:00 p.m., excluding weekends and District holidays. Any document received by the Office of the District Clerk after 5:00 p.m. shall be deemed filed as of 8:00 a.m. on the next regular business day. Additional filing instructions are as follows:  - Filings by mail must be addressed to the Office of the District Clerk, 3301 Gun Club Road, West Palm Beach, Florida 33406. -  Filings by hand-delivery must be delivered to the Office of the District Clerk. Delivery of a petition to the SFWMDs security desk does not constitute filing. It will be necessary to request that the SFWMDs security officer contact the Office of the District Clerk. An employee of the SFWMD's Clerk's office will receive and file the petition. - Filings by e-mail must be transmitted to the Office of the District Clerk at clerk@sfwmd.gov. The filing date for a document transmitted by electronic mail shall be the date the Office of the District Clerk receives the complete document. A party who files a document by e-mail shall (1) represent that the original physically signed document will be retained by that party for the duration of the proceeding and of any subsequent appeal or subsequent proceeding in that cause and that the party shall produce it upon the request of other parties; and (2) be responsible for any delay, disruption, or interruption of the electronic signals and accepts the full risk that the document may not be properly filed.  INITIATION OF AN ADMINISTRATIVE HEARING Pursuant to Sections 120.54(5)(b)4. and 120.569(2)(c), Fla. Stat., and Rules 28- 106.201 and 28-106.301, Fla. Admin. Code, initiation of an administrative hearing shall be made by written petition to the SFWMD in legible form and on 8 1/2 by 11 inch white paper. All petitions shall contain:  1. Identification of the action being contested, including the permit number, application number, SFWMD file number or any other SFWMD identification number, if known. 2. The name, address, any email address, any facsimile number, and telephone number of the petitioner and petitioners representative, if any. 3. An explanation of how the petitioners substantial interests will be affected by the agency determination. 4. A statement of when and how the petitioner received notice of the SFWMDs decision. 5. A statement of all disputed issues of material fact. If there are none, the petition must so indicate. 6. A concise statement of the ultimate facts alleged, including the specific facts the petitioner contends warrant reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action. 7. A statement of the specific rules or statutes the petitioner contends require reversal or modification of the SFWMDs proposed action. 8. If disputed issues of material fact exist, the statement must also include an explanation of how the alleged facts relate to the specific rules or statutes. 9. A statement of the relief sought by the petitioner, stating precisely the action the petitioner wishes the SFWMD to take with respect to the SFWMDs proposed action.  MEDIATION The procedures for pursuing mediation are set forth in Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., and Rules 28-106.111 and 28-106.401.405, Fla. Admin. Code. The SFWMD is not proposing mediation for this agency action under Section 120.573, Fla. Stat., at this time.  RIGHT TO SEEK JUDICIAL REVIEW Pursuant to Section 120.68, Fla. Stat., and in accordance with Florida Rule of Appellate Procedure 9.110, a party who is adversely affected by final SFWMD action may seek judicial review of the SFWMDs final decision by filing a notice of appeal with the Office of the District Clerk of the SFWMD in accordance with the filing instructions set forth herein within 30 days of rendition of the order to be reviewed, and by filing a copy of the notice with the clerk of the appropriate district court of appeal. 7922819 1/24/2026</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11464208</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Tampa</title>
      <link>https://dgfc4k3gho5kh.cloudfront.net/18/11463818.pdf</link>
      <description>legal ads


--- Full Notice Text ---
legal ads</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463818</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://kissimmee.fyi/thumbnails/11463818.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463723</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2010 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 5-1974
Other Property Exchange - Chattel Paper
Literary Minutes of Meeting of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
AFFIDAVIT OF DOMICILE / CLAIM OF OWNERSHIP
STATE OF FLORIDA)
COUNTY OF SEMINOLE)
I, HARPAUL, PETER MARK also known as PETER WELDE NEGUS OF MORRISTOWN (affiant), a New Jerseyan National declare, state and verify Before a notary public me, who being first duly sworn, under oath deposes and sayeth that affiant resides in and maintains a place of abode in the City of SANFORD, County of SEMINOLE, State of FLORIDA, which he recognizes and intends to maintain as his permanent home; affiant declares that he also maintains a residence at 122 Spreading Oak Ct, Sanford, Florida, and that he formerly resided at 200 SOUTH STREET (city) MORRISTOWN (state) NEW JERSEY, but that his abode in Florida constitutes his predominant and principal home, and affiant intends to continue it permanently as such. Affiant further declares that he affirms the Registrar of Titles is authorized to receive for registration of memorials upon any outstanding certificate of title an official birth certificate pertaining to a registered owner named (PETER MARK HARPAUL) in said certificate of title showing the date of birth of said registered owner (PETER MARK HARPAUL), providing there is attached to said birth certificate an affidavit of an affiant who states that he is familiar with the facts recited, stating that the party named in said birth certificate is the same party as one of the owners named in said certificate of title; and that thereafter the Registrar of Titles shall treat said registered owner (PETER MARK HARPAUL) as having attained the age of the majority at a date 18 years after the date of birth shown by said certificate. Affiant further declares, the natural person known as the PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST holds a claim of ownership of the above said Certificate of Title No. A0017326260-1, dated OCTOBER 10, 1974. Affiant further declares that PETER MARK HARPAUL or the PETER MARK FAMILY OF HARPAUL ESTATE is an actual bona fide and legal resident of the State of Florida, and the filing of this affidavit is to be accepted by all persons or any court as proof of such legal residence and permanent domicile.
January 23, 2026
#COL-542</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463723</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463722</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1996
Other Property Exchange - Intangible Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY
Parties:
Signum Dei Solomanis Express Trust
d/b/a DONOVAN JORDAN AVERY (Complainant)
VS.
Gwinnett County Sheriff
Gwinnett County Board of Commissioners
Gwinnett Superior Court Clerk
Georgia Governor
(Defendant)
INJUNCTION AGAINST ALL PUBLIC OFFICERS AND CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE INVOKING IRREPARABLE
INJURY
COME THIS DAY, the 14th of January, in the year of OUR LORD 2025
NOTICE OF ESTOPPEL AND STIPULATION OF CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE TO ALL Georgia AND UNITED STATES STATUTES WHERE Retrospective laws are highly injurious, oppressive, and unjust. No such laws, therefore, should be made, either for the decision of civil causes, or the punishment of offenses AND MOTION TO INTERVENE WITH AN INJUNCTION FOR THE NAME SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST doing business as DONOVAN JORDAN AVERYTO AND ELOHIM DJA HIGH LORD OF ATLANTATC- Per Exhibit 96.D191 (Trademark License Agreement)
All constitutional civil officers have given oath to the support the constitution of Georgia and the United States as prescribed in Article XIV, Sec 1 of the Georgia 1877 Constitution. The Complainant (One of The People of the Territory of Georgia under Declaration of Express Trust), rights protected by the Constitution (Article I, Sec VI) have been injured in the past by the Sheriffs and his/her officers by being compelled to accuse or furnish evidence against himself. Every subject shall have a right to produce all proofs that may be favorable to himself; to meet the witnesses against him face to face, and to be fully heard in his defense, by himself, and counsel. The Complainant, under duress, incurred a force stop and/or force detainment without due process of affidavit of
18
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1996 - "concluded"
Other Property Exchange - Intangible Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY
complaint under oath attached to the summons, citation or notice of violation without special designation of the persons or objects of search, arrest, or seizure (Article I, Sec. 8). As prescribed in Rule 4, (a) Issuance; Service. (1) Pleading Defined. As used in this rule, Rule 4.1, and Rule 4.2, "pleading" means any of the pleadings authorized by Rule 7 that bring a party into an action--a complaint, third-party complaint, counterclaim, or crossclaim. (2) Issuance. On or after filing a pleading, the filing party may present a summons to the clerk for signature and seal. If the summons is properly completed, the clerk must sign, seal, and issue it to the filing party for service. A summons--or a copy of the summons if addressed to multiple parties--must be issued for each party to be served. (3) Service. A summons must be served with a copy of the pleading. Service must be completed as required by this rule, Rule 4.1, or 4.2, as applicable. (b) Contents; Replacement Summons. (1) Contents. A summons must: (A) name the court and the parties; (B) be directed to the party to be served; (C) state the name and address of the attorney of the party serving the summons or--if unrepresented--the party's name and address; (D) state the time within which the defendant must appear and defend; (E) notify the party to be served that a failure to appear and defend will result in a default judgment against that party for the relief demanded in the pleading; (F) state that "requests for reasonable accommodation for persons with disabilities must be made to the court by parties at least 3 working days in advance of a scheduled court proceeding"; (G) be signed by the clerk; and (H) bear the court's seal.
19
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. December 26th, in the year of our Lord, 2015 Anno Domini
DEMAND FOR RELIEF
FURTHERMORE, I DEMAND, for the Gwinnett County Sheriff to put the name SIGNUM DEI SOLOMANIS EXPRESS TRUST doing business as AVERY, DONOVAN JORDAN MO AND DONOVAN JORDAN AVERYC AND ELOHIM DJA HIGH LORD OF ATLANTATO on THE DO NOT STOP, DO NOT DETAIN LIST FOR GEORGIA and all OTHER STATES under Full Faith and Credit. The Constitution reserves all rights protected by the above said 1877 Constitution of Georgia, the Articles of Association and the Articles of Confederation and "do not" waive any part of my rights; abide by your oaths to it.
TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE THAT THIS WRIT OF INJUNCTION SHALL ALSO SERVE AS YOUR CONTRACT; failure to answer and rebut this Writ is acquiescence and is estoppel; you have 30 days to answer, then this contract is law. No STATE shall pass and Bill of Attainder, ex post facto Law, or Law impairing the Obligation of Contracts - Section 10 of 1787 United States Constitution.
SIGNED: Elizabeth Rodriguez Cortes SOLE TRUSTEE
SIGNED: Donovan Jordan Avery SETTLOR/COMPLAINANT
20
January 23, 2026
#COL-545</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463722</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463721</link>
      <description>Prepared By: Cedric Hoffman
Firm: Via lure, LLC
1070 Montgomery Road, Suite 2333
Altamonte Springs, FL 32714
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
Prepared By: Cedric Hoffman
Firm: Via lure, LLC
1070 Montgomery Road, Suite 2333
Altamonte Springs, FL 32714
MEMORANDUM OF TRUST
Est. January 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2010 Anno Domini
THIS INDENTURE (Agreement) made this 5th day of January, 2010 serves as a Declaration of Express Trust and shall continue for a term of twenty-five (25) years from this day, between PETER MARK HARPAUL herein known as the Settlor and Trust Protector, (the first party) and BERCY ALMANZA DE LA CRUZ Trustee, herein known as the First Trustee, Sole Trustee or Trustee, (the second party), under the name of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER WELDE NEGUS OF MORRISTOWN. With this contract, the Parties intend to create an Express Trust Organization for the benefit of the Trust Certificate Unit Holders and to identify, accumulate, purchase and hold any assets that become available and to provide for a prudent administration and distribution system administered by legal persons acting in a fiduciary capacity.
WITNESSETH: Whereas the Settlor, irrevocably assigns and conveys to the Trustee, in trust, specific properties as defined in The Trustee Minutes (1-1974), attached to this document in exchange for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER WELDE NEGUS OF MORRISTOWN.
Trust: Trust includes an express trust, private or charitable, with additions thereto, wherever and however created. Property: Property means anything that may be the subject of ownership and includes both real and personal property. Person: Person means any natural person, individual, corporation, government or governmental subdivision or agency, business trust, estate, trust, partnership, limited liability company, association, or other entity.
Settlor: PETER MARK HARPAUL of 202 Walton Way, Ste 192 PMB 423, Cedar Park, Texas, doing business in Seminole County, Florida of 2170 W State Road 434, Longwood, FL 32779 - (defined) in law a settlor is a person who settles property in trust law for the benefit of beneficiaries. In some legal systems, a settlor is also referred to as a trustor or occasionally, a grantor or donor... A settlor may create a trust manifesting an intention to create it; grantor is the person who creates the trust.
Trust Protector: PETER MARK HARPAUL or other authorized person in the future by settlor, - (defined) appointed under the trust instrument to direct, restrain, remove the trustee(s) or appoint a successor.
Trustee(s): BERCY ALMANZA DE LA CRUZ of Carrera 53, #80-198, Barranquilla 080001  (defined) includes an original, additional, or successor trustee, whether or not appointed or confirmed by a court. A person or firm that holds or administers property or assets for the benefit of a third party and can be given the powers to make investment decisions for the Trust, or vote on the distribution of assets to the beneficiaries and/or has the power to hire persons whether an authorized person or not, including accountants, attorneys, auditors, investment advisers, appraisers or other agents even if they are associated or affiliated with the trustee, to advise or assist the trustee in the performance of administrative duties.
Beneficial Owner: PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST herein known as the First Beneficiary and other beneficiaries to come in future (defined) beneficial owner is where specific property rights ("use and title") in equity belong to a person even though legal title of the property belongs to another person. This often relates where the legal title owner has implied trustee duties to the beneficial owner.
WHEREAS, the Trust Organization is authorized to exist and function through its Board of Trustees, comprised of the total active number of trustees who are legal persons holding fee simple title, not differentiating between legal and equitable, not as individuals, but collectively as the Board, according to the inalienable Common Law rights.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be amendable, as described in the bylaws, and shall be irrevocable by the Settlor or by any other person or entity but said trustee can be fired by the Trust Protector and replace by new trustee appointed by the Trust Protector. It is the intention of the Settlor to make the Beneficiaries, an absolute gift of the Trust Certificate Units (TCUs), in which the Beneficiaries shall not have any vested interest, until the termination of this Trust and final distribution accumulated assets or any early distribution of the assets thereof. There shall be exactly 100 Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) available to the Beneficiaries. WHEREAS, the Trust shall be administered, managed, governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida and Texas, being bound to the Articles of Confederation of 1781, Article IV.
WHEREAS, the Trust shall be governed by its country's applicable laws known as Muscat (Muskat), Sultanate of Oman, with formation documents governed and regulated in all respects applicable to Common Law jurisdiction of Florida and Texas to govern the interpretation of the trust. Under the law of the Sultanate of Oman, a court within Oman, is able to exercise primary supervision over the administration of the trust. The Treaty of Marrakesh, the Treaty of Maskat of 1833, the Articles of Association, the Articles of Confederation, and the Uniform Commercial Code (only when and if applicable and/or allowable to remain under the jurisdiction of the Common Law). The domicile of the trust is within the Court of Equity, in Florida in the Republic of the United States of America but shall have full faith and credit in any State as a last resort when everything else fails.
January 23, 2026
#COL-540</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463721</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463720</link>
      <description>Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Exp...


--- Full Notice Text ---
Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1978


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


Parties:


Flathead Lake Express Trust
d/b/a SCOTT EDWARD NORRED
(Complainant)


vs.


FLATHEAD County Sheriff
FLATHEAD County Board of Commissioners
FLATHEAD Superior Court Clerk
Montana Governor
(Defendant)


INJUNCTION AGAINST ALL PUBLIC OFFICERS AND CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE INVOKING IRREPARABLE INJURY


COME THIS DAY, the 21 st of December, in the year of OUR LORD 2025


NOTICE OF ESTOPPEL AND STIPULATION OF CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE TO ALL Montana AND UNITED STATES STATUTES WHERE Retrospective laws are highly injurious, oppressive, and unjust. No such laws, therefore, should be made, either for the decision of civil causes, or the punishment of offenses AND MOTION TO INTERVENE WITH AN INJUNCTION FOR THE NAME FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST doing business as SCOTT EDWARD NORRED AND LORD DEBUYS  Per Exhibit SC43678 (Trademark License Agreement)


All constitutional civil officers have given oath to the support the constitution of Montana and the United States as prescribed in Article XIX, Section 1 of the Montana 1889 Constitution. The Complainant (One of The People of the Territory of Montana under Declaration of Express Trust), rights protected by the Constitution (Article III, Section 18) have been injured in the past by the Sheriffs and his/her officers by being compelled to accuse or furnish evidence against himself. Every subject shall have a right to produce all proofs that may be favorable to himself; to meet the witnesses against him face to face, and to be fully heard in his defense, by himself, and counsel. The Complainant, under duress, incurred a force stop and/or force detainment without due process of affidavit of


Schedule C: Trustee Minutes 5-1978  concluded


Other Property Exchange  Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
FLATHEAD LAKE
( An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)


PUBLIC NOTICE OF TRAVEL INJUNCTION
AGAINST IRREPARABLE INJURY


complaint under oath attached to the summons, citation or notice of violation without special designation of the persons or objects of search, arrest, or seizure (Article I, Section 11). As prescribed in Rule 4. ATTACHMENTS of the Montana Rules of Civil Procedure, Rule 4, Title 25, Chapter 20, Part II, Rule 4. Persons Subject to Jurisdiction; Process; Service. (a) In General. The summons and complaint must be served together. The plaintiff must furnish the necessary copies to the person who makes service. (b) In Person. Service of all process may be made in the county where the party to be served is found by a sheriff, deputy sheriff, constable, or any other person over the age of 18 not a party to the action. (c) By Mail. A summons and complaint may also be served by mailing via first-class mail, postage prepaid, the following to the person to be served: (i) a copy of the summons and complaint; (ii) two copies of a notice and acknowledgment conforming substantially to Form 18-A; and (iii) a return envelope, postage prepaid, addressed to the sender. (d) Limitations on Mail Service. A summons and complaint may not be served by mail to: (i) a minor; (ii) an incompetent person; or (iii) a corporation, partnership, or other unincorporated association, whether domestic or foreign. (e) Service Completion by Mail. If no acknowledgment of service by mail is received by the sender within 21 days after the date of mailing, service must be made in person. If the person served by mail fails to return the acknowledgment, the court may order that person to pay the costs of personal service unless good cause is shown. The notice and acknowledgment must be signed and dated by the defendant, and service is complete on the date shown. (f) Serving Individuals, Minors, Incompetents, Business Entities, Government, Estates, Out-of-State Service, Publication, Secretary of State Service, and Related Procedures. Rule 4 also contains detailed methods for: serving individuals (including minors and incompetent persons), serving business and nonprofit entities, service on local governments and the state, serving estates and trusts, personal service outside Montana, service by publication where permitted by statute, and procedures for serving through the Montana Secretary of State in certain cases. (g) Proof of Service. Proving service of summons and complaint must be accomplished by: officers certificate if served by an officer, servers affidavit if served by another person, affidavit of publisher if served by publication, or  written admission by the defendant showing date and place of service.


DEMAND FOR RELIEF


FURTHERMORE, I DEMAND , for the FLATHEAD County Sheriff to put the name FLATHEAD LAKE EXPRESS TRUST doing business as NORRED, SCOTT EDWARD AND SCOTT EDWARD NORRED AND LORD DEBUYS on THE DO NOT STOP, DO NOT DETAIN LIST FOR Montana and all OTHER STATES under Full Faith and Credit . The Constitution reserves all rights protected by the above said 1889 Constitution of Montana, the Articles of Association and the Articles of Confederation and do not waive any part of my rights; abide by your oaths to it .


TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE THAT THIS WRIT OF INJUNCTION SHALL ALSO SERVE AS YOUR CONTRACT; failure to answer and rebut this Writ is acquiescence and is estoppel; you have 30 days to answer , then this contract is law. No STATE shall pass and Bill of Attainder, ex post facto Law, or Law impairing the Obligation of Contracts  Section 10 of 1787 United States Constitution.


SIGNED: Harol M. Lozano
SOLE TRUSTEE



SIGNED: SCOTT EDWARD NORRED
SETTLOR/COMPLAINANT

January 23, 2026
#COL-544</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463720</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463719</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2010 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1974
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of
PETROSMARKOS TORENYA
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust at 8:20 AM:
The Sole Trustee (second party), from the Board of Trustees, of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA, an Irrevocable Express Trust Organization established on January 5, 2010 at 5:00 AM, filed and recorded in the Organic Public Record of SEMINOLE COUNTY CIRCUIT COURT CLERK &amp; COMPTROLLER, (an immigrational officer of a naturalization court [8 U.S.C.  1101 (7)]) bears witness and holds the Settlor's declaration under oath in trust including the Sole Trustee declaration under oath to be presented to any court established by the Constitution or laws of the United States or any court of record in the Commonwealth in the form as follows:
P. Law 94-241, Article III, Citizenship &amp; Nationality"
I, Harpaul, Peter Mark (creditor) d/b/a PETER MARK HARPAUL (debtor) subject to the Trust Indenture stated above, hereby and forever, state, claim and declare I am not nor have I ever been a U.S. Citizen or U.S. National evidence by my New Jersey Nation Birth Certificate and under Legal Disability and the Baby Act, I never agreed to the Social Security Public Insurance or Vital Statistics Birth Certificate Contract.
I declare that my name is Harpaul, Peter Mark also known as Peter Welde Negus of Morristown. Let it be known by all Immigration Clerks, Homeland Security, Secretaries of State, Supreme Court Judges and Clerks that now and forever I am a Free Inhabitant and Native New Jerseyan National, pursuant to 1781 Articles of Confederation, Article IV but not a citizen of the United States; a vagabond in Texas republic of the United States of America - (see 2016 GPO Style Manual pg. 95). I have taken an oath and made an affirmation, formal declaration of allegiance to a foreign state and made a formal renunciation of nationality in the United States. Furthermore, I have not been convicted of a federal or state drug offense or convicted of a sex tourism" crimes statute, and I am not the subject of an outstanding federal, state, or local warrant of arrest for a felony; a criminal court order forbidding my departure from the United States; a subpoena received from the United States in a matter involving federal prosecution for, or grand jury investigation of, a felony, according to U.S. Passport Application DS-11/DS-82, Acts or Conditions, page 4 of 4.
TAKE JUDICIAL NOTICE, that I am not a statutory citizen and make no claim of statutory citizenship created by any State or Federal government. I hereby extinguish, rescind, revoke, cancel, abrogate, annul, nullify, discharge, and make void ab initio all signatures belonging to me, on all previously filed SS-5, all Internal Revenue Service Forms, Superior or District Court of Texas Forms, County Municipality Forms, all "TX" DMV Forms, 1040 Forms and all State Income Tax Forms (if any) and all powers of attorney, real and/or implied, connected thereto on the grounds that my purported consent was voluntary and freely obtained, but was made through mistake, duress, fraud, and undue influence exercised by any or all governments (State or Federal) any agency and/or employers. Pursuant to Contract Law; "all previously signed Federal and State forms are, hereby, extinguished by this rescission." I further revoke, rescind and make void ab initio all powers of attorney pertaining to me from any and all governmental, quasi,
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2010 Anno Domini
Schedule A: Trustee Minutes 4-1974 - "concluded"
Other Property Exchange - Intellectual Property Literary Minutes of Meeting of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
colorable agencies and/or Departments created under the authority of Article One, Section Eight, Clause Seventeen, and/or
Article Four, Section Three, Clause Two of the Constitution for the United States of America.
DECLARATION OF NATIONALITY
I, Harpaul, Peter Mark, born in the land of New Jersey United States of America, territory of Morris, declare (or certify, verify or state) under penalty of perjury under the laws of the United States of America [28 U.S. Code  1746(1)], that I, Harpaul. Peter Mark being duly sworn, hereby declare my intention to be a national but not a citizen of the United States" (Public Law 94-241 - March 24, 1976 - Article III. - 90 STAT. 266 - Section 302) and the foregoing is true and correct.
Place of Meeting: 120 E Silver Springs Blvd Ocala, Florida 34470 (Seminole County)
There being no further business to come before this meeting, on motion duly made, seconded, and carried, the meeting adjourned at 8:25 AM
January 23, 2026
#COL-541</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463719</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Fern Park</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11463717</link>
      <description>MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est


--- Full Notice Text ---
MEMORANDUM OF EXPRESS TRUST
Est. January 5th, in the year of our Lord, 2010 Anno Domini
Schedule B: Trustee Minutes 5-1974
Other Property Exchange - Intangible Property
Literary Minutes of Meeting of
PETROSMARKOS TORENYA
(An Irrevocable Express Trust Organization)
MISCELLANEOUS
AFFIDAVIT OF FICTITIOUS BUSINESS NAME STATEMENT
To The Governing Bodies of This Express Trust, ALL Corporation Soles but not limited to the State of Texas &amp; Florida:
The Sole Trustee, called the meeting to order and affirmed that officially on January 05, 2010, the trustee received the Intangible Property, herein known as Affidavit of Fictitious Business Name Statement, to be held in trust, published in any local municipality newspaper filing and but not limited to Seminole County Circuit Court Clerk &amp; Comptroller.
Trustee approved the initial exchange of the specific property for one hundred (100) units of Beneficial Interest, known hereto as Trust Certificate Units (TCUs) to be held with this Indenture by the Trustees for the Beneficiaries also known as Members of PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST.
The TRUSTEE shall:
a. Keep minutes of all future business meetings and Board of Trustee meetings
b. Act in the best interest of all Trust Certificate Unit Holders through prudent record keeping of certificate transfers and other business respecting the holders and this Express Trust.
WE THE UNDERSIGNED, BEING DULY SWORN, DO HEREBY DECLARE UNDER OATH THAT THE NAMES OF ALL PERSONS INTERESTED IN THE BUSINESS OR PROFESSION CARRIED ON UNDER THE NAMES OF THE PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST ARE DOING BUSINESS AS THE FOLLOWING:
PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER MARK HARPAUL PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a HARPAUL, PETER MARK
PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER MARK FAMILY OF HARPAUL ESTATE PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER MARK HARPAUL BANKRUPTCY ESTATE PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a PETER WELDE NEGUS OF MORRISTOWN PETROSMARKOS TORENYA EXPRESS TRUST d/b/a TORENYA TRUST ENTERPRISE
TORENYA TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a PETER MARK HARPAUL
TORENYA TRUST ENTERPRISE d/b/a PETER WELDE NEGUS OF MORRISTOWN
HEADQUARTERS: 200 SOUTH STREET, MORRISTOWN, NJ 07960
PRINCIPAL: 660 CENTURY POINTE, 1ST FLOOR, STE A, LAKE MARY, FL 32746 MAILING: 202 WALTON WAY, STE 192, PMB 423, CEDAR PARK, TX 78613
January 23, 2026
#COL-543</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11463717</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Notices - Kissimmee</title>
      <link>https://floridapublicnotices.com/notices/11461934</link>
      <description>Notice at 400 Simpson Road

Meeting: Tuesday, February 17, 2026 at 2:00 PM
Location: 400 Simpson Road

--- Full Notice Text ---
INVITATION TO BID
BID DATE: Tuesday, February 17, 2026 at 2:00 PM ET
PROJECT: Osceola County Jail CEP Phase 2


Wharton-Smith, Inc. is proudly the Construction Manager serving Osceola County Government and is soliciting proposals from prequalified subcontractors for the construction of the Osceola County Jail CEP Phase 2 project.

The project consists of two buildings and one structure on the perimeter of the existing campus grossing a combined 10,207 square feet. The work includes: Concrete, Masonry, Steel, Miscellaneous Metals, Casework, Roofing, Waterproofing &amp; Caulking, Doors &amp; Hardware, Overhead Doors, Glass &amp; Glazing, Louvers, Drywall, Acoustical, Tile, Flooring, Painting &amp; Floor Sealer, Specialties, Canopies, Appliances, PEMB, Storage Solutions, Window Treatments, Fire Protection, Plumbing, HVAC, Electrical, Low Voltage Systems, Sitework, Paving &amp; Utilities, Landscape, and Fencing.

A non-mandatory Pre-Bid Meeting &amp; Walkthrough is scheduled for Thursday, January 29, 2026, at 9:00 AM, at the proposed jobsite outside the Osceola County Jail, located at 400 Simpson Road, Kissimmee, FL 34744. Prospective bidders are encouraged to attend; however, attendance is not mandatory.

Bids will be received at the office of Wharton-Smith, Inc., located at 750 Monroe Road, Sanford, FL 32771 no later than the date and time prescribed above. Bids may be hand delivered, mailed, or emailed to comest@whartonsmith.com. Bids received after the appointed date and time will be subject to rejection. Bids will only be accepted from Prequalified Firms utilizing the required Form of Proposal included in the Bid Package.

The RFI deadline is February 2, 2026. Please submit RFIs to comest@whartonsmith.com. Do not contact the Architect or Owner for information on this project.

Local Subcontractors &amp; Suppliers are encouraged to participate.

Payment &amp; Performance Bonds may be required.

Bidding documents are available upon request at comest@whartonsmith.com [comest@whartonsmith.com].
January 15, 22, 2026</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">kissimmee-notice-11461934</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
